<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-17"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350446446846-1</Id><Title>Intel is looking...</Title><Msg>The dividend is nice but the companys conference call has me selling. Releasing a new product such as windows 8 doesn't mean computer sells will pick up. They sound stupid saying that it will. If I bought a computer today, it would only cost me $50.00 to upgrade to windows 8. The new "Pad" style of computer will keep taking away from computer companies bottom line. The whole samsung chip/Apple stuff made me short the stock before earnings. Losing money is terrible, and I'm sorry for those of you that traded on that headline. I believe most of you saying otherwise about this stock it's because you're stuck in major losses from it. There is no reason to buy this company with the results they are producing. Dell/HPQ the guys that pay them to put the chips in their computers; their profit warnings should of tipped some of you off to sell. This is all my own view point don't invest off of my information.</Msg><Username>pv.miller</Username><Timestamp>1350446446846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:00:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350446463642-2</Id><Topic><Title>Over 120,000,000 shares all selling at the same time tomorrow</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1350444196288</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love buying INTC on the dips. Remember when INTC hit $14 in 2009? Well, I bought a ton back then and I'm loving the 6.4% yield now from those levels.</Msg><Username>aurin_res</Username><Timestamp>1350446463642</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350446841103-3</Id><Topic><Title>I checked NYK2OH's lengthy posting history...he's not a short</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350444224196</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:23:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's a paid basher as are most trying to scare retail on this board. It's a sick part of our disturbed capital markets. They are predators trying to get people to make decisions on emotion (fear, greed) rather than rational thought. Buy long dated calls. Beat them at their game...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1350446841103</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350447212805-4</Id><Topic><Title>14nm</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1350431940099</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:59:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple will need everything it can get to maintain the distinctiveness to justify the price premium in its products. Strategically speaking, it would be foolish for Apple NOT to consider locking up an exclusive on Intel's more advanced process technology. The incremental cost would be trivial compared to the value at risk for Apple is it loses its perceived position as the leader.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1350447212805</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350447239628-5</Id><Topic><Title>I checked NYK2OH's lengthy posting history...he's not a short</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350444224196</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:23:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No thanks, I like to make money in the markets.</Msg><Username>pv.miller</Username><Timestamp>1350447239628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350447364150-6</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is looking...</Title><Username>pv.miller</Username><Timestamp>1350446446846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:00:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're the first person on here that doesn't sound like a complete idiot.</Msg><Username>transcend8177</Username><Timestamp>1350447364150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:16:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350447939745-7</Id><Topic><Title>Yo Whobeli.. ask yourself these questions....</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1350429868407</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:24:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are plenty of dividend that cannot be maintained in a recession, which is why the perpetual comparison of bond yield to dividend yield by Wall Street pundits is so misleading (frankly disingenuous). That is why every investor should evaluate CASH FLOW YIELD.. Those high multiple stocks are complete scams. Complete scams. Cash flow yield is nonexistent in many and it will go negative (see Scamazon). In contrast, Intel's competitive position will only improve in a downturn that shakes out weaker players. It is why the BEST companies in the world have been holding cash, to deploy strategically when asset prices correct, rather than spending like drunken sailors at Amazon on value destroying, strategically misguided "invesments". Those holding through earnings there will be looking for a job at the end of the year... And it will be a tough time to be looking.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1350447939745</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:25:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350448944397-8</Id><Topic><Title>Boomers not buying anymore PCs...sorry but it's game over dudes</Title><Username>trader.quick</Username><Timestamp>1350429677096</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:21:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, but I'm not going to give up my PC. I'd rather give up my cellphone. A dumb smartphone is not a PC nor a game machine. A tablet might be a book substitute, but you know what, I'd rather have a book.</Msg><Username>patient2invest</Username><Timestamp>1350448944397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:42:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350449376725-9</Id><Topic><Title>I have friend that has an Ipad</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350444415264</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:26:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He expects Obama to buy him one by taxing the rich.</Msg><Username>patient2invest</Username><Timestamp>1350449376725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350450115426-10</Id><Topic><Title>Over 120,000,000 shares all selling at the same time tomorrow</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1350444196288</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It seems like they can't sell big blocks in after hours, but I'm not sure. Maybe they just wait until the next day so that they can get filled. Anyone, anyone, Buhler?</Msg><Username>surfnstien</Username><Timestamp>1350450115426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 01:01:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350450784681-11</Id><Topic><Title>Over 120,000,000 shares all selling at the same time tomorrow</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1350444196288</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yummy, INTC at sub $19. The dividend will then be about 4.75%. I'll buy more to capture that dividend. The dividend is about as solid as a Treasury but with a rfar superior return.</Msg><Username>p2ialias</Username><Timestamp>1350450784681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 01:13:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350451136913-12</Id><Topic><Title>So.. how low will it go?? Serious replies?</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1350430692954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:38:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$</Msg><Username>patient2invest</Username><Timestamp>1350451136913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 01:18:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350451215992-13</Id><Topic><Title>So.. how low will it go?? Serious replies?</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1350430692954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:38:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great, I'll buy for the 5.1% dividend.</Msg><Username>patient2invest</Username><Timestamp>1350451215992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 01:20:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350451284771-14</Id><Topic><Title>So.. how low will it go?? Serious replies?</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1350430692954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:38:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The answers are: great, Romney, and yes.</Msg><Username>patient2invest</Username><Timestamp>1350451284771</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 01:21:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350451495856-15</Id><Topic><Title>So.. how low will it go?? Serious replies?</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1350430692954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:38:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The dumb PC makers will rule the day that they didn't stock up for window8. They must read the stupid articles about the death of the PC and believe it.</Msg><Username>patient2invest</Username><Timestamp>1350451495856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 01:24:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350457101387-16</Id><Topic><Title>Over 120,000,000 shares all selling at the same time tomorrow</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1350444196288</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$. 120m sellers= idiots and 120 mil buyers on the other side of those sellers are opportunistic smart guys. Anyone who sells tomorrow at any big gap down is an idiot selling under a forced situation totally unfree like a woman RAPED. Plain and simple. Reject Rape always. Never sell then. If you want to sell Intel wait to see a rally to 2sd even if it goes to 20 first (2sd will still be ultimately higher than the low tomorrow because the low is near if not already established). The stock is so oversold for months now. You will be selling a crashed stock that has proven the idiots that the earnings were better than they expected and will do the same next quarter during which we will have clear signs the situation is improving. So expect 25+ by the end of this year even if they try to scare you more here. And expect a massive market rally once Obama is re-elected and if congress or senate republicans lose some edge. A super tsunami of buying. Intel is always able to deliver even in the worse cases as it proved just now. And we are about to believe the #$%$ idiots that were fine with a 50c prediction here??? A company that adds 3 bil $ of cash every quarter or 2$ book value each year doesnt deserve to be year after year in lower levels regardless of the #$%$ earning projections of the same #$%$ that were nowhere to suggest a buy at 19-20 last year or here or to tell you to hedge over 28-29 this year. Of course they will also fail to tell you to buy here. Who the f@K cares if the stock goes to 19 if it can also go to 30 and its 50-50 now at this oversold point. Have any of you losers looked at a long term chart of intel to recognize a massive BUY. IT IS HERE. Idiots and weak cowards sell tomorrow. If you want exit sell at rallies or be the coward these punks want you to be. Punks and plutocrats worldwide and their lackeys republicans want a disaster and they are betting on you to drop your pants. Well drop your pants and #$%$ them instead!</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1350457101387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 02:58:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350458209105-17</Id><Title>Intel beat estimates by 10 cents!</Title><Msg>Yes. Beat EPS estimates by 10 cents. That's 20% better than expected. So they guided slightly lower than Q4 expectations. Very slightly. How many times has Apple done that? Lower the bar so that the beat looks that much better. Is Intel sales not growing? From 2 years ago, current Q3 was better than 18% growth. That's an average of about 9% annual growth rate. My bet is that Intel will come in at least at high end of Q4 guidance, which is about $14.1 Billion in revenues. That's much better than the $13.78 Billion that was expected by ANALysts.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1350458209105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 03:16:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350458614391-18</Id><Topic><Title>Over 120,000,000 shares all selling at the same time tomorrow</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1350444196288</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like a spamming &amp;$^@&amp;#</Msg><Username>zbgb952</Username><Timestamp>1350458614391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 03:23:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350458642865-19</Id><Title>Are tablets a success?</Title><Msg>That's a big fat NO! The iPad has been successful only with the lates unit sales being about 17 million. It's a new Apple product so the success should not come as a surprise and a reason to believe tablets are a logical replacement of the PC. How are tablets doing so far. Over two years after the introduction of tablets witht he iPad release by Apple, the number two seller of tablets is Samsung with only 2.3 million unit sales. The number six seller of PC units is Acer which sold in its most recent quarter over 6 million PC units. That's almost 3 times the number two tablet seller. Does not sound like the tablet form factor with ARM based processors has had much success other than the iPad. And the 17 million quarterly sales for Apple has not dropped sales in PCs. Since the iPad's introduction, quarterly PC unit sales have actually jumped by 4 million, from 85 million units in Q3 of 2010 to 89 million units in Q3 of 2012. No evidence of cannibalization there.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1350458642865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 03:24:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350458937274-20</Id><Topic><Title>Regarding "Silvermont Details"</Title><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1350389676128</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:14:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The game-changer happens at 14nm because Paul is going to ramp it in 2014 only one year after Silvermont, faster than Moore's Law. Intel's massive fabrication machine will leave the competition struggling in the dust.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1350458937274</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 03:28:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350459546635-21</Id><Topic><Title>Regarding "Silvermont Details"</Title><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1350389676128</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:14:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, I guess not. Latest AT review shows single core Medfield hanging with the S4 and the Apple A6. And by hanging I mean beating.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1350459546635</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 03:39:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350459566081-22</Id><Title>Has Intel progressed in tablets and smartphones?</Title><Msg>In smartphones, it has major players already with Motorola in Europe. Lava in India. ZTE in China and Europe. Lenovo in China. And Orange in Europe. It will be a major player in USA after it has 4G capabilities, which will happen by year's end to 1st quarter of 2013. In tablets, we already have 20 on the way with at least 6 OEMs. And if ultrabooks were not gaining traction, why would there be over 140 models to be released in the upcoming quarters. Over a dozen being convertibles between ultrathin laptops and tablets. Companies such as Dell, HP, Lenovo, and others must have come to the conclusion that ultrabooks are a better bet to compete against similar Apple products rather than tablets competing against the iPad. Why? Let's say a convertible ultrabook may cost about $1200 by lenovo with an Atom processor in the screen that detaches as a tablet and an iCore Intel Processor in the keyboard section. This will replace the need to buy a 13 inch MacBook Air for $1199 and a 32 GB iPad for $599. So you're getting a similar product as the Macbook Air with a powerful $600 tablet for free. Just one example of a possibility. Many possibilites will come in time.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1350459566081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 03:39:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350459940960-23</Id><Topic><Title>Intel beat estimates by 10 cents!</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1350458209105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 03:16:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is obviously a ton of negative sentiment surrounding INTC right now. It has been very disappointing seeing the stock fall from the $29 level to basically $21 especially while the DOW has been chugging higher. At it's current valuation you would think that the company was losing money hand over fist versus making billions in profits. Everyone seems to have forgotten that the company is also sitting on a mountain of cash, has virtually no debt and pays out a very solid dividend. It isn't a sexy name at all so the Street is throwing out the stock with the bathwater. It will be interesting to see how far it falls today. I still like the stock long term and certainly won't be selling but I would suggest waiting at least a couple of sessions before buying more.</Msg><Username>iwynne2002</Username><Timestamp>1350459940960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 03:45:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350462521058-24</Id><Topic><Title>"Nobody wants Intel" says NYK2OH.....Not so, says Cisco</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350438466424</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 21:47:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Unfortunately, they are very poor at chip design and design innovation. The evidence is clear - ARM is kicking their #$%$ despite inferior fabrication.' LOL, you are going to get seriously burnt if that is the whole and complete extent of your semiconductor industry insight and analysis. There is probably a fool shortage at some analyst brokerages which you could fill quite nicely ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1350462521058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 04:28:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350463767483-25</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when Apple missed earnings and guided way down?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1350431656016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:54:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Intel has gone nowhere during the past decade - simply swinging between $17 and $25.' Hmmm I am sure it was as low as 12 and as high as 33 in that decade but I suppose when you are making up #$%$, facts don't really matter http://finance.yahoo.com/echarts?s=INTC+Interactive#symbol=intc;range=my;compare=;indicator=volume;charttype=area;crosshair=on;ohlcvalues=0;logscale=off;source=undefined; 'What is going to drive Intel shares to $50? Are people dumping tablets and going back to PCs? ' For a start Intel has been given an abnormally low P/E based on the notion you are pumping that PCs are dying. Well PCs are not dying, they may have been static for a quarter but that is just the pause before Windows 8 and the OEMs having low inventory because of all the new form factors Intel is throwing at them, they want to see the winners first before committing to inventory building. Intel chips are going into tablets and phones far quicker and more quickly and effectively than ARM is going into PCs and notebooks. In fact there are no ARM notebooks or PCs, their best quad-cores cannot even beat the dual-core Atoms coming down in power to greet them in tablets nevermind the quick dual-core i3 chips found in the lowest notebooks. ARM PC penetration is a myth just like I have been saying for years, if they ever approach VIA's marketshare of about 1% that would be an achievement. INTC will be $50 within 5 years, its designs are too great and its P/E too falsely undervalued for that not to be the case eventually.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1350463767483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 04:49:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350463878354-26</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins Debate #2</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1350445556813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In between your mama legs.</Msg><Username>jerrykit50</Username><Timestamp>1350463878354</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 04:51:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350464601185-27</Id><Topic><Title>Tooofunnny, Marcopubio, Singhlion and NYK20h thinking they can affect a stock price...</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350427129178</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 18:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1) revenue guidance is flat 2) profits are high and stable, GMs still will be higher than Apple's for a sense of perspective in your distorted world. Apple is a two-trick pony, once the iPad and iPhone get dragged down by the sheer number and weight of its competition its growth story will be over in fact it is already over, $705 will be its peak. 3) better to have the capacity for future quick growth 4) saves money !</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1350464601185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 05:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350464755698-28</Id><Topic><Title>Ask Yourself These Questions??</Title><Username>wbobeli</Username><Timestamp>1350423403974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 17:36:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 is touch enabled but still keep the full legacy of Wintel applications. It's a game changer for MSFT/INTC and will spur new PC growth.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1350464755698</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 05:05:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350465575079-29</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith just said Margins would BOTTOM in Q4 then move UP as they focused capacity on 14nm</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350419413422</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 16:30:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'They are locked out of Apple and Samsung which have their own in-house chip designs. There is no mobile market outside these two companies.' Qualcomm must be a phantom company then ;-). Nokia and all those Chinese vendors must be ghosts too ;-). My, such simplistic thoughts.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1350465575079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 05:19:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350466080624-30</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith just said Margins would BOTTOM in Q4 then move UP as they focused capacity on 14nm</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350419413422</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 16:30:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'No wonder ARM is kicking their #$%$ Intel lives in its own world and is completely ignoring its customers and their needs.' ARM is a hype stock, once the reality of losing Apple as an ARM design licensee hits its revenue long term its price will take a big drop. Its latest dual and quad cores lose to a single core 32nm Medfield in javascript apps, God knows what dual and quad core 22nm Silvermonts will do to them in all apps. I have never seen Intel move so quickly as it has in the last couple of years in getting a competitive mobile solution (Medfield and Clover Trail) and new form factors (convertible ultrabooks) to suit its customers new needs.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1350466080624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 05:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350467522934-31</Id><Topic><Title>Regarding "Silvermont Details"</Title><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1350389676128</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:14:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"confusion has its costs..."</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1350467522934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 05:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350467937272-32</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins Debate #2</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1350445556813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this why intrade moved Obama up to 64% after the debate from 61% and the national polls dropped a bit too for Romney and will be down over 2% pretty soon like where he deserved to be anyway? Round 3 is the elimination round. And by the way Obama never lost round 1. He only lost in the eyes of inept ignorants that think what defines a winner is not integrity and logically legitimate ideas but some actor made up #$%$ macho bully crap at the cost of the truth. Then again Americans "elected" Bush twice and loved Nixon too so what do you expect from them but to elect Obama and then take out congress allowing republicans to demolish the country to undermine his presidency in order to manipulate the ignorant masses a 3rd time in 12 years and complete their mission to turn US to a banana republic plutocracy. But then again Churchill was the one that said Americans will try everything else before finally doing the right thing, you know back in the day where actually being a conservative wasnt equal to being a traitor. If this country had what it takes to move forward it would remove congress from Republicans one more time and give Obama 2 years to pass what he wants and then after 2 years destroy Obama and democrats if he didnt take it it all in the right direction. This is what a civilized society that learns from its corrupt politicians history does to correct itself and punish them for politically undermining the country in order to improve their presidency chances. Only traitors do that and we shoot traitors in war time. This is war in case you do not get it yet. Its a war with the death spiral that must be avoided at all cost. Either we make it or a revolution with real violence will take place this decade against everything powerful and corrupt.</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1350467937272</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 05:58:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350468132769-33</Id><Topic><Title>Ask Yourself These Questions??</Title><Username>wbobeli</Username><Timestamp>1350423403974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 17:36:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No it won't. You cannot spur growth into a dying product and the worst thing about Windows 8 is that it's ARM compatible.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350468132769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 06:02:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350468269818-34</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith just said Margins would BOTTOM in Q4 then move UP as they focused capacity on 14nm</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350419413422</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 16:30:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Qualcom does a lot more than processors and Intel does not and cannot compete with Qualcom.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350468269818</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 06:04:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350468595202-35</Id><Topic><Title>Tooofunnny, Marcopubio, Singhlion and NYK20h thinking they can affect a stock price...</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350427129178</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 18:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1) Revenue guidance below expectations and points to another Y/oY DECLINE 2) profits are NOT STABLE. They are collapsing with GMs on a a Y/oY basis. A 7% decline is GMs means $1B less in profits. That s COLLAPSE. 3) Multi-Billion dollar plants are sitting idle. There is no growth in the PC market. 4) Cutting CAPEX shows you exactly what the company thinks about future growth. ULTRA BULLISH. BUY!!!</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350468595202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 06:09:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350468727190-36</Id><Topic><Title>Tooofunnny, Marcopubio, Singhlion and NYK20h thinking they can affect a stock price...</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350427129178</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 18:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you know the difference between revenues and profits? Q4 profits are collapsing. Nothing less.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350468727190</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 06:12:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350469325468-37</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when Apple missed earnings and guided way down?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1350431656016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:54:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. So why isn't it $50 right now if they are so great? Why aren't they selling these great designs in the mobile/tablet markets. Why are Samsung and Apple building their own designs? ARM is going to sell low-end PC processors for $50 or less. Those are going to kill the $150 Intel Atom/i3 chips. Performance is yesterday's game. Price and battery life is today's game and that's why Intel is failing. The bottom line is that the days of $300+ processors are long gone and not coming back. The bulk of the PC market will be moving to $50 generic processors. Just think of the implications for Intel. LOL.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350469325468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 06:22:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350469894815-38</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when Apple missed earnings and guided way down?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1350431656016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:54:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This whole Windows 8 launch with its myraid form factor options is only going to confuse customers and make them run away. This shotgun approach to gadget design used to work in the past but of late specific gadgets, with a specific customer base in mind, and a user tuned use scenario is what sells. In other words, the iPads, iPhones and Kindles are the wave of the future -- gadgets with character. The age of the generic (supply chain optimized) PC is over.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1350469894815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 06:31:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350469993068-39</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins Debate #2</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1350445556813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said Mr. Maximum_Probability. Thank you Sir.</Msg><Username>jerrykit50</Username><Timestamp>1350469993068</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 06:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350470839980-40</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins Debate #2</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1350445556813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and then lie about it in a debate for all to see. That cost Obama 2% easy.</Msg><Username>kevivoe</Username><Timestamp>1350470839980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 06:47:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350471418789-41</Id><Title>14nm Ramp Up meant for Apple A7 chip?</Title><Msg>I guess, it is...TSMC was open to customers to diversify their fab. vendors. My guess is that coupled with Atom chip power, Apple may be looking to switch to INTEL camp seriously.</Msg><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1350471418789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 06:56:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350471602153-42</Id><Topic><Title>14nm Ramp Up meant for Apple A7 chip?</Title><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1350471418789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 06:56:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Given the power, performance and convenience that comes with Intel powered tabs (yes, these tabs can be your "pc" also when you want to sit down and work), I am not going back to ARM based tablet anymore. I have an iPad and I am ready to get rid of it (on eBay).</Msg><Username>markettraker009</Username><Timestamp>1350471602153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:00:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350471611679-43</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins Debate #2</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1350445556813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Dems had their 2 years when Obama was first elected and failed us all. He is one and done.</Msg><Username>kevivoe</Username><Timestamp>1350471611679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:00:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350473215668-44</Id><Title>14nm 14nm 14nm</Title><Msg>I wonder how many of you idiots understand what that means? That's 100 atoms on a side. That's a tiny fraction of the power consumption of a 32 nm chip. It's ultra fast. I don't think you #$%$ have any idea what is going to hit you. The world will be transformed and it will all be INTEL inside. AND, you get a 4+% dividend that doubles every 5 years.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350473215668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:26:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350473242903-45</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when Apple missed earnings and guided way down?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1350431656016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:54:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'LOL. So why isn't it $50 right now if they are so great? Why aren't they selling these great designs in the mobile/tablet markets. Why are Samsung and Apple building their own designs? ARM is going to sell low-end PC processors for $50 or less. Those are going to kill the $150 Intel Atom/i3 chips. Performance is yesterday's game. Price and battery life is today's game and that's why Intel is failing. The bottom line is that the days of $300+ processors are long gone and not coming back. The bulk of the PC market will be moving to $50 generic processors. Just think of the implications for Intel. LOL.' You haven't been around long enough to see Intel take down all the cheap low price low power contenders who tried that approach e.g. Transmeta, Via, AMD, Cyrix, ARM (first time around) etc. If people are buying a PC which is not mobile and fixed to mains electricity they will want the best performance. If they are buying notebooks all they want is a device that will last a day just like tablets and phones. Expensive high performance x86 processors will still meet these requirements while still maintaining a clear performance advantage over their rivals which will continue to justify their price. As to this 'collapse' in profits you keep bleating on about, I remember when Intel made $2bn net quarterly profit when there were no iPads or iPhones or Galaxies around. Now it it's making 50% more, so let's keep this in some historical perspective, Intel's profits and revenue are still on a historically upward high trend. Otellini was right, this is a transition period for both Windows and x86 processors going deep into low power mobile devices. In a few years time the superiority of Intel architecture will be clear for all to see against the best 32-bit ARM technology in all power envelopes and INTC's stock price will suitable readjust to its correct long term value which is over double what it is now..</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1350473242903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:27:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350473307118-46</Id><Topic><Title>14nm Ramp Up meant for Apple A7 chip?</Title><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1350471418789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 06:56:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AAPL? Who?</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350473307118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:28:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350473346574-47</Id><Title>lntel upgraded to strong buy</Title><Msg>Intel upgraded to strong buy</Msg><Username>dmjohnson_and_co</Username><Timestamp>1350473346574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:29:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350474096491-48</Id><Title>(Exclusive) INTC Runored Buy Out report ! (Exclusive)</Title><Msg>Just reviewed this report outlining a potential INTC buy out: mcaf.ee/hlxzq</Msg><Username>rickflynn40</Username><Timestamp>1350474096491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:41:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350474449546-49</Id><Topic><Title>14nm Ramp Up meant for Apple A7 chip?</Title><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1350471418789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 06:56:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>theyll design a7 in house and perhaps use intel for fab instead of samsung</Msg><Username>d186282mps</Username><Timestamp>1350474449546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:47:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350474745132-50</Id><Topic><Title>lntel upgraded to strong buy</Title><Username>dmjohnson_and_co</Username><Timestamp>1350473346574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:29:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>underperform, your glasses are upside-down</Msg><Username>d186282mps</Username><Timestamp>1350474745132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:52:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350475156101-51</Id><Topic><Title>14nm 14nm 14nm</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350473215668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:26:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>long term yes, short term this stock is going to the woodshed</Msg><Username>d186282mps</Username><Timestamp>1350475156101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:59:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350475664283-52</Id><Topic><Title>14nm 14nm 14nm</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350473215668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:26:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. 14mn. Drink the koolaid. Who are they going to sell those chips to? Apple doesn't want Intel chips. Neither does Samsung. Apple is investing $10B with TMSC and TMSC will roll out 14nm in 2015. Windows 8 is ARM compatible. Intel is dead. Margins are collapsing. The dividend will be cut in 2013. You are living in dreamland.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350475664283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:07:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350475681554-53</Id><Topic><Title>lntel upgraded to strong buy</Title><Username>dmjohnson_and_co</Username><Timestamp>1350473346574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:29:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. LOL. LOL.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350475681554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:08:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350475749352-54</Id><Title>Under $21 today. Under $20 by Friday. Drink the 14nm Koolaid.</Title><Msg>Lower revenues, collapsing margins, collapsing profits. Declining market. Buy fools, BUY!</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350475749352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350475928568-55</Id><Title>didn't they beat EPS by a landslide?</Title><Msg>hmmmmmmmmmmmmm</Msg><Username>johnkelly6914593</Username><Timestamp>1350475928568</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:12:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350476020410-56</Id><Topic><Title>Ask Yourself These Questions??</Title><Username>wbobeli</Username><Timestamp>1350423403974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 17:36:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>games, animation, hd video editing, simulations, etc.. there are many reasons to upgrade html5 is a game-changer with web applications rivaling native code now possible, but a lot of horsepower is lost on the client side.. an upgrade to faster hardware is important for access to "the new web" in the near future</Msg><Username>d186282mps</Username><Timestamp>1350476020410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350476021729-57</Id><Topic><Title>14nm Ramp Up meant for Apple A7 chip?</Title><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1350471418789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 06:56:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple is investing more than $10B with TMSC. It will not use Intel any time during the next decade. Keep on fantasizing in dreamland though.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350476021729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350476039007-58</Id><Title>INTC may be TEEN again</Title><Msg>OMG .............</Msg><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1350476039007</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350476147140-59</Id><Topic><Title>Under $21 today. Under $20 by Friday. Drink the 14nm Koolaid.</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350475749352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:09:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Teen again</Msg><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1350476147140</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:15:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350476381659-60</Id><Title>Tablets are a major paradigm shift</Title><Msg>I have an iPhone 5, MacBook Pro retina and an iPad 2. Guess which one I wrote this post with? INTC is a buy at $13. Not a penny more.</Msg><Username>edison20</Username><Timestamp>1350476381659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:19:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350476708466-61</Id><Title>at 4% dividend plus I get to sell covered calls???? Buy it now.</Title><Msg>Simple formula, 4% in divs plus another easy 6% in call premiums. It can go down a little, but I'll make plenty while the ship turns around. They'll also be a dividend hike soon, their dividend growth is massive. Easy money.</Msg><Username>fishfryer527</Username><Timestamp>1350476708466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:25:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350476835001-62</Id><Topic><Title>So.. how low will it go?? Serious replies?</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1350430692954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:38:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mega-cap stocks like Intel usually don't crash the morning after earnings; they trend down for quite some time until capitulation. I think you are right. This stock could trend down into the teens--just like CSCO did--as more and more fund magagers decide it is too ugly for their portfolio. Not until after that will it turn back around. Big ships like these take longer to turn around. It should trend down to $19-and-change.... maybe lower.... before enough value investors come in to prop it back up.</Msg><Username>profitgrowthfirst</Username><Timestamp>1350476835001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:27:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350476870705-63</Id><Title>This will fall to $19/share</Title><Msg>9 downgrades on the earnings report/forecast. Nomura says $19 is the new target. Nomura has credibility. Good luck.</Msg><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1350476870705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350476892696-64</Id><Topic><Title>at 4% dividend plus I get to sell covered calls???? Buy it now.</Title><Username>fishfryer527</Username><Timestamp>1350476708466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:25:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did the Titanic turn around? 4.34% 4.47% 4.28% 4.14% 4.25% 4.31% 4.48% 4.59% Here's where I bought dividend wise, wait for a turn around and take the div or dump and get better dividends elsewhere? Intel is a very hard stock to hold. $25 or $26 this morning, L O L !!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350476892696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:28:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350476952751-65</Id><Topic><Title>Tablets are a major paradigm shift</Title><Username>edison20</Username><Timestamp>1350476381659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:19:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>6.92% it is a buy, do you know how stupid that is to say ?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350476952751</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:29:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350476953872-66</Id><Topic><Title>Tablets are a major paradigm shift</Title><Username>edison20</Username><Timestamp>1350476381659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:19:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know someone that has an Ipad and already wants the CloverTrail Windows Tablet as he says "I can actually get some work done with it." Do you have an Apple Tattoo on your forehead?</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350476953872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:29:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477024770-67</Id><Topic><Title>14nm 14nm 14nm</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350473215668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:26:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't you mean staying....</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350477024770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:30:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350477055887-68</Id><Title>I will be buying big as the shorts try to rob the shareholders blind.....</Title><Msg>AS they have to beg me to sell it back to them before they end up on the street.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350477055887</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350477130377-69</Id><Title>Make no mistake, NYK2OH is DYING to buy Intel under 20</Title><Msg>He's peed his pants trying to scam little old ladies out of their shares.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350477130377</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:32:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477143825-70</Id><Topic><Title>This will fall to $19/share</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1350476870705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:27:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It has been my experience that you buy on the downgrades,signaling that big money is getting ready to buy. You know the game is rigged and this is how they do it. Notice that no one was downgrading at 29,when they were getting out.</Msg><Username>blair.wagner</Username><Timestamp>1350477143825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:32:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477173344-71</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins Debate #2</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1350445556813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a draw at best. watched 40 minutes of it and 1 tweet went by that said Watching Obama talk avout econmics in painful. Have to agree that O doesn't seem to know crap about running a business. he would be gone if Bernanke hadn't propped up the market</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350477173344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477315858-72</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins Debate #2</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1350445556813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too much heat to post as ww ?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350477315858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:35:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477343450-73</Id><Topic><Title>at 4% dividend plus I get to sell covered calls???? Buy it now.</Title><Username>fishfryer527</Username><Timestamp>1350476708466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:25:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tigle, Do you sell covered calls? The div is only part of the story when it comes to income.</Msg><Username>fishfryer527</Username><Timestamp>1350477343450</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:35:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477459408-74</Id><Topic><Title>Intel beat estimates by 10 cents!</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1350458209105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 03:16:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so is WW taking the day off? what a #$%$!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350477459408</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:37:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350477466845-75</Id><Title>Intel CEO need to resign</Title><Msg>INTC = 19</Msg><Username>vinhxle</Username><Timestamp>1350477466845</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477578206-76</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone5 review (vs RAZRi etc)</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1350419386939</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 16:29:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good link, thanks for posting. I disagree with your conclusions regarding Silvermont, if the A15 doesn't kill battery at high clocks it'll walk all over Silvermont. We'll see when the benchmarks arrive:)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1350477578206</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350477611405-77</Id><Title>INTC Might Trend Downward for Months</Title><Msg>Mega-cap stocks like this one tend to trend down for months after an earnings disappointment, similar to the way Sisco trended down for almost a full year before it finally started to turn things around. With these mega-cap stocks, so much of their float is held by institutions that have to unload millions-upon-millions of dollars worth, so they cannot sell all of that at once. They have to slowly unload those shares over time. With many funds slowly unloading their shares (hundreds of millions of shares over an extended period of time), that is just too much mass selling for enough "value investors" to come in to stabilize the price. So the "value investors" who are pondering buying the now-cheaper shares are also having to ask themselves if they want to be the one to "catch the falling knife", and if they do buy, how long are they willing to watch the downward trend continue before they throw in the towel as well? The downward pressure should be strong for a while until a firm support level shows. Therefore, do not buy INTC for quite some time.</Msg><Username>profitgrowthfirst</Username><Timestamp>1350477611405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:40:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477629085-78</Id><Topic><Title>Over 120,000,000 shares all selling at the same time tomorrow</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1350444196288</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>T is higher</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350477629085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:40:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477721666-79</Id><Topic><Title>Boomers not buying anymore PCs...sorry but it's game over dudes</Title><Username>trader.quick</Username><Timestamp>1350429677096</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:21:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the problem is you are not the norm. I need a PC as well. Can't run a business from a tablet. I refuse to buy an Apple product.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350477721666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:42:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477802405-80</Id><Topic><Title>Yo Whobeli.. ask yourself these questions....</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1350429868407</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:24:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so you're saying Intel is smart...........even though they have failed miseerably and watched the mobile world sail away without them?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350477802405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477840983-81</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is looking...</Title><Username>pv.miller</Username><Timestamp>1350446446846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:00:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about the people that sold at $28? how do they sound?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350477840983</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477893179-82</Id><Topic><Title>$450 Ivy Bridge Laptop vs $599 Microsoft Surface RT (With optional keyboard)</Title><Username>publicservice100</Username><Timestamp>1350445827611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The tablet includes 2GB of RAM, roughly about 1/3rd one gets with the laptop.</Msg><Username>mega.hurts</Username><Timestamp>1350477893179</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:44:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477893722-83</Id><Topic><Title>$450 Ivy Bridge Laptop vs $599 Microsoft Surface RT (With optional keyboard)</Title><Username>publicservice100</Username><Timestamp>1350445827611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The tablet includes 2GB of RAM, roughly about 1/3rd one gets with the laptop.</Msg><Username>mega.hurts</Username><Timestamp>1350477893722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:44:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477941106-84</Id><Topic><Title>So.. how low will it go?? Serious replies?</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1350430692954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:38:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You do mean "rue the day"? However, yes I agree that w8 will boost chip sales in 2013.</Msg><Username>winmore_98</Username><Timestamp>1350477941106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:45:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350477947392-85</Id><Title>Another day, more crying and whining by Tiglet</Title><Msg>Sell your puny stake in Intel and get lost, Tampon loser.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350477947392</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477999906-86</Id><Topic><Title>So.. how low will it go?? Serious replies?</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1350430692954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:38:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes it is simple math... they make well over $ 2 a share and pay a 90 cent dividend.... why would they have to reduce the dividend... you people talk like they are losing money</Msg><Username>darkrai468</Username><Timestamp>1350477999906</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350478182678-87</Id><Topic><Title>Another day, more crying and whining by Tiglet</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350477947392</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He spams multiple threads with the exact same crying and whining every day. Instead of blaming it on himself for not selling at 29, it's somebody elses fault. What a coward. Hope he doesn't have kids.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350478182678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:49:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350478278684-88</Id><Title>BUYING all those cheap INTC shares before market open</Title><Msg>You will not see this low when it open folks.</Msg><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1350478278684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:51:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350478451945-89</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama: "Intel was founded by immigrants."</Title><Username>aviacionado</Username><Timestamp>1350440577863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 22:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the intelligence of the American voter" As they should, he got in once already.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350478451945</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:54:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350478553220-90</Id><Topic><Title>All Obama has done all night is bash the rick folks</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350441196017</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 22:33:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all night? and the last 4 yeas as well. He has divided the country over this.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350478553220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350478583517-91</Id><Topic><Title>at 4% dividend plus I get to sell covered calls???? Buy it now.</Title><Username>fishfryer527</Username><Timestamp>1350476708466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:25:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350478583517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:56:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350478585872-92</Id><Topic><Title>So.. how low will it go?? Serious replies?</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1350430692954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:38:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't fall into that trap. "Great, I'll buy for the 5.1% dividend." That's the exact same thing people said when HPQ fell from $43 to $32, when BBY fell from $42 to $21, and when RadioShack fell from $22 to $10. Too many people have let nice-looking dividends trick them into buying into falling stocks.</Msg><Username>profitgrowthfirst</Username><Timestamp>1350478585872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:56:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350478857869-93</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone5 review (vs RAZRi etc)</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1350419386939</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 16:29:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'I disagree with your conclusions regarding Silvermont, if the A15 doesn't kill battery at high clocks it'll walk all over Silvermont.' Not a chance especially when it will be faced with similar core counts but double the threads. The A9 to A15 is going from an OoO 2-wide to 3-wide processor while Atom will be taking the far more important performance step of going from in order to out of order which will be an instant all round 30%+ integer performance improvement e.g. like the jump from A8 to A9 which is a bigger jump than going from A9 to A15. They could also increase the issue width to 3 too, we shall see. I expect Atom will retain its javascript advantage while adding a lot more in other apps, both cpu and gpu.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1350478857869</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:00:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350478867439-94</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama: "Intel was founded by immigrants."</Title><Username>aviacionado</Username><Timestamp>1350440577863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 22:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most truthful statement by Captain America? "Romney is extreme and dishonest" , not to mention a draft dodger and income-tax evader. Besides that, he's not even a Xtian.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1350478867439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:01:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350479085067-95</Id><Topic><Title>This will fall to $19/share</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1350476870705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:27:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is often true; the downgrades and upgrades do tend to come too late to matter. However, in this case, I think the decline in PC sales will continue to bring down that segment of Intel's business for quite some time.</Msg><Username>profitgrowthfirst</Username><Timestamp>1350479085067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:04:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350479198220-96</Id><Title>Something To Consider</Title><Msg>Bonanza Goldfields, BONZ, is a junior gold mining start-up company with tremendous potential. The new C.E.O. was a director at the U.S. Mint. Financing secured. Gold production will begin at the company's Tarantula site soon. Read the recent Yahoo news. 300-500% upside over the next 90 days is possible. "Penny stock today. Dollar stock tomorrow."</Msg><Username>aunttizzy</Username><Timestamp>1350479198220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350479333045-97</Id><Topic><Title>Intel beat estimates by 10 cents!</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1350458209105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 03:16:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and cut guidance and margins. You need to be fired along with Wally.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1350479333045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:08:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350479368665-98</Id><Title>IS THIS REALLY USA?US Presidential Candidate Jill Stein Arrested at Debate Site</Title><Msg>IS THIS REALLY USA?US Presidential Candidate Jill Stein Arrested at Debate Site US Presidential Candidate Jill Stein Arrested at Debate Site Tue, 10/16/2012 - 21:23 in [RT]: Police arrested Green Party Presidential candidate Jill Stein and her running mate, Cheri Honkala, after they tried to enter the site of tonights presidential debate at the Hofstra University. The two were protesting against the exclusion of all but the two major political parties from taking part in the debate. Jill Stein, Cheri Honkala arrested, call tonight's #debate a "mockumentary", said a tweet posted on her account. The presidential candidate and her vice-presidential nominee were arrested by local police when they tried to enter the grounds of Hofstra University, in Hempstead, New York, Stein's campaign website says. The women are currently still in police custody. --------------------------------------------------- Nation Tunes In To See Which Sociopath More Likable This Time Tue, 10/16/2012 - 20:28 "HEMPSTEAD, NYAccording to reports, millions of viewers across the country are expected to tune in to tonights town-hall-style presidential debate at Hofstra University in order to determine which complete and utter sociopath they find more likable this time around." Theonion web domain</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1350479368665</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:09:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350479408988-99</Id><Title>buffet got out at 27$, he must have known some thing? gotta follow the big $.</Title><Msg>yeah, buffet got the word at 27$. question is when does it bottom! jmo g/l.</Msg><Username>jondow69</Username><Timestamp>1350479408988</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:10:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350479500113-100</Id><Topic><Title>I will be buying big as the shorts try to rob the shareholders blind.....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350477055887</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:30:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This PPs will be the historical low for a decade.... BUY all the shorts want to sell you!</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1350479500113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:11:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350479898913-101</Id><Topic><Title>The haters just can't stand that they are paying a staunch Dividend AND buying shares back.</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350445536556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:45:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC woefully overpaid for it's own shares, percentage ofprofit payout for dividends getting too high</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1350479898913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:18:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350479959642-102</Id><Topic><Title>Wally in the Woodwork</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1316637403000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2011-09-21 16:36:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>upppppppppppppp</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1350479959642</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:19:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350480101125-103</Id><Topic><Title>buffet got out at 27$, he must have known some thing? gotta follow the big $.</Title><Username>jondow69</Username><Timestamp>1350479408988</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forget that he got in at around these levels....which means he found value at these levels.</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1350480101125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:21:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350480109445-104</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1323902498000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2011-12-14 17:41:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>uppppppp</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1350480109445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:21:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350480264719-105</Id><Topic><Title>buffet got out at 27$, he must have known some thing? gotta follow the big $.</Title><Username>jondow69</Username><Timestamp>1350479408988</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I DIDN'T FORGET, he got in at 21 sold at 27, took his 60$ million, i remember when this sold at 17's i'll just see what happens, just look at dell,hpq, supposedly INTC is coming out with a chip for mobile devices, just see what happens! jmo g/l.</Msg><Username>jondow69</Username><Timestamp>1350480264719</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:24:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350480275961-106</Id><Title>No downgrades...Ha ha ha</Title><Msg>Bottommmmmed???</Msg><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1350480275961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:24:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350480280783-107</Id><Title>Fast money said to buy at $28?</Title><Msg>They were sure wrong!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! INTC is a dinasoar@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@ OLD POS</Msg><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1350480280783</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:24:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350480341562-108</Id><Topic><Title>No downgrades...Ha ha ha</Title><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1350480275961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:24:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Downgrades are going to come in like crazy today!</Msg><Username>maveric_trader1</Username><Timestamp>1350480341562</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:25:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350480343546-109</Id><Topic><Title>No downgrades...Ha ha ha</Title><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1350480275961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:24:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>give it time-their will be</Msg><Username>marrohead</Username><Timestamp>1350480343546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:25:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350480366357-110</Id><Title>New low today</Title><Msg>Open at $21.28 with today's low at $20.25 Go short on this &amp; win..............It will down another 3% tomorrow.</Msg><Username>pple64</Username><Timestamp>1350480366357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:26:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350480561701-111</Id><Title>Chump Street Blows the Earnings Call - Big Time</Title><Msg>Chump Street predicted a huge and overwhelming revenue miss for Q3. And then priced it in eight times. But guess what? There wasn't ANY revenue miss. And earnings exceeded the estimate by 10 cents. And yet Chump Street is now trying to ignore all of the actual results and price the miss in a NINTH time. You can't make this stuff up. Just say no to Chump Street's continuing stupidity...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350480561701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350480587764-112</Id><Topic><Title>WHEN WILL WALLIS SURFACE?</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1350425531534</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 18:12:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm worried about Wallis. He may be out on a window ledge somewhere. TOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1350480587764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:29:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350480616935-113</Id><Topic><Title>New low today</Title><Username>pple64</Username><Timestamp>1350480366357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:26:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>new low keep coming , i told peop le so many times , who listen to me shoud have been made a lot of money! shortshortshortshortshort i told you so</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1350480616935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:30:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350480833025-114</Id><Title>Housing Starts in U.S. Surged in September to Four-Year High</Title><Msg>[Yet more bad news for the doom and gloom crowd on Chump Street. What is their problem and why do they continuously attack the US economy and US manufacturing???] New-home construction in the U.S. surged in September to the highest level in four years, a sign the industry is on the road to recovery. Starts jumped 15 percent to an 872,000 annual rate last month, the most since July 2008 and exceeding all forecasts in a Bloomberg survey of economists, Commerce Department figures showed today in Washington. The median estimate of 81 economists surveyed by Bloomberg called for 770,000. An increase in building permits may mean the gains will be sustained. A pickup in sales stoked by record-low mortgage rates and population growth combined with dwindling supply indicates construction can continue strengthening, contributing more to economic growth. At the same time, the level of starts remains below the pre-recession peak, limiting how much the industry can boost the rate of expansion. The housing market certainly has turned, said Brian Jones, a senior U.S. economist at Societe Generale in New York, whose forecast for 790,000 starts was among the highest. But we still have a long way to go. The good thing is that construction will pull employment with it. Stock-index futures extended earlier gains after the report. The contract on the Standard &amp; Poors 500 Index maturing in December climbed 0.3 percent to 1,452.8 at 8:45 a.m. in New York. Treasury securities fell, sending the yield on the benchmark 10-year note up to 1.77 percent from 1.72 percent late yesterday. Survey Results Estimates in the Bloomberg survey for housing starts ranged from 735,000 to 800,000, and the prior month was revised up to 758,000 from a previously reported 750,000 pace. Over the past 12 months, work began on 34.8 percent more homes, the biggest year-over-year gain since April. Building permits, a proxy for future construction, jumped to an 894,000 annual rate, also exceeding the median forecast and the most since July 2008. They were projected to rise to 810,000, with a range of 780,000 to 850,000. The number of permits swelled by 45.1 percent since September 2011, the biggest annual jump since 1983. Construction of single-family houses climbed 11 percent from August to a 603,000 rate. Work on multifamily homes, such apartment buildings, increased 25.1 percent to an annual rate of 269,000. Three of four regions showed gain in starts last month, led by a 20.1 percent jump in the West.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350480833025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350480833792-115</Id><Topic><Title>Under $21 today. Under $20 by Friday. Drink the 14nm Koolaid.</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350475749352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:09:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It crashed through the 52-week low like it wasn't even there. This will trend down for quite some time before finding new support.</Msg><Username>profitgrowthfirst</Username><Timestamp>1350480833792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350480871963-116</Id><Title>OH THE HUMANITY!!!!</Title><Msg>Lemme guess, good time to double down? Buy with both fists? This is what happens when you completely miss the mobile revolution. I told you 10 years ago. This thing will never see $30 again. Ever. I do applaud them for keeping jobs in the US, though, and their fabs are top notch.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1350480871963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350480975053-117</Id><Title>Wow, 14M shares dumped in 5 minutes.</Title><Msg>That can't be good.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1350480975053</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:36:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481076491-118</Id><Title>Thanks for letting me reinvest the upcoming Dividend cheaply</Title><Msg>Candy from a baby.</Msg><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1350481076491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:37:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481081471-119</Id><Title>Chump Street Shills LIke NYK20h</Title><Msg>We continue to have to put up with Wall Street shills like NYK20h whose knowledge of technology would fit on the head of a pin measured in nanometers. Wall Street had the full court shill press on. Just more attempts to defraud the average investor. Why can't these people simple get a real job instead of getting out of bed every single day trying to destroy the wealth of people who have earned it?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350481081471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:38:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481096067-120</Id><Title>You can bet this is a</Title><Msg>Great time to buy. Intel is a good place to put some money for a long term investment. jmho</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1350481096067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:38:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350481103370-121</Id><Topic><Title>Housing Starts in U.S. Surged in September to Four-Year High</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350480833025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>then buy housing stocks, unlike intc, they're green</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1350481103370</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:38:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350481157295-122</Id><Topic><Title>You can bet this is a</Title><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1350481096067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:38:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BIG support at 21.40...If it does goes below 21 it will be only for an instant before the money bids it up.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350481157295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:39:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481239606-123</Id><Title>Had a limit order in for 21.25...never hit stock going up!</Title><Msg>Wow it didn't even get to 21? I wanted to buy cheaper but its running away from me.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350481239606</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:40:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481297210-124</Id><Title>Just Ask Chump Street</Title><Msg>Where's the miss? Where is the great big huge monstrous miss that you projected? That you promised? The $8 billion revenue miss you projected? Where is that miss? Come on, you can tell us. Where exactly is that miss?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350481297210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:41:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481436026-125</Id><Title>TADF NEWS,BIG SUPPORT.TADF 2000% GAINS POSSIBLE ON ACQUISITIONS ANNOUNCED.READ</Title><Msg>TADF NEWS,BIG SUPPORT.TADF 2000% GAINS POSSIBLE ON ACQUISITIONS ANNOUNCED.READ The company is growing at an amazing rate, almost 4 acquisitions in 60 days. TADF, through its subsidiary has 5 contract bids with the Department Of Defense. TADF WILL BE CLOSING 4 ACQUISITIONS CLOSING IN OCTOBER TADF Contract Announcement expected any day. Penny Stock Analyst suggest TADF is for a HUGE BREAKOUT. The stock price has the potential to go up 5c to 15c. And buying the stock for nothing at 0.0007 will bring unbelievable profit. 1 million shares@ 0.0007= $700. Sell 1 million shares@ 1 cent = $10,000 or 5 cents= $50,000. 2000% GAINS can turn your trading losses to gains and bring your trading account back to positive.</Msg><Username>pennyupdates</Username><Timestamp>1350481436026</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:43:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481452303-126</Id><Title>S&amp;P REITERATES HOLD RECOMMENDATION ON SHARES OF INTEL CORP</Title><Msg>S&amp;P REITERATES HOLD RECOMMENDATION ON SHARES OF INTEL CORP. (S&amp;P Capital IQ) We are lowering our 2012 EPS estimate $0.01 to $2.10 and 2013's by $0.10 to $2.03 following INTC's Q3 report. Guidance was weak as expected, but INTC guided Dec-Q gross margins to 57%, well below our 62.5% estimate. Management indicated that it needs to drive down utilization to reduce inventory. This is our key concern against a weak macro backdrop and lowered expectations for new Ultrabooks. We look for a slow recovery, but lower gross margins and EPS in '13. INTC reported Q3 EPS of $0.58, vs. $0.65, above our $0.50 estimate, due to higher revenue. Print</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1350481452303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:44:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481518103-127</Id><Title>Solid ER and we 7 points down ??</Title><Msg>we should be 10% up</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350481518103</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:45:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481519926-128</Id><Title>What happen?</Title><Msg>who is buying and selling?</Msg><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1350481519926</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481544151-129</Id><Title>time to load up the shares</Title><Msg>believe it is good to time to buy and hold for the dividend</Msg><Username>bepatientforever</Username><Timestamp>1350481544151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:45:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481548265-130</Id><Title>INTEL holding...will close $20.00 end of day</Title><Msg>Support at 21.40...buyers flocking for dividend.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350481548265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350481552575-131</Id><Topic><Title>Just Ask Chump Street</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350481297210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:41:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis, you "missed," the mobile computing revolution. That was the miss and people are just starting to acknowledge it. From here on out, it's catch-up ball.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1350481552575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:45:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350481583328-132</Id><Topic><Title>Just Ask Chump Street</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350481297210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:41:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's the best news I could find for Intel today: Intel INTC numbers cut at UBS. Shares of INTC now seen reaching $29, UBS said. Estimates also lowered on expected lower server processor growth, gross margin. Intel numbers lowered at Jefferies. Shares of INTC now seen reaching $24, Jefferies said. Estimates also lowered on slower growth, lower margins. Hold rating.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1350481583328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:46:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350481603969-133</Id><Topic><Title>time to load up the shares</Title><Username>bepatientforever</Username><Timestamp>1350481544151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:45:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep just got in for another 200 @ 21.40 this am</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350481603969</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:46:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481608992-134</Id><Title>Just Ask Chump Street - Part II</Title><Msg>Hey, Chump Street. A couple more things. Maybe you haven't heard about these either - along with that miss you promised not materializing. 1.) Housing starts up. You heard about those? 2.) Consumer sentiment up. You must have heard about that. Right? 3.) Manufacturing up. Don't tell me you missed that too. How is that possible? 4.) Employment up. Okay I suppose you're going to say that you're four for four. Chump Street - they don't get out much....</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350481608992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481690680-135</Id><Title>Dividend puts a floor on the stock</Title><Msg>There is no cash flow problems even in worse case 2013 scenario.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1350481690680</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481747263-136</Id><Title>Lower lows every other day = stay away for now?</Title><Msg>It does look tempting though.</Msg><Username>barneylipps</Username><Timestamp>1350481747263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:49:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481853714-137</Id><Title>Chump Street Mitigation</Title><Msg>Okay Chump Street is obviously trying to mitigate the effects of its horrid earnings projection. I mean - you project an $8 billion revenue miss and there isn't any revenue miss. How do you spin that? Well, read any of the one man shill show messages from today to answer that...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350481853714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:50:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350481894224-138</Id><Title>shorts just a reminder to pay my comiing divy + the next 20</Title><Msg>total of ~ 60000$</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350481894224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:51:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350482042334-139</Id><Topic><Title>This Latest Downturn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345732452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 10:34:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I repeat!....... ultrabooks are the new, improved buggy whips. intel's efforts are misguided. all of the work and $$$ put into ultrabooks should have gone into mobile. until intel has a solid presence in mobile, the stock is dead money.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1350482042334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350482135397-140</Id><Title>Lucy Does Sybil</Title><Msg>LOL, Lucy switching back and forth between the Notttt Funny and the Vinnie IDs amongst others. Well, if you are going to try to spin that horrid earning miss projection, you are going to need a lot of IDs and no one has more than the one man shill show. You go Lucy. You blew the call. You blew the call big time. No matter. You'll spin it. Spin on Lucy. Try to pump some air back into that ego. The Fudd Fade started at the opening...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350482135397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:55:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350482181898-141</Id><Title>$22 hitting soon</Title><Msg>Buy now for 21's cause it will be gone by end of day</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350482181898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350482270067-142</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy Does Sybil</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350482135397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:55:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lucy really exposed himself with the Vinny alias...a guy that worked for Intel, got fired, picked up a job at AMD, pumped the stock at 40 and now what? LOL! Even funnier, all the barking he does here doesn't change the Dividend from hitting our accounts every three months. He IS alone in his own personal He11.</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1350482270067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:57:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350482335384-143</Id><Title>This will only go up...</Title><Msg>because I sold my holdings at 21.40...Retail Investor is gone now...</Msg><Username>markettraker009</Username><Timestamp>1350482335384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:58:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350482338367-144</Id><Title>I cannot believe this CASINO</Title><Msg>OMG .............</Msg><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1350482338367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:58:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350482350856-145</Id><Title>I cannot believe this CASINO</Title><Msg>OMG .............</Msg><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1350482350856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:59:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350482354478-146</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL holding...will close $20.00 end of day</Title><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350481548265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:45:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buyers seeing opportunity</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350482354478</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:59:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350482390871-147</Id><Title>Both said Mit and Obama to lower corp. taxes last night --- good for Intel and other use comp.</Title><Msg>.........</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350482390871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350482471639-148</Id><Title>NYK2OH nowhere to be found when price is rising</Title><Msg>He and Lucy worship Satan.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350482471639</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:01:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350482667360-149</Id><Topic><Title>This will only go up...</Title><Username>markettraker009</Username><Timestamp>1350482335384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:58:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree all news are out and Intel will go up.</Msg><Username>aak47_2</Username><Timestamp>1350482667360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:04:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350482690195-150</Id><Title>Intel doing better than IBM. Stick that up your derrier, MARCOFAGGGGIO</Title><Msg>Bend over, putz.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350482690195</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350482715534-151</Id><Title>INTC Foundry?</Title><Msg>I think it may be time for INTC to start concentrating on becomming a foundry. TSM can't keep up with 28nm for all their clients and Dr. Chang has told them to find other vendors to help fill their need. TSM currently enjoys a PE=17 and a forward PE=14.3. Compare this with INTC who has state of the art processing and fabrication and has a PE=9 and a forward PE=10. If we followed suit, excluding all the R&amp;D savings etc. we would be trading at a comfortable $40.00/share. If this makes sense, I encourage you to contact investor relations and demand the board of directors address this issue immediately. NVDA has already gone public and said INTC should produce the Tegra3 for them. Then you have QCOM and AAPL, but if you waiy long enough, the opportunity may abate.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350482715534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:05:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350482814109-152</Id><Topic><Title>Chump Street Mitigation</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350481853714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:50:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you project an $8 billion revenue miss and there isn't any revenue miss</Msg><Username>c757172</Username><Timestamp>1350482814109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:06:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350482891336-153</Id><Title>Thanks Sellers!! Got 2200 @ 21.31</Title><Msg>Will finish positive today. Love this game!!!</Msg><Username>cinqolok</Username><Timestamp>1350482891336</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:08:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350482894034-154</Id><Topic><Title>BUYING all those cheap INTC shares before market open</Title><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1350478278684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:51:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder if anyone here took my buy early in the morning ?</Msg><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1350482894034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:08:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350482954275-155</Id><Topic><Title>I cannot believe this CASINO</Title><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1350482350856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:59:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Believe it !! This market is so rigged it's not even funny anymore! Stocks go up that should be going down and vice versa all because of the options gaming that goes on! Look at AMZN and AAPL for a great illustration on how the privileged entities on wall street can do whatever they want to a stock price regardless of company prospects. AAPL's stock price struggles to go up and stay up even though AAPL is selling every product it can make. Meanwhile AMZN is basically a low margined , tremendously overvalued internet retailer, but the stock pops on nothing and struggles to go down. INTC's core business is under assault because of tablets and mobile, but the stock will not crash!!</Msg><Username>wuwuwu3</Username><Timestamp>1350482954275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:09:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350482980408-156</Id><Topic><Title>Chump Street Mitigation</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350481853714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:50:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Misinformation propagated by one of the greatest shills on this board, Wallis.</Msg><Username>c757172</Username><Timestamp>1350482980408</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:09:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350482996756-157</Id><Title>NYK20H and his Marco alias have to pay my Dividend</Title><Msg>BWAH HAHAHAHAHAAHA</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350482996756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:09:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350483102410-158</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Foundry?</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350482715534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You think this way because you are enveloped by the mythology out there, ie, PC is dead, INTC a dying company, this things' goin' to $10, etc etc. If you think for yourself, you'll realize that this is all about who has greatest tech, and that is primarily node size, as speed and efficiency derive from that. It isnt SoC (that's just a design), it's basic technology...how few atoms are needed for a node and how do we get there? If only you could come to understand in the larger picture what this is all about you would understand that INTC is no more interested in becoming a foundry than Einstein was about Swiss patents.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350483102410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350483105051-159</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend puts a floor on the stock</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1350481690680</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NEVER think that.</Msg><Username>whowants2be</Username><Timestamp>1350483105051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:11:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350483184432-160</Id><Title>Price was already taken down with HPQ results.</Title><Msg>INTC results were better than expected. Got in cheaper than the 21.50 that I had planned to purchase by waiting for this morning. It will only be a trade because I do think this market is overpriced. Obama wins debate because he identified that Romney has been successful and we do not want a president like that. I am not Republican or Democrat but this is ridiculous that both Biden and Obama think that the whole voter public is ignorant and uneducated. It is identified how much the present president has failed with Obama nailing Romney on what a success he has been basically saying that there is no place in politics for a successful man like this.</Msg><Username>happyperson_1</Username><Timestamp>1350483184432</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:13:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350483438742-161</Id><Title>I bought another 20K shares at $21.25 today</Title><Msg>Need to double-down on these absurd low prices. I'll be buying more beach-front property with this dividend check.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1350483438742</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:17:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350483573994-162</Id><Topic><Title>I bought another 20K shares at $21.25 today</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1350483438742</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:17:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too bad the low of day was 21.26 and 21.27 in pre mkt you lying sack - O- Crap</Msg><Username>marrohead</Username><Timestamp>1350483573994</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350483680581-163</Id><Title>Can anyone please tell me why INTC's volume is so high?</Title><Msg>Is it best time to buy this?</Msg><Username>ashwani_rana55</Username><Timestamp>1350483680581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:21:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350483723372-164</Id><Topic><Title>Both said Mit and Obama to lower corp. taxes last night --- good for Intel and other use comp.</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350482390871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:59:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The tax code predates the trade agreements that the US has signed with many countries. Those agreements made it easier to move a company to those countries and ship the good back. Companies could expand where the cost of getting a manufactured product to the customer was lowest. Companies could not only take advantage of lower taxes but also lower wages and fewer regulations. The country with the the best combination of those three things will attract business. Oppressed people work cheaper. Countries will impose regulations as they see what the worst company will do to the environment. There is tangible value to the government supported infrastructure of roads, dams, .... There will be some changes made to Medicare and Social Security to address funding. I do not trust the Republicans with that decision. I do not think there is any Democrat who will take that step. I don't know who the leader will be or where he/she will come from but America needs that person.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350483723372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:22:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350484041187-165</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Foundry?</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350482715534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually I'm long, my point is INTC is several years ahead of the competition and we have excess capacity and TSM is running full bore. If we took that excess capacity and started working on the fab in Oregon that we just quit working on, we could become the ultimate decider in cell phones and tablets. If say QCOM were to get ARMH processors from INTC in the interm while we worked and improved our cell phone chips, they would instantly dominate the cell phone market with ARMH 22nm technology. That would put AAPL and NVDA a year behind waiting on TSM. Then when we get the 86 processor that will demolish ARMH, we offer it to the highest bidders and then deep 6 ARMH. All we do in the mean time is make more money, increase stock price, and increase number of plants which we will need when the improved 86 processor is ready.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350484041187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:27:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350484090840-166</Id><Title>In 6 months ...</Title><Msg>Wallus and Mux will still be looking like the looooooooooooosers they are.</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1350484090840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:28:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350484203116-167</Id><Title>President Obama said to buy Intel and Google EOM</Title><Msg>EOM</Msg><Username>yorslo</Username><Timestamp>1350484203116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:30:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350484287116-168</Id><Topic><Title>14nm 14nm 14nm</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350473215668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:26:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the woodshed behind the other woodshed</Msg><Username>d186282mps</Username><Timestamp>1350484287116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:31:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350484424132-169</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Might Trend Downward for Months</Title><Username>profitgrowthfirst</Username><Timestamp>1350477611405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:40:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>16 million shares traded in just the first few minutes, but for INTC the negative outlook outweighs any positive sentiment (other than the fact that the dividend yield gets better as the price falls). Therefore, this stock should continue to have a lot of downward pressure as sellers outweigh buyers, and the 52-week low that was broken this morning should continue to see pressure.</Msg><Username>profitgrowthfirst</Username><Timestamp>1350484424132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:33:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350484425705-170</Id><Title>Last night both Mutt and Barry promised ...</Title><Msg>to repeal Wallis Weaver Day as they've come to appreciate that honoring a shill is counterproductive for the nation.</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1350484425705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350484469393-171</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Foundry?</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350482715534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It may not be possible for Intel to improve the x86 processor for low power applications much further within a reasonable time frame. ARM is so far ahead in this game that if Intel lost their process advantage, they might fall too far behind to ever catch up.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1350484469393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:34:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350484894895-172</Id><Title>Where's the Miss, Lucy???</Title><Msg>It's a simple question. You promised the big huge honking miss. Where is it? There wasn't ANY miss. Not even an earnings miss. Heck the whisper earnings number was 43 cents and earnings came in at 60 cents. A huge beat. Where's the miss, Lucy? Don't go quiet on us now. Crank up one of those million IDs you are running and explain what happened to the $8 billion revenue miss you promised would occur...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350484894895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350484967639-173</Id><Title>average volume in 1 hour</Title><Msg>buy ...........................</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1350484967639</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:42:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350485079381-174</Id><Topic><Title>Where's the Miss, Lucy???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350484894895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:41:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean "Where is Miss Lucy." LOL!777777777777777777777777</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350485079381</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:44:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350485080709-175</Id><Topic><Title>Where's the Miss, Lucy???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350484894895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:41:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy Intel? Why?</Msg><Username>bridgecrew</Username><Timestamp>1350485080709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:44:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350485613801-176</Id><Title>Intel set to continue its impressive profitability</Title><Msg>Yahoo news wire. F'n Dagger for the Lucies..</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1350485613801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350485704954-177</Id><Title>I keep forgetting that ...</Title><Msg>for Wallis this is a game in which the share price doesn't count for anything.</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1350485704954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:55:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350485823709-178</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>terinavok57883</Username><Timestamp>1350478389422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope it contains great info. I just joined. Many thanks</Msg><Username>burgess_christina611</Username><Timestamp>1350485823709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350485857346-179</Id><Topic><Title>14nm 14nm 14nm</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350473215668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:26:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I wonder how many of you idiots understand what that means? That's 100 atoms on a side." IDIOT !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1350485857346</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:57:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350485939555-180</Id><Topic><Title>I keep forgetting that ...</Title><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1350485704954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:55:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound ultra frustrated that Wally and the Longs are enjoying the Dividend and life in general and aren't do or die by the daily pricing..........while you are scraping daytraders together to pay rent. OUCH...for you.</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1350485939555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350486252281-181</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>terinavok57883</Username><Timestamp>1350478389422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finally! I found something informative.</Msg><Username>mckinney_lara552</Username><Timestamp>1350486252281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:04:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350486486844-182</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Foundry?</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350482715534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think that the point would be for Intel to use the empty fab capacity that they announced yesterday to manufacture ARMH for QCOM or .... and that would put Apple, Nvidia and TSM under pressure. ARM does have a lead in low power today. That gap is closing fast and there should be no reason that I can think of that an x86 product can not match the performance and power profiles of ARM. In the conference call yesterday, Paul O. said that Intel was lowering the Haswell TDP from 17W to 10W. That is not a low power product but it indicates that Intel reduced the power consumption by 70% on a notebook/desktop product. I expect that a big part of that might apply to ATOM also.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350486486844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350486571621-183</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>terinavok57883</Username><Timestamp>1350478389422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for this guys!</Msg><Username>bates_anne556</Username><Timestamp>1350486571621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:09:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350486958744-184</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>terinavok57883</Username><Timestamp>1350478389422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great , i just subscribed!</Msg><Username>haynes_jeanette559</Username><Timestamp>1350486958744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:15:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350487328267-185</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Foundry?</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350482715534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is an interesting thought. Intel does not need to be an open foundry -- only need to strike a strategic deal with one or two leading accounts. Apple would be ideal (for e.g. the next generation iMAC/Macbook lines); or Amazon; or Microsoft (if they are serious about competing on tablets).</Msg><Username>nbedh</Username><Timestamp>1350487328267</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350487443564-186</Id><Topic><Title>Where's the Miss, Lucy???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350484894895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:41:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Waldo, promised that shorts would get burned when INTC reported, instead INTC dropped to a new 52 week low, $8.00 below where Waldo could have sold and shorted. Never fear, in the next economic downturn, it'll go a lot lower, and Waldo will probably still be a long term investor with a strong buy and comments about how Wall Street is stupid.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1350487443564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:24:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350487518097-187</Id><Topic><Title>Get latest Information on INTC</Title><Username>albertinajsk59220</Username><Timestamp>1350480790139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:33:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love this article. Keep it coming.-- bz.am/INTC</Msg><Username>hesternhe89567</Username><Timestamp>1350487518097</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:25:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350487526390-188</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>morganwbki25914</Username><Timestamp>1350482317803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:58:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok thanks. I will take a look at this.</Msg><Username>clairvnrh52236</Username><Timestamp>1350487526390</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:25:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350487555498-189</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Foundry?</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350482715534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like Wallis' Khitchd'uh: It may not be possible for Intel to improve the x86 processor for low power applications much further within a reasonable time frame. ARM is so far ahead in this game While discussing Apple's A6 processor, Anand Lal Shimipi (one of the best tech blogs I have read) says: At least based on this data, it looks like Intel is the closest to offering a real competitor to Apple's own platform from a power efficiency standpoint. We're a couple quarters away from seeing the next generation of mobile SoCs so anything can happen next round, but I can't stress enough that the x86 power myth has been busted at this point. Posted by Marsavian yesterday...check out search anandtech...print/6330.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1350487555498</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:25:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350488055672-190</Id><Topic><Title>(Exclusive) INTC Runored Buy Out report ! (Exclusive)</Title><Username>rickflynn40</Username><Timestamp>1350474096491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good report !</Msg><Username>bobbyfischer520</Username><Timestamp>1350488055672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350488109104-191</Id><Topic><Title>14nm 14nm 14nm</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350473215668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:26:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>14mn. Drink the koolaid. Cymer is being bought by ASML - does this ring a light?. You just don't understand the manufacturing aspect...the chip analysts are clueless when it comes to manufacturing and it's getting only worse... Four of my holdings (ETEC, NVLS and Varian) were bought out - and now Cymer that's why I am semi equipment junkie - that's were I invest because I know the fabless ARM guys will pay through their nose... I know for a fact that TSMC et al are desperate for EUV - I hope Intel has a small working group at ASML that specifically focuses on Intel's needs. Apple would be stupid not to evaluate Intel - one big rattle on this tiny island... Remember Japan? Remember the flooding?</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1350488109104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:35:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350488150326-192</Id><Title>is the divie safe?</Title><Msg>????????????????????????</Msg><Username>slice_hicks</Username><Timestamp>1350488150326</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:35:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350488219063-193</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Foundry?</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350482715534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said: If say QCOM were to get ARMH processors from INTC in the interm That may have been okay couple of years back when Intel was way behind. But Intel now has its chips in Smartphones already. Also getting ready to release new Atoms Z2580 and Z2000. No point helping your competitors compete with you own chips at this stage of the game! Check out AnandTech article: Intel Goes Higher &amp; Lower End With Atom SoCs: Z2580 &amp; Z2000 Announced at MWC</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1350488219063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:36:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350488576043-194</Id><Title>According to the expert pundits on this board ...</Title><Msg>Intel was supposed to move below 20 .....What happened? thought this was a no brainer. One guy even referred to it as investment 101. What a #$%$_k !</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1350488576043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:42:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350489326909-195</Id><Topic><Title>According to the expert pundits on this board ...</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1350488576043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If there is a market (S&amp;P 500) correction of %5+, iNTC will move below $20 and it will be a safe buy then.</Msg><Username>c757172</Username><Timestamp>1350489326909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350489963504-196</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>morganwbki25914</Username><Timestamp>1350482317803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:58:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just joined.</Msg><Username>demetriambus292386</Username><Timestamp>1350489963504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350490359793-197</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>terinavok57883</Username><Timestamp>1350478389422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this here.</Msg><Username>love_maria569</Username><Timestamp>1350490359793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:12:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350490515622-198</Id><Topic><Title>According to the expert pundits on this board ...</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1350488576043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the liklihood of another 5 percent drop in the SPY in the near term is rather low at this point, by most indications, the correction in the SPY ended with the low set Monday, been pretty much uphill since then. most pc related stocks in their own bear markets since the lofty highs earlier this year</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1350490515622</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350490664992-199</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>terinavok57883</Username><Timestamp>1350478389422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like these guys, they're really good.</Msg><Username>powers_carol565</Username><Timestamp>1350490664992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:17:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350491245772-200</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>terinavok57883</Username><Timestamp>1350478389422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just joined. Heard a lot about these guys</Msg><Username>young_deborah573</Username><Timestamp>1350491245772</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:27:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350491575576-201</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>terinavok57883</Username><Timestamp>1350478389422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds interesting. Let me try this.</Msg><Username>wright_vickie569</Username><Timestamp>1350491575576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:32:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350491728972-202</Id><Topic><Title>Get latest Information on INTC</Title><Username>albertinajsk59220</Username><Timestamp>1350480790139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:33:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm subscribed. Cool</Msg><Username>audreapho064221</Username><Timestamp>1350491728972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:35:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350491822489-203</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>terinavok57883</Username><Timestamp>1350478389422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is what i exactly need at the moment</Msg><Username>mullins_ashley574</Username><Timestamp>1350491822489</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:37:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350491862169-204</Id><Topic><Title>According to the expert pundits on this board ...</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1350488576043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My point is: no one can predict where exactly a stock will move over an interval of time, but there are those here who think they can. Also, Obama and Biden are (K)ICKS! Please replace the first K in Kicks with a (D). Yahoo likes to censor comments.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1350491862169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350491958226-205</Id><Title>SATC 1$ Down to 7 Cents in 5 days Stock is going to Bounce Hard</Title><Msg>Huge bounce coming in SATC Check the chart stock is compressed to the max low float huge volume</Msg><Username>huge_profits_follow_me</Username><Timestamp>1350491958226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:39:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350492088587-206</Id><Topic><Title>INTC - Word on the Street</Title><Username>warner_stevenson</Username><Timestamp>1350483636401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:20:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For every times i buy my shares, i depend on your such contributions online because it give me full strength to invest more safely.thank you.</Msg><Username>romanroman79</Username><Timestamp>1350492088587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:41:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350492185577-207</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone5 review (vs RAZRi etc)</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1350419386939</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 16:29:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not a chance especially when it will be faced with similar core counts but double the threads ----- We shall see:)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1350492185577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:43:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350492420434-208</Id><Title>Calxeda plots server dominance with ARM SoCs</Title><Msg>Interesting tech details for those inclined. --- Calxeda plots server dominance with ARM SoCs Prepping a MEEELLION-NODE fleet services enema for data centers By Timothy Prickett Morgan  Get more from this author Posted in Servers , 17th October 2012 13:26 GMT Free Report: Backup and Recovery ofVMware Environments ARM server chip upstart Calxeda just bagged $55m in funding last week, and now we know what the company is going to do with the dough: plot a steady course to boost the performance of its ARM processors and the scalability of its on-die integrate Layer 2 distribute switch fabric until there is no reason to buy an x86 server chip. Karl Freund, vice president of marketing at Calxeda, told El Reg that the funding would be used, in part, to do a follow-on EnergyCore chip (really a system on chip, or SoC, since it includes integrated switching) based on 40-bit Cortex-A15 cores based on the ARMv7 specs from ARM Holdings. The kit is due around this time in 2013, with its first 64-bit EnergyCore due around a year later in 2014 or so. As it turns out, Calxeda's plans are considerably more ambitious than it was hinting last week. So much so that it might prompt in-state friend and foe Advanced Micro Devices to wonder why it didn't buy Calxeda instead of SeaMicro earlier this year. (There were unconfirmed rumors that AMD had in fact tried to do just that.) Calxeda has raised $103m in two rounds of venture funding from Austin Ventures, Vulcan Capital, ARM Holdings, Advanced Technology Investment Company (which owns the GlobalFoundries chip fab), Battery Ventures, Flybridge Capital Partners, and Highland Capital Partners. It used some of that money to seed its initial EnergyCore design and will use the rest to significantly expand its reach  if it all goes according to plan over the next several years. Calxeda is banking on the founders of the company  Barry Evans, who used to run Intel's low-power x86 and XScale ARM processor business; co-founder Larry Wikelius, who was at Opteron server maker Newisys; and co-founder David Borland, who was a chip designer at Marvell, Intel and AMD. The firm is hoping the trio can come up with clever cluster designs that scale across "warehouse-scale data centers," as Calxeda puts it. When it was set up in January 2008, Calxeda was known as Smooth-Stone  named for the stone used by David to kill Goliath  and its founders are taking a very long view and waiting as patiently as they can as they promote a software ecosystem around ARM-based servers and the integrated switching and management features that their chips offer. While 64-bit processing is something that all ARM server chip makers want and need, the issues they are trying to wrestle with are a lot larger than 32, 40, or 64 bits. The architecture of the Calxeda system on chip With the 32-bit EnergyCore ECX-1000 processor announced last November, the goal of the chip and distributed L2 switch was to get a complete system on a chip based on ARMv7 cores into the field and scale that interconnect, then called the EnergyCore Fabric, across a rack and spanning 4,096 nodes. The chip also included an on-chip management coprocessor to optimize and manage power use within each node and across a rack-level cluster. Freund tells El Reg as the big web properties took a look at what Calxeda and its server partners Hewlett-Packard and Boston had built, they wanted more. "They said to us that over 4,000 nodes in a cluster was interesting, but then they asked us if we could do 100,000 nodes on a cluster," says Freund. "And then they asked us if we could do a million." So with the coming generations of the EnergyCore chips, not only will Calxeda beef up the ARM cores on its processors, but it will bust that on-chip switching and management out of the rack and across "warehouse-scale" data centers  while rebranding the switching to Fleet Service Fabric Switch and the management engine to Fleet Services Engine. The future chips will also sport additional I/O controllers, potentially with integration to GPU coprocessors and other kinds of accelerators. Calxeda will be upgrading the current EnergyCore sockets with an upgraded chip based on the Cortex A15 design code-named "Midway," to give customers 40-bit extended memory and support for hardware-based virtualization. Generally speaking, the Midway chip is expected to deliver about 50 per cent more integer and 2X more floating point performance and support four times the memory (16GB per node and 4GB per thread) as the current ECX-1000 chip while sporting a new 2.0 release of the distributed L2 switch. Nothing comes for free, of course, so this Midway chip will deliver only the same or maybe slightly better performance per watt, according to Freund. And despite all the chatter about how 32-bit processors are not useful in the modern world, Calxeda continues to believe otherwise and says it has the customers to prove it. "With media streaming and media content services, you are pretty much just putting bits on a wire, and you don't need 64-bits for that," says Freund. "The EnergyCore ECX-1000 using the Cortex-A9 core is the right product for this. The Cortex-A15 doesn't replace the Cortex A9, which we think has a very long tail." Freund adds that the first-generation Calxeda chip would make a good storage controller, too, for clustered disk arrays. Aside from the core swap, the Midway chip will have the first generation of Fleet Services policy-based management and a set of APIs into the Fleet Services engine for fine-grained allocation and resource control that spans an entire rack. Midway will be available in 2013, perhaps around this time of the year. The company is not disclosing what process it is using to etch the chips or who the fab partner is that is doing the etching, but the current chips are made using 40 nanometer processes and are baked by Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Corp. It stands to reason that Calxeda will stick with TSMC and move on down to the 28 nanometer processes that it has been ramping for the past year and should have in better shape a year from now. About a year later comes the "Lago" SoC from Calxeda, and in case you are wondering, Calxeda is picking its code names from a map of Texas and using towns that have 1,000 people or less in their population. With Lago, Calxeda will move to the ARMv8 core, which has 64-bit processing and memory addressing and next-generation hardware virtualization circuits, among many other features. With this third generation SoC, Calxeda will add more cores, move to the 64-bit Neon floating point unit, offer faster single-thread performance, and add a significantly upgraded L2 switch interconnect that will be able to scale up to 100,000 nodes in a single cluster without having to add any external switches. The company is not providing any more specs on this interconnect, but says it will have much higher bandwidth (obviously) and much lower latency. This is a big deal, and it explains, more than anything else, why Intel has been buying up switching assets for the past year and getting paychecks to significant networking talent. Switching, not just network controller ports, is the next thing that is going to be integrated onto processors. The Lago chip will sport about twice the performance (presumably compared to the Midway chip, and presumably on integer work) and boosted floating point performance (by how much, Calxeda is not saying). Again, no word on what chip process or what fab will be used for Lago, but it could end up being a 28 nanometer chip from TSMC as well. EnergyCore clusters get bigger, chips get more powerful over time But that's not all. Calxeda has two more SoCs in the works as it plots its data center domination. With the future "Ratamosa" chip, Calxeda will be able to take on enterprise applications and high performance computing, and Microsoft might even have a Windows Server variant out by then. The company is not saying anything about timing on the Ratamosa chip, but it stands to reason that it will keep to a year cadence and we should see it around the end of 2015. And even further out, the fifth generation "Navarro" chip is in development, timed for the "enterprise server era," according to Calxeda, which is coded talk for when the Linux and possibly Windows operating systems and various hypervisors are fully mature on ARM processors. Although Calxeda did not confirm this, this would be the logical place to get a distributed L2 switch interconnect into the field that could handle the 1 million nodes that some customers are asking for. The ARM server race is afoot. </Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1350492420434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:47:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350492812213-209</Id><Title>CRAPTEL PINCHES OFF A LOAF....</Title><Msg>On Waldo's head! TOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1350492812213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:53:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350492871193-210</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>morganwbki25914</Username><Timestamp>1350482317803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:58:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow free of charge. I love it. Thanks</Msg><Username>babarakwzom985899</Username><Timestamp>1350492871193</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:54:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350492938344-211</Id><Topic><Title>Where's the Miss, Lucy???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350484894895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:41:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't you feel stupid enough? Give it a rest.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1350492938344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:55:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350493075805-212</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>terinavok57883</Username><Timestamp>1350478389422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love it. thanks</Msg><Username>graham_natalie576</Username><Timestamp>1350493075805</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350493553642-213</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>terinavok57883</Username><Timestamp>1350478389422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great share. Many thanks</Msg><Username>reeves_catherine585</Username><Timestamp>1350493553642</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:05:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350493587151-214</Id><Title>$19 support. dead money till than.</Title><Msg>check the 5 yr chart not the 1 or 2 year. this is a long term intc problem.</Msg><Username>febru3012</Username><Timestamp>1350493587151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350493642995-215</Id><Topic><Title>INTC - Word on the Street</Title><Username>warner_stevenson</Username><Timestamp>1350483636401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:20:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for the help. I love spam #$%$. pure junk. I love this cr ap.</Msg><Username>chevymalibu1966</Username><Timestamp>1350493642995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:07:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350493788588-216</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>terinavok57883</Username><Timestamp>1350478389422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks legit. Thank you for sharing this</Msg><Username>cross_tara587</Username><Timestamp>1350493788588</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:09:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350493826152-217</Id><Topic><Title>This Latest Downturn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345732452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 10:34:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember one thing, the traders and speculators on Wall Street don't give a rat's #$%$ about the United States. All they care about is profits, nothing but profits, and if that means destroying a company or even the country to do so, they would.</Msg><Username>nickster135796</Username><Timestamp>1350493826152</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:10:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350494091957-218</Id><Title>Ex Dividend and holiday season will move stock price to $23 min</Title><Msg>Any news on new contracts will propel this stock to new highs. Bottom has been hit with a 4+ dividend. Only but up from here.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350494091957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:14:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350494142518-219</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>terinavok57883</Username><Timestamp>1350478389422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this one ROCKS! two thumbs UP! subscribe now!!!</Msg><Username>manning_beth588</Username><Timestamp>1350494142518</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350494194156-220</Id><Topic><Title>Ex Dividend and holiday season will move stock price to $23 min</Title><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350494091957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:14:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree</Msg><Username>fitandsearching</Username><Timestamp>1350494194156</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350494534689-221</Id><Topic><Title>Ex Dividend and holiday season will move stock price to $23 min</Title><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350494091957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:14:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All shares between 1/1/2012 and last week are now underwater. Do you think that might "inspire" some tax loss selling before year end?</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1350494534689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:22:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350494737037-222</Id><Topic><Title>Ex Dividend and holiday season will move stock price to $23 min</Title><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350494091957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:14:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah that drop from $25 to under $22 sure has been buffeted by that $0.225 dividend</Msg><Username>wbobeli</Username><Timestamp>1350494737037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:25:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350494768639-223</Id><Title>INTC LONGS ARE A BUNCH OF CLOWNS!</Title><Msg>it's been stuck in a range of $17-$29 for years now, and when it was in the highend of it's range i told people this here. they laughed at me and were so confident that it would be different this time. what a bunch of freakin clowns, and yup, they paid for their mistake by losing $$$ LOL! i will buy intc again, but not before it hits the $18's like IT ALWAYS DOES!</Msg><Username>you_got_owned_bich</Username><Timestamp>1350494768639</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:26:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350494839723-224</Id><Topic><Title>Ex Dividend and holiday season will move stock price to $23 min</Title><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350494091957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:14:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe NOT looking at the history of the ex-div date, that doesn't usually seem to make much difference when were this close to it... Sad, would have liked to have sold for a small loss yesterday, then sold short, then bought to cover and bought in again this morning... that would have been a genius move, but I'm an idiot and not a genius...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350494839723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:27:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350494890630-225</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>terinavok57883</Username><Timestamp>1350478389422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i wont censor myself to comfort your ignorance ^_^ ain't no spammer here!</Msg><Username>edwards_katie592</Username><Timestamp>1350494890630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:28:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350494901341-226</Id><Topic><Title>According to the expert pundits on this board ...</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1350488576043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give it ten days. It seems to be doing well today BUT that appears to be distribution as a big block traded at 21.25 is sold off. Let's see today's close and tomorrow's open, before you gloat even a little.</Msg><Username>whowants2be</Username><Timestamp>1350494901341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:28:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350494945845-227</Id><Title>Young people not buying PCs for games anymore..game over..</Title><Msg>cheap chips only</Msg><Username>trader.quick</Username><Timestamp>1350494945845</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:29:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350495027687-228</Id><Title>INTC ALWAYS TRADES BETWEEN $17-$29</Title><Msg>you decide where you want to buy and sell.</Msg><Username>crap_in_my_lulus</Username><Timestamp>1350495027687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:30:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350495037602-229</Id><Topic><Title>Ex Dividend and holiday season will move stock price to $23 min</Title><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350494091957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:14:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today's low of $21.265 is a new 52 week low</Msg><Username>wbobeli</Username><Timestamp>1350495037602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:30:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350495244383-230</Id><Topic><Title>According to the expert pundits on this board ...</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1350488576043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right... if someone could truly predict it they would be busy making money hand over fist... usually I end my speculation comment with..I could always be wrong...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350495244383</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:34:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350495521477-231</Id><Topic><Title>Ex Dividend and holiday season will move stock price to $23 min</Title><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350494091957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:14:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Today's low of $21.265 is a new 52 week low" True, but as it is now trading 21.70, not all the shares bought today, yesterday, Monday ... and some of last week are NOT underwater.</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1350495521477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:38:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350495723046-232</Id><Title>There's still hope for $23 by Friday, but it seems likely that we'll hit $21 instead</Title><Msg>Of course I'm just speculating based on more analyst lowering their price targets... beating the @%#$ out of it... I've no where to go from where I'm at so I'll just wait till the other side and hope that INTC was way off on their 4th quarter estimates.... at this rate I'm thinking we'll not even reach $23 by the end of the year... but we might reach $18 by then...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350495723046</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:42:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350496839365-233</Id><Topic><Title>INTC - Word on the Street</Title><Username>warner_stevenson</Username><Timestamp>1350483636401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:20:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your life will never be the same again after investing your amount on such shares ,can grunt u on these. hope for the best.</Msg><Username>v.roman61</Username><Timestamp>1350496839365</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:00:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350497142570-234</Id><Title>New PC not on anyones Christmas list..Lump of coal or Apple product maybe.</Title><Msg>buy in teens</Msg><Username>trader.quick</Username><Timestamp>1350497142570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350497316902-235</Id><Topic><Title>There's still hope for $23 by Friday, but it seems likely that we'll hit $21 instead</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350495723046</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:42:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there ain't no way this stock hits 23 in 2 days, and it has likely seen it's highs for a very long time. Given that INTC peaked at 34.00 in 2004, there is no reason to belive it hits 29.00 again for quite some time</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1350497316902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:08:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350497399147-236</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>morganwbki25914</Username><Timestamp>1350482317803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:58:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Continue sharing this to us please. Thanks in advance.</Msg><Username>deboraqbcqo683461</Username><Timestamp>1350497399147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:09:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350498031869-237</Id><Title>INTC down while NLY gets upgraded!</Title><Msg>I actually made $$$ yesterday as my INTC shares went down in AH...Annaly announced a 1.5B buy back propping the stock over $16 and climbing. I had just bought 500 shares late yesterday so lucked out. Will be buying more NLY and INTC on dips.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350498031869</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:20:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350498371738-238</Id><Topic><Title>There's still hope for $23 by Friday, but it seems likely that we'll hit $21 instead</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350495723046</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:42:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will run up to its ex dividend date on Nov 5th. Investors have amnesia and as we approach elections and a dividend distribution I think it will hit 23 before 18.</Msg><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1350498371738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:26:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350498631604-239</Id><Title>Mobile</Title><Msg>Anyone catch their % of mobile chip growth for next year? Or, I guess they do not expect to compete that much in the space? Maybe 1 to 2 % growth....anyone know? TIA!</Msg><Username>michael_d_angelo</Username><Timestamp>1350498631604</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:30:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350498903765-240</Id><Topic><Title>This Latest Downturn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345732452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 10:34:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC is victim of it's own mistakes and it's continued reliance on what most could easily forsee, a rapid decline in pc's as the vast majority of the population shifted to tablets. As for the rest of the market, the QQQ's remain above the October 2007 highs, and are down a mere 5 percent from the highs of this year. Diehard INTC bulls have only themselves to blame for failing to realize the obvious</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1350498903765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:35:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350498986758-241</Id><Topic><Title>Young people not buying PCs for games anymore..game over..</Title><Username>trader.quick</Username><Timestamp>1350494945845</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:29:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But Wallis is making up for all those lost sales by buying new computers every few months to expand his burgeoning business. His computers are running 24/7/365, pumping out predictions for ever high prices for INTC shares.</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1350498986758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:36:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350499533585-242</Id><Title>Price Action Not Nearly as Bad as I Expected</Title><Msg>I fully expected an 8%-10% silde today based on bearish sentiment and short sellers piling into INTC. I think earnings were decent and the fundamentals are still intact. Billions in profit, a ton of cash on the books, a fat dividend yield and the stock is badly oversold. I guess that's why it's only down about 3% so far today. Looks like value hunters are buying the fear and overreation. I'm holding my shares.</Msg><Username>iwynne2002</Username><Timestamp>1350499533585</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350499695067-243</Id><Topic><Title>Get latest Information on INTC</Title><Username>albertinajsk59220</Username><Timestamp>1350480790139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:33:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I followed your reports since last week. Nice work.</Msg><Username>maireedp279</Username><Timestamp>1350499695067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:48:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350499842481-244</Id><Title>Chump Street #$%$ Have to Try to Keep the Price Down Until after Friday</Title><Msg>Options expiration. Chump Street projected an $8 billion revenue miss, didn't get ANY...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350499842481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:50:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350500244944-245</Id><Topic><Title>Price Action Not Nearly as Bad as I Expected</Title><Username>iwynne2002</Username><Timestamp>1350499533585</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Dividen yield is very good and lots of buyers including myself got in really low. I am in at $22. I see this as a 20% increase no later then 6 months.</Msg><Username>verioinc</Username><Timestamp>1350500244944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:57:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350500700550-246</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>morganwbki25914</Username><Timestamp>1350482317803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:58:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I never missed a single article from you. Thank you and please keep it coming.</Msg><Username>dorindapedq42783</Username><Timestamp>1350500700550</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350500718598-247</Id><Topic><Title>Mobile</Title><Username>michael_d_angelo</Username><Timestamp>1350498631604</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:30:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can listen to the archive of the earnings conference call on the Intel IR page but there was not a single word from Intel or question from analyst about smartphone. I am not sure which of the current customers will be breaking out that number either. I will dig through the 10q but it probably not there either. I think there are several dozen product introductions timed for 10/26 Windows 8 intro by MSFT. Of course that is preceded by the 10/23 announcment by Apple of what is expected to be the 7in iPad.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350500718598</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:05:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350501029952-248</Id><Topic><Title>Mobile</Title><Username>michael_d_angelo</Username><Timestamp>1350498631604</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:30:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alex, how many share do you expect them to retire if they bought back 1 billion worth last Quarter? Do they retire a certain percentage of the shares bought?</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1350501029952</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:10:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350501391387-249</Id><Topic><Title>Price Action Not Nearly as Bad as I Expected</Title><Username>iwynne2002</Username><Timestamp>1350499533585</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm in at $22.19. I sold some of my shares when INTC was trading up around $26. I felt like I needed to take some profit off the table but I'm very comfortable with my remaining shares. I'd consider adding more on a dip under $20.50.</Msg><Username>iwynne2002</Username><Timestamp>1350501391387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350501465087-250</Id><Topic><Title>Price Action Not Nearly as Bad as I Expected</Title><Username>iwynne2002</Username><Timestamp>1350499533585</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you really expect it to go up over $26 in 6 months... I hope you're right, but if they drive it down to $18 before then it will be a long haul... I'm in at an average of 22.60, so fairly close as well, but would have liked to have bought this morning instead... WOW.</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350501465087</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:17:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350501567731-251</Id><Topic><Title>Chump Street #$%$ Have to Try to Keep the Price Down Until after Friday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350499842481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah their doing their best to beat the &amp;T^* out of it... we'll see. how high do you think it REALISTICALLY goes before/on Friday?</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350501567731</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:19:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350501872978-252</Id><Topic><Title>There's still hope for $23 by Friday, but it seems likely that we'll hit $21 instead</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350495723046</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:42:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wdblawgrow, how high do you think it gets before ex div date...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350501872978</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350501903006-253</Id><Title>Intel has a beautiful historic Dividend chart</Title><Msg>dividendchannel(dotcom) /symbol/intc/</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1350501903006</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:25:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350502061783-254</Id><Title>Intel on track for $ 1.44 per yera Dividend by 2017</Title><Msg>BOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO YA !</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1350502061783</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350502199929-255</Id><Topic><Title>INTC - Word on the Street</Title><Username>warner_stevenson</Username><Timestamp>1350483636401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:20:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when i came to know about the feature returns of the share's policy,i became more interested to invest my money on this.thanks for letting me know.have a good time ahead.</Msg><Username>dickersonh73</Username><Timestamp>1350502199929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:29:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350502390402-256</Id><Topic><Title>Mobile</Title><Username>michael_d_angelo</Username><Timestamp>1350498631604</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:30:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see no reason why their share buyback representative who is managing the buyback will not buy another $1b+ worth of shares or about 50m shares. Just my guess. Since there are about 50 trading days per quarter, they would be buying back 1m per day. They bought back $1.5b, $1.1b, and $1.1b in Q1, Q2, and Q3 respectively. About 50m shares. They bought back $4b, $2b, $4b, $4.1b in 2011 Q1, Q2, Q3, Q4. $4b is about 180m shares. You can examine their repurchase history yourself if you search the phrase: intel buyback shares history</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350502390402</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:33:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350502788608-257</Id><Topic><Title>Intel on track for $ 1.44 per yera Dividend by 2017</Title><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1350502061783</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not if earnings and revenue contine to decline, then the dividend gets cut, and the share price goes down. Pity INTC spent way too much buying back stock at lofty levels earlier this year.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1350502788608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350503177217-258</Id><Topic><Title>Intel on track for $ 1.44 per yera Dividend by 2017</Title><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1350502061783</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at the cash flow. Even if the worst estimates are used ($1.75 for 2013), Intel will generate cash over fist in 2013 over what they have now.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1350503177217</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:46:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350503304378-259</Id><Title>Positive</Title><Msg>Intc &amp; touchscreen ultrabook &amp; win8 = adult supervision for ipad</Msg><Username>huron80</Username><Timestamp>1350503304378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:48:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350503490819-260</Id><Title>Retail fools buying at $21.7</Title><Msg>Good luck with that. Under $20 by Friday.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350503490819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350503698960-261</Id><Topic><Title>Retail fools buying at $21.7</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350503490819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:51:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Under $20... I say NO WAY... I'm going to guess between $21.30 and $22.60</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350503698960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:54:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350503752288-262</Id><Topic><Title>Retail fools buying at $21.7</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350503490819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:51:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they want to buy it is none of your business. I bet you are short and stand to lose big time.</Msg><Username>northvisitor34</Username><Timestamp>1350503752288</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:55:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350503850508-263</Id><Topic><Title>Retail fools buying at $21.7</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350503490819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:51:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The stock just dropped from $29 to $21 and the shorts are going to lose "bigtime". You cannot lose when you short Intel - it's the biggest dog in the Tech stock. Only fools buy it for the "dividend". Yeah, you get a 4% dividend while revenues and margins are collapsing. Great deal. LOL.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350503850508</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:57:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350503902911-264</Id><Topic><Title>Retail fools buying at $21.7</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350503490819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:51:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More warnings coming from MSFT and GOOG. Should be around $20 bu Friday.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350503902911</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350504157834-265</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>morganwbki25914</Username><Timestamp>1350482317803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:58:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I followed your reports since last week. Nice work.</Msg><Username>domenicauzkji33360</Username><Timestamp>1350504157834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350504494212-266</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>kevininthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1350496349107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well this is not a mind blowing app, but it is useful and I like it - thanks for the tip.</Msg><Username>peelingoutsummer</Username><Timestamp>1350504494212</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:08:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350504521316-267</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>morganwbki25914</Username><Timestamp>1350482317803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:58:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey spammers..get your a** off this board</Msg><Username>zbgb952</Username><Timestamp>1350504521316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:08:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350504936887-268</Id><Title>Predict INTC will hit 20.80 as low before it moves higher toward Nov 5th</Title><Msg>Just a guess.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1350504936887</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:15:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350505121619-269</Id><Title>14nm timeline for Broadwell</Title><Msg>when is the haswell migration to 14nm expected 2013/2014 ?/</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1350505121619</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350505280093-270</Id><Topic><Title>Intel on track for $ 1.44 per yera Dividend by 2017</Title><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1350502061783</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not if earnings and revenue contine to decline, then the dividend gets cut, and the share price goes down. Pity INTC spent way too much buying back stock at lofty levels earlier this year. _________________________________________________________________ Coming from a guy that was so dumb that he thought selling Intel under 20 was smart instead of buying it........your words ring hollow. No wonder you never got wealthy, old man.</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1350505280093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:21:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350505542293-271</Id><Topic><Title>INTC - Word on the Street</Title><Username>warner_stevenson</Username><Timestamp>1350483636401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:20:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can count on your money by investing in the stock market for better future returns.</Msg><Username>flynnacosta69</Username><Timestamp>1350505542293</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:25:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350505694909-272</Id><Title>Re: Margins</Title><Msg>Everyone is pointing to Intel's gross margin drop and the fact that if they do intend to be a player in the mobile space, that margins will even further be hit as they try to be competitive with pricing. But what no one is talking about is how the competing mobile chip designers will manage to keep their margins intact as the costs to get their chips manufactured rise as the manufacturer's chase smaller nodes. I would think that at some point, the costs of lower end mobile chips from the ARMH camps are going to have to increase.</Msg><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1350505694909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350505818086-273</Id><Topic><Title>Good time to short on INTC tomorrow</Title><Username>chidragon38</Username><Timestamp>1350436634388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 21:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure. Feel free to ignore the FACT that Intel has gone nowhere for a decade and will go nowhere but down for the next 10 years. __________________________ The 3 year Intel chart just laughed at you.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350505818086</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:30:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350505959693-274</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>morganwbki25914</Username><Timestamp>1350482317803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:58:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the awesome spam. I enjoy licking goats' balls too, so I really enjoyed your link!</Msg><Username>drensber</Username><Timestamp>1350505959693</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:32:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350505979616-275</Id><Topic><Title>Chump Street #$%$ Have to Try to Keep the Price Down Until after Friday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350499842481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you saw the high today when it hit 21.96</Msg><Username>marrohead</Username><Timestamp>1350505979616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:32:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350506007840-276</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>morganwbki25914</Username><Timestamp>1350482317803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:58:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh yeah, I forgot to say "keep it coming".... the pictures of the goats definitely kept me coming!</Msg><Username>drensber</Username><Timestamp>1350506007840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:33:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350506375078-277</Id><Topic><Title>14nm timeline for Broadwell</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1350505121619</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:18:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Intel keeps to its tick-tock cadence, they should start: - limited manufacturing towards the end of 2013 - and shipping in Q1 or Q2 of 2014</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1350506375078</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:39:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350507750148-278</Id><Title>Intel Net Income of 3b with PC's dying, bad economy, business in holding period, emerging markets stalling, etc..</Title><Msg>Booooya.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350507750148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:02:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350508122306-279</Id><Title>TOP in the market must be in if CNBC thinks the market can't go down every again</Title><Msg>TOP in the market must be in if CNBC thinks the market can't go down every again</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1350508122306</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:08:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350508144962-280</Id><Topic><Title>another new low next under $20</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1350507130824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Central banks are printing new money like crazy. Inflation is in the cards. All prices will go up including price of stocks.</Msg><Username>joshua1779</Username><Timestamp>1350508144962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:09:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350508231272-281</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation</Title><Username>morganwbki25914</Username><Timestamp>1350482317803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:58:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have it already. It's the best.- y.ahoo.it/5Un5k</Msg><Username>alisancmj814474</Username><Timestamp>1350508231272</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350508265268-282</Id><Topic><Title>INTC - Word on the Street</Title><Username>warner_stevenson</Username><Timestamp>1350483636401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:20:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the info..very useful. Volume not what I would like so we'll see what happens. Any thoughts? Thanks again!</Msg><Username>monroenicholson62</Username><Timestamp>1350508265268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:11:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350509377477-283</Id><Topic><Title>another new low next under $20</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1350507130824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree Intel will see the teens, but it'll be a great place to start buying for two to four years out. As soon as it breaks $20 bucks, I'm gonna start slowly accumulating.</Msg><Username>batmensch</Username><Timestamp>1350509377477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:29:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350509658707-284</Id><Topic><Title>Chump Street #$%$ Have to Try to Keep the Price Down Until after Friday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350499842481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It WILL break $22 tomorrow, but where it closes at I don't know... Could be wrong, but I doubt that I am...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350509658707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:34:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350509794474-285</Id><Topic><Title>Get latest Information on INTC</Title><Username>albertinajsk59220</Username><Timestamp>1350480790139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:33:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am waiting for. Thanks for giving out this article for free.</Msg><Username>marandabsj4872</Username><Timestamp>1350509794474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:36:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350509862483-286</Id><Topic><Title>Good time to short on INTC tomorrow</Title><Username>chidragon38</Username><Timestamp>1350436634388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 21:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope, should be shorting it when it breaks $22 tomorrow, which it will... NO WAY will it open even close to 21.21...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350509862483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350509913356-287</Id><Topic><Title>Chump Street #$%$ Have to Try to Keep the Price Down Until after Friday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350499842481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you even listen to the stupid shyt you're saying? "Projected an $8B revenue miss"? Do you even know what a revenue miss is?</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350509913356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:38:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350509939619-288</Id><Topic><Title>Predict INTC will hit 20.80 as low before it moves higher toward Nov 5th</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1350504936887</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:15:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm speculating that you're correct... but it may even go a little lower, I think it will hit a high of 22.70 before the ex div date...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350509939619</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:38:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350510173687-289</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Net Income of 3b with PC's dying, bad economy, business in holding period, emerging markets stalling, etc..</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350507750148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And projections for Q4 are? 2B? Booooya? what a brilliant investor you are.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350510173687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:42:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350510595989-290</Id><Topic><Title>Chump Street #$%$ Have to Try to Keep the Price Down Until after Friday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350499842481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even at 22.50 it's a 1% gain on your money for holding it for less than a month, I don't know who wouldn't want to get in on that... so I'm guessing that it goes up to at least $22.50 before the ex-div date... but I also think it will drop to around $21 at some point between now and then... if it does, I'm going scrounge up what I can to buy buy buy.... Congratulations to anyone that shorted at the end of the day, before close, yesterday, BTW...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350510595989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:49:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350510973251-291</Id><Title>Intel is the next RIMM</Title><Msg>The days of $300 laptop processors are becoming a thing of the past. The new normal will be $40 - $50 processors. Say goodbye to 65% margins and hello to 30% margins. In 3-4 years we are looking at a $5-$10 stock.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350510973251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:56:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350511343055-292</Id><Topic><Title>Get latest Information on INTC</Title><Username>albertinajsk59220</Username><Timestamp>1350480790139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:33:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow free of charge. I love it. Thanks</Msg><Username>wesleyuzq42372</Username><Timestamp>1350511343055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350511886077-293</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is the next RIMM</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350510973251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:56:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>idiot</Msg><Username>the4ateam2004</Username><Timestamp>1350511886077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:11:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350511891979-294</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is the next RIMM</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350510973251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:56:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If we suffer another recession/depression, YUP... other wise NOPE... buy hey I appreciate your variety...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350511891979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:11:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350511904147-295</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Margins</Title><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1350505694909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:28:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. Someone is actually considering the fact that if Intel cannot make money, no one can and the rest will go out of business. Leaving Intel... See TI's strategic decision... Currency will be a tailwind once the deflationary event is done...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1350511904147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350511928341-296</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Net Income of 3b with PC's dying, bad economy, business in holding period, emerging markets stalling, etc..</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350507750148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PC's are NOT going to die. Small tablet and phone screens will not wipe out PC's, any more than laptops killed desktops. People are gonna slow down on buying every iteration of tablet and phone.</Msg><Username>akrinn</Username><Timestamp>1350511928341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:12:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350512589726-297</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Margins</Title><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1350505694909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:28:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mobile is not Intel's only business, they sell servers to support this growing number of mobile devices.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350512589726</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350512683278-298</Id><Title>For the same price buy Ultrabook instead of a useless tablet</Title><Msg>.........</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350512683278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350512923960-299</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Margins</Title><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1350505694909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:28:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A one time charge for unused capacity. 22nm yields just too high. Now they will just convert it now to 14nm. They will be incurring charges because of the production builds of Haswell. Intel reported third quarter revenue of $13.5 billion (down 5% year-over-year), operating income of $3.8 billion (down 20% compared to the year ago quarter), net income of $3.0 billion (14% lower than a year ago) and EPS of $0.58 (down 11% year-over-year). For the fourth quarter of 2012, the world's largest chipmaker expects revenue of $13.6 billion  $500 million and gross margins of around 57%~58%. To respond to a weaker than expected demand environment, Intel has taken several actions. In particular, the chipmaker substantially cut wafer starts at its factories in late Q3 2012 and intends to maintain lower factory utilization rates throughout the fourth quarter. Intel projects these factory adjustments to help bring down its total inventory levels by approximately $500 million. At the same time, Intel stressed that despite of lower demand for PCs, it will start initial volume manufacturing of its next-generation Haswell central processing units this quarter, which will cause an uptick of inventory levels. "We expect an increase in inventory reserves as we start production on our next-generation micro architecture product code-named Haswell, which we expect to qualify for sale in the first quarter of 2013," said Stacy Smith, chief financial officer of Intel. At present Intel still does not specifically reveal when does the Haswell chips and products on their base are scheduled to hit the market. The company only claims that the first Haswell-based systems will be available in the first half of the year.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350512923960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:28:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350513235406-300</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is the next RIMM</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350510973251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:56:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You appear to be completely clueless about the entire thing dude. Intel has a monopoly on the very best personal CPU's mankind can make. Research in Motion on the other hand makes cellular devices. I could go into detail about the differences but then you probably wouldn't understand.</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1350513235406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:33:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350513268696-301</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is the next RIMM</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350510973251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:56:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about if we suffer from a flood of $25 ARM processors for low-end laptops? Have you heard that Windows 8 is ARM compatible. Recession has been over since 2009. It's not the economy stupid - PCs are dying and $300 processors are dying even faster. Only retail fools buy this for a 4% dividend while the stock tanks 30% in 3 months.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350513268696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:34:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350513288452-302</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is the next RIMM</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350510973251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:56:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're the one holding INTC long and I'm the idiot? LOL.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350513288452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:34:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350513394803-303</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Margins</Title><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1350505694909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:28:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Server business is worth maybe $4. The rest is dying.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350513394803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:36:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350514088879-304</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is the next RIMM</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350510973251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:56:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PCs are dying and $300 processors are dying even faster. Only retail fools buy this for a 4% dividend while the stock tanks 30% in 3 months. --------------------------------------- So i guess you wouldn't buy INTC at any price then? LOL</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1350514088879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:48:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350514237374-305</Id><Topic><Title>Sox down 1.2% INTC down 2.2% why?</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1312996107000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2011-08-10 13:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AGREED</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1350514237374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350514298601-306</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Margins</Title><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1350505694909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:28:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See TI's strategic decision... TI exited DRAM business about 15 years ago...quite possible the ARM "ecosystem" will be facing a similar (DRAM) scenario... TI had always their own logic fabs and outsourced advanced technology long before AMD. Now TI calls it quits ... the ARM crowd is kidding themself in believing Intel is the only one facing margin pressure.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1350514298601</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:51:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350514746575-307</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is the next RIMM</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350510973251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:56:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would buy it at $17, but even that is not a sure thing. It's all a guess of how fast things will deteriorate.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350514746575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:59:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350514841910-308</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Margins</Title><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1350505694909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:28:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We expect an increase in inventory reserves as we start production on our next-generation micro architecture product code-named Haswell, which we expect to qualify for sale in the first quarter of 2013," said Stacy Smith, chief financial officer of Intel. will put NVDA and AMD out of business</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1350514841910</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:00:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350515116008-309</Id><Title>ahh carp</Title><Msg>still holding. just incredible. looks like a nother quarter of chop, at best. good luk longs. deth to shortwads</Msg><Username>sharppolly</Username><Timestamp>1350515116008</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:05:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350515472415-310</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Margins</Title><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1350505694909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:28:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>then why did you say you'd buy at $17 ?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350515472415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:11:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350515518789-311</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is the next RIMM</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350510973251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:56:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great but if no one is buying them, does that matter?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350515518789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350515606987-312</Id><Title>Don't le NY2KOH fool you, he isn't short, he wants to BUY from weak sellers</Title><Msg>Sox down 1.2% INTC down 2.2% why? By nyk20h . Aug 10, 2011 1:08 PM . Permalink Intel is the most compelling chip buy. Why is the stock performing so poorly?</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350515606987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350515739375-313</Id><Topic><Title>another new low next under $20</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1350507130824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>isn't that old news? and not all stocks went up, this 1 for example.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350515739375</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:15:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350515761236-314</Id><Topic><Title>Don't le NY2KOH fool you, he isn't short, he wants to BUY from weak sellers</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350515606987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL - you're pulling out a post from when Intel was $19, was growing, made 20% higher profits and guided higher? Are you that desperate?</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350515761236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:16:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350515957790-315</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is the next RIMM</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350510973251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:56:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. A monopoly over a market declining 10% Y/oY? that's awesome. How about you Google Windows on ARM - try it. Who do you think is going to buy those $300 CPU when $50 ARM chips will do just fine. You are living in 1990.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350515957790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350515987752-316</Id><Topic><Title>Price Action Not Nearly as Bad as I Expected</Title><Username>iwynne2002</Username><Timestamp>1350499533585</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you aware it may be down 3% today but down from $29 in a short timeframe.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350515987752</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350515991390-317</Id><Title>Ultrabooks will reach $ 699 next year + Windows 8, Touchscreen AND 22nm</Title><Msg>Plus Intel mobile will introduce the first 4gLTE phone in the U.S. PC's aren't dying, they are transforming for the next decade. Anybody bashing the stock can't invest. They are simply daytraders or have a bone to pick with Intel (worked there, etc.) It's that simple.</Msg><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1350515991390</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:19:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350516027147-318</Id><Topic><Title>another new low next under $20</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1350507130824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not Intel stock.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350516027147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:20:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350516038880-319</Id><Topic><Title>Young people not buying PCs for games anymore..game over..</Title><Username>trader.quick</Username><Timestamp>1350494945845</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:29:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wallus weiner, imagine how much worse it would be now if all those letters to Intel had not been sent.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350516038880</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:20:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350516084849-320</Id><Topic><Title>There's still hope for $23 by Friday, but it seems likely that we'll hit $21 instead</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350495723046</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:42:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you mean $23??? Just yesterday we had a clown in here saying it was going to open at $25 or $26 this morning :)</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350516084849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:21:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350516147056-321</Id><Topic><Title>This Latest Downturn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345732452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 10:34:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, should have owned qcom &amp; intc all along, i believe alexander does. Diverify. Heck, VTSMX for that matter.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350516147056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:22:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350516187159-322</Id><Topic><Title>Young people not buying PCs for games anymore..game over..</Title><Username>trader.quick</Username><Timestamp>1350494945845</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:29:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But, but, but, there's a 4% dividend. Who cares it will disappear within less than 12 months.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350516187159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350516254837-323</Id><Topic><Title>Don't le NY2KOH fool you, he isn't short, he wants to BUY from weak sellers</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350515606987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, but you clearly are for rating your own posts.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350516254837</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:24:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350516372004-324</Id><Topic><Title>Don't le NY2KOH fool you, he isn't short, he wants to BUY from weak sellers</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350515606987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you too stupid to know that's not possible.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350516372004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:26:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350516386414-325</Id><Topic><Title>This Latest Downturn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345732452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 10:34:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why we have laws and regulations. Blame unions as well for that.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350516386414</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:26:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350516504145-326</Id><Topic><Title>Don't le NY2KOH fool you, he isn't short, he wants to BUY from weak sellers</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350515606987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you'[re too stupid to think anybody with any common sense can't see your agenda. You have multiple aliases. Anyway, how about we meet for lunch? My treat. I like to look cowards in the eye and tell them they are cowards to their sleazy faces.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350516504145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:28:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350516636206-327</Id><Topic><Title>This Latest Downturn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345732452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 10:34:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you 12 years old? Seriously - wake up. Did you not notice a -7% Y/oY revenue decline? did you miss margins collapsing? did you miss Multi-Billion dollar plants sitting idle? Intel is still overvalued at these levels, and that's because of dividend chasing fools like you. You're a child.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350516636206</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:30:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350516894357-328</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P REITERATES HOLD RECOMMENDATION ON SHARES OF INTEL CORP</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1350481452303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:44:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But WW said $3 eps was coming.........</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350516894357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:34:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350517144836-329</Id><Topic><Title>Don't le NY2KOH fool you, he isn't short, he wants to BUY from weak sellers</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350515606987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. I have no other aliases. 2. Are you in the NYC area? 3. Stop being a child - pointing out reality is not being a "coward". The reality for Intel is sad - revenues are declining (-7% Y/oY), margins are collapsing (57% expected in Q4 vs. 64% in Q3), the market is shrinking, and there are ZERO growth opportunities for the company. All the company's cash was wasted on dividends and expensive buybacks, so they can't even make a significant acquisition to save their business. Ultrabooks are failing miserably and Intel's mobile market-share is less than 0,2%. On top of everything, Windows 8 is ARM compatible and that means $25 ARM chips will be replacing $300 Intel CPUs and eroding the little that is left of this once high-flyer. Intel is fighting for its life and it doesn't look good right now. By the end of the decade, what's left of this company will probably be taken over for scrap.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350517144836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350517304013-330</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P REITERATES HOLD RECOMMENDATION ON SHARES OF INTEL CORP</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1350481452303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:44:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even these estimates are too high. Look for $1.5 in 2013. Look for the dividend to be reduced.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350517304013</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350517342882-331</Id><Topic><Title>Housing Starts in U.S. Surged in September to Four-Year High</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350480833025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$24 in 2011 and now a complete flop, you want to point out more good news? you're so FOS.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350517342882</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350517377917-332</Id><Topic><Title>WHEN WILL WALLIS SURFACE?</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1350425531534</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 18:12:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>where's the party? count me in.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350517377917</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:42:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350517446639-333</Id><Topic><Title>Chump Street Blows the Earnings Call - Big Time</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350480561701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Under $22 and you're celebrating. Can you post 1 of your letters here so we can see what has propped up the stock?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350517446639</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350517491883-334</Id><Topic><Title>New low today</Title><Username>pple64</Username><Timestamp>1350480366357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:26:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>20.25 ? not true</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350517491883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:44:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350517564746-335</Id><Topic><Title>Housing Starts in U.S. Surged in September to Four-Year High</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350480833025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, does Intel sell homes? The economy is just fine, it's only Intel that's having problems. So much for the "macro" excuse.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350517564746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350517656494-336</Id><Topic><Title>Chump Street Blows the Earnings Call - Big Time</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350480561701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fantasy world. When was your last psychiatric evaluation?</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350517656494</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350517672248-337</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P REITERATES HOLD RECOMMENDATION ON SHARES OF INTEL CORP</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1350481452303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:44:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>doubt it</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350517672248</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:47:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350518353106-338</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P REITERATES HOLD RECOMMENDATION ON SHARES OF INTEL CORP</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1350481452303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:44:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you see -7% revenue decline coming? did you see 57% GMs coming? Then what makes you think you can see the dividend cut coming?</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350518353106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:59:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350519017421-339</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P REITERATES HOLD RECOMMENDATION ON SHARES OF INTEL CORP</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1350481452303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:44:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They exceeded my expectations this quarter after warning. Right now I think Intel can afford .90 a share. You never know and that's why I said doubt it. I didn't say it could never happen.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350519017421</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:10:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350519940333-340</Id><Topic><Title>Chump Street Blows the Earnings Call - Big Time</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350480561701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep spinning shill boy. Faster, faster...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350519940333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350520051137-341</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P REITERATES HOLD RECOMMENDATION ON SHARES OF INTEL CORP</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1350481452303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:44:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where's the miss, shill boy? The big, huge, honking miss? You know the one you posted on and on and on and on and on and on about. The one that didn't happen. It didn't happen so why are you still here spinning your #$%$. Your cover is blown. Move on...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350520051137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:27:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350520095901-342</Id><Topic><Title>Chump Street Blows the Earnings Call - Big Time</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350480561701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>time to take your meds walli. The only conspiracy is in your brain.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350520095901</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:28:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350520237489-343</Id><Topic><Title>This Latest Downturn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345732452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 10:34:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really are desperate... You aren't helping your cause. By now, everyone recognizes that when the bashers are in overdrive, the stock is near a bottom and when the pumpers are in overdrive bashing shorts, it is near a top. Retail investors have wised up to the games... It is why retail will not participate until WS deflates the bubble scams. When the market is ACTUALLY cheap (and not compared to short term UST bonds which have little interest rate risk and no credit risk because in the event of default, the entire world is screwed), retail will come back in. Intel, OTOH, is both cheap and distinctive...</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1350520237489</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:30:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350520254101-344</Id><Title>Chump Street Totally Exposed</Title><Msg>Charge: Projecting huge Intel miss based on no evidence. Result: No revenue miss, no earnings miss. Finding: Guilty as charged.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350520254101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:30:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350520370187-345</Id><Topic><Title>Chump Street Blows the Earnings Call - Big Time</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350480561701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where's the miss, shill boy? Fess up. It was all #$%$ from the beginning. The curtain has been pulled back and your little shill show has been exposed. Move along, Lucy...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350520370187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:32:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350520557785-346</Id><Topic><Title>Chump Street Blows the Earnings Call - Big Time</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350480561701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you realize that they WARNED and lowered revenue expectations by 10% last month you psychotic lunatic? And you're asking about the "miss". Are you actually trying to spin a -7% revenue decline as a "good" thing?</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350520557785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350520638896-347</Id><Topic><Title>Chump Street Totally Exposed</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350520254101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:30:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. Intel warned last month and decreased revenue guidance by 10%. You should really get hospitalized and soon.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350520638896</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:37:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350520644657-348</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is the next RIMM</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350510973251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:56:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suppose you pay more for the extra key board compared to what the processor costs.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1350520644657</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:37:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350520653506-349</Id><Title>Microsoft Deliberately Sets the ARM Surface RT Price Too High</Title><Msg>The sooner Microsoft kills off the RT the better they will like it. Then they can move the Intel version down to the lower price. Microsoft never did like ARM...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350520653506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:37:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350520695295-350</Id><Topic><Title>Don't le NY2KOH fool you, he isn't short, he wants to BUY from weak sellers</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350515606987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL at NYK2oh. wow, he's short the stock and saying the most outrageous things possible about Intel's future. Shocking! Never listen to a guy that has nothing but HIS bank account in mind. Idiot.</Msg><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1350520695295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:38:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350520747118-351</Id><Topic><Title>This Latest Downturn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345732452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 10:34:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is it "cheap"? What is a "cheap" valuation for a company with declining revenues and margins?</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350520747118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:39:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350520904411-352</Id><Topic><Title>Don't le NY2KOH fool you, he isn't short, he wants to BUY from weak sellers</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350515606987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Attacking the messenger only makes you look stupid. Point out a single thing that I said which is wrong or "outrageous". Go ahead. What wrong? declining revenues? collapsing margins? collapsing profits? declining market? What am I saying that isn't true?</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350520904411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350520972947-353</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Deliberately Sets the ARM Surface RT Price Too High</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350520653506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. Even Microsoft is ditching Intel. Windows on ARM will be the final nail in the coffin.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350520972947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:42:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350521025919-354</Id><Topic><Title>This Latest Downturn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345732452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 10:34:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should know what cheap is, shill boy. It's when a company gets beaten down because a huge miss is projected and then there isn't ANY miss at all. It turns out to be just a bunch of bull puckey promulgated by a bunch of postings from cretins who used to be delivering pizzas a short time ago...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350521025919</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:43:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350521063283-355</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Deliberately Sets the ARM Surface RT Price Too High</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350520653506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOA - DOA</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350521063283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:44:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350521159603-356</Id><Topic><Title>Don't le NY2KOH fool you, he isn't short, he wants to BUY from weak sellers</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350515606987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What am I saying that isn't true?" [Um, all of it? Where's the miss, shill boy? If what you are saying is true, then where is the miss???]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350521159603</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:45:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350521170439-357</Id><Topic><Title>This Latest Downturn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345732452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 10:34:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you have no clue what "cheap" is. Come on walli, don't attack, tell us what's the proper valuation for a company with negative earnings growth, collapsing margins and a declining market? what multiple would be "cheap" for such a company?</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350521170439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350521221000-358</Id><Topic><Title>Don't le NY2KOH fool you, he isn't short, he wants to BUY from weak sellers</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350515606987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "miss" came in September with the 10% revenue warning, Did you miss that?</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350521221000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350521306067-359</Id><Topic><Title>Don't le NY2KOH fool you, he isn't short, he wants to BUY from weak sellers</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350515606987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If putting 2 to 3 billion in the BANK every 3 months is collapsing, I hope my business collapses. LOL, get lost pud.</Msg><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1350521306067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:48:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350521407285-360</Id><Title>nyk20h</Title><Msg>He knows everything but why there wasn't any miss. LOL It means everything you say is total #$%$. Otherwise there would have been the big miss that you have been projecting. Collapsing margins. But, gee no miss. Negative earnings growth. But, gee no miss. Declining market. But, gee no miss. No miss on revenues and no miss on earnings. Just the facts, shill boy...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350521407285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:50:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350521575916-361</Id><Topic><Title>Don't le NY2KOH fool you, he isn't short, he wants to BUY from weak sellers</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350515606987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, you don't know the difference between a miss and a warning. That's funny. September was a warning, butkus. A great big huge honking miss is what you expected yesterday but didn't happen...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350521575916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:52:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350521577031-362</Id><Topic><Title>nyk20h</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350521407285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:50:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a true psycho. Intel lowered revenue projections in September by 10%. They missed their own projections from July by 9%. Just go home you delusional psychopath. Stock lost 30% in a few weeks and you're talking smack in your little fantasy land? Intel is dead. Face it.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350521577031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350521706078-363</Id><Topic><Title>Don't le NY2KOH fool you, he isn't short, he wants to BUY from weak sellers</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350515606987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody was expecting a miss. I clearly said they would beat their own lowered expectations. Intel always does the same thing - they come out with a MASSIVE warning, they beat those lowered numbers. You really are clueless, are you?</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350521706078</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350521842600-364</Id><Topic><Title>nyk20h</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350521407285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:50:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tsk, Tsk. Tsk. Getting a little upset are we?. Well projecting a big huge honking miss and not getting one will tend to get a rookie shill a little worked up. Call the shill boss and tell him you're not ready for prime time. Tell him you need to go home for a time out and maybe a nap and that he shouldn't be hiring teenagers to begin with...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350521842600</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350522028334-365</Id><Title>NYK20h Says No One Was Expecting a Miss</Title><Msg>Hahahahahahahahahahaha. No one was expecting a miss. That's priceless. Yeah, shill boy - that's why the stock got priced down by eight bucks. Because no one was expecting a miss. Hahahahahahahahaha. Stocks always get priced down when no one expects a miss. You're a hoot...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350522028334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350522235093-366</Id><Topic><Title>NYK20h Says No One Was Expecting a Miss</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350522028334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stock got killed because of the September warning and because of fears over lower guidance. Everybody knows the Intel MO of having a massive warning and then beating. Q3 results were already known in September. Stock was trading on Q4 expectation and Intel was able to put out guidance which was even worse than expected (margin collapse was the shocker). Look for another 10% warning in December.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350522235093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:03:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350522347171-367</Id><Topic><Title>nyk20h</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350521407285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:50:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a clown. Stock falls from $30 to $21 within weeks and you're celebrating. Fine. Knock yourself out. Keep the rants coming while we dip under $20. "Chump Street". LOL.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350522347171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:05:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350522868060-368</Id><Topic><Title>nyk20h</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350521407285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:50:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You're a clown. Stock falls from $30 to $21 within weeks and you're celebrating." [I'm celebrating that there was no reason for the drop. No miss, no reason it should have dropped. The logic is pretty straightforward. You keep saying that the company is in a state of total disaster. But wouldn't a company in a state of total disaster have a big huge miss??? Well Intel didn't. Yet you continue to make a total embarrassment of yourself. So, I'll ask again. Where's the miss?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350522868060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:14:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350523090605-369</Id><Title>Romney now up 51 to 45 in latest Gallup Poll</Title><Msg>LANDSLIDE, business hiring, people getting employed and their employers having to buy them COMPUTERS.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350523090605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:18:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350523665849-370</Id><Topic><Title>NYK20h Says No One Was Expecting a Miss</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350522028334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Stock got killed because of the September warning and because of fears over lower guidance." [The warning wasn't that large. The stock got killed because the same news got priced in eight times. So, to justify the 8x on the stock price reduction there had to be a huge miss. There wasn't. You want to pretend there was. This isn't Fantasy Island, shill boy. No huge honking miss means the stock price is at least 7 bucks too low now...] "Everybody knows the Intel MO of having a massive warning and then beating." [If you think there is any rule on the stock market that repeats itself consistently then are a total #$%$..] "Q3 results were already known in September." [Gee, then why did the miss get priced in eight times?] "Stock was trading on Q4 expectation and Intel was able to put out guidance which was even worse than expected (margin collapse was the shocker). [Oh, so none of those extra seven times the miss got priced in was enough to cover a weak Q4??? The margin projection was to 57 percent. Yeah, that's a real collapse, accounting boy. You really know your stuff. Where did you get your MBA? Sears or Wal*Mart?] "Look for another 10% warning in December." [Judging from your prediction of a huge honking Q3 miss that never happened, maybe you should give up making projections for a while. Just an idea, shill boy...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350523665849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:27:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350523847402-371</Id><Topic><Title>NYK20h Says No One Was Expecting a Miss</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350522028334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is a daytrader.....he doesn't track Intel everyday. He didn't read the constant downgrades from Analysts that were expecting a miss. Put the loser on ignore. He spends 12 hours here a day trying to get anybody he can to believe him because it's in his best interest if they sour on Intel and sell. Total loser, Ignore him.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350523847402</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:30:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350523874422-372</Id><Title>Obama now up 47 to 45 in latest IBD/TIPP Tracking Poll</Title><Msg>Gallup is an average over seven days. Doesn't have the effect of yesterday's debate or all the recent good economic news reflected in it yet...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350523874422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350524021974-373</Id><Topic><Title>Obama now up 47 to 45 in latest IBD/TIPP Tracking Poll</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350523874422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are indeed a sore loser and it will be a BLAST to watch you cry about the GOP for the next eight years. Enjoy your last 2+ weeks. Knock yourself out bro.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350524021974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350524061412-374</Id><Topic><Title>Obama now up 47 to 45 in latest IBD/TIPP Tracking Poll</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350523874422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And what relevance does this have concerning INTC?</Msg><Username>green1tyler</Username><Timestamp>1350524061412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:34:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350524131546-375</Id><Topic><Title>Obama now up 47 to 45 in latest IBD/TIPP Tracking Poll</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350523874422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney up 51 to 45 on Real Clear Politics..........funny how you referenced RCP when Obama was ahead, but not now.........lol, you are a psychotic sore loser wierdo. Go F yourself dork.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350524131546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:35:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350527628704-376</Id><Topic><Title>Romney now up 51 to 45 in latest Gallup Poll</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350523090605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:18:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rombo still lacks specifics about what "loopholes" will be closed (carried interest?). The middleclass would not pay a dime on dividends anyway but Rombo sells it ... amazing. Portrays himself as a business man and still does not understand the price for gasoline is set by supply and demand - so while US reduced gasoline consumption gasoline is now exported by domestic refiners...and Rombo promises cheaper gas.- Joe Six Pack would not see one cent from Keystone - don't they get it. and the same about letting automakers go bankrupt - which would have created a huge degree of uncertainty eventually putting the supply chain in the toilet as well. Rombo is highly overrated as a "business man and job creator" - Obummer needs to punch Rombo hard over and over again in regards to lack of loophole specifics</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1350527628704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 22:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350527842858-377</Id><Topic><Title>Romney now up 51 to 45 in latest Gallup Poll</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350523090605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:18:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's gonna build bridges and roads! LOL Remind me again what he's accomplished other than perfecting the art of printing money, making government bigger, etc? Enjoy your food stamps this weekend.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350527842858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 22:37:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350527965374-378</Id><Title>Hi folks, coverd pre market</Title><Msg>I covered around 8:30 @ $21.42 3,200 shares. Made $13,026 less margin, I trade free for another 40 days. Oh, I went long 1,000 shares @ $21.48. GO INTC! Apparently, a 4% dividend is a nice safety net. I sold some Nov., out of the money, coverd calls so I don't know how long I'm long. Nobody buys and holds these days and there's nothing scarier and exciting that making money on the short side. I have to wear a barrel to work, my balls are way too big to fit in my pants. ...marco</Msg><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1350527965374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 22:39:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350528258316-379</Id><Topic><Title>Romney now up 51 to 45 in latest Gallup Poll</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350523090605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:18:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no "growth" solution to where we are now. Mitt will do no better. In fact, he will usher in collapse far more rapidly. Just be grateful you are a citizen of the USA. Man in about to come back into balance with nature via economics.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1350528258316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 22:44:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350528671038-380</Id><Topic><Title>Hi folks, coverd pre market</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1350527965374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 22:39:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep telling yourself that it's true and maybe at least one person will believe it. Claiming a win anonymously on the internet when you never announced when you shorted and are announcing you covered after the fact. FAIL</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1350528671038</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 22:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350528935212-381</Id><Topic><Title>Obama now up 47 to 45 in latest IBD/TIPP Tracking Poll</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350523874422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You will be sporting a new I'd in a couple of weeks as Obama goes down. Scott walker was said to be losing by the liberal media biased polls, he won by 8%. Larger margin then his first run. LOL</Msg><Username>kevivoe</Username><Timestamp>1350528935212</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 22:55:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350530506547-382</Id><Title>PC World says Windows RT (Arm Based chip) Surface Tablets suck for doing work on.</Title><Msg>When Microsoft unveiled its Surface tablet earlier this year, it looked impressive, but left us with few details. This week, Microsoft invited a select group of tech writers for a closer look behind the curtain, and began taking pre-orders for the device that will be available as of October 26. As anxious as some are to get a hold of the new Windows RT tablet, though, there are a few good reasons businesses might think twice. At face value, a Windows-based device engineered by Microsoft would seem to be a slam dunk for businesses considering tablets. However, Windows RT is a different animal than Windows 8. It relies strictly on the Modern (formerly known as Metro) UI with its colorful tiles, and it can only use apps acquired from the Windows Store. The Surface RT has some serious caveats when it comes to business use. In both hardware and software, the Surface RT is a bit closer to rival tablet platforms like iOS and Android, and a bit less like the traditional Windows operating system. Still, it comes with Office apps pre-installed, and it could still be a viable mobile productivity tool for businesses. There are three serious caveats to consider, though. 1. Not for Commercial Use Paul Thurrott, a prominent expert on Windows, pointed out that the license for Office 2013 Home &amp; Student 2013 RT allows only for non-commercial usejust like the PC version. That means that even though the Surface RT tablet comes with the Office apps pre-installed, the tablet cant actually be used for business productivity out of the box. Thurrott explains in a separate post that it isnt entirely true that the Office 2013 Home &amp; Student 2013 RT apps cant be used for business. Microsoft has clarified that customers simply need to buy the standard Office 2013 license, and that allows them to also legally use the Office RT apps for commercial use. That is a workaround, but basically means the Office RT apps that come pre-installed can only be used for business productivity if you also subscribe to Office 365, or invest additional money to buy the full PC version as well. 2. No Outlook Another problem with the Surface RT when it comes to business use is that the Microsoft Office tool that is probably the most widely used of the entire suite is absent from the RT appsOutlook. Many companies rely on Microsoft Outlook for email, calendar, and contacts, and the integration with Microsoft Exchange helps IT admins manage it all. The Mail, People, and Calendar apps in Windows RT perform similar functions. These apps can integrate with Exchange using Exchange ActiveSync, but lack the consistent look and feel of Outlook that users are accustomed to, and fall short of delivering all of the capabilities users expect from Outlook. 3. Cant Join a Domain Another issue that might deter some businesses is the fact that Windows RT cant join a traditional Windows network domain. Granted, neither can iOS or Android tablets, so this isnt exactly an Earth-shattering deal breaker as far as tablets go. There are two things to consider, though, when it comes to the ability of a business to manage its tablets. First, is to consider the options available. There are many mobile device management (MDM) platform options that can provide some control over iOS and Android, and Apple has made significant strides over the years to make iOS more manageable through Exchange ActiveSync. Windows RT probably has similar capabilities available through Exchange ActiveSync. The other option is to hold out for Windows 8 Pro tablets. Windows 8 Pro tablets have standard Intel or AMD processors like those in desktops and laptops, and theyre capable of running the full Windows 8 operating system. That means they can use all of the same software, and connect to a domain to be managed through Active Directory and Group Policy just like any other Windows 8 PC. The caveat here is that Windows 8 Pro tablets will most likely cost significantly more than the Surface RT, so you sort of get what you pay for. Overall, the Surface RT still seems like it has potential. But, businesses that are chomping at the bit to get their hands on one should be aware of these limitations before investing in the new tablet.</Msg><Username>sanjitkumar23</Username><Timestamp>1350530506547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 23:21:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350531409581-383</Id><Topic><Title>PC World says Windows RT (Arm Based chip) Surface Tablets suck for doing work on.</Title><Username>sanjitkumar23</Username><Timestamp>1350530506547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 23:21:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The issues highlighted here have nothing to do with WinRT being ARM based. So you would expect these to be ironed out over time. Bigger issue is whether Office is usable at all on tablets.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1350531409581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 23:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350532177640-384</Id><Topic><Title>Price Action Not Nearly as Bad as I Expected</Title><Username>iwynne2002</Username><Timestamp>1350499533585</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think it's because it got beat down as far as it did already.</Msg><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1350532177640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 23:49:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>