<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349242517951-1</Id><Topic><Title>Guess What? Wall Street Really Is Stupid and Here's Why</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349199880510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 13:44:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But wait: there's a lot more to Intel's tablet story than "Clover Trail." I'm going to dig deeper into the official road map as well as the leaked road maps to give investors an even clearer picture of just where Intel is going on tablets.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349242517951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 01:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349243245081-2</Id><Topic><Title>"Oh God," he said. "I was born in California and raised here. But, we've messed it up so much. ... I'm afraid the abyss will be like Greece." Otellini</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1349236589725</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:56:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you know about Californian economics would fit on the head of a pin. So shut the hay up doom and gloom boy. California's economic problems stem almost entirely from when conservatives changed the property tax laws making the state overly dependent on income taxes. While it seemed like a good idea at the time, it's been an unmitigated disaster since then. Property taxes are relatively stable - income states are horribly dependent on general economic issues. Therein lies the rub. But you don't care about any of this. You are just an arm-flapping parasite on the US economy and card carrying member of the #$%$ group that continuously attacks Intel. Your avarice ate your ethics a long time ago and this is what you have been reduced to. A sad and pathetic drain on the human race.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349243245081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 01:47:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349244011235-3</Id><Title>Intel - How 22nm Yield Changes The Industry</Title><Msg>During Intel's (INTC) fourth-quarter 2010 conference call CEO Paul Otellini first told us about the Intel 22nm process. He also told us about "Intel's three fabrication manufacturing model." The surprising thing was that he next said that the company felt the 22nm process would be in such high demand that it planned to build a fourth fab center for 22nm. The combination of the process shrink from 32nm to 22nm and the additional fab center would nearly double the potential chip output. Back then Intel was placing a wager, betting the company could build these revolutionary 22nm Trigate products in very high volume and with a yield that would continue high profitability for Intel. No one knew what the yield would be, and I think that uncertainty is the real reason Intel built the fourth fab. The extra capacity would provide insurance that if yields on the new 22nm process were low, the company could brute force extra wafers through the factories to insure there would be no shortages of Ivy Bridge processors to end customers. Now we are ending 2012 and the four 22nm fabs are online. According to Mark Bohr's comments during multiple interviews at the recent Intel Developers Forum, "22nm yields are excellent," "22nm yields are better than we expected," and "22nm yields are the same as 32nm." Bohr is an Intel Technical Fellow and Chief Process Technologist. Bohr, like many technical professionals, is genetically incapable of lying or even fibbing. Now, if Bohr were a marketing guy, his comments might be suspect. It appears that we have a major new fact: 22nm yields turned out to be much better than expected. That means that the fourth fab was unnecessary and will be empty or under-utilized. Ottelini's next step could be to go to Apple (AAPL) and offer to build the A6 chip in 22nm Trigate at the cost (yes, the cost) of the A6 chip now being built on Samsung's 32nm process in Austin. The A6 chip is about a 97 sq mm chip now; on Intel's 22nm it would drop down to about 55 sq mm, or about a 44% size reduction. The A6 chip built on a 22nm wafer will produce approximately 78% more chips than on the Samsung 32nm wafer. 22nm Trigate wafers cost more to manufacture than 32nm wafers. Nevertheless, Intel's cost to make an A6 chip would be at least 30% lower than Samsung's cost. This means that Intel could sell its version of the A6 chip to Apple at or near Samsung's cost and still make 30% gross margin and fill that fourth fab center in the process. Samsung, which has about 50% of the smartphone SoC business (Apple's A6 and Samsung's own requirements), would suddenly lose 50% of its SoC business. Intel would go from "zero to hero" in one stroke. When the industry recovered from the shock of this single action, the pundits will understand very clearly that one node, let alone two nodes (14nm next year), is such a smothering advantage for Intel that the fabless semiconductor model (at least for these very high volume, leading edge chips) can't compete against an aroused Intel. During 2013-14 Intel would have such an overpowering advantage in new SoC design wins over Qualcomm (QCOM), Nvidia (NVDA), and even Samsung that it would go on to ultimately dominate the mobile SoC business. Other than the Apple chip, these SoCs will be Intel Atom-based, because in the real world customers don't care anymore about processor architecture as long as the chip does what they want at very low power and at a low price. That means ARM (ARMH) gets nicked in the long run as well. While all this is going on, and since the cost of Ivy Bridge processors is lower than expected, Intel will likely cut prices on selected devices in order to put more pressure on AMD (AMD). That will allow Intel to pick up the 20% of the PC CPU business still at AMD. A great deal of the current Nvidia discrete GPU business will just quietly migrate into the Ivy Bridge chip with "good enough" graphics, leaving Nvidia in a very precarious position. The next Intel CPU architecture, due to ship in late 2013, with even better graphics could well kill off AMD and Nvidia. All this happens because Intel's 22 nm yields exceed expectations. It's a crazy business! Action: Buy Intel or Intel LEAPs and watch the story unfold. Sell or short AMD, Nvidia, ARMH, and QCOM, since there is no reason to own them.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349244011235</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 02:00:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349267619244-4</Id><Topic><Title>I stated boldly ten years ago. Barring a real innovation, INTC is a toothpick factory from here on out.</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349236524549</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:55:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah but you got shunned by Intel and were pumping AMD at 40 as your posts clearly show........so we kinduh gottuh laugh at your sarcastic, bitter rants. Poor Vinnie, just another day writing Cobol programs in a tiny cubicle at some bank.</Msg><Username>vinnie_bagofhotwind</Username><Timestamp>1349267619244</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:33:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268889045-5</Id><Title>reminds me of the JOHN D time period.</Title><Msg>giving dimes away. 28-30 2013.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1349268889045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:54:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270677276-6</Id><Title>get this stock back over 24.25</Title><Msg>someone please</Msg><Username>raygeo2003</Username><Timestamp>1349270677276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:24:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349270884410-7</Id><Topic><Title>I stated boldly ten years ago. Barring a real innovation, INTC is a toothpick factory from here on out.</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349236524549</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:55:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>coming from a guy who thinks a toothpick is a daily suppository.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349270884410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:28:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349272062616-8</Id><Topic><Title>I stated boldly ten years ago. Barring a real innovation, INTC is a toothpick factory from here on out.</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349236524549</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:55:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"coming from a guy who thinks a toothpick is a daily suppository." *** Hahahahahahaha Good one, bro...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349272062616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349272203980-9</Id><Title>From Mark Cuban: High Frequency Trading Insanity</Title><Msg>In today's stock market, there are two types of trader. The other, the high-frequency trader, deploys massive computer capacity and complex algorithms to buy and sell individual stocks multiple times in a fraction of a second, all in search of micro-profits with each trade. This trader cares not a whit about a stock's fundamentals. In a sane world, high-frequency trading would be a minor specialty at best. But in the bizarro world that Wall Street has become, such activity now makes up the majority of all trades. It is manufacturing risk while siphoning money and talent that growth-producing sectors of the economy need. It has also sparked a technological arms race aimed at shaving milliseconds off each trade. New, more direct fiber optic cable routes have been laid between major trading cities, and now there are even serious proposals to position drone aircraft over the Atlantic Ocean to speed transmission times between New York and London. And what does all this mean for conventional investors? Nothing good. Just gobs of needless danger. The biggest problem with high-frequency trading is that it greatly increases the chances of a major market crash. In 2010, the "flash crash" took the Dow Jones average down more than 1,000 points in a matter of minutes. Finding the cause — a single massive computerized trade made in error — took months. Imagine, then, what might happen if the market started falling in response to a sudden event, such as an attack on Iran. The computers, which act on their own, would likely overwhelm the market with sell orders. Similar circumstances in 1987 caused a crash that took the Dow down 22.6% in a day and nearly crippled the entire financial system. Today, the trade volume would be massively larger. Yet the regulatory response has been negligible, even as problems have continued. Just last month, a trading company called Knight Capital Group nearly collapsed after malfunctions in its computers sent the shares of 148 companies on wild rides. Behind these events is a high-tech war fought among computer algorithms challenging each other for supremacy and unmindful of the destabilizing effect they are having. The growing concern they are causing was evident at a Senate hearing last week, and in a report by the Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago. Beyond the crash risk, these practices undermine the core purpose of markets, which is to raise capital in pursuit of enterprise, profit and economic growth. That's not happening the way it used to. Even though the Dow is back above 13,000 and bond yields are low, investors have been pulling money out of stock mutual funds most of this year, according to the Investment Company Institute. And even sophisticated investors such as billionaire Mark Cuban say they're "terrified" about potential flash crashes triggered by high-frequency trading. The traders argue that they add liquidity to markets that lowers transaction costs and eases dealing in thinly traded shares. There is some truth to this. But the negatives far outweigh the positives. Next week, the Securities and Exchange Commission is holding a meeting to solicit ideas about what to do. Here's a simple one: Slap a small transaction tax on rapid trades, impeding the practice and returning markets to their core purpose. That would be a big win for small investors, and the only people harmed would be those now putting everyone else at risk.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349272203980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:50:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349272301293-10</Id><Title>Buffet_Graham_Weaver PUMPED ALL NIGHT</Title><Msg>Only to see InSmell in the REDDDDDD Today. So what's new, Pumpwad? Same old, same old.. TOOOOOOOOO BADDDDDDDDD! TOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349272301293</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:51:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349272514810-11</Id><Topic><Title>get this stock back over 24.25</Title><Username>raygeo2003</Username><Timestamp>1349270677276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:24:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Relax, wait for earnings. Wall Street has priced a $7 billion revenue miss into the stock. What a joke. This incredibly large disconnect won't withstand any basic fact check. The stock is at least 5 bucks below what earnings will justify... From "The Street" "NEW YORK (TheStreet) -- Intel (Nasdaq:INTC) has been reiterated by TheStreet Ratings as a buy with a ratings score of B . The company's strengths can be seen in multiple areas, such as its revenue growth, largely solid financial position with reasonable debt levels by most measures, notable return on equity, attractive valuation levels and expanding profit margins."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349272514810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:55:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349272865684-12</Id><Title>ARM gets weapon in server battle vs. Intel</Title><Msg>SAN JOSE, Calif. – Russian engineers are developing software to run x86 programs on ARM-based servers. If successful, the software could help lower one of the biggest barriers ARM SoC makers face getting their chips adopted as alternatives to Intel x86 processors that dominate today’s server market. Elbrus Technologies has developed emulation software that currently delivers 40 percent of native ARM performance. The company believes it could reach 80 percent native ARM performance or greater by the end of 2014. Analysts and ARM execs described the code as a significant, but limited option. A growing list of companies—including Applied Micro, Calxeda, Cavium, Marvell, Nvidia and Samsung—aim to replace Intel CPUs with ARM SoCs that pack more functions and consume less power. One of their biggest hurdles is their chips do not support the wealth of server software that runs on the x86. The emulation code from Elbrus Tech could help lower that barrier. The team will present a paper on its work at the ARM TechCon in Santa Clara, Calif., Oct. 30-Nov. 1. The team’s software uses 1 Mbyte of memory. “What is more exciting is the fact that the memory footprint will have weak dependence on the number of applications that are being run in emulation mode,” Anatoly Konukhov, a member of the Elbrus Tech team, said in an e-mail exchange. The team has developed a binary translator that acts as an emulator, and plans to create an optimization process for it. "Currently, we are creating a binary translator which allows us to run applications," Konukhov said. "Implementation of an optimization process will start in parallel later this year--we're expecting both parts be ready in the end of 2014." "The major concern for us is lack of software developers with binary translation expertise," he added. "This is also the reason for us to estimate project release in late 2014." The Elbrus Tech software uses a parallel compilation process and stores translations in volatile memory to decrease overhead when starting up. The binary translator will have "several levels of optimization for 'cold' and 'hot' regions of code," said Konukhov. Work on the software started in 2010. Last summer, Elbrus Tech got $1.3 million in funding from the Russian investment fund Skolkovo and MCST, a veteran Russian processor and software developer. MCST also is providing developers for the project.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349272865684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:01:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349273023571-13</Id><Topic><Title>Buffet_Graham_Weaver PUMPED ALL NIGHT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349272301293</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:51:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe Buffet_Graham_Weaver doesn't like mini-golf like you! He is probably adverse to exercise like you when you go for 18.</Msg><Username>pumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1349273023571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:03:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349273123945-14</Id><Topic><Title>ARM gets weapon in server battle vs. Intel</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349272865684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:01:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is a sure winner!!!</Msg><Username>pumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1349273123945</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349273126336-15</Id><Topic><Title>From Mark Cuban: High Frequency Trading Insanity</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349272203980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:50:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should never put money in the stock market that you can't be without for a minimum of 5 years. Using that responsible strategy, a flash crash would have absolutely ZERO effect on your investment.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349273126336</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349273178266-16</Id><Topic><Title>From Mark Cuban: High Frequency Trading Insanity</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349272203980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:50:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did Cuban say anything about people like you who practice high-frequency posting on public message boards, Pumpwad? TOOOOO FUNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349273178266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:06:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349273341087-17</Id><Title>Apple begins mass production of dead-in-the-water tablet</Title><Msg>[It seems that this is Apple after Jobs: Trying to maximize what existed before Jobs departed. Difficult to see how this will end well....] Smaller tablet against the will of Jobs Apple is pressing ahead with a smaller tablet that its sainted founder Steve Jobs said would be dead-in-the-water. Apple has reportedly instructed partners in its Asian supply chain to begin production of the iPad Mini, which means that the smaller tablet might be ready in time for the holiday season. According to the Wall Street Journal the tablet is confirmed to feature a 7.85-inch LCD display and will not feature Apple’s Retina display technology. The tablet is supposed to compete in the smaller tablet market, against Google’s Nexus 7 and Amazon’s new Kindle Fire devices. Despite what Jobs said, these tablets did rather well, mostly because they were super-cheap. It seems that now that Steve has gone, the mini-tablet has gone into production. From Fudzilla</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349273341087</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:09:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349273574825-18</Id><Topic><Title>Apple begins mass production of dead-in-the-water tablet</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349273341087</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:09:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are guilty of high-frequency pumping, Waldo! TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349273574825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:12:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349273663482-19</Id><Title>Branded notebook vendors, ODMs post strong shipment growth in September</Title><Msg>[Oh, nooooooooooo Wall Street, how does this square with your prediction of a $7 billion Intel revenue miss???] Notebook shipments from both branded vendors and ODMs staged a rebound in September 2012 after a month of depressed sales in August when the notebook industry was busy clearing out Windows 7 models, according to Digitimes Research. Among the major brands, Hewlett-Packard (HP) and Asustek Computer saw their shipments increase significantly in September, with HP's shipments for the month likely to mark the highest level for 2012. Inventec and Pegatron Technology led other ODMs with each posting an over 40% sequential growth in notebook shipments in September, said Digitimes Research.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349273663482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:14:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349273777723-20</Id><Title>Many US$699 ultrabook models to be available in 2013, say Taiwan makers</Title><Msg>PC vendors are expected to offer many entry-level ultrabook or ultra-like models for sale at up to US$699 to generate large shipment volumes, and high-end ultrabook models for sale at above US$1,000 in a bid to maintain profitability in 2013, according to Taiwan-based supply chain makers. High-end ultrabooks will feature aluminum unibody or carbon-fiber chassis, SSDs, Li polymer batteries and Windows 8 touch screens, the sources indicated. In order to minimize production costs to keep retail prices at or below US$699, fiberglass-reinforced plastic or metal-plastic hybrid chassis, slim HDDs or HDD/SSD hybrid drives, conventional batteries and non-touch screens will be adopted for entry-level ultrabook or ultra-like models, the sources pointed out. According to Taiwan-based Topology Research Institute, there will be 16.7 million ultrabooks sold globally in 2012, accounting for 8% of all notebooks sold, and the sales volume will increase to 31.6 million units in 2013, accounting for 14.6% of total notebook sales.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349273777723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:16:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349273933455-21</Id><Title>Yahoo News - Intel is a solid pick worth over 35/share</Title><Msg>Seeking Alpha Article posted today.</Msg><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1349273933455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:18:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349274312344-22</Id><Title>Wall Street's Prediction of a $7 Billion Intel Revenue Miss in Q3 Looms Large</Title><Msg>Push is coming to shove. Wall Street has priced in a $7 billion revenue miss for Intel in Q3. Intel has, of course, warned of a billion dollar revenue miss. Now that Wall Street has bet huge on the miss being 7 times higher than what Intel has projected, how will they approach earnings which will provide the facts on Intel's current revenue and profit picture?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349274312344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349274477852-23</Id><Title>Where's the PRE-EARNINGS RAMP UP?</Title><Msg>The closer we get to earnings, the faster Wallis pumps. Too bad that WS doesn't share Wally's excitement. TOOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349274477852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:27:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349274604991-24</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo News - Intel is a solid pick worth over 35/share</Title><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1349273933455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:18:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not to rain on your parade, because I am a super-bull on INTC, but frankly, Seeking Alpha is written by high school sophomores. I mean, really, short Dec puts; multiply that by 5 to get 27% per year? Why not double up and get 52%/year? That's all this article prescribes (heck, I'm already short 40 INTC 25's, 27.5's and 30's out to 2014, a little underwater, but I don't mind being put..INTC is a $100 stock in due course).. You get more content out of Wallis' posts in here than seeking alpha. I long ago stopped reading seeking alpha (and stopped listening to Cramer as well, talk about jokers).</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349274604991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:30:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349274706896-25</Id><Title>Is Intel STUFFING THE CHANNEL?</Title><Msg>I don't know. Only asking. Anyone have an opinion?</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349274706896</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:31:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349274855047-26</Id><Topic><Title>I stated boldly ten years ago. Barring a real innovation, INTC is a toothpick factory from here on out.</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349236524549</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:55:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's pretty funny. Show me a link where I pumped AMD at $40. Yeah, you can't. Because there aren't any. IAL offered me 25K options to stay on and I said no way. Best move I ever made. Those options are still worthless. I'm sure they repriced them at some point, maybe to $25? Ironically, I don't despise INTC like I once did. You know, the days when people would walk around Jones farm laughing about the poor people outside the window and how they were going to go crush a few companies today. INTC ruined a lot of startups just because they could. Now, they are just a big human cattle ranch up in the rainforest, stock stuck under $30 just like I said it would be forever. A couple compliments, though. They do keep a lot of jobs in the US and their fabs are unmatched anywhere and I've always said that about them. But, man, are there some serious a-wholes up in Oregon.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349274855047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349274907657-27</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>Yesterday the mkts continued to see both "sell the rips" and "buy the dips" today. This is not a market for long term investing. The last hour bounce saved what could have been a poor session but the overall technical condition has been deteriorating as the momentum readings are heading lower. With that said, as long as there is buying on the dips, downside is limited. In addition, the S&amp;P 500 has a couple of support areas not far below where it closed today. The first support is near 1430, last week's low. The second support is in the 1418-1422 area, its prior significant highs as well as an area that will become its 50-day moving average in two sessions. have a nice day.</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1349274907657</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:35:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349274954032-28</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo News - Intel is a solid pick worth over 35/share</Title><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1349273933455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:18:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I stopped reading your posts long ago because you change your mind like a woman. So I guess we are even.</Msg><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1349274954032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:35:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349275864210-29</Id><Title>Oh well. Of course Intel needs to make massive moves into phones.</Title><Msg>Insiders are talking about an Apple -Intel deal sooner than we think. One would not wanting to be sitting short on Intel as Apple stood with Intel for the announcement. 40</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349275864210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:51:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349276241906-30</Id><Topic><Title>Oh well. Of course Intel needs to make massive moves into phones.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349275864210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:51:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very informatinve post, as usual (rolls eyes). Why'd you switch from your Flumoxed alias? Bring out your gay liberal cornholers, ok ???</Msg><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1349276241906</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:57:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349276339699-31</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Shareholders, This Is A Must Read...</Title><Username>vaughnparks181</Username><Timestamp>1349269195094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think this is a great resource for any one looking for good reliable information. Don't listen to the bashers, get your own information and make your own educated decisions.</Msg><Username>vargasboris55</Username><Timestamp>1349276339699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349276516393-32</Id><Title>But Rombo Rommney can make a complete clown of himself tonight.</Title><Msg>We know he will be flip flopping all over the place with his lies but that is not the funniest thing. Rombo will then call The pres a liar when the Pres calls him on the lies. Then the moderator will point out the facts and still Rombo will insist that the moderator too is wrong. I never did healthcare in --oh--I did it but only in a state--people liked it but it is not good for other states--but I am against it--but I was for it--a national plan--but now--against it. yes I was in France during the Vioetnam war and yes I do have money in offshore accounts but noo-you cannot see my tax returns for the last ten years but I have nothing to hide but I will not show you but I did show mcpain over 10 years when he wanted to look at me for VP. I am solid and I have a plan but I cannot give you the plan because. I never said the pres was a foreigner--Oh I did make a joke--oh but I was joking so--and I am not a Mormon and we need not talk about religion here because those right-wing #$%$ in my party hate Mormons. Elect me and I will do this and that and I hate GW so--but I have all his people working for me-- If I lose--and I will--the rightwing redneck #$%$ in my party will shiiiet themselves but I do not give a rat's about those idiots.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1349276516393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:01:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349276802857-33</Id><Topic><Title>Oh well. Of course Intel needs to make massive moves into phones.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349275864210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:51:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not flumoxed you illiterate teabagging loser. You want your country back? Come to Chicago and we will stick it up yours. You Mormon loving redneck KKK Birther clowns need to get your upchuck bags ready for when Romney implodes tonight.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349276802857</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:06:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349277093843-34</Id><Topic><Title>Oh well. Of course Intel needs to make massive moves into phones.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349275864210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:51:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only one delusional dirt-bat would talk like you AND support someone as digusting as Bill Maur. Warren Buffet, President for Life By flumoxed11.Feb 25, 2012 11:41 AM.Permalink and Bill Maur, Vice President for Life. Clean this stinking village up!</Msg><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1349277093843</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349277252081-35</Id><Title>LET'S CLEAN UP THIS FORUM NOW!</Title><Msg>It's time to sweeeeeep out the trash on this message board!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349277252081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:14:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349277297446-36</Id><Title>Service Sector Up Much More than Expected</Title><Msg>Take that, doom and gloom boys, parasites, shills and #$%$ rooting for demise of the American economy. And particularly the big firms on Wall Street who have bet heavy on a US economic collapse...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349277297446</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:14:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349278084553-37</Id><Title>no power</Title><Msg>no power to go up and hold, i told u so!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349278084553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:28:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349278941581-38</Id><Topic><Title>no power</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349278084553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:28:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's keep falling, no power to hold the gains, i told u so, lobster red soon!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349278941581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:42:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349279073995-39</Id><Topic><Title>INTC might possibly skyrocket! View why!</Title><Username>alejandrowilson90</Username><Timestamp>1349278418182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:33:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He are on a volcano hot streak currently. I don't contemplate that they will quit or stall just yet.</Msg><Username>michaelsalvaggio464</Username><Timestamp>1349279073995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:44:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349279483520-40</Id><Title>Earnings + Shareholders of record on Nov.7 + Late year tech does well</Title><Msg>This thing could easily see 26 or 27 before November 7th.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349279483520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349279599730-41</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings + Shareholders of record on Nov.7 + Late year tech does well</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349279483520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:51:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shareholders of record as of November 7th get the Dividend. This is perfectly timed just after earnings. Runup into earnings, slight dip after earnings even though earnings and out look will be good and then a strong runup for the dividend. 25-27 coming soon.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349279599730</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:53:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349279681170-42</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings + Shareholders of record on Nov.7 + Late year tech does well</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349279483520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:51:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This thing could easily see 26 or 27 before November 7th -------------- November 7th of what year, jackwad? 2013? 2014? 2015?</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349279681170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:54:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349279872681-43</Id><Title>Wow, this board has turned into a SPAMAPALOOZA</Title><Msg>Seems like just ten years ago it was a snake's pit of Intel pimps. That was before the stock plunged under $30 never to recover. That's what happens when your 64 bit solution is two years late and you completely miss the mobile revolution. Whoops.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349279872681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:57:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349279977490-44</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings + Shareholders of record on Nov.7 + Late year tech does well</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349279483520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:51:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You think the stock could rise almost 5 points in 30 days over a lousy 22 cent dividend and an earnings warning? I have a truckload of hula-hoops to sell to ya, rube.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349279977490</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:59:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349280214923-45</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, this board has turned into a SPAMAPALOOZA</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349279872681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:57:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you sure you didn't mean WALLISPALOOZA? TOOOO FUNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349280214923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:03:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349280226360-46</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Shareholders, This Is A Must Read...</Title><Username>vaughnparks181</Username><Timestamp>1349269195094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fantastic. I will check it out.</Msg><Username>romanroman79</Username><Timestamp>1349280226360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:03:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349280266435-47</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings + Shareholders of record on Nov.7 + Late year tech does well</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349279483520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:51:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please keep bashing the stock. It ran up 50 percent on your last bash campaign. Again, keep screaming, yelling and insulting. Longs love you.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349280266435</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349280346193-48</Id><Topic><Title>From Mark Cuban: High Frequency Trading Insanity</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349272203980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:50:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mark Cuban is right, but nothing will be done about HFT. I personally know several people who are out of the market because they think it's a scam. These are people who just got fed up and don't trust the market, especially when it's up 100 points all day, then at 3:57pm it suddenly goes down 100 points in a matter of minutes for no reason, then the negative "talking heads" on CNBC say it was a bad day and the next will be worse.</Msg><Username>nickster135796</Username><Timestamp>1349280346193</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:05:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349280397561-49</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings + Shareholders of record on Nov.7 + Late year tech does well</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349279483520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:51:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PS, where did you drop out from school? Who Tell me how 27-22.84 OR 26-22.84 = 5 points? No need to answer. You are a very very damaged soul, and I pity your soul.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349280397561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349280549571-50</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings + Shareholders of record on Nov.7 + Late year tech does well</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349279483520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:51:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even Wallis the Pumper realizes that the stock has been unchanged for years. Maybe in a few more years of rangebound you'll get the message, dolt.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349280549571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349280661234-51</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings + Shareholders of record on Nov.7 + Late year tech does well</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349279483520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:51:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stock ran from 20 to 29 after you said you sold it and bought Cisco at 20....2 years of losses on Cisco and missing out on a 50 percent runup on Intel after you sold makes you the dolt of all dolts. You're parents waisted alot of years of their lives, I pity them.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349280661234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:11:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349281059830-52</Id><Title>Tooofunnny's ugly wife divorced him and took half of nothing with her.</Title><Msg>ROFLMAO !!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349281059830</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:17:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349281265649-53</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings + Shareholders of record on Nov.7 + Late year tech does well</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349279483520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:51:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are your parents proud of the fact that you have a little too much sugar in your tank, cretin? TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349281265649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:21:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349281363063-54</Id><Topic><Title>From Mark Cuban: High Frequency Trading Insanity</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349272203980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:50:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agree, but how to prevet HFT is the Q.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1349281363063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:22:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349281476722-55</Id><Title>Meg Whitman speaks, HPQ gets destroyed</Title><Msg>Looks like ToooFunnny's portfolio over there.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349281476722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:24:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349281502733-56</Id><Topic><Title>From Mark Cuban: High Frequency Trading Insanity</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349272203980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:50:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about preventing HFP on this message board, pumper boy?</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349281502733</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349281511231-57</Id><Title>Look at HPQ, TIC TOC Always remember to sell the rips, lower lows to come</Title><Msg>Look at HPQ, TIC TOC Always remember to sell the rips, lower lows to come</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349281511231</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:25:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349281968094-58</Id><Topic><Title>no power</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349278084553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:28:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i told u so, no power, couldn't hold the gains, wake up and run away!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349281968094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:32:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349282214747-59</Id><Title>All I can is</Title><Msg>F* HP. They ruined the moment today.</Msg><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349282214747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:36:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349282265985-60</Id><Topic><Title>All I can is</Title><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349282214747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:36:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I meant " all I can say"</Msg><Username>tnp_us</Username><Timestamp>1349282265985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:37:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349282963304-61</Id><Title>adding AMD... HEDGE MANIPULATION... and BUYOUT seen..AMD EASY DOUBLE DIGITS on BUYOUT</Title><Msg>BUY AMD.. NOW</Msg><Username>buywhenallbazh</Username><Timestamp>1349282963304</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:49:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349283360431-62</Id><Topic><Title>From Mark Cuban: High Frequency Trading Insanity</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349272203980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:50:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The proposal to tax these types of synthetic trades would be a very effective way of stopping them, by hitting them where it hurts the most,... in their bottom line. BTW,... this is a very interesting thread,... too bad "Too Funny" feels the need to keep showing up to make a fool of himself. What motivates such behavior is beyond me. Very odd person. Come back and insult me Too Funny. We would all be disappointed if you didn't.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1349283360431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:56:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349284193127-63</Id><Topic><Title>no power</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349278084553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:28:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>junk is junk, won't change, i told you so!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349284193127</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:09:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349284865662-64</Id><Topic><Title>Look at HPQ, TIC TOC Always remember to sell the rips, lower lows to come</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349281511231</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:25:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HPQ problems are INTC problems</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349284865662</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:21:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349284907217-65</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Shareholders, This Is A Must Read...</Title><Username>vaughnparks181</Username><Timestamp>1349269195094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be waiting for more great news to come.</Msg><Username>dickersonh73</Username><Timestamp>1349284907217</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:21:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349284931030-66</Id><Title>HPQ problems are INTC problems</Title><Msg>HPQ problems are INTC problems</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349284931030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349285275234-67</Id><Title>HPQ tanking can't be good for INTC</Title><Msg>That's an understatement. The era of the PC is coming to a close. Too bad INTC missed the mobile revolution.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349285275234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:27:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349287499220-68</Id><Topic><Title>INTC might possibly skyrocket! View why!</Title><Username>alejandrowilson90</Username><Timestamp>1349278418182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:33:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC jumped by very nearly 100% give or take just within seven days of him alerting it.</Msg><Username>paulaparicio440</Username><Timestamp>1349287499220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:04:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349288031432-69</Id><Title>I see INTC having big inventory problems with HPQ and DELL and the other PC companies have big problems</Title><Msg>I see INTC having big inventory problems with HPQ and DELL and the other PC companies have big problems</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349288031432</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349288445839-70</Id><Title>INTC the next HPQ dead money</Title><Msg>INTC the next HPQ dead money</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349288445839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:20:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349289105104-71</Id><Title>Wow, Lucy stops posting and Coinmaker takes over.......dUHHHHH</Title><Msg>Paid loser. Sold his soul to the Wallstreet demons.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349289105104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:31:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349290372646-72</Id><Title>Wall Street Doubles Down on Stupid</Title><Msg>No surprise. Looking forward to earnings and sanity...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349290372646</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349290486316-73</Id><Topic><Title>I see INTC having big inventory problems with HPQ and DELL and the other PC companies have big problems</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349288031432</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lucy, you don't know enough about accounting to have an opinion on inventory problems. You've brought this up every single quarter for years. You need some new material, dufus...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349290486316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:54:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349290739011-74</Id><Title>U.S. met 83% of its energy needs in the first 6 months of the yr!</Title><Msg>It will be the highest level of self-sufficiency since '91 if the trends continues through '12. Drill baby drill</Msg><Username>yawnfestblink</Username><Timestamp>1349290739011</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349290847291-75</Id><Topic><Title>We're Good for 30</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1327420596000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-01-24 10:56:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Solid call, Pumpwad! The stock has lost only about $6 since you called for 30. If you told me that tomorrow would be a sunny day, I'd rush out and buy an umbrella! TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349290847291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:00:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349291135816-76</Id><Title>Paid basher Lucy Nuff's aliases. Let's track him down and expose whoever it is that's paying him.</Title><Msg>tooofunnny coinmaker will_amd_yu lucy_nuff lucifer_nuff wilder_blitch win_dexit wallisschmallis stupidstewie gordon.greco kored65 obamaloveswallst kohighbloodpressure Jimbohomegamedyou CrazyWally Foxnewzzz(with three z's) maximumwalrus winteldead think5pm pedroexressway wallisweiner walldexit trixeee777777 vinnie_baggadonitz jessejames_blitch wallywiththereddress_nuff pumpwad No less than 100 others</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349291135816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349291851674-77</Id><Title>Next stop down is $20, that's were we will bounce!</Title><Msg>Buckle up. $20 next stop down!</Msg><Username>buyrightone</Username><Timestamp>1349291851674</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:17:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349292247024-78</Id><Title>Message to retail investors</Title><Msg>Technology is hot Dont fallow DELL HPQ AMD INTC and think economy is bad Its all about smart technology Look at GOOG AMZN SAMSUNG QCOM SNDK AAPL or even Brother International</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1349292247024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349292824429-79</Id><Title>INTC: Put OCT 19$ cost 0.02 cents may make lots of $$$$</Title><Msg>=============eom ==========================</Msg><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1349292824429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:33:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349293395092-80</Id><Title>Wished I dumped my INTC to buy more AAPL yesterday :(</Title><Msg>This stock sucks!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>jdr52683</Username><Timestamp>1349293395092</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:43:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349293598224-81</Id><Title>INTC needs to buyback stock and or raise div. MGMT SUCKS! Stock down 20% in 6mo.</Title><Msg>Horrible.</Msg><Username>jdr52683</Username><Timestamp>1349293598224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:46:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349293701782-82</Id><Title>So who bought in May??</Title><Msg>More cool aid on the way.</Msg><Username>jacksparrow777722</Username><Timestamp>1349293701782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:48:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349294169820-83</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street's Prediction of a $7 Billion Intel Revenue Miss in Q3 Looms Large</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349274312344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:25:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But Wallis: I think they've also priced in the death of PC (which is #$%$, but not what it used to be) and the not-so-#$%$ underwhelming by ultrabooks, and the fact that INTC is yet to get a significant foothold in the smartphone space. I am a little worried. There's something very 1990's about INTC's style. They need to land some big ones. And soon.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349294169820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:56:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349294211727-84</Id><Title>WOW look at HPQ drop, MAN how low is INTC going to go. HPQ problems are INTC's problems</Title><Msg>WOW look at HPQ drop, MAN how low is INTC going to go. HPQ problems are INTC's problems DEAD MONEY WALKING</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349294211727</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:56:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349294357341-85</Id><Topic><Title>Paid basher Lucy Nuff's aliases. Let's track him down and expose whoever it is that's paying him.</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349291135816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>upppppppppppppppppppppp</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349294357341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349294682312-86</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street's Prediction of a $7 Billion Intel Revenue Miss in Q3 Looms Large</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349274312344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:25:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not to worry. The high-end always sells. Just look at AMD, Nvidia and Qualcomm begging TSMC for some lousy 28nm production. All that 22nm production is not going to waste. And even if there were a temporary demand problem, Intel is the world's best at adjusting to this type of thing in the most efficient way ever. Wall Street is pricing Intel like Intel is going out of business. They really have priced in a $7 billion revenue miss. It's ridiculous. And that's what we will find out come earnings...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349294682312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:04:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349294753091-87</Id><Topic><Title>WOW look at HPQ drop, MAN how low is INTC going to go. HPQ problems are INTC's problems</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349294211727</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:56:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>coinmaker = lucy</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349294753091</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:05:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349295428161-88</Id><Title>INTC investors literally being held hostage</Title><Msg>by idiots like Meg Whitman, Michael Dell, Ballmer....these are supposedly Intel's friends &amp; they seem to be bashing the PC as much as analysts. Paul O. has lost total control of Intel's message &amp; should be replaced ASAP.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349295428161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295491896-89</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street's Prediction of a $7 Billion Intel Revenue Miss in Q3 Looms Large</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349274312344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:25:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All INTC has to do is start making 22nm ARMH chips and sell them to the highest bidder and we go to 35/share in a heart beat. INTC will have to do this soon as they don't have enough demand for their chips now. Every PC, netbook and phone maker would have to bid on 22nm as the ones who don't buy it will go by the way of the dodo bird. contrary to popular opinion, INTC has a fudicary duty to protect the stockholders and by not doing this, they are in breach of fudicary duty.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349295491896</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:18:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295573908-90</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street's Prediction of a $7 Billion Intel Revenue Miss in Q3 Looms Large</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349274312344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:25:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you think ARMH would grant INTC a fab license??????? Doubt it, Herb.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349295573908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295676436-91</Id><Topic><Title>Singhlion burst in here crushing Intel down to single digits..........then got stopped out of his short at 23 just hours later. LMAO</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349208093506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 16:01:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hpq busting and wintel gang getting crushed road map lol</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349295676436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:21:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295677515-92</Id><Topic><Title>Paid basher Lucy Nuff's aliases. Let's track him down and expose whoever it is that's paying him.</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349291135816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not Lucy Nuff. And, what does that have to do with INTC scrooing the pooch? Missing the entire mobile computing revolution?</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349295677515</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:21:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295789582-93</Id><Topic><Title>INTC investors literally being held hostage</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349295428161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:17:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Classic blame game. Pass the blame and you will be just fine. Paul is trying to take the high ground but in doing so is violating his fudicary duty to the shareholders and leaving himself and INTC at risk.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349295789582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295845734-94</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street's Prediction of a $7 Billion Intel Revenue Miss in Q3 Looms Large</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349274312344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:25:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course they would. ARMH does not compete with fabs. they design chips only. the more fabs the better. They want their licensed designs made into chips. does not matter where. you don't seem to understand much about arm or intc or the chip industry</Msg><Username>equityrich</Username><Timestamp>1349295845734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349296006797-95</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street's Prediction of a $7 Billion Intel Revenue Miss in Q3 Looms Large</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349274312344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:25:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They already have an ARMH license. They got that when they bought Infenon</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349296006797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:26:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349296054849-96</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street's Prediction of a $7 Billion Intel Revenue Miss in Q3 Looms Large</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349274312344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:25:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>armh was up again</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349296054849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:27:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349296128764-97</Id><Title>Mitt armed with Quiver full of Zingers!!</Title><Msg>Watch this #$%$-bag shoot himself on to his foot tonight</Msg><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349296128764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349296131456-98</Id><Topic><Title>INTC investors literally being held hostage</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349295428161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:17:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you putting that in your letter?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349296131456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:28:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349296268334-99</Id><Title>SO CALLED BLUE CHIPS OF USA ARE NOW DEBT LOADED AND WHY? WHERE DID THE CASH GO? BUY BACK SCAMS TO ENRICH INSIDERS AND WALL STREET BANKSTERS</Title><Msg>So called blue chips of usa are now debt loaded and why? Where did the cash go? Buy back scams to enrich insiders and wall street banksters usa is a failed state: americans are history without revolution; read on dr. Paul craig roberts usa hijacked by home grown financial al qaeda led by bankster terrorists high treason criminal rulers in their pockets........... hpq/dell/ibm/intc ... All slapped massive debt on balance sheets,.. all tech bubble paper now in usa working class pensions is ticking nuke bomb and when this scam fraud street casino blows up next...massive riots in usa ..in 2013 buy back scams is wiping out usa working class pensions as they are the ultimate bag holders of scam bubble corporate paper via mutual fund scam criminals.............. wall street= fraud street casino and "hft' machine guns create massive fraud volume and loot billions in hours daily..............</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349296268334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:31:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349296290050-100</Id><Topic><Title>INTC investors literally being held hostage</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349295428161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:17:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is Hector Ruiz available ?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349296290050</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:31:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349296427367-101</Id><Topic><Title>INTC investors literally being held hostage</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349295428161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:17:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If he is, we would go to 50/share in a week or 2.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1349296427367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349296689683-102</Id><Topic><Title>INTC investors literally being held hostage</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349295428161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:17:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>50 cents ?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349296689683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:38:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349296777886-103</Id><Topic><Title>WOW look at HPQ drop, MAN how low is INTC going to go. HPQ problems are INTC's problems</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349294211727</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:56:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mega itemized several things happening at HPQ. The PC and server business was not identified but it would not be a surprise after what LeoA. did before he left. PC is 15% of HPQ and servers are another 15%. They were not singled out as being a problem or a bright spot. As a new CEO, Meg is cleaning the books and lowering the bar so she can easily exceed it. She is writing down the goodwill that is still on the books and is taking an $8bil charge. She says specifically that the Technology Consulting Division (EDS) is where the problems are focused. "Next year’s revenue also will decrease, although HP didn’t say by how much. The biggest problems will be concentrated in HP’s technology consulting division, where revenue is expected to fall by 11 percent to 13 percent next year. Technology consulting also faltered during the past year, prompting HP to absorb an $8 billion charge to account for the diminished value of Electronic Data Systems, which HP bought for $13 billion in 2008."</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349296777886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:39:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349297028280-104</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street's Prediction of a $7 Billion Intel Revenue Miss in Q3 Looms Large</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349274312344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:25:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right. Good point. forgot about that acquisition.</Msg><Username>equityrich</Username><Timestamp>1349297028280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:43:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349297827030-105</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street's Prediction of a $7 Billion Intel Revenue Miss in Q3 Looms Large</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349274312344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:25:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally is stupid and stubborn. It's not down 7 dollars just because of earnings and it's laughable to think they will get that 7 dollars back no matter what they report. It was overvalued at 29 and anyone that didn't sell is stuck. It is what it is.</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1349297827030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:57:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349297845783-106</Id><Title>#$%$???</Title><Msg>Was today's daily debacle due to Meg Whitman....???? Uggh. (and ugly too).</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349297845783</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349298016122-107</Id><Title>Wall Street is Starting to Drink Its Own Swill</Title><Msg>The media is swarming with reports of Intel's demise. The easiest way to tell the people without the right to an opinion is to look for the discussion on fabrication. In about 99 percent of the articles the authors don't know enough about fabrication (just like the fanbois on this board) to offer a cogent thought. Which is why it rarely gets mentioned. Without an inclusion of the fabrication topic, there is no sense in talking about the future. The future and mobility are all about fabrication. Earnings just around the corner and the end to Wall Street's fantasy and the $7 billion revenue miss they have priced into the stock...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349298016122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:00:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349298027781-108</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$???</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349297845783</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:57:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pretty much Meg's fault. Even if the PC market is dying, you might want to keep it to yourself.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349298027781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:00:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349298336574-109</Id><Title>PC shipments have stalled as people are waiting on Windows 8. Ya bunch of idiots</Title><Msg>Hopefully, you bought at 20 like me last year and no have 100% of your shares vested, collected a fat dividend all year and are in the clear when you sell higher at the lowest capital gains tax since you held a year.</Msg><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1349298336574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349298961612-110</Id><Topic><Title>PC shipments have stalled as people are waiting on Windows 8. Ya bunch of idiots</Title><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1349298336574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ooops, I mean to say "Ya bunch of idiot daytraders". Thx.</Msg><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1349298961612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:16:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349299691348-111</Id><Title>Intel’s Process Lead Will Make Strides in Mobile, Says Stifel</Title><Msg>Intel’s Process Lead Will Make Strides in Mobile, Says Stifel By Tiernan Ray Stifel Nicolaus‘s Kevin Cassidy today pounds the table for shares of Intel (INTC), which he rates a Buy, with a $33 price target, writing that the company will gain an edge in the smartphone and tablet markets as processing power becomes more important. Intel this year has announced a number of partnerships to develop smartphones based on its chips, with companies that include Google‘s (GOOG) Motorola unit. To date, however, Intel has gained little traction selling chips for either phones or tablets. Intel is up against a gaggle of chip makers, including Broadcom (BRCM), Qualcomm (QCOM), Nvidia (NVDA), all of whom license the competing chip architecture of ARM Holdings (ARMH). Cassidy opines that increasing processor demands dovetail with Intel’s ability to manufacture chips better than anyone else:</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349299691348</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:28:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349301638884-112</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt armed with Quiver full of Zingers!!</Title><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349296128764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:28:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are an IDIOT!</Msg><Username>hangmanzz</Username><Timestamp>1349301638884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:00:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349302529593-113</Id><Title>How Wall Street Prices Intel</Title><Msg>Negative Developments: 1.) News releases: Price it in. 2.) Repetition of the same news: Price it in again. And again. And again. 3.) Company revenue warnings: Price it in. Price it in again the next week. And the week after that. 4.) Analyst downgrades: Price it in. Call the trading desk and activate the canned attack program. Alert the other firms. 5.) Additional analyst downgrades: Price them in. Call the trading desk and activate the level II canned attack program. Alert the other firms that the terror threat level is being increased. 6.) Any other negative developments: Price them in, price them in, price them in. Pause and repeat. No Developments: Price in previously identified negative developments. Again. Positive Developments: 1.) Fabrication: Ignore all developments. Do not price them in. 2.) New products: Ignore all developments. Do not price them in. 3.) Smartphones: Ignore all developments. Do not price them in. 4.) Tablets: Ignore all developments. Do not price them in. 5.) R&amp; D Break-throughs: Ignore all developments. Do not price them in.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349302529593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:15:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349302614839-114</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street is Starting to Drink Its Own Swill</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349298016122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep pumping Wally, maye INTC will see 24.00 again.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349302614839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:16:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349303359893-115</Id><Title>Paul O. equates California to Greece</Title><Msg>Our "fearless" leader isnt afraid to make these outlandish statements about our economy in the WSJ, yet he doesnt have a peep to support suffering Intel shareholders by showing up on Wall Street, CNBC &amp; promote our company &amp; stock. Time to go Paul O. You've been a failure as CEO.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349303359893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:29:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349303709610-116</Id><Topic><Title>How Wall Street Prices Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349302529593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:15:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seriously who cares how/why Wall St. is doing that. We are here not because of love of Intel nor we are here to fight and prove Wall St. wrong. Most of us are here to make money. If Wall St. is holding Intel to a different standard than any other company and Intel management can't or won't change it then perhaps its time to jump the ship. I've been Intel long for 5 years and am underwater now (not counting dividend). I've been patient but for how long? How about people who owned Intel for the last 10 years and are underwater? Who's to say that Intel will not have a PE of 4.3 (like HP has now)? Is this a fair PE? - of course not! But again if management can't change this perception then why keep money invested in Intel? I feel they need a new blood. Wall St simply doesn't trust old guard. I am afraid you are right with your assessment of how Wall St prices Intel - So what? - PE can get down to 8 despite earnings growth, or worse scenario one more missed quarter - and PE is down to 5 like HP.</Msg><Username>bubbagumphere</Username><Timestamp>1349303709610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:35:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349303834982-117</Id><Title>oh boy...</Title><Msg>here we go. intel stayed strong thru HPQ's demise, now its following it down?? gimme a break.</Msg><Username>sharppolly</Username><Timestamp>1349303834982</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:37:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349305451009-118</Id><Topic><Title>How Wall Street Prices Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349302529593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:15:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel will get a bump from the WIndows 8 release. I just bought in recently, also ATML (for same reason). Long-term, I have to question some of INTC's acquisitions: McAfee, Wind River Systems ... but it does pay a good divi. But, long-term, this is not a stock I would like to hold. I'm just holding for the short-term pop.</Msg><Username>furball_80110</Username><Timestamp>1349305451009</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:04:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349306037720-119</Id><Topic><Title>How Wall Street Prices Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349302529593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:15:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, I get it - you want to make money but you don't care if Intel is valued fairly. Yeah, that makes total sense. Just not on this planet. Here's the deal - no one is going to make any money if Wall Street can arbitrarily change valuations. Or if they can use money, leverage and the media to distort valuations while they play the stock with their trading desks. What you said is equivalent to saying if you were at a casino you wouldn't care if the dice were loaded. I'll take my chances with a fair market. Wall Street makes sure that isn't the case...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349306037720</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:13:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349306149291-120</Id><Topic><Title>How Wall Street Prices Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349302529593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:15:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>McAfee brought a billion dollars a year in revenue to the company. It's been a huge success...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349306149291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:15:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349306502199-121</Id><Title>Bought 711 shares today at: $22.50</Title><Msg>Wish me luck guys! Any thoughts on where we might be headed?</Msg><Username>deep22_76</Username><Timestamp>1349306502199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:21:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349308675369-122</Id><Topic><Title>How Wall Street Prices Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349302529593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:15:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To continue with your casino comparison - If I noticed that winning number most often falls onto 1, 3, 5, 7 and 23 and never or rarely on the number I was betting on - 6, then I would be stupid to continue betting on 6 just to prove the odds. Eventually I would start betting on the winning numbers. On the other hand if I noticed that the winning number always falls onto number with the least payout by the house then I would be suspicious and would complain. It seems we have a former case where winning number consistently falls somewhere else (Apple, Goog, Amzn, PCLN), but Intel.</Msg><Username>bubbagumphere</Username><Timestamp>1349308675369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349308854091-123</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street Doubles Down on Stupid</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349290372646</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if INTC is so great, and semis are so great, why, even at the recent highs, were they still below the peaks hit in 2004 when INTC was 34.00 the SMH was 45.00 and AMAT was 26.00? only fools buy and hold as long term investments any semiconductor stock, the chips are little more than commodities dependent entirely on the success of the products they go into. Hot DVD market, ESST soars, DVD players a 29.00 price at Walmart and no more ESST. Hot pc market INTC soars, along come mobile phones and tablets, pc's tank. By the time old foggie INTC gets into mobile, who's to say that the market won't be flooded with current mobile as the latest greatest thing?</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349308854091</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349309241241-124</Id><Topic><Title>I see INTC having big inventory problems with HPQ and DELL and the other PC companies have big problems</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349288031432</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Wally, one does not need an advanced degree or tech geek knowledge to have common sense.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349309241241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349310048219-125</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Shareholders, This Is A Must Read...</Title><Username>vaughnparks181</Username><Timestamp>1349269195094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was really looking for some great news. Now I found it.</Msg><Username>espinoza.flynn43</Username><Timestamp>1349310048219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349311307094-126</Id><Topic><Title>Bought 711 shares today at: $22.50</Title><Username>deep22_76</Username><Timestamp>1349306502199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:21:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hopefully upwards with Windows 8 on the horizon. Still see INTC as the market leader in chip technology.</Msg><Username>nyscally</Username><Timestamp>1349311307094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:41:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349311309776-127</Id><Title>INTC+ MU....</Title><Msg>EQUALS HUGE LOSES FOR INTC!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>nk499</Username><Timestamp>1349311309776</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:41:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349311801054-128</Id><Topic><Title>Intel’s Process Lead Will Make Strides in Mobile, Says Stifel</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349299691348</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Alex. There's a reason Intel absolutely DOMINATES difficult to make, top of the line server chips........ Mobile is coming.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1349311801054</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349312393425-129</Id><Topic><Title>RED ALERT IN USA : NEW BANKING CARTEL FINANCIAL TERRORISTS FRAUD ON USA TAX PAYERS: VISIT MAX KEISER WEB SITE AND LISTEN</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349222729750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 20:05:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SO CALLED BLUE CHIPS OF USA ARE NOW DEBT LOADED AND WHY? WHERE DID THE CASH GO? BUY BACK SCAMS TO ENRICH INSIDERS AND WALL STREET BANKSTERS By singhlion2001 . Oct 3, 2012 4:31 PM . Permalink So called blue chips of usa are now debt loaded and why? Where did the cash go? Buy back scams to enrich insiders and wall street banksters usa is a failed state: americans are history without revolution; read on dr. Paul craig roberts usa hijacked by home grown financial al qaeda led by bankster terrorists high treason criminal rulers in their pockets........... hpq/dell/ibm/intc ... All slapped massive debt on balance sheets,.. all tech bubble paper now in usa working class pensions is ticking nuke bomb and when this scam fraud street casino blows up next...massive riots in usa ..in 2013 buy back scams is wiping out usa working class pensions as they are the ultimate bag holders of scam bubble corporate paper via mutual fund scam criminals.............. wall street= fraud street casino and "hft' machine guns create massive fraud volume and loot billions in hours daily..............</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349312393425</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:59:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349312432216-130</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL BE SINGLE DIGIT STOCK IN 2013:THIS IS THE REAL PROBLEM FOR INTEL NEXT $30 SoC or $250 CPU?</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1348796337780</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:38:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SO CALLED BLUE CHIPS OF USA ARE NOW DEBT LOADED AND WHY? WHERE DID THE CASH GO? BUY BACK SCAMS TO ENRICH INSIDERS AND WALL STREET BANKSTERS By singhlion2001 . Oct 3, 2012 4:31 PM . Permalink So called blue chips of usa are now debt loaded and why? Where did the cash go? Buy back scams to enrich insiders and wall street banksters usa is a failed state: americans are history without revolution; read on dr. Paul craig roberts usa hijacked by home grown financial al qaeda led by bankster terrorists high treason criminal rulers in their pockets........... hpq/dell/ibm/intc ... All slapped massive debt on balance sheets,.. all tech bubble paper now in usa working class pensions is ticking nuke bomb and when this scam fraud street casino blows up next...massive riots in usa ..in 2013 buy back scams is wiping out usa working class pensions as they are the ultimate bag holders of scam bubble corporate paper via mutual fund scam criminals.............. wall street= fraud street casino and "hft' machine guns create massive fraud volume and loot billions in hours daily..............</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349312432216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:00:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349312591975-131</Id><Topic><Title>Bought 711 shares today at: $22.50</Title><Username>deep22_76</Username><Timestamp>1349306502199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:21:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do suspect you get a bounce, the pc may be dying, but's it's not dead just yet.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1349312591975</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349312705268-132</Id><Topic><Title>Bought 711 shares today at: $22.50</Title><Username>deep22_76</Username><Timestamp>1349306502199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:21:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't listen to wdblawgrow, buddy. He bought at 19.58 last year, sold at 19.78, paid maximum taxes on a 20 cent gain and then watched Intel rise almost 50 percent.........LOL! He'd try to talk his mom out of her last meal.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1349312705268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:05:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349313821769-133</Id><Topic><Title>How Wall Street Prices Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349302529593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:15:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just did not understand the combination ... it is like "Intel Group" now, with a chips division, an antivirus division, a whatever-you-call-WRS division, etc. I know that Intel left WRS (Wind River Systems) to run their own show, so my take is that is a loosely-managed acquisition. I would assume the same is true for McAfee, but I don't know for sure. What you have is a company that specializes in making chips diversifying into software WITHOUT ANY UNIFYING PLAN. Sure, they have lots of money to throw at these acquisitions, but do they really understand it? I think they don't ... perhaps the bean counters do, but that's why they left WRS management intact and didn't want to interfere in the direction of that company. Because they had no real plan for the acquisition, other than IT IS SOFTWARE and EMBEDDED LINUX. What was the justification for the McAfee acquisition? Probably IT IS SECURITY. JEEZ.</Msg><Username>furball_80110</Username><Timestamp>1349313821769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:23:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349314190149-134</Id><Topic><Title>How Wall Street Prices Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349302529593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:15:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who knows ... perhaps INTC had a big angel investor (fund) that told them to make those acquisitions. That would explain why they seem to come from the Warren Buffett universe (i.e. a "knowledgeable" old-school investor, who probably doesn't really understand the technical details of Intel's products), rather than being something that really fits their existing business. Anyways ... I found it baffling enough that I want to stay away from this cash machine, except for this short-term Windows 8 opportunity.</Msg><Username>furball_80110</Username><Timestamp>1349314190149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:29:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349314196248-135</Id><Topic><Title>Intel’s Process Lead Will Make Strides in Mobile, Says Stifel</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349299691348</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lots of cash. Very strong dividen. It is why I bought shares to go with my calls. Lets see what earnings brings.</Msg><Username>verioinc</Username><Timestamp>1349314196248</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:29:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349314225507-136</Id><Title>HaHa, Obama getting his tail KICKED</Title><Msg>He can't point to one good thing he's accomplished and is just standing there making stuff up to try and make Romney look bad. Can't wait to he pulls out he "I killed Bin Laden!" card.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349314225507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349314287157-137</Id><Topic><Title>How Wall Street Prices Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349302529593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:15:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DEFINITELY, I want to make money. That's all investing is about. Do you know what a "value trap" is? Follow the money. Buy in the shadow of the big funds buying (or anticipate the news that will cause them to begin buying, as in the pop from Windows 8 release).</Msg><Username>furball_80110</Username><Timestamp>1349314287157</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:31:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349314482230-138</Id><Title>Go ROMNEY! Landslide coming baby! No increase in Dividend taxes either !</Title><Msg>ROMNEY and RYAN boys !!!!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349314482230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:34:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349314787243-139</Id><Title>INTC Is Not Bouncing off an oversold condition....................</Title><Msg>It should have made a decent bounce off the low 23 area, that didn't happen. It appears it's doing the same thing it did a point higher. Look for a bounce off the 21 area, it that doesn't happen , then 19, and if not that, then just forget it, because the stock will be way out of favour if the market is still up. INTC's relative performance to the S&amp;P is very bad, So Institutions will be dumping INTC into the end of the year, unless the market corrects.</Msg><Username>stoptheinsanity2000</Username><Timestamp>1349314787243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:39:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349315046562-140</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Shareholders, This Is A Must Read...</Title><Username>vaughnparks181</Username><Timestamp>1349269195094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I followed your reports since last week. Nice work.</Msg><Username>nash.summers56</Username><Timestamp>1349315046562</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349315173603-141</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Is Not Bouncing off an oversold condition....................</Title><Username>stoptheinsanity2000</Username><Timestamp>1349314787243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:39:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's happening with Intel happens with every single stock that warns......it aint goin anywhere until we here from them on the earnings call.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1349315173603</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:46:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349315499549-142</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Is Not Bouncing off an oversold condition....................</Title><Username>stoptheinsanity2000</Username><Timestamp>1349314787243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:39:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still a solid bet with decent div. Good article on Seeking Alpha - http://seekingalpha.com/article/902051-intel-is-a-solid-pick-worth-over-35</Msg><Username>nyscally</Username><Timestamp>1349315499549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:51:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349315787352-143</Id><Topic><Title>Go ROMNEY! Landslide coming baby! No increase in Dividend taxes either !</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349314482230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama looks weak/ has had four years to fix the country and totally failed. Another 4 years of this wimp will kill the country.</Msg><Username>sanjitkumar23</Username><Timestamp>1349315787352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:56:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349316224255-144</Id><Topic><Title>I see INTC having big inventory problems with HPQ and DELL and the other PC companies have big problems</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1349288031432</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Poor Wally, one does not need an advanced degree or tech geek knowledge to have common sense." And Wally's pretense of being a tech geek hasn't prevented him from backing a losing stock for years and years. In fact, wasn't he all over this dead money at $24+ back in the spring of 2010? And didn't he insist that those who paid $24+ would "look just fine" in six months? Well, not only did that happen, but when those buyers finally had a small profit (in one of the biggest stock market rallies of all time), Wally continued to beat the drum at the highs rather than suggest that anyone should sell the highs, and lo and behold, here they are back under water after 2 1/2 years. Way to go, Wallus!</Msg><Username>myle_der_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1349316224255</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:03:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349317051740-145</Id><Title>Obama looking like the piece of garbage</Title><Msg>We know he is...Stutter much???? NOT QUALIFIED</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349317051740</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:17:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349317229450-146</Id><Title>Twitter showing Romney winning big. LOL!</Title><Msg>bangbangbang!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349317229450</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349317624832-147</Id><Title>Cliff notes didn't work for NObama tonight. LOL!</Title><Msg>Lazy bum.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349317624832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:27:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349317703880-148</Id><Title>Top shelf booze for Michelle Obama?</Title><Msg>She'll have to get it on her own dime a month from now. See ya !!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349317703880</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:28:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349317808788-149</Id><Topic><Title>no power</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349278084553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:28:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I told you so! I will be a millionaire!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1349317808788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:30:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349318132025-150</Id><Title>Looks like a Republican clean sweep in Nov.</Title><Msg>We will own all 3 branches..as it should be. The U.S. represents capitalism, not socialism, Mr. Obama. You learned that hard lesson tonite.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349318132025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:35:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349318202567-151</Id><Title>Obama performed worse than Lucy tonite</Title><Msg>Thats saying a lot.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349318202567</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:36:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349318616192-152</Id><Topic><Title>Paul O. equates California to Greece</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349303359893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>California has been governed by a Republican for years. INTC moved everything out of California fifteen years ago. What is your point.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349318616192</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:43:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349318927672-153</Id><Title>Romney Looked Like Nixon Against Kennedy</Title><Msg>Wow, Mitt looked seriously nervous and uncomfortable tonite. Like in the Kennedy-Nixon debate: Don said that in the end, Kennedy triumphed due to appearances: Kennedy, "looking tan and fit...this guy was a matinee idol," vs. Nixon looking "like death warmed over," sweating and in pain, and pale from a recent hospitalization. Yep, Obama looked very tan. And Mitt looked like he would need hospitalization by the time it was over. Jim Lehrer and Obama had a few nice moments smiling at each other as neither was able to get Mitt to stop talking when his time was up. Obama looked calm and relaxed and presidential. An easy win on style. Oh, and Mitt said he wasn't giving the rich any $5 trillion tax cuts. So, I guess you fat cats backed him for nothing. D'oh...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349318927672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:48:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349319179613-154</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Shareholders, This Is A Must Read...</Title><Username>vaughnparks181</Username><Timestamp>1349269195094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I read your comments with interest - thanks for continuing to post.</Msg><Username>atkinsw85</Username><Timestamp>1349319179613</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:52:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349319207211-155</Id><Topic><Title>Paul O. equates California to Greece</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349303359893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are 5,000 employees in Santa Clara. There are 7,500 employees in Folsom. Those are the headcount totals have been in place for many years, like you suggest. But not zero but a total of 12,500.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349319207211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:53:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349319464389-156</Id><Title>white vs black</Title><Msg>that's what it comes down to</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1349319464389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:57:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349320416875-157</Id><Title>MEDIA SHILLS INFLUENCE USA ZOMBIES...........LOL WHY GREEN PARTY CANDIDATE NOT ALLOWED TO DEBATE?</Title><Msg>MEDIA SHILLS INFLUENCE USA ZOMBIES...........LOL WHY GREEN PARTY CANDIDATE NOT ALLOWED TO DEBATE? BOTH $UCKERS ...AMERICANS HAVE NO CHOICE Truth Has Fallen and Taken Liberty With It by PAUL CRAIG ROBERTS There was a time when the pen was mightier than the sword. That was a time when people believed in truth and regarded truth as an independent power and not as an auxiliary for government, class, race, ideological, personal, or financial interest. Today Americans are ruled by propaganda. Americans have little regard for truth, little access to it, and little ability to recognize it. Truth is an unwelcome entity. It is disturbing. It is off limits. Those who speak it run the risk of being branded “anti-American,” “anti-semite” or “conspiracy theorist.” Truth is an inconvenience for government and for the interest groups whose campaign contributions control government. Truth is an inconvenience for prosecutors who want convictions, not the discovery of innocence or guilt. Truth is inconvenient for ideologues. Today many whose goal once was the discovery of truth are now paid handsomely to hide it. “Free market economists” are paid to sell offshoring to the American people. High-productivity, high value-added American jobs are denigrated as dirty, old industrial jobs. Relicts from long ago, we are best shed of them. Their place has been taken by “the New Economy,” a mythical economy that allegedly consists of high-tech white collar jobs in which Americans innovate and finance activities that occur offshore. All Americans need in order to participate in this “new economy” are finance degrees from Ivy League universities, and then they will work on Wall Street at million dollar jobs. --------- Usa empire collapses next fraud street casino bankster hijacked USA enterprise Americans are history without revolution: Dr. Paul Craig Roberts silicon valley will destroy California ..like auto industry destroyed Michigan Google SEARCH: RED ALERT IN USA BANKERS GONE WILD - HOW THE US GOVERNMENT HELPED WALL STREET GANG-RAPE AMERICA'S MIDDLE CLASS</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349320416875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:13:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349320695909-158</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Looked Like Nixon Against Kennedy</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349318927672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:48:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hahahahahaha! Wallisweaver, wrong on Intel and now claims Romney was the one uncomfortable when Obama couldn't even look him in the eye!...and MILLIONS on twitter agree.....with ME, nobody agrees with Wallytwit..... This is going to be SOOOOO much fun watching these lazy Liberal clowns have to find a job.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349320695909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:18:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349320840058-159</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Looked Like Nixon Against Kennedy</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349318927672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:48:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PBS LOVES Obama and even THEY admitted he got his tail kicked tonight. LOL!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349320840058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:20:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349321019758-160</Id><Title>Futures up HUGE! Business will hire again under Romney and............</Title><Msg>Investors will invest, knowing they aren't gonna have their stock gains practically taken away by the government. What idiot other than sick Wally would vote for Obama? Idiot Wally just wants more QE. Where has THAT gotten Intel????</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349321019758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349321466529-161</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Is Not Bouncing off an oversold condition....................</Title><Username>stoptheinsanity2000</Username><Timestamp>1349314787243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:39:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think the conference call will be enough to turn the stock around. Generally, when a company warns so early, the situation is not good. On the call, you can expect some very tough questions. The stock is now a relative performance loser, you've got to accept this year is finished for the stock. It could be a buy in late December for a nice move into the beginning of next year, but the overall market seems strange. Usually when semis are having trouble, it's a tell on the overall health of the market, but Apple may be changing the rules or at least blurring them.</Msg><Username>stoptheinsanity2000</Username><Timestamp>1349321466529</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:31:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349321575933-162</Id><Title>Three years of bad news for INTC</Title><Msg>After the election anyone with a brain can see that govenment spending at all levels will get sacked BIG TIME. There is no possible way INTC can avoid being sucked into the recession and fell the same pain as all the other bleeding edge tech companies. The social media companies are really the only growth game now. In seven years, they'll be dying out to some other new tech phase. Face INTC alumni, you had your time in the sun, but now that sun is setting on your chips, and soon the only people getting rich off of INTC will be your greedy, stupid management and a lot of shorts who already figured it out. have a bad earnings report marco :</Msg><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1349321575933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:32:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349321636815-163</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like a Republican clean sweep in Nov.</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349318132025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:35:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney is our new president. Business environment will be better. Intel will benefit.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1349321636815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349322010088-164</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Is Not Bouncing off an oversold condition....................</Title><Username>stoptheinsanity2000</Username><Timestamp>1349314787243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:39:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stocks always look good before a storm. The guy writing the article is likely very long and must have not seen the earnings warning coming. Can we really assume anything else? Absolutely Not! We must assume Intel's' earnings growth has peaked and the same goes for the dividend, This condition may not last long or define a negative trend for the company, but look what Apple is doing to it's competition, Hewlett and Dell are at 9 and 14 bucks per share while the S&amp;P500 is at multi-year highs.</Msg><Username>stoptheinsanity2000</Username><Timestamp>1349322010088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:40:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349322349014-165</Id><Topic><Title>Futures up HUGE! Business will hire again under Romney and............</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349321019758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:23:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No matter what they tell you, all the women in your family will vote for Obama. If I agree to vote for Romney, will you stop spamming the board?</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1349322349014</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:45:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349323029195-166</Id><Topic><Title>Futures up HUGE! Business will hire again under Romney and............</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349321019758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:23:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet WW is grouchy tonight. Reagan was an actor, Romney is a businessman so Obama is up against a guy with more gov't experience, more business experience, seems like a higher IQ, I was shcoked. Obama looked like a deer caught in the headlights tonight.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349323029195</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:57:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349323080005-167</Id><Topic><Title>Futures up HUGE! Business will hire again under Romney and............</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349321019758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:23:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>att4, don't be so quick, that 47% still want their handouts but tonight was very telling that's for sure.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349323080005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:58:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349323158669-168</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like a Republican clean sweep in Nov.</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349318132025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:35:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>huh? not a ww alias? ww would NEVER say that.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1349323158669</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:59:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>