<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351572374761-1</Id><Topic><Title>Young Women Voting Early Coast to Coast for Mitt Romney</Title><Username>political_gangsters</Username><Timestamp>1351120370532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:12:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am gettingcareless</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351572374761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351572389895-2</Id><Topic><Title>Young Women Voting Early Coast to Coast for Mitt Romney</Title><Username>political_gangsters</Username><Timestamp>1351120370532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:12:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they did the 1st time, will they a 2nd time? Cramer will.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351572389895</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:46:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351576191641-3</Id><Topic><Title>W8 Reviews - What They Don't Say</Title><Username>publicservice100</Username><Timestamp>1351376841744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 18:27:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am still use Office 2003. A great suite of productive office programs. However, MSFT has been ramming 2010 Office down our throats. At least we can download a compatibility package to read 2007 and 2010 files. Now they're going to ram Windows 8 down our throats. I'll still use a mouse. I don't want to get my monitor dirty while I eat and work.</Msg><Username>stok1mom</Username><Timestamp>1351576191641</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 01:49:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351590885743-4</Id><Title>Exynos 5 Dual handily beats Apple’s A6 chip, Intel’s Atom Z2460</Title><Msg>Exynos 5 Dual benchmark scores Tofel ran several benchmark suites on the new ARM Chromebook. Here are the benchmarks and the scores: SunSpider: 668.5ms (lower is better) V8: 3871 (higher is better) Octane: 3465 (higher is better) Now that we have these scores, let’s compare them to the main competitors of the Exynos 5 Dual chip: the A6 chip in the iPhone 5 and the Atom Z2460 in the Motorola Razr i. Exynos 5 Dual (Samsung Chromebook) Apple A6 (Apple iPhone 5) Intel Atom Z2460 (Motorola Razr i) Snapdragon S4 (HTC One X) Tegra 3 (HTC One X) SunSpider 668.5 908 1086.6 1608 1737.7 V8 3871 1533 2209 1507 1162 Octane 3465 1672 2048 1280 1131 * The benchmark scores listed above are courtesy of AnandTech. As you can see, Samsung’s latest chip handily beats the previous leaders, with the difference being especially visible in the SunSpider test. For some perspective, consider that the iPhone 5 is the first device to complete SunSpider in less than 1000ms. At 668.5, the new Exynos just smashes that record. SunSpider, V8, and Octane are all JavaScript tests, so results may vary when using other benchmark suites. Still, it’s impressive to see what Samsung was able to achieve, and we are looking forward to see what the Exynos 5 Dual can do in next year’s Samsung Galaxy S4 and Galaxy Note 3.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351590885743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:54:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351594024673-5</Id><Topic><Title>Exynos 5 Dual handily beats Apple’s A6 chip, Intel’s Atom Z2460</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351590885743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple A6, Exynos if we face-off. 1.3 to 1.7 clock speed difference. My guess would be gate count is pretty even. The big difference seems to be memory bandwidth. At such a high system clock processor spins -- through good memory it stays fed for a speed boost. Apple's A6 targets the iPhone 5. The Exynos does not have a phone target. I would venture it's more a tablet part. Higher clock speed, more power, big device.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1351594024673</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 06:47:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351601593313-6</Id><Title>Motorola Razr Maxx and Razr Maxx HD</Title><Msg>Both are good phones, but their cameras suck. Just wait til next year when the first U.S. based Intel Motorola phones are launched. Bet you over time all Motorola phones have Intel inside..........and good cameras. Cameras are CRUCIAL to consumers wheh selecting a Smartphone. Generally speaking, with moderate use, smartphones can give you a full day's performance before needing to be recharged, but not all gadgets are created equal - some simply run out of steam early, whereas others will hang in there for the long haul. We've rounded up several smartphones with battery life that really impressed us. Motorola Droid Razr Maxx HD (Verizon) Cnet rating: 4 out of 5 stars The good: The Droid Razr Maxx HD (Verizon) offers fast performance, a big, impressive screen and luxurious design. It also has great call quality, lots of storage, 4G data speeds and unbeatable battery life. The bad: The major weakness is a camera that produces subpar images. The phone is filled with Verizon bloatware as well. The price: $200 to $702 The bottom line: Motorola's fast, stylish Droid Razr Maxx HD offers outstanding battery life, but its camera captures unimpressive images. Motorola Droid Razr HD (Verizon) Cnet rating: 4 out of 5 stars The good: The Droid Razr HD offers fast performance, a big, impressive screen and luxurious design. It also has great call quality and satisfying 4G speeds. The bad: The Achilles' heel is a camera that produces subpar images. The phone is loaded with Verizon bloatware, too. The cost: $150 to $200 The bottom line: Motorola's lovely new Droid Razr HD is fast and thin, but its weak camera should make mobile shutterbugs wary.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351601593313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 08:53:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351602096456-7</Id><Title>Intel working on 48 core chip for phones/tablets while ARMH tries to build a server LOL!</Title><Msg>Intel working on 48-core chip for smartphones, tablets A smartphone with 48 cores could change our concept of what it is and what it does By Sharon Gaudin October 30, 2012 06:00 AM ET Add a comment. .Computerworld - Intel researchers are working on a 48-core processor for smartphones and tablets, but it could be five to 10 years before it hits the market. "If we're going to have this technology in five to 10 years, we could finally do things that take way too much processing power today," said Patrick Moorhead, an analyst with Moor Insights and Strategy. "This could really open up our concept of what is a computer... The phone would be smart enough to not just be a computer but it could be my computer." Enric Herrero, a research scientist at Intel Labs in Barcelona, said so far the lab has built a prototype of a 48-core chip designed to run different apps on different cores on a smartphone or tablet. Today, some small mobile devices use multi-core chips. However, those multi-cores might be dual- or quad-core CPUs working with a few GPUs. Having a 48-core chip in a small mobile device would open up a whole new world of possibilities. Emerging tech Intel working on 48-core chip for smartphones, tablets Intel readies for programmable smart cars Autonomous cars will arrive within 10 years, Intel CTO says NASA's Curiosity makes first drive at Bradbury Landing 'Talking' smart cars begin year-long test aimed at accident reduction Harvard stores 70 billion books using DNA IBM claims spintronics memory breakthrough Watch out Google: Apple gets patent for wearable device Google Glass launches new age of personal computing NASA shoots for riskier Mars rover landing More: Emerging Tech page At this point, researchers are working to see how to best use so many cores for one device. "Typically a processor with one core would do jobs one after another," Herrero told Computerworld. "With multiple cores, they can divide the work among them." He explained that with many cores, someone could, for instance, be encrypting an email while also working on other power-intensive apps at the same time. It could be done today, but the operations might drag because they'd have to share resources. Tanausu Ramirez, another Intel research scientist working on the 48-core chip, said that if someone was, for example, watching a high-definition video, a 48-core chip would be able to use different cores to decode different video frames at the same time, giving the user a more seamless video experience. Ramirez also said that instead of one core working at near top capacity and using a lot of energy, many cores could run in parallel on different projects and use less energy. "The chip also can take the energy and split it up and distribute it between different applications," he added. Justin Rattner, Intel's CTO, told Computerworld that a 48-core chip for small mobile devices could hit the market "much sooner" than the researchers' 10-year prediction. "I think the desire to move to more natural interfaces to make the interaction much more human-like is really going to drive the computational requirements," he said. "Having large numbers of cores to generate very high performance levels is the most energy efficient way to deliver those performance levels." Rattner said functions such as speech recognition and augmented reality will push the need for more computational power. "If it's doing speech recognition or computer vision... that's very computational intensive," he added. "It's just not practical to just take sound and pictures and send it up to the cloud and expect that some server is going to perform those tasks. So a lot of that will be pushed out to the client devices." Rob Enderle, an analyst with the Enderle Group, said being able to have different device functions, as well as apps all running on their own cores would be a great advance.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351602096456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:01:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351602201275-8</Id><Title>Intel shows off first 20nm Flash Solid State Drive</Title><Msg>Intel debuts its first 20-nanometer flash solid-state drive Summary: Intel shows off its 20-nanometer NAND flash memory in the new SSD 335. While the SSD 335 uses the smallest and most efficient MLC NAND flash memory on the market today, it is functionally identical to its predecessor. By Adrian Kingsley-Hughes for Hardware 2.0 | October 30, 2012 -- 10:52 GMT (03:52 PDT) Intel will today ship its first solid-state drive -- the SSD 335 -- featuring 20-nanometer NAND flash memory. The new drive stores 240GB in total and offers 500MB/s read speeds and 450MB/s write speeds via the SATA 6Gbps interface. The drive is a 2.5-inch model and is 9.5mm thick, but the retail kit contains all the fittings you need to fit this into a 3.5-inch drive bay. The drive is also backed by Intel's 3-year warranty. "The Intel SSD 335 uses Hi-K/metal gate planar cell technology, which overcomes NAND process scaling constraints to deliver the smallest-area NAND cell and die in the industry," said Rob Crooke, Intel vice president and general manager for the Intel Non-Volatile Memory (NVM) Solutions Group. "By pushing technology constraints and using process innovation, Intel can continue to progress SSD technology and pass along savings to our customers." The SSD 335 uses the smallest and most efficient MLC NAND flash memory on the market today. Intel's earlier SSDs, such as the SSD 330, made use of 25-nanometer, and apart from the architecture shrink, the new SSD 335 is essentially identical to the SSD 330. The only exception being that the SSD 330 came in 60GB, 120GB, 180GB, and 240GB capacities. Rather than breaking new ground here, Intel seems to be simply using the SSD 335 to showcase the shrink to 20-nanometers. This technology is likely to lead to increased storage densities in the future, but for now Intel is playing it safe and sticking to 240GB as the ceiling. You can grab the new drive for around $200 from all usual, good retailers.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351602201275</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351602291145-9</Id><Topic><Title>Intel working on 48 core chip for phones/tablets while ARMH tries to build a server LOL!</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351602096456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:01:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is it... ?? How will it compare to competitors products when it's released years from now...?? Or you have NO CLUE...NONE !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351602291145</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:04:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351602434481-10</Id><Topic><Title>Intel working on 48 core chip for phones/tablets while ARMH tries to build a server LOL!</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351602096456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:01:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look how TERRIFIED and PO'd Getanid 61 is that his show keeps getting stolen by Intel. LOL! He replied IMMEDIATELY and is SEETHING. LOL! The #$%$s tiny little company is parterning with a dying AMD and he's all excited about it. DESPERATE LOSER. Justin Rattner, Intel's CTO, told Computerworld that a 48-core chip for small mobile devices could hit the market "much sooner" than the researchers' 10-year prediction.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351602434481</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:07:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351602539915-11</Id><Topic><Title>Intel working on 48 core chip for phones/tablets while ARMH tries to build a server LOL!</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351602096456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:01:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got it... you have NO CLUE... NONE !!!! but good to know it's sooner than 10 yrs...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351602539915</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:08:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351602547036-12</Id><Topic><Title>Intel working on 48 core chip for phones/tablets while ARMH tries to build a server LOL!</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351602096456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:01:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is ARMH's 54 bit Sever? How will it compare to competitors products when it's released years from now...?? Or you have NO CLUE...NONE !!!!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351602547036</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351602838869-13</Id><Topic><Title>Intel working on 48 core chip for phones/tablets while ARMH tries to build a server LOL!</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351602096456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:01:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see... post a thread on INtel 48 core... can't answer... so dodge and bash ARMH... good luck with your 48 core... let us know when it comes out in 10 yrs...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351602838869</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:13:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351603833212-14</Id><Topic><Title>Intel working on 48 core chip for phones/tablets while ARMH tries to build a server LOL!</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351602096456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:01:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see... post a thread on ARM 64 bit... can't answer... so dodge and bash Intel... good luck with your 64 bit...... let us know when it comes out, if it ever does. HP laughed at it.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351603833212</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:30:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351603945403-15</Id><Title>Hey Getanid61</Title><Msg>You got alot of ego, pal. Posting an ARMH vs Intel stock chart on the Intel board isn't taunting Intel? I mean, you come to the INTEL board to chastise Intel longs and they aren't allowed to defend theirselves on their board??? You are a bully, and bullies are really just scared little cowards when punched in the face. Enjoy that Nvidia you bought at 18.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351603945403</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:32:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351604377611-16</Id><Topic><Title>Intel working on 48 core chip for phones/tablets while ARMH tries to build a server LOL!</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351602096456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:01:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've run out of anything to say, so you have to repeat my comments... "good luck with your 64 bit...... let us know when it comes out," you've already posted the answer in many threads... but you've just run out of things to say...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351604377611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:39:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351604863426-17</Id><Topic><Title>Exynos 5 Dual handily beats Apple’s A6 chip, Intel’s Atom Z2460</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351590885743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple A6, Exynos if we face-off. 1.3 to 1.7 clock speed difference. My guess would be gate count is pretty even. The big difference seems to be memory bandwidth. At such a high system clock processor spins -- through good memory it stays fed for a speed boost. Apple's A6 targets the iPhone 5. The Exynos does not have a phone target. I would venture it's more a tablet part. Higher clock speed, more power, big device. ----- The A15 is slatted to go onto phones, but as you hint at there could be issues in regards to power/die size. This chip is also in googles new tablet, the nexus 10, so we should see more information on performance/battery use over the next few days.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351604863426</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:47:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351604966925-18</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Getanid61</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351603945403</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:32:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You got alot of ego, pal. Posting an ARMH vs Intel stock chart on the Intel board isn't taunting Intel? I mean, you come to the INTEL board to chastise Intel longs and they aren't allowed to defend theirselves on their board??? " I only do it for one reason: The naive are convinced it's all about fabs...just exposing it ain't so But yeah, I shouldn't be so combative... With your id, I will back off cause I realize now you're not wallis, duhboys, mystk, getanidxx, etc... it's just one poster that's obsessed with me... My ignore list is pages long for just one poster... yet he keeps inventing ids to get thru to me... just to throw out falsehoods "Enjoy that Nvidia you bought at 18." Now you see, you guys just throw that stuff out that you know ain't true... NVDA long from 4 splits ago INTC long from the 13s peace</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351604966925</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:49:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351606481527-19</Id><Title>Selling options was a perfect strategy before the Hurricane</Title><Msg>Got 2 days "free" &amp; will sell tomorrow at the open for a mint (if the market opens). Rumour is the market may be closed all week!</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351606481527</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:14:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351607704819-20</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Getanid61</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351603945403</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:32:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel from 13, LOL. Funny how that works on an anonymous message board where it can't be proved. Long Intel EXACTLY from the bottom! Amazing! Obsessed with you? Get over yourself, chump. You're an ARMH homer on the Intel board and it's not gonna fly.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351607704819</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351607881859-21</Id><Topic><Title>Intel shows off first 20nm Flash Solid State Drive</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351602201275</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:03:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel's 330 SSDs are already impressive drives for the money offering consistent performance and great reliability. The 335s will be even better.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1351607881859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:38:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351607884573-22</Id><Topic><Title>Intel working on 48 core chip for phones/tablets while ARMH tries to build a server LOL!</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351602096456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:01:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VMware Boss Puts Brakes on ARM Server Revolution By Cade MetzEmail Author08.30.123:08 PM</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351607884573</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:38:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351609867858-23</Id><Title>Looks just like the 1937 recession are you ready for the big drop, it's coming</Title><Msg>Looks just like the 1937 recession are you ready for the big drop, it's coming</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351609867858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:11:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351609883131-24</Id><Topic><Title>W8 Reviews - What They Don't Say</Title><Username>publicservice100</Username><Timestamp>1351376841744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 18:27:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As I said before Microsoft wanted it's turn to fail with ARM. Windows 8 is a culmination of previously failed ARM based Windows ideas that Microsoft has a 15 year track record with. When you compare Windows 8 to Windows CE yes it's better. When you compare it to Android and iOS, RT really sucks. Microsoft saw movement with iOS products and then Android and felt that Intel was holding them back. Now here's the big question. What will do better in the future, Windows RT or Intel in Android phones?</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1351609883131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:11:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351609954858-25</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 Commercials everywhere</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1351220615714</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 23:03:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So let's see... With this 20k shares you say you just bought that would add to all your other boasts of bought 20k here and 25k there amounting to somewhere in the vicinity of 100k-125k shares purchased over the last 1-2 years. #$%$! Who are you, some pimple faced 15 yo geek getting his jollies on a high school library computer during study hall? Your posts are pathetic, but then maybe they are so bad because of something that Paul Otellini either did or didn't say or do !</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1351609954858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:12:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351612767516-26</Id><Topic><Title>Intel working on 48 core chip for phones/tablets while ARMH tries to build a server LOL!</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351602096456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:01:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My little brother, getanid61, scurried away in a hurray after this article was posted. ARM is spending what little money it has to chase a dream while Intel is developing 48 core SmartComputer phones. LOL! This article is just more evidence that future Intel Server Technology will dance circles around anything ARM could even dream of coming up with.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351612767516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:59:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351614556177-27</Id><Title>ARM unveils 64-bit designs for future smartphones, servers</Title><Msg>I'm long intel and i don't like this headline. comments please</Msg><Username>varlabania</Username><Timestamp>1351614556177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:29:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351614778130-28</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Getanid61</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351603945403</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:32:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"ntel from 13, LOL" At the time kicked myself for not buying at 9 "Get over yourself, chump." apparently it's yourself who's not over this chump... "You're an ARMH homer on the Intel board and it's not gonna fly." Have you noticed the charts for ARMH &amp; INTC... or is your head still in the sand...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351614778130</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:32:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351614904225-29</Id><Topic><Title>ARM unveils 64-bit designs for future smartphones, servers</Title><Username>varlabania</Username><Timestamp>1351614556177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not to worry, INtel announced they are working a 48 core product that will be here in 10 yrs... LMAO !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351614904225</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351615338992-30</Id><Topic><Title>ARM unveils 64-bit designs for future smartphones, servers</Title><Username>varlabania</Username><Timestamp>1351614556177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In Getanid61's dreamworld, vendors everywhere are gonna toss Intel out the door and go with ARM, even as ARMH has no way to ensure said vendors that they won't have any issues with Manufacturing and even as Intel is mapping out the future with said clients to include 48 core chips. Intel is in it with its customers for the long haul, ARMH wants data center hiring managers to risk their jobs by tossing Intel out and bringing ARMH in. LOL!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351615338992</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:42:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351615744966-31</Id><Topic><Title>ARM unveils 64-bit designs for future smartphones, servers</Title><Username>varlabania</Username><Timestamp>1351614556177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"In Getanid61's dreamworld," Microsoft is porting to ARM... Apple developing ARM chips and will eventually cut out INtel altogether... ARM getting into servers with 64-bit.. who's dreaming... "ARMH has no way to ensure said vendors that they won't have any issues with Manufacturing" Oh man, are you another Wallis id... no one else posts the nonsense... "Intel is mapping out the future with said clients to include 48 core chips" OH MY, said clients are holding their breadth for INTel products 10 yrs from now...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351615744966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351616100768-32</Id><Topic><Title>ARM unveils 64-bit designs for future smartphones, servers</Title><Username>varlabania</Username><Timestamp>1351614556177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Getanid61 claims he's long Intel from 13 yet spends every waking hour trying to scare Intel holders out of their shares. He's an honest decent little ARMH Techy Homer! He'd NEVER tell a lie!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351616100768</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:55:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351616251915-33</Id><Topic><Title>ARM unveils 64-bit designs for future smartphones, servers</Title><Username>varlabania</Username><Timestamp>1351614556177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple developing ARM chips and will eventually cut out INtel altogether... _________________________ Where's your proof? Or you have no clue, none. You're a putz bro. No wonder I'm the only one here that hasn't put your lies and rhetoric on ignore. No need to worry about losers I can't control, so adios. Apple even laughs at you.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351616251915</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351617962604-34</Id><Topic><Title>ARM unveils 64-bit designs for future smartphones, servers</Title><Username>varlabania</Username><Timestamp>1351614556177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Getanid61 claims he's long Intel from 13" Yes, and I've been right. " yet spends every waking hour trying to scare Intel holders out of their shares. " The rest is just having fun exposing that guys like you have NO understanding of how this industry works... You constantly blast ARMH, but are oblivious to ARMH vs INTC Anyone who reads this can check the charts for their own verification of your stock picking... but hey... keep the faith</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351617962604</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:26:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351618244824-35</Id><Topic><Title>ARM unveils 64-bit designs for future smartphones, servers</Title><Username>varlabania</Username><Timestamp>1351614556177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As always, the devil is in the detail. More detail: --- ARM launches 64bit processors David Manners Tuesday 30 October 2012 16:20 Today, ARM announced the first two parts in its 64bit processor family today – the A-53 and A-57. "The A-57 delivers three times the performance of today’s mobile phones with the same power budget and the A-53 delivers four times the power efficiency of today’s mobile phones," says Noel Hurley, vp of ARM’s processor division. Silicon is expected in 2013/14 with devices out in 2014/15, says Hurley. "It’s been a rare opportunity to start with a clean sheet of paper to develop a new architecture," adds Hurley," we paid particular attention to power efficiency. Instead of just adding another 32-bits we have stripped out complexity and made it a very power-efficient architecture." Licensees of A-57 and A-53 are Broadcom, Calxeda, AMD, HiSilicon, Samsung and ST. Being soft IP, A-53 and A-57 can be made on 28nm and 20nm planar processes at TSMC, Globalfoundries and Samsung, on the upcoming 16nm TSMC finfet process and 14nm Globalfoundries’ finfet process and on the 28nm Globalfoundries FD-SOI process. The A-53 has a smaller die size than the A-9 on the same process geometry and is therefore cheaper to make. It also has better power-efficiency and higher performance than the A-9. ARM says it is the smallest 64bit processor on the planet. As well as servers, the A-53 and A-57 are for future superphones, mobile computers, tablets and anything looking at larger data-sets. The A-53 and A-57 can work together as a big-LITTLE implementation or can be used separately. Where ARM’s partners have manufactured silicon of the A-15/A-7 bigLITTLE combination a 50% improvement in power consumption is being achieved. "bigLITTLE allows delivery of an incredible increase in performance while staying within the power budget of a consumer device," says Hurley.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351618244824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351618257581-36</Id><Topic><Title>ARM unveils 64-bit designs for future smartphones, servers</Title><Username>varlabania</Username><Timestamp>1351614556177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wouldn't worry. They won't have the 64-bit designs ready until "2014." By that time, Intel will be way ahead of the game in PCs as well as Smartphone devices.</Msg><Username>stok1mom</Username><Timestamp>1351618257581</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:30:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351618509472-37</Id><Topic><Title>ARM unveils 64-bit designs for future smartphones, servers</Title><Username>varlabania</Username><Timestamp>1351614556177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"devices out in 2014/15, says Hurley." lol</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351618509472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:35:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351618994174-38</Id><Topic><Title>Looks just like the 1937 recession are you ready for the big drop, it's coming</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351609867858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:11:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>recession, almost every company that has reported earnings also reported big layoffs</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351618994174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:43:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351619107054-39</Id><Topic><Title>ARM unveils 64-bit designs for future smartphones, servers</Title><Username>varlabania</Username><Timestamp>1351614556177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""It’s been a rare opportunity to start with a clean sheet of paper to develop a new architecture," adds Hurley," we paid particular attention to power efficiency. Instead of just adding another 32-bits we have stripped out complexity and made it a very power-efficient architecture."" And with a fixed-length ISA... I'm really looking forward to how modern compilers will work with data dependencies and parallelizing instruction code. Looking forward to the white-papers...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351619107054</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:45:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351620839041-40</Id><Topic><Title>ARM unveils 64-bit designs for future smartphones, servers</Title><Username>varlabania</Username><Timestamp>1351614556177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2014/2015 is a long time. Also, armh don't make chips. Unless if you're samsung, the company that will make the servers will also need to order the chip from a 3rd party source, which adds uncertainty and increased costs. Would be much easier to just buy chips from intel.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1351620839041</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351621389238-41</Id><Title>1.3 GHz Celeron 867 crushes latest 1.7 GHz ARM A15</Title><Msg>Two Chromebook processors compared and the cheapest most underpowered 32nm Sandy Bridge derivative (no hyperthreading even) absolutely slaughters ARM's latest 32nm performance champ. What will the 22nm Ivy Bridge/Haswell Celerons do to it in 2013 ?!! gigaomDOTcom/mobile/intel-v-arm-the-chromebook-performance-battle/ arkDOTintelDOTcom/products/63918/Intel-Celeron-Processor-867-2M-Cache-1_30-GHz samsungDOTcom/global/business/semiconductor/product/application/detail?productId=7668&amp;iaId=2341 Peacekeeper +77% SunSpider +72% V8 +47% Octane +59% Boot up time +51%</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351621389238</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351622158858-42</Id><Topic><Title>Looks just like the 1937 recession are you ready for the big drop, it's coming</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351609867858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:11:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look up on MSN bing Dangerous Lessons of 1937 we did not learn</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351622158858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:35:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351622296851-43</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement for Intel Corporation . Read Now!</Title><Username>gaylordchristopher29</Username><Timestamp>1351612425542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:53:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I appreciate it I was really shopping for some thing like this service.</Msg><Username>josephlambert84622</Username><Timestamp>1351622296851</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:38:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351623522174-44</Id><Topic><Title>Looks just like the 1937 recession are you ready for the big drop, it's coming</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351609867858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:11:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>look that up on BING .... Debunking Catalán on the Recession of 1937-1938 then .... look up "Flatulence" on BING to understand everything about coinmaker77.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351623522174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:58:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351623856096-45</Id><Topic><Title>Looks just like the 1937 recession are you ready for the big drop, it's coming</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351609867858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:11:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>some believe that the SPY has to get back up over 1500 first.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1351623856096</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:04:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351624420802-46</Id><Topic><Title>Exynos 5 Dual handily beats Apple’s A6 chip, Intel’s Atom Z2460</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351590885743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mixing and matching benchmarks from different sites is not really feasible as Tofel found even the A9 broke 1000s in Sunspider and he is the only guy on the planet who has found that. Best to wait for someone to do tests under similar conditions at one site alone. I don't remotely believe the title 'handily beats' in either A6 or Z2460 case and proper comparative tests will show that.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351624420802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351625185256-47</Id><Topic><Title>Exynos 5 Dual handily beats Apple’s A6 chip, Intel’s Atom Z2460</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351590885743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mixing and matching benchmarks from different sites is not really feasible as Tofel found even the A9 broke 1000s in Sunspider and he is the only guy on the planet who has found that. Best to wait for someone to do tests under similar conditions at one site alone. I don't remotely believe the title 'handily beats' in either A6 or Z2460 case and proper comparative tests will show that. ------ 'handily beats', was his words not mine. As for the A15, we shall soon see with the Nexus 10 and geekbench...:) So, what would you say good numbers over the A6 would be? 10%? 30%? 50%?</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351625185256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:26:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351625643844-48</Id><Topic><Title>1.3 GHz Celeron 867 crushes latest 1.7 GHz ARM A15</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351621389238</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:23:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah but but but ARM has 64 bit Servers coming sometime this decade! Stop with all your nasty facts that make ARM look like ROADKILL ! UNCLE!!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351625643844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:34:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351626371782-49</Id><Topic><Title>Exynos 5 Dual handily beats Apple’s A6 chip, Intel’s Atom Z2460</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351590885743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anand is doing an extensive chromebook performance review which should be out soon and give us a more detailed look. If the A15 consistently beats the A6 in ipc i.e. performance/clock I would be impressed as I think what Apple have done in performance (and performance/power) at 1.3 GHz is quite impressive for an ARM architecture chip which are usually bringing up the rear when it comes to ipc.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351626371782</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351627913546-50</Id><Topic><Title>Exynos 5 Dual handily beats Apple’s A6 chip, Intel’s Atom Z2460</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351590885743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you ever looked at benchmarks included in Geekbench and examined how they arrive the geekbench score? They run a single threaded and multithreaded version of each of the benchmarks. They then take a simple arithmetic average of the individual scores of both the single thread and multitreaded versions to arrive at their number for each section. They don't use a geo mean like the SPEC guys do. They quickly discarded the arithmetic average metric. They mix the single and multithreaded versions where 50% of the benchmark weighting is given to the single thread and 50% to multithreading. That seems to underweight the multithreaded benchmarks by giving them 50% weight. Thoughts?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351627913546</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:11:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351628086579-51</Id><Topic><Title>Exynos 5 Dual handily beats Apple’s A6 chip, Intel’s Atom Z2460</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351590885743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anand is doing an extensive chromebook performance review which should be out soon and give us a more detailed look. If the A15 consistently beats the A6 in ipc i.e. performance/clock I would be impressed as I think what Apple have done in performance (and performance/power) at 1.3 GHz is quite impressive for an ARM architecture chip which are usually bringing up the rear when it comes to ipc. ----- Interesting. I would be frankly shocked if it didn't have a higher IPC than the A6/S4. For me it's all about the die size and power. No point having the best-in-class performance if it costs and kills the battery.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351628086579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:14:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351630083553-52</Id><Title>Even AMD says ARM power advantage is short-lived - AMD GM for server products</Title><Msg>Perhaps 5 years....Two issues with that reasoning: (a) I think Intel is already there. Medfield...Atom #$%$ server products....Haswell with 20x reduction in TDP. (b) ARM will have server products in another 2 years...and they will be competitive for another couple of years...? And this is the architecture all OEMs want to bet on? Methinks AMD is just buying time for the management to figure out what to do. And sell whatever remaining options they have for the most they can get for them! Check out ZDNet for the article. ====================================== AMD: ARM's power advantages could wane in the coming years ARM's power advantages over typical x86 chips from Intel and AMD will continue for around half a decade before fading away, according to AMD. Yesterday, AMD announced it would start making ARM-based servers in 2014, and today Suresh Gopalakrishnan, general manager of AMD's server business unit, told ZDNet that ARM's power advantages could be short-lived. "If you increase the capabilities of the [ARM] processor, it will consume more power. At the same time, if you start working on the [x86] architecture and process together you can bring the power down as well," Gopalakrishnan told me. "Right now ARM has the [power] advantage - five years down the road we'll see." In the future, Intel will bring in new energy-thrifty chips built on its advanced 14nm and 10nm fabrication methods, which will help it lower their power consumption, while ARM's chips will consume more power as more features are added to them to let them tackle more advanced server workloads. So, in a few years, the power advantages which are propelling ARM's chips into cloud datacentres like Facebook's could fade as technological forces conspire to close the gap in electricity usage. Why is AMD licensing ARM for servers now then? Because it can bring the 64-bit chips out years before the power window closes, Gopalakrishnan said.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1351630083553</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:48:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351630893973-53</Id><Topic><Title>Looks just like the 1937 recession are you ready for the big drop, it's coming</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351609867858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:11:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>idiot!</Msg><Username>jravera</Username><Timestamp>1351630893973</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:01:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351632064455-54</Id><Topic><Title>Looks just like the 1937 recession are you ready for the big drop, it's coming</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351609867858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:11:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>look up "Flatulence" on BING to understand everything about coinmaker77</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1351632064455</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:21:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351632275119-55</Id><Topic><Title>Exynos 5 Dual handily beats Apple’s A6 chip, Intel’s Atom Z2460</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351590885743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you ever looked at benchmarks included in Geekbench and examined how they arrive the geekbench score? They run a single threaded and multithreaded version of each of the benchmarks. They then take a simple arithmetic average of the individual scores of both the single thread and multitreaded versions to arrive at their number for each section. They don't use a geo mean like the SPEC guys do. They quickly discarded the arithmetic average metric. They mix the single and multithreaded versions where 50% of the benchmark weighting is given to the single thread and 50% to multithreading. That seems to underweight the multithreaded benchmarks by giving them 50% weight. ----- All benchmarks have their issues, and all vendors choose benchmarks that make them look good:) Personally, I like Geekbench (cross platform and all that) but as you point out you do need to look deeper than just the overall number. I still question the need for more than 2 CPU cores on a phone/tablet SOC, so the quad core numbers are suspect in my view. Then you look at the javascript benchmarks and they are all single threaded. One extreme to the other.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351632275119</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:24:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351635574293-56</Id><Title>Intel News - Shipping industry's first SDD series with a 20-nanometer NAND flash memory process</Title><Msg>Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) announced on Monday that it was shipping the industry’s first solid state drive series with a 20-nanometer NAND flash memory process, which is the 335 Series. The 6 gigabit-per-second SATA drive, which features a 240 gigabyte capacity that performs 500 megabytes-per-second sequential reads and 450 MB/s sequential writes, represents Intel’s first SSD to utilize the latest 20nm NAND flash memory, which was jointly developed by IM Flash Technologies.</Msg><Username>stok1mom</Username><Timestamp>1351635574293</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:19:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351635723644-57</Id><Topic><Title>1.3 GHz Celeron 867 crushes latest 1.7 GHz ARM A15</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351621389238</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:23:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM 64 bit servers coming in 2014 - not sometime soon. Intel is way way ahead of ARM.</Msg><Username>stok1mom</Username><Timestamp>1351635723644</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:22:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351636998519-58</Id><Title>Even ARMH's new partner, AMD admits ARM servers might be worthless</Title><Msg>LOL! sounds like this AMD employee doesn't like the recent partnership for ARM Servers. And what manager of a data center wants to change vendors for a few years? Maybe a small plumbing company? A gas station? lol.... AMD: ARM's power advantages could wane in the coming years ARM's power advantages over typical x86 chips from Intel and AMD will continue for around half a decade before fading away, according to AMD. Yesterday, AMD announced it would start making ARM-based servers in 2014, and today Suresh Gopalakrishnan, general manager of AMD's server business unit, told ZDNet that ARM's power advantages could be short-lived. "If you increase the capabilities of the [ARM] processor, it will consume more power. At the same time, if you start working on the [x86] architecture and process together you can bring the power down as well," Gopalakrishnan told me. "Right now ARM has the [power] advantage - five years down the road we'll see." In the future, Intel will bring in new energy-thrifty chips built on its advanced 14nm and 10nm fabrication methods, which will help it lower their power consumption, while ARM's chips will consume more power as more features are added to them to let them tackle more advanced server workloads. So, in a few years, the power advantages which are propelling ARM's chips into cloud datacentres like Facebook's could fade as technological forces conspire to close the gap in electricity usage. Why is AMD licensing ARM for servers now then? Because it can bring the 64-bit chips out years before the power window closes, Gopalakrishnan said.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351636998519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:43:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351638879861-59</Id><Title>Massachusetts = Hurricane experts</Title><Msg>Massachusetts = Hurricane experts</Msg><Username>hell.succubus</Username><Timestamp>1351638879861</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:14:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351647413653-60</Id><Topic><Title>Exynos 5 Dual handily beats Apple’s A6 chip, Intel’s Atom Z2460</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351590885743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. I agree that having a cross platform metric is very nice. I like SPEC but it will be awhile before it is used on ARM. I am struck by the difference that can be measured by changing small elements of the configurations. It seems like the people running the benchmarks may not even be aware of these inconsistencies. Intel is trying to make Parallel Javascript work and widely available. Do you know if it will take much effort to take advantage of parallel Javascript?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351647413653</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:36:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351649982840-61</Id><Topic><Title>Exynos 5 Dual handily beats Apple’s A6 chip, Intel’s Atom Z2460</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351590885743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Javascript is high-level for writing scripts. HTML programmers are its authors. For supporting parallel, need extensions that these authors can simply start using. Extensions for parallel are not simple. Adoption of technology is in question. Next generation processors are best served by native apps that can unlock their potential.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1351649982840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 22:19:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351651422735-62</Id><Topic><Title>Intel working on 48 core chip for phones/tablets while ARMH tries to build a server LOL!</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351602096456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:01:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, fascinating. 48 cores. Something tells me that Intel will still be in business 10 years from now and will be paying a Dividend of 2 dollars or more !</Msg><Username>beer_bladder_lucy</Username><Timestamp>1351651422735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 22:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351652857480-63</Id><Title>Obama getting CRUSHED in early voting per new Gallup poll</Title><Msg>52 % for Romney 45% for Obama And Replublican voters tend to be old and vote late, so this is devastating to Obama. Young people who don't see a future after college are out there in full force bringing Obama to his knees, IMHO.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351652857480</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:07:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351654760423-64</Id><Topic><Title>Obama getting CRUSHED in early voting per new Gallup poll</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351652857480</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:07:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROMNEY: NOPE .... 2013-2017 US citizen, CAYMAN bank accounts. OBAMA: YEP ..... US PRESIDENT, 2nd TERM SANDY AFTERMATH: Old, late voting seniors, duped by ROMNEY LIES won't be able to get to polls to vote. Their CLOCK RADIOS are RESET to JAN 1st . Ohio Early Voting: Over 1.2 Million Ballots Cast In Critical Swing State: 63% OBAMA 37% ROMNEY The Ohio Secretary of State's office said that as of Oct. 26, about 1.26 million voters had cast ballots by mail-in absentee ballots or through early in-person voting. That represents about 22 percent of the number of people who voted in the 2008 presidential election. Secretary Jon Husted said the pace of early voting was picking up ahead of next week's election. Absentee ballots must be postmarked by Nov. 5 or they can be delivered in person to the board of elections until the close of polls on Nov. 6. The Secretary of State's office said 1.32 million absentee ballots had been sent out this year. About 64,000 have not yet been cast.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351654760423</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:39:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351655402935-65</Id><Topic><Title>Obama getting CRUSHED in early voting per new Gallup poll</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351652857480</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:07:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That won't last once he convinces his flock that GWB caused Sandy.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351655402935</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351655422487-66</Id><Topic><Title>Obama getting CRUSHED in early voting per new Gallup poll</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351652857480</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:07:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, very worried.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351655422487</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351655783216-67</Id><Title>Latest Election Projections</Title><Msg>Real Clear Politics: Obama: 281 Romney: 257 538: Obama: 294.6 Romney: 243.4 Romney's message to victims of disasters like SuperStorm Sandy: Deal with it. The federal government is not here to bail you out. Yet here is what New Jersey Governor Christie had to say: One of Mitt Romney’s biggest supporters, New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie, had nothing but praise for President Barack Obama today, as his state prepares to rebuild from the damage caused by Hurricane Sandy. “I have to say, the administration, the president, himself and FEMA Administrator Craig Fugate have been outstanding with us so far,” Christie said on Good Morning America. “We have a great partnership with them.” Full Coverage: Hurricane Sandy Christie told ABC’s George Stephanopoulos that Obama called him on Monday night around midnight to ask if there was anything else the federal government could do to help. Christie added that they worked together to move forward with a Major Disaster Declaration for New Jersey. The Major Disaster Declaration provides funding for recovery efforts, including infrastructure projects, temporary housing, low-cost loans to cover uninsured property loss and assistance to individuals and businesses.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351655783216</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:56:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>