<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356670904091-1</Id><Topic><Title>The Precarious Nature of ARM's Existing Situation</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356653731924</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 19:15:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"1.) ARM foundries are still unable to produce enough 28nm capacity to satisfy demand. Not true. They have been operating at over 80% for a while now. [There's a ton of articles stating that TSMC won't meet demand until some time into 2013, if then. But why read anything when you can just make stuff up? But here's the deal. TSMC needs to be at volume production on 20nm by the middle of 2013 or its game over. They will be lucky to be at full volume production on 28nm. TSMC couldn't even produce a decent ramp on planar 28nm. You want to see what a ramp is supposed to look like review Intel's ramp on 22nm FinFET. TSMC has no chance of reaching volume production on 20nm in 2013.] 2.) Opinions of 20nm planar technology have now reached a consensus level that the technology is noncompetitive with FinFET and therefore doesn't have the economics to be viable. Not true. There is the usual power/performance benefit from scaling down. Leakage is an issue that they are working out. [Go ahead post up some articles touting the economics of 20nm planar. There aren't any. Put up or shut up.] 3.) The ARM foundries are therefore left with two equally ugly options. Stick with a doable move to 20nm planar leading to production of a inferior product that leaves Intel a huge opening into the mobile world. Or attempt the almost impossible two process level jump to 14/16nm FinFET that would take three years even if successful. They are going to 20 nm first then to 14nm just like everyone else including Intel. [Just like everyone else? Don't make me laugh. It's Intel and Intel only. There isn't anyone else. ARM is two years out on 20nm and four or more on 14nm FinFET. ] 4.) The other option which appears to be the most reckless due to the extreme cost is to do both at the same time. This appears to be the approach that has been settled upon. All foundries including Intel work on processes simultaneously. This is because it takes too long to develop a process to work on them serially." [Really? So, we can expect to see all foundries produce 5nm at the same time? Don't be ridiculous. Each process builds on the preceding one. That's why it is utterly impossible for ARM to jump two process levels. They wouldn't even attempt it except 20nm is such a total economic loser.] [If ARM doesn't have a better shill than you to throw into the mix, then their PR is as bad as their fabrication....]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356670904091</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 00:01:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356671362264-2</Id><Title>Intel gets patent for motion control safety</Title><Msg>Merges Nintendo and Microsoft consoles Intel has gained a new patent that could mix motion control popularised by Nintendo with a variety of safety features to protect gamers and their furniture. United States Patent 8333661, a “Gaming System with Safety Features”, is being seen that as Intel developing a multi-core processor designed to help “avoid or minimise the probability of a collision between the user of the gaming console and the surrounding objects while the user is playing a game. According to Intel’s patent claims, such a device would include an array of sensors working in tandem with the game console to capture images of a player’s body movement inside a 3D space, similar to Microsoft’s Kinect device. However, Intel’s chip would also continuously monitor objects around a player and the player’s proximity to them. If a player gets dangerously close to colliding with an object, the safety system would signal an audible warning alert and pause the game. Intel seems to think that Microsoft’s system will be the way forward. It said that the new generation gaming systems support features that detect and respond to motion and emotion of the users of the gaming system. “However, the new generation gaming systems lack safety features, which may provide an opportunity to the users to avoid being injured caused by inadvertently colliding with the surrounding objects,” the patent said. Since only the Xbox 360 supports “remote control-less” gaming it means that either Intel thinks that Nintendo and Sony will follow suit or Microsoft will be the winner of the long running console wars. Also interesting is that Intel mentioned “emotion.” So far the only one who has a patent for that sort of thing is Sony. From Fudzilla</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356671362264</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 00:09:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356671639523-3</Id><Title>CES 2013 and Mobile World Congress 2013</Title><Msg>Looking for some big Intel mobility news to kick the year off right...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356671639523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 00:13:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356674371513-4</Id><Topic><Title>CES 2013 and Mobile World Congress 2013</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356671639523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 00:13:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one listens to Intel's news on mobile anymore. They've made a string of announcements in the last few years and failed miserably to capture 0.2% market share. Without market traction, most of the consumers of your newsbites are your employees and stock holders.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1356674371513</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 00:59:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356678213094-5</Id><Topic><Title>CES 2013 and Mobile World Congress 2013</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356671639523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 00:13:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Things change fast in tech. When Android came out, who would have thought that within just a couple of years they would over take iOS as the dominant platform? What was Samsung's smartphone market share a couple of years ago? Now they are outselling the iPhone. Intel's next Medfield SoC will have LTE support to enter the US smartphone market. Mostly like Motorola will carry this SoC in their next superphone(s). We'll see how it compares to the iPhone and Samsungs very soon. On the tablet side, within just a couple months since the Windows 8 launch you are already seeing PC convertibles and detachables exploding into the market. Beginning of next year, 7W Ivy Bridge parts will be available for OEMs to build more sleeker PC convertibles and detachables. After that Haswell comes out. Do you think these will not eat into the iPads and other larger tablets? The value proposition for these new touch-enabled PCs can't be ignored. The old adage of Intel missing out on mobile is getting old.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356678213094</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 02:03:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356679639995-6</Id><Topic><Title>The Precarious Nature of ARM's Existing Situation</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356653731924</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 19:15:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple's A6 at 28nm is at par with Intel next generation chip at 22nm so it doesn't really matter. Good luck Intel/Motorola, maybe Google can revive some of that old Razr magic and out-market the #$%$ out of the iPhone 6 and the Galaxy 4. That should make a huge difference to Intel's top-line growth.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1356679639995</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 02:27:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356680950876-7</Id><Topic><Title>Feel sorry for all those who sold today out of sheer panic</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356638568970</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 15:02:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont worry- as we fall off the cliff it will be lower- or as soon as a deal is made and the market sells on the news it will be lower- either way - you will get another chance under 20 to get in</Msg><Username>marrohead</Username><Timestamp>1356680950876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 02:49:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356699288455-8</Id><Title>INTC SHORT INTEREST 229,603,159</Title><Msg>short squeeze coming</Msg><Username>dedrapop</Username><Timestamp>1356699288455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 07:54:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356702387027-9</Id><Title>GOP teabagging Nazi clowns taking the market much lower.</Title><Msg>God is talking to them. Their god of course is a white wing old man wearing a white hood. Just make some money or at least avoid losing money. If you are already long in Intel, HOLD ON and under NO circumstances, sell at this ridiculous price or the lower prices that likely will come as the GOP in the House suck DICCCCCKKKK! BUT--of course--you should be short the market for now and be laughing as #$%$ John--beats ooooooffff and cries as his teabaggging right members of his house yell a rebel yell causing disaster for a time. Those good old boys just cannot take the fact that the Pres is BLACK. They are willing to cut off their little nuts just to hurt him. They cannot believe that they--Masta--cannot tell that Yankee sccccccum what to do. He is laughing at them and they are just throwing a fit for now. But in the end--HUGE corporate money will push the GOP in the house to have a vote in the house and the Obummer plan will pass. Hey boy--Virginia went OB AGAIN. You LOST AGAIN. Likely, your wife voted for OB! By the way----Intel Apple is going to happen in phones and Ipads.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1356702387027</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 08:46:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356702534161-10</Id><Topic><Title>GOP teabagging Nazi clowns taking the market much lower.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1356702387027</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 08:46:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google and watch CONSERVATISM IS CALLING. It will BLOW your mind to watch Obama blast Bush for raising the debt......called him unpatriotic......then he raises it by MORE in HALF THE TIME! LOL! Are you serious? Watch it. Nice to hear from Ronald Reagen in that video as well on why he switched from Liberal to Conservative.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1356702534161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 08:48:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356703240252-11</Id><Title>mellanox stock long strong bullish today</Title><Msg>long strong</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1356703240252</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:00:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356703749059-12</Id><Title>ultrabooks on list of biggest product flops....go Intel !!</Title><Msg>win 8 got a pass so did Intel's mobile results. LTE anyone ?</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356703749059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:09:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356704600462-13</Id><Topic><Title>INTC SHORT INTEREST 229,603,159</Title><Username>dedrapop</Username><Timestamp>1356699288455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 07:54:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>see ya at 13. That is a lot of short shares....and it is getting larger too. You guys kept saying it would be at 25 now .....hmmm. Oh well, ignorance is bliss.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356704600462</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:23:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356705005083-14</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell will be huge</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356640080333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 15:28:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>haswell is all ready a has been, it really changes nothing. That is the unvarnished truth.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356705005083</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:30:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356705625742-15</Id><Title>A warning about warnings....</Title><Msg>I saw some amateur at seeking alpha give Intel a thumbs up because it had not warned. I just shook my head in amazement. Intel may make the quarter in parts of their statements or they may not and still not warn. The real driver of the stock on that day at least will be the forward looking announcements. This could swing the stock 20 percent or more either way. Plenty of companies have not warned and then open up a box of poop. Have a nice day.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356705625742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:40:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356706431782-16</Id><Topic><Title>A warning about warnings....</Title><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356705625742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats nothing!!! I saw some amateur on the Intel message board prediciting a possible 20% Intel stock move either way!!! Then the idiot wished everyone to have a nice day!!! Can you believe that!! Some uninformed pretender giving advice and complaining about the same thing from others???? What a goof! TOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYYYY</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1356706431782</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:53:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356706592761-17</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell will be huge</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356640080333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 15:28:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The unvarnished truth was revealed when you opened your mouth for your first sentence. It was a confession of your ignorance. TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYYY</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1356706592761</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:56:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356706673533-18</Id><Title>Haswell to be Released on June 2, 2013</Title><Msg>tomshardwareDOTcom/news/intel-haswell-cpu-processor,20042.html</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356706673533</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:57:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356706693101-19</Id><Topic><Title>GOP teabagging Nazi clowns taking the market much lower.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1356702387027</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 08:46:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The GOP Rombo lost. Get over it.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1356706693101</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:58:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356706711156-20</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell will be huge</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356640080333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 15:28:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorts like luvinitalwu are a HOOT! We already know they aren't very smart, but as soon as they speak they remove all doubt.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1356706711156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:58:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356707008955-21</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be Released on June 2, 2013</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356706673533</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:57:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The mainstream mobile i7s will be released the same time though as the desktop variants. Looks like the most expensive low volume products first. Makes sense as you would want to supplant Ivy Bridge from the top down. chineseDOTvr-zoneDOTcom/45571/intel-adjust-haswell-introduction-date-before-computex-2013-12252012</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356707008955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:03:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356707165321-22</Id><Title>This market is about to turn greatly on the upside.</Title><Msg>Seems like in the afternoon hour.</Msg><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1356707165321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:06:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356707283588-23</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be Released on June 2, 2013</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356706673533</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:57:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kew-ell</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1356707283588</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:08:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356707557292-24</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be Released on June 2, 2013</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356706673533</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:57:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5 months??????</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1356707557292</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:12:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356707895684-25</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be Released on June 2, 2013</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356706673533</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:57:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does it matter ? Is Ivy Bridge in mortal threat from anyone ? It's going to produce 7W skus already so Haswell will just be a nice mid year bonus. I think mid year updates are ideal as you get time to build steam up before each year's Q4 but are still far away enough from last year's Q4s not to impact its sales.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356707895684</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:18:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356707919067-26</Id><Topic><Title>Conroe Takes On The AMD Athlon 64 FX-62</Title><Username>nothingman2006</Username><Timestamp>1151135032000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2006-06-24 03:43:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kew-ell</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1356707919067</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:18:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356708032247-27</Id><Title>iWatch will be a hit</Title><Msg>Women will love it! Here are features of an iWatch: - fashion statement - do not have to take phone out of purse to make a quick call - do not have to take phone out of purse to see who is calling - do not have to take phone out of purse to read text messages and emails - gps replacement; use siri to find location and then can glance at screen on wrist while driving to see turn by turn directions - calendar and appointments show up as alerts - show current temperature and forecast On top of these there could be thousand of additional apps and games that can be created.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356708032247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:20:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356708523652-28</Id><Topic><Title>iWatch will be a hit</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356708032247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:20:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Women will love it!" They'll love the i Dill Doe even more!</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1356708523652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:28:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356708560580-29</Id><Topic><Title>INTC SHORT INTEREST 229,603,159</Title><Username>dedrapop</Username><Timestamp>1356699288455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 07:54:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>long term investment</Msg><Username>dedrapop</Username><Timestamp>1356708560580</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:29:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356708594315-30</Id><Topic><Title>This market is about to turn greatly on the upside.</Title><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1356707165321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:06:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kew-ell</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1356708594315</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:29:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356708624141-31</Id><Topic><Title>This market is about to turn greatly on the upside.</Title><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1356707165321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:06:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>buy signal across the floor</Msg><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1356708624141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:30:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356708799730-32</Id><Topic><Title>iWatch will be a hit</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356708032247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:20:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah like ultrabooks and intel smart phones and tablets !! Life sucks for Intel right now and evidently for you too. Your woman does not want you to know when her boy toy is calling. That 2 inch screen sounds like a real gas.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356708799730</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:33:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356709027850-33</Id><Title>I think we're going over the cliff, so I had to get out... good luck to all who are hanging on, I hope I was wrong...</Title><Msg>I was in at 22.60 average and took a $4000 hit, but I fear the idiots in Washington are going to send us over the cliff and INTC will hit close to $11 like it did last recession... like I said, I hope I'm wrong, and best of luck to all who are hanging on, I hope I was wrong and it turns out good for you...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1356709027850</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:37:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356709185019-34</Id><Topic><Title>I think we're going over the cliff, so I had to get out... good luck to all who are hanging on, I hope I was wrong...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1356709027850</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:37:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cliff, schmliff</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1356709185019</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:39:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356709305362-35</Id><Title>Lost 25K On This POS In Less Than 2 Weeks I'm OUT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>COMPLETE MANIPUALTION BY WALL STREET THUGS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>fairwarning50</Username><Timestamp>1356709305362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:41:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356709559881-36</Id><Topic><Title>iWatch will be a hit</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356708032247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:20:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about a tv remote that you never misplace?</Msg><Username>livingsez</Username><Timestamp>1356709559881</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:45:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356709562604-37</Id><Topic><Title>This market is about to turn greatly on the upside.</Title><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1356707165321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:06:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>right aound 10 et...Watch the afternoon rally</Msg><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1356709562604</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:46:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356709893671-38</Id><Topic><Title>This market is about to turn greatly on the upside.</Title><Username>planet0723</Username><Timestamp>1356707165321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:06:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So is INTC good for 30 this afternoon?</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1356709893671</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:51:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356710012644-39</Id><Topic><Title>ultrabooks on list of biggest product flops....go Intel !!</Title><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356703749059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:09:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Intel Corp. /quotes/zigman/20392/quotes/nls/intc INTC -0.34% released the Ultrabook, it looked to be the key competitor to Apple’s MacBook. That clearly hasn't happened. Earlier this year, research firm IHS had forecast that 22 million ultrabooks would be shipped by the end of 2012 and an additional 61 million would be shipped in 2013. However, by October, the firm changed its projections drastically, predicting that just 10 million would be sold this year, and only 44 million would be sold in 2013. The problem with the Ultrabook is twofold. Ultrabooks are highly expensive in a market where pricing is everything—the majority cost around $1,000. But the larger issue is the increasing movement to mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356710012644</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:53:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356710119383-40</Id><Topic><Title>CROX/INTEL PACT RUMOUR</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1311862299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2011-07-28 10:11:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RUMOUR- INTC to merge with Fossil! HI-HO WEAVERINO!!! TOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356710119383</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:55:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356710686702-41</Id><Topic><Title>iWatch will be a hit</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356708032247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:20:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will this be a "smart watch?" Will it be like a modern version of the watch #$%$ Tracy wore?</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356710686702</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:04:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356710731292-42</Id><Topic><Title>CROX/INTEL PACT RUMOUR</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1311862299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2011-07-28 10:11:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>karin finneramin sayed to bius CROX in afterhours at $1.40</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1356710731292</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:05:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356710894413-43</Id><Title>TIGLET dumped Intel at 20 and bought Textainer for the Divvy</Title><Msg>What a #$%$ ROFpointingandlaughing</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1356710894413</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:08:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356711367351-44</Id><Topic><Title>Lost 25K On This POS In Less Than 2 Weeks I'm OUT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>fairwarning50</Username><Timestamp>1356709305362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:41:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Intel price two weeks ago closed at $20.49. How could you be so LUCKY to lose $25k on INTC? At 5 cents per share loss ( $20.49 - $20.44 = $.05 ) you would have had to purchase 500,000 shares!!!! and then forget to sell all the two weeks that Intel was above your purchase price. WHAT A DOPE!!! in all caps TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYYY</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1356711367351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:16:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356711377611-45</Id><Title>Intel Smart TV's coming in 2013 from various vendors !!</Title><Msg>A report in Digitimes quoting component makers says Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) will join hands with Hewlett-Packard (NYSE:HPQ), Lenovo, Quanta Computer and Compal Electronics to launch Smart TVs in 2013. According to the sources, Intel’s effort will include a user interface along with voice, gesture, and face recognition systems, thus going beyond the simple marriage of a TV with inbuilt PC functionality.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1356711377611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:16:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356711498113-46</Id><Topic><Title>I think we're going over the cliff, so I had to get out... good luck to all who are hanging on, I hope I was wrong...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1356709027850</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:37:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Politicians will do one of 3 things, agree on a bill, agree on a partial bill, or extend the deadline. There will be no going over the cliff.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1356711498113</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:18:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356711568176-47</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Smart TV's coming in 2013 from various vendors !!</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1356711377611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:16:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kew-ell! Everyone I know is waiting for the next big thing and it could just be TV!</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1356711568176</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:19:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356711595725-48</Id><Title>NOT GOOD for INTC, Demand For Windows 8 Is Weak, Says Fujitsu President</Title><Msg>NOT GOOD for INTC, Demand For Windows 8 Is Weak, Says Fujitsu President</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356711595725</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:19:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356711810416-49</Id><Topic><Title>NOT GOOD for INTC, Demand For Windows 8 Is Weak, Says Fujitsu President</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356711595725</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The public really likes Mojave and Jerry Seinfeld will appear in adverts!</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1356711810416</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:23:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356711870058-50</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Smart TV's coming in 2013 from various vendors !!</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1356711377611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:16:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>consumers so far dislike smart tvs. Check it out on google.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356711870058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:24:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356711960042-51</Id><Topic><Title>Lost 25K On This POS In Less Than 2 Weeks I'm OUT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>fairwarning50</Username><Timestamp>1356709305362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:41:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe he bought options, hoping it would jump to 30.</Msg><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1356711960042</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:26:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356712070705-52</Id><Topic><Title>Lost 25K On This POS In Less Than 2 Weeks I'm OUT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>fairwarning50</Username><Timestamp>1356709305362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:41:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Smart move INTC is going back down to test 19.23</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356712070705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:27:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356712136345-53</Id><Topic><Title>NOT GOOD for INTC, Demand For Windows 8 Is Weak, Says Fujitsu President</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356711595725</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NOT good for INTC, HPQ, DELL or MSFT</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356712136345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:28:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356712158967-54</Id><Topic><Title>Lost 25K On This POS In Less Than 2 Weeks I'm OUT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>fairwarning50</Username><Timestamp>1356709305362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 10:41:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe he bought options, hoping it would jump to 30. ------- Intel is "good for 30"</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356712158967</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:29:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356712253742-55</Id><Title>2013 Could Be a Turnaround Year for Intel</Title><Msg>The company reported this week that they were planning to release a new mobile operating system next February, which will add diversity to the company’s product mix. Additionally, a report released on Friday from Digitimes announced that INTC also plans on producing a new smart TV next year. Reports have suggested that this TV will not be limited to ordinary PC functions, but will also include functions which will involve users voice, face, and movements. Intel will also be working to produce other products such as new chips for mobile devices including tablets made by Microsoft(MSFT).</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356712253742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:30:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356712274669-56</Id><Title>GOOD for INTC, DELL seeing strong demand for computers and tablets running Windows 8</Title><Msg>Dell Inc. (DELL), the world’s third-largest PC maker, said Dec. 12 it’s seeing strong demand for computers and tablets running Windows 8. Interest in the operating system is “quite high,” Dell Chief Executive Officer Michael Dell said at a conference in Austin, Texas.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356712274669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:31:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356712282017-57</Id><Title>Earnings are going down , Forecast is for lowered earnings NOT GOOD</Title><Msg>Earnings are going down , Forecast is for lowered earnings NOT GOOD</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356712282017</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:31:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356712372489-58</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Smart TV's coming in 2013 from various vendors !!</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1356711377611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:16:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This sounds exciting. This is like taking the all-in-one systems and cannibalizing the TV market!</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356712372489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:32:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356712444860-59</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Smart TV's coming in 2013 from various vendors !!</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1356711377611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:16:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Lucy, hiding as Wallusweener and talking about dil do's all day. He beingreen.....you're miserable and you have ZERO effect on sales. I can google Windows 8 and see that people hate it......then I can google it again and see that people love it. You are IRRELIVANT. How's it feel ?</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1356712444860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:34:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356712445171-60</Id><Title>Quick and dirty non-delusional analysis.</Title><Msg>First off, no stock is a buy until at least one week from now, not even INTC. We might have a huge correction. I would hold off and wait for at least one week from now. Then, I would buy Intel. It has been battered because it isn't growing but other tech companies are. Well, Google isn't really growing that much. Smartphone market is close to saturation, at which points profits fall off a cliff -- no good high-tech growth unless you are insane or .. aspirational?... enough to consider the plastic model maker toy companies like DDD. If no tech stock is growing, and people still want to be in the tech sector, Intel is going to start looking much more attractive. It's a real company. It makes real things. It has real patents. It's been around for a really long time. It even has a ginormous dividend. This stock can easily go from 15 (no fiscal cliff resolution, worst case) / 20.4 (current price) to 30 or even 40 on institutions reallocating to safer dividend yielding low-growth stocks. It has happened in other sectors for solid companies last year and the dividend there is only 2.2%-~3.5%. (V, PG, GE, JNG). It won't happen overnight, though.</Msg><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1356712445171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:34:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356712453675-61</Id><Topic><Title>CES 2013 and Mobile World Congress 2013</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356671639523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 00:13:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Motorola X phone could show up at Mobile World Congress</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356712453675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:34:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356712460734-62</Id><Topic><Title>Quick and dirty non-delusional analysis.</Title><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1356712445171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:34:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's JNJ.</Msg><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1356712460734</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:34:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356712559131-63</Id><Topic><Title>The Precarious Nature of ARM's Existing Situation</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356653731924</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 19:15:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Apple's A6 at 28nm is at par with Intel next generation chip at 22nm" Now you are just flat-out spreading lies</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356712559131</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:35:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356712712009-64</Id><Topic><Title>GOOD for INTC, DELL seeing strong demand for computers and tablets running Windows 8</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356712274669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:31:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>interest in it was high, now we have seen what a low bar MS shoots for, the purchasing follow through has been underwhelming.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356712712009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:38:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356712765334-65</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings are going down , Forecast is for lowered earnings NOT GOOD</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356712282017</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:31:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They just keep dropping the earnings forecast NOT GOOD</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356712765334</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:39:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356712780060-66</Id><Topic><Title>The x86 Power Myth Busted: In-Depth Clover Trail Power Analysis</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356650441237</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 18:20:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With the added VRM, Haswell is taking it to the next level. A Core Broadwell SoC could make it into phones in 2014!</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356712780060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:39:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356712830414-67</Id><Topic><Title>Quick and dirty non-delusional analysis.</Title><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1356712445171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:34:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a real company. It makes real things. It has real patents. It's been around for a really long time ----------------------------------- Some overly enthusiastic shareholders said similar things about General Motors a few years ago. TOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356712830414</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:40:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356712882267-68</Id><Topic><Title>Intel’s Haswell to Feature Secrete Weapon: Integrated Voltage Regulator</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356623185017</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 10:46:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL...maybe an anti-arm hormone</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356712882267</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:41:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356713063904-69</Id><Topic><Title>GOOD for INTC, DELL seeing strong demand for computers and tablets running Windows 8</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356712274669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:31:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow...this is great to hear!</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356713063904</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:44:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356713083351-70</Id><Topic><Title>ultrabooks on list of biggest product flops....go Intel !!</Title><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356703749059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:09:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tvs and watches and shoes next year !</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356713083351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:44:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356713313956-71</Id><Title>RUMOUR-</Title><Msg>Williams-Sonoma will soon have a state-of-the-art egg timer on its shelves. The timer will be powered by an Intel chip.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356713313956</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:48:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356713397989-72</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Smart TV's coming in 2013 from various vendors !!</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1356711377611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:16:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what happened to 3 D TVS ???? epic fail</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356713397989</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:49:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356713443980-73</Id><Topic><Title>Quick and dirty non-delusional analysis.</Title><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1356712445171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:34:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The last year Intel has had a growth rate of 23% which is higher than your "it isn't growing" assessment. Revenue growth (last year) +23.79% Next 5-years forecast: Earnings growth (next 5 years) +10.00% Earnings growth (last year) +18.91% But ... this year Earnings growth (this year) -11.60% For every dollar that Intel drops, the $6bil share buy back will retire another 20mill shares of stock. If Intel is going to retire 300mill plus shares, they will be buying more aggressively as the share price drops since their dollars will go farther.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356713443980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:50:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356713445519-74</Id><Topic><Title>ultrabooks on list of biggest product flops....go Intel !!</Title><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356703749059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:09:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about PC convertibles and detachables? These reports are talking about ultrabooks before taking into account of windows 8 and touch-enabled PCs. The newer and sleeker Convertibles and detachables PCs are going to be flood the market and cannibalized the tablets. The value proposition for these newer PCs are: better performance, better battery life, both a PC and tablet in one device (why buy two separate device?), and abilility to use your existing PC software.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356713445519</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:50:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356713484913-75</Id><Topic><Title>NOT GOOD for INTC, Demand For Windows 8 Is Weak, Says Fujitsu President</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356711595725</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good morning coinmaker77, nice to see at the job bashing. Didn't see you earlier, were you late for work today?</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356713484913</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:51:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356713499789-76</Id><Topic><Title>RUMOUR-</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356713313956</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:48:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, this will surely save dimtel. 9.</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1356713499789</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:51:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356713779509-77</Id><Title>2013 looking like awesome year for INTC</Title><Msg>- new phones ( Motorola X phone) - new 7" tablet (google Red Ridge and Asus intel tablet) - inside Apple's new device the iWatch - inside new Smart TVs developed by Lenovo, HP and others - new PC convertibles and detachables with new 7W ivy bridge and Haswell - possible foundry deal with Cisco - possible foundry deal with Apple and rumored to be inside next iPad</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356713779509</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:56:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356713863458-78</Id><Topic><Title>2013 looking like awesome year for INTC</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356713779509</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:56:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear Gawd, please stop posting the same thing over and over and over as well as bumping old posts. NOTHING you say will change the stock price. NOTHING!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1356713863458</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:57:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356713894609-79</Id><Topic><Title>ultrabooks on list of biggest product flops....go Intel !!</Title><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356703749059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:09:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more idiocy written by high school sophomores.</Msg><Username>previs_beameister</Username><Timestamp>1356713894609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:58:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356713930972-80</Id><Topic><Title>Quick and dirty non-delusional analysis.</Title><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1356712445171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:34:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Effective share buybacks are always a nice safety floor to have.</Msg><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1356713930972</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:58:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356713967727-81</Id><Topic><Title>2013 looking like awesome year for INTC</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356713779509</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:56:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ok shortie...better cover soon</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356713967727</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:59:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356714055124-82</Id><Topic><Title>NOT GOOD for INTC, Demand For Windows 8 Is Weak, Says Fujitsu President</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356711595725</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Michael Dell said Win8 and PC in general were strong!!!</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356714055124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:00:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356714156868-83</Id><Topic><Title>2013 looking like awesome year for INTC</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356713779509</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:56:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"bacbacker" is a WW alias. SOOOOOO DUHHHHHHHHHHHHB! SOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356714156868</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:02:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356714169282-84</Id><Topic><Title>Quick and dirty non-delusional analysis.</Title><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1356712445171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:34:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good analysis...thank you.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356714169282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:02:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356714265752-85</Id><Topic><Title>2013 looking like awesome year for INTC</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356713779509</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:56:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm Long for years and love the company, check my posts......but the board has been RUINED by your incessant and worthless posts. Put the Lucy's and coinmakers on IGNORE! Are you so stupid that you think pushing anti-intel posts down to the bottom of the board and pro-Intel posts to the top have ANY and I mean ANY effect on the stock price you psychotic idiot????????????? Are you so dumb to think that Intel, a 50 billion dollar a year company has it's stock price determined by what's said on this pathetic yahoo board? My Gawd.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1356714265752</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:04:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356714304376-86</Id><Topic><Title>Quick and dirty non-delusional analysis.</Title><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1356712445171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:34:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If INTC gets to 15 the GOP will have succeeded in destroying the whole stock market. Perhaps, finally, the grownups with the biggest money, and the biggest losses, will step in cauterize these creeps. The GOP is a pestulence. It must be exterminated in its present form.</Msg><Username>previs_beameister</Username><Timestamp>1356714304376</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:05:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356714336019-87</Id><Topic><Title>RUMOUR-</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356713313956</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:48:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since you can't shake the bitterness of losing on Intel in the past, have you ever considered suicide as an option? I'd be happy to guide you thru it.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356714336019</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:05:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356714372858-88</Id><Topic><Title>ultrabooks on list of biggest product flops....go Intel !!</Title><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356703749059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:09:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey wow I agree with you here !! problem is ultrabook is Intel, convertibles and cloud books are everyone. See the problem ? Google office is making inroads into MS office so win8 compatibility is way way less of any issue. Intel monopoly is being challenged like never before.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356714372858</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:06:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356714537123-89</Id><Topic><Title>GOOD for INTC, DELL seeing strong demand for computers and tablets running Windows 8</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356712274669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:31:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The big volume will come from company upgrades to Win8. When will they do that? When they deploy touch screen systems. This is the first OS that MSFT has released that was tied so closely to the hardware. For companies, I expect them to make moves after the Win8 evaluation/qual is complete and as PC refresh systems are deployed. I am working on Win7. The company has decided to deploy Win8 and will do so with new hardware during the refresh cycle.It won't be like the WinXP to Win7 upgrade where the change was rapid.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356714537123</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:08:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356714738427-90</Id><Topic><Title>2013 looking like awesome year for INTC</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356713779509</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:56:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dude...don't underestimate the power of mass media! Look at the hype surrounding arm.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356714738427</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:12:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356715439033-91</Id><Title>bacbacker3 is Ashraf Eassa</Title><Msg>Immature little twit. PSYCHOPATH.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1356715439033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:23:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356715479005-92</Id><Title>GAMEOVER for Armh and it's associates</Title><Msg>so say the cogniscenti with the largest wallets.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1356715479005</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:24:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356715536431-93</Id><Title>INTC to $30 in a few months</Title><Msg>after this GOP nonsense is behind us. Death rattle of the gun-toting t-league.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1356715536431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:25:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356715722136-94</Id><Title>I want in to Intel stock...humongous</Title><Msg>I need as many shares as I can get. Margin myself to the hilt. Think I cen get a second mortgage. In INTC.</Msg><Username>saskatoon_louie</Username><Timestamp>1356715722136</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:28:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356715746999-95</Id><Topic><Title>bacbacker3 is Ashraf Eassa</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1356715439033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:23:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who's being immature now? I think you are a shortie is disguise...better cover.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356715746999</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:29:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356716087553-96</Id><Title>can't promise anything but,</Title><Msg>If fiscal cliff addressed, market rally could be the mother of all rallies. Shorts would get horribly crushed. It would be similar to stepping on an ant on the sidewalk.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356716087553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:34:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356716785135-97</Id><Topic><Title>can't promise anything but,</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356716087553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:34:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't promise anything either Jerry. When the tax increases are agreed, the spending cuts don't materialize and everyone says we averted disaster and pats themselves, the economy will be slowed down. Money you once spent will be spent by a politician somewhere to buy someone else something they did not earn. That is called Socialism and it did so well in USSR and China and DPKR and on and on that we must do it here, it is only fair.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356716785135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:46:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356717207371-98</Id><Title>Over the cliff will be the best for the USA, Spending cuts first then higher taxes</Title><Msg>Over the cliff will be the best for the USA, Spending cuts first then higher taxes</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356717207371</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:53:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356717312624-99</Id><Title>We need the spending cut we get by going over the cliff, If not there will never be any spending cuts</Title><Msg>We need the spending cut we get by going over the cliff, If not there will never be any spending cuts</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356717312624</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:55:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356717572226-100</Id><Title>2012's WORST DOW STOCKS</Title><Msg>MCD, HPQ, and INTC. per CNBC.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356717572226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:59:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356717574995-101</Id><Title>CNBC Pete the con man still pumping and dumping INTC, Good job PETE always buy all the way from 29.25</Title><Msg>CNBC Pete the con man still pumping and dumping INTC, Good job PETE always buy all the way from 29.25, not time to buy until Pete the con man says sell</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356717574995</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:59:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356718176800-102</Id><Title>Get IN now</Title><Msg>Time to accumulate INTC, CSCO, AAPL, HP. Switch retailors and oil companies to TECHS</Msg><Username>songliu002</Username><Timestamp>1356718176800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:09:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356718319639-103</Id><Title>Don't worry 2 much about the CLIFF, the mini Plan will go though the House Sunday evening</Title><Msg>Now that Republicans agreed to raise taxes on the rich, Obama and the Demos should comprise on spending cut</Msg><Username>songliu002</Username><Timestamp>1356718319639</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:11:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356718394330-104</Id><Topic><Title>2013 looking like awesome year for INTC</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356713779509</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:56:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good timing to get in</Msg><Username>songliu002</Username><Timestamp>1356718394330</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:13:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356718451732-105</Id><Topic><Title>2013 Could Be a Turnaround Year for Intel</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356712253742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:30:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good time to get in</Msg><Username>songliu002</Username><Timestamp>1356718451732</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:14:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356718477145-106</Id><Topic><Title>bacbacker3 is Ashraf Eassa</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1356715439033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:23:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uh, what? How am I a psychopath? And no, I'm not bacbacker3.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1356718477145</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:14:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356718592065-107</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Smart TV's coming in 2013 from various vendors !!</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1356711377611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:16:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't need to</Msg><Username>songliu002</Username><Timestamp>1356718592065</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:16:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356718835479-108</Id><Title>The mini plan is not good for the USA it has no CUTS the House should vote no without big spending cuts, We need spending CUTS, CUTS and more CUTS</Title><Msg>The mini plan is not good for the USA it has no CUTS. The House should vote no without big spending cuts, We need spending CUTS, CUTS and more CUTS</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356718835479</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:20:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356719063046-109</Id><Title>MLNX stock long strong bullish today</Title><Msg>long strong target 71$</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1356719063046</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:24:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356719075375-110</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Smart TV's coming in 2013 from various vendors !!</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1356711377611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:16:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big question is, will it support PC games? if so, then it is not just a Smart TV, it is also a game box!</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356719075375</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:24:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356719628333-111</Id><Topic><Title>2012's WORST DOW STOCKS</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356717572226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:59:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CNBC ... total jokers.</Msg><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1356719628333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:33:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356719737862-112</Id><Topic><Title>Get IN now</Title><Username>songliu002</Username><Timestamp>1356718176800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:09:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HPQ is falling into the ocean. "retailors"?</Msg><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1356719737862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:35:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356720017941-113</Id><Topic><Title>2012's WORST DOW STOCKS</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356717572226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:59:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you switch back and forth between aliases? Do you ever get tired of bashing? If you are paid, how much do you get? Do you have to clock in and out each day?</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356720017941</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:40:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356720499657-114</Id><Topic><Title>2012's WORST DOW STOCKS</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356717572226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:59:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>perfect prediction scam. one group of IDs bashing and another group of IDs pumping.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77_1923</Username><Timestamp>1356720499657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:48:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356720523369-115</Id><Topic><Title>Get IN now</Title><Username>songliu002</Username><Timestamp>1356718176800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:09:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you're recommending people buy hpq.... you don't have any credibility with me!</Msg><Username>i.alaric</Username><Timestamp>1356720523369</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:48:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356720585440-116</Id><Topic><Title>2013 Could Be a Turnaround Year for Intel</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356712253742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:30:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is not a company that is in a "turnaround" mode. It's massively profitable, dominates all of its core markets, and is looking to expand into others.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1356720585440</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:49:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356723550263-117</Id><Topic><Title>Intel gets patent for motion control safety</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356671362264</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 00:09:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Integrate it into their smartTV product. Will Intel Lead a Television Revolution in 2013? Warning signs show that Internet-connected smart TVs may not be heading for widespread popularity any time soon; a December report from the research firm NPD found that less than 15 percent of smart-TV owners use the devices for listening to music, surfing the Internet, or shopping online. Even though Intel’s (NASDAQ:INTC) Smart TV platform has seen only a few successful designs so far, the company is looking to capitalize on the changing habits of television watchers with a new offering. Digitimes reported on Friday that Intel would be joining with Hewlett-Packard (NYSE:HPQ), Lenovo (LNVGY.PK), Quanta Computer (QUCPF.PK), and Compal Electronics (CMPCY.PK) to launch a new smart-TV platform in 2013.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356723550263</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 14:39:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356723715607-118</Id><Title>With the market and Intel down, Lucy in full jack off mode</Title><Msg>has pants rolled down to ankles and is grabbing himself with both hands.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356723715607</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 14:41:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356724037502-119</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Smart TV's coming in 2013 from various vendors !!</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1356711377611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:16:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who needs it? I'll just turn up the brightness on my old flatscreen. /hat tip to George Carlin</Msg><Username>whowants2be</Username><Timestamp>1356724037502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 14:47:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356724050215-120</Id><Topic><Title>2013 Could Be a Turnaround Year for Intel</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356712253742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:30:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is not a company that is in a "turnaround" mode. It's massively profitable, dominates all of its core markets, and is looking to expand into others. I believe he meant turn the stock price around.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356724050215</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 14:47:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356724104417-121</Id><Topic><Title>2013 Could Be a Turnaround Year for Intel</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356712253742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:30:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fair enough :-)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1356724104417</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 14:48:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356724559214-122</Id><Topic><Title>Intel gets patent for motion control safety</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356671362264</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 00:09:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Integrate it into their smartTV product." My thought exactly. If the Smart TV is like a big screen version of the all-in-one systems, with bolted on TV and Ethernet connectivities, then it will support PC gaming. Articles are saying that these smart TVs will have built in motion sensors (Kinect-like). If this is true, then wouldn't it be possible for PC game makers to create PC games similar to the xbox? this would be where is motion control patent comes in. This smartTV could catch on since leverages the 80% windows user base. The TV becomes another PC device that can you can share photos, music, movies and...play PC games. And the cool part is with Windows 8, the TV will have touch!</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356724559214</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 14:55:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356724735130-123</Id><Topic><Title>The Precarious Nature of ARM's Existing Situation</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356653731924</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 19:15:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This judgement is my projection of current relative performance into the future.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1356724735130</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 14:58:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356724896851-124</Id><Topic><Title>With the market and Intel down, Lucy in full jack off mode</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356723715607</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 14:41:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>go lucy, go. Maybe you can secrete a few drops out of that tiny androgynous weener.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356724896851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:01:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356725210178-125</Id><Topic><Title>Get IN now</Title><Username>songliu002</Username><Timestamp>1356718176800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:09:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not until MID JAN 2013. This could very easily go to $19 or lower</Msg><Username>chachachia34</Username><Timestamp>1356725210178</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:06:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356725874668-126</Id><Title>Mandy on CNBC</Title><Msg>Get that ugly Ho off off CNBC immediately!! Even a pig looks better than Mandy the Donkey's AxSxS face HO. She is ugly, dumb as a rock and talks like a Horse's AxSxS....and that are her good points....</Msg><Username>simpleawright</Username><Timestamp>1356725874668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:17:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356726857382-127</Id><Topic><Title>NOT GOOD for INTC, Demand For Windows 8 Is Weak, Says Fujitsu President</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356711595725</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not good, not selling new computer, Not good for INTC</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356726857382</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:34:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356727261250-128</Id><Title>End of year tax sell off</Title><Msg>We could see a bounce in the new year</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356727261250</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:41:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356727266896-129</Id><Title>Sell ,Sell, Sell no deal, no deal, no deal</Title><Msg>Sell ,Sell, Sell no deal, no deal, no deal</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356727266896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:41:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356727389955-130</Id><Topic><Title>NOT GOOD for INTC, Demand For Windows 8 Is Weak, Says Fujitsu President</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356711595725</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's what waldo never seems to figure out. good chips, bad economy awash in pc's potato chips a far better commodity</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1356727389955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:43:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356727609614-131</Id><Topic><Title>End of year tax sell off</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356727261250</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:41:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>some are of the belief, tax loss selling goes into effect January 1, ie of stocks that sucked last year, ie INTC</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1356727609614</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:46:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356727834150-132</Id><Topic><Title>NOT GOOD for INTC, Demand For Windows 8 Is Weak, Says Fujitsu President</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356711595725</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Michael Dell said Win8 and PC in general were strong!!!</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356727834150</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:50:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356727969691-133</Id><Topic><Title>End of year tax sell off</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356727261250</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:41:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is Intel still "good for 30?" HI-HO WEAVERINO!!!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356727969691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:52:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356728346006-134</Id><Topic><Title>Over 14,000 $22.50 call contracts traded today... speak well for upward motion...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1356576877025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 21:54:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't it possible to tell from the open interest numbers whether it was a buy to open or sell to close? Anyone keep track of the open interest?</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356728346006</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:59:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356728643269-135</Id><Topic><Title>Over 14,000 $22.50 call contracts traded today... speak well for upward motion...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1356576877025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 21:54:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it takes a buyer and a seller to make a market.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1356728643269</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:04:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356728826755-136</Id><Title>well that was kind of brutal at the end.</Title><Msg>Hopefully better days ahead.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356728826755</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:07:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356729119270-137</Id><Topic><Title>End of year tax sell off</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356727261250</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:41:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>better yet, is it still good for 24.00?</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1356729119270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:11:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356729541110-138</Id><Title>20.19 in AH</Title><Msg>lots of stuff down in AH. Maybe new year brings new attitude of joy and merriment ?</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356729541110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:19:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356729630283-139</Id><Topic><Title>Over 14,000 $22.50 call contracts traded today... speak well for upward motion...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1356576877025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 21:54:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is true that a "TO OPEN" transaction increases the OPEN INTEREST "TO CLOSE" transaction decreases the OPEN INTEREST The problem is that the "TO OPEN" can be a SELL or a BUY instigated transaction. "TO CLOSE" can be a SELL or a BUY instigated transaction. The next day OPEN INTEREST is todays OPEN INTEREST + all TO OPEN transactions - all TO CLOSE transactions. There could be a mix of open and close transactions. Today I could SELL TO OPEN some call options early in the day and then BUY TO CLOSE near the end of the trading session for a profit. I think there are people who do same day buy/sell of options. Even the option sites make simplifying assumptions that are guaranteed. I think they can see if the transaction takes place at the BID or the ASK and which way the stock and volatility is going.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356729630283</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:20:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356729716610-140</Id><Topic><Title>Don't worry 2 much about the CLIFF, the mini Plan will go though the House Sunday evening</Title><Username>songliu002</Username><Timestamp>1356718319639</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:11:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>calling rich 250k is way too low. NO DEAL.</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1356729716610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:21:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356729816356-141</Id><Topic><Title>20.19 in AH</Title><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356729541110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:19:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>alas, Santa did not come to Broad and Wall. Bodes poorly for 2013. Any fix by the idiots in Washington is likely, at best,to produce a brief, countertrend rally.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1356729816356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:23:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356730078557-142</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Smart TV's coming in 2013 from various vendors !!</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1356711377611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 11:16:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I feel special.....like every one else.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356730078557</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:27:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356730188399-143</Id><Title>Futures down 219 and dropping INTC going to test 19.23 Monday</Title><Msg>Futures down 219 and dropping INTC going to test 19.23 Monday</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356730188399</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:29:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356730681089-144</Id><Topic><Title>Futures down 219 and dropping INTC going to test 19.23 Monday</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356730188399</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:29:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess we'd better sell then Mr. Nuff, er, I mean Mr. Coinmaker since you're always right. Wish you would take a broom handle and shove it so far up your rear that it tickles your tonsils! Go F yourself.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356730681089</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:38:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356730696239-145</Id><Title>Will Intel Lead a Television Revolution in 2013?</Title><Msg>[Just more evidence that Chump Street has no idea what it is doing...] Digitimes reported on Friday that Intel would be joining with Hewlett-Packard (NYSE:HPQ), Lenovo (LNVGY.PK), Quanta Computer (QUCPF.PK), and Compal Electronics (CMPCY.PK) to launch a new smart-TV platform in 2013. What does Intel have in store for television in 2013? Since 2007, Intel has been releasing home entertainment products including IPTV set-top boxes and low-power processors for networked media players, interactive televisions, and Google TV products. However, the publication’s sources in the component industry stated that the new platform will go beyond basic PC functionality by focusing on its user interface, and it will incorporate voice, gesture, and face recognition systems…</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356730696239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:38:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356730851825-146</Id><Title>nasdaq fut. contracts down 1.5 percent in AH</Title><Msg>ouch. Dow down over 200 points in AH contracts. ouch</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1356730851825</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:40:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356731011345-147</Id><Topic><Title>Futures down 219 and dropping INTC going to test 19.23 Monday</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356730188399</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:29:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The DJI futures fair value is -225 and the futures are -203. Isn't the fair value the zero point normalized for todays drop? You subract the fair value from the futures to get the projected open. That would imply a light "green" open tomorrow by +22. -203 - (-225) = +22</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356731011345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:43:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356731261069-148</Id><Topic><Title>nasdaq fut. contracts down 1.5 percent in AH</Title><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1356730851825</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:40:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think you are another alias for that rick Lucy Nuff. Oops, forgot the "P" in front of rick. Sorry :-)</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356731261069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:47:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356731389388-149</Id><Topic><Title>Will Intel Lead a Television Revolution in 2013?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356730696239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:38:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[Intel has been building the foundation for this for some time. Now their play starts to come clear. Bump for Intel. Bruises for Chump Street...] The Wall Street Journal reported in March that Intel Chief Executive Paul Otellini intended to move the company beyond the computer industry, as the demand for PCs has grown increasingly weak. While Intel’s previous efforts in the TV business have failed to gain much traction, the company has seen an opportunity in the transitioning television industry. With growing number of television watchers turning to the Internet and mobile devices, smart TVs are being considered by Google, Apple, and Microsoft as well. According to the WSJ, Intel has envisioned itself as a virtual cable operator, offering U.S. television channels over the Internet in packages similar to the subscriptions currently sold by cable and satellite-TV providers. Such a service would allow the company to make use of its newly released Atom processor, which has provided Intel with the means to grow beyond its traditional business and put its chips in consumers’ living rooms in increasing numbers.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356731389388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:49:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356731464028-150</Id><Topic><Title>Futures down 219 and dropping INTC going to test 19.23 Monday</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356730188399</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:29:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FUTURES Index Close Cur Future Change 13096.31 12796.0 &amp;nbsp; -207.00 FUTURES FAIR VALUE (22.31) Fair Val Close Cur Future Change 13025.31 12796.0 &amp;nbsp; -229.31</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356731464028</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:51:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356731517737-151</Id><Topic><Title>Don't worry 2 much about the CLIFF, the mini Plan will go though the House Sunday evening</Title><Username>songliu002</Username><Timestamp>1356718319639</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:11:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope you're right, I doubled down today before Obama's comments sent the market down at the end of the day.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1356731517737</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:51:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356731521434-152</Id><Title>Intel® Insider, Delivery Agent to Power New Entertainment Experiences for Ultrabook</Title><Msg>NTERNATIONAL CONSUMER ELECTRONICS SHOW, Las Vegas, Jan. 9, 2012 –Intel Corporation is working with Delivery Agent, Inc., the leader in multi-channel commerce for the largest global media companies and an Intel Capital portfolio company, to bring a vast library of premium television content, from top TV and cable networks, in 1080p HD to Ultrabooks™ and PCs with Intel® Insider. Intel Insider is a hardware feature of the 2nd generation Intel Core processor that allows online content services to offer the latest high-definition (HD) movies and television content in 1080p on Ultrabook, notebook and desktop computers. At the end of 2011, Intel had shipped over 70 million processors that support Intel Insider. Starting later this year, Delivery Agent will integrate Intel® Insider™ technology into its complete commerce engine, which includes Delivery Agent’s proprietary contextual product mapping functionality that lets people watch TV and purchase products tied to the content they are viewing. In addition, people can access Delivery Agent’s TV Wallet™, a transaction engine used by top media companies to process multi-platform commerce transactions tied to their entertainment content. These two features, combined with Intel Insider, will allow people to download TV content in full 1080p HD on their 2nd Generation Intel Core processor-powered Ultrabook, notebook or desktop computer, as well as buy products that are contextually relevant to the show they’re viewing via TV Wallet.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356731521434</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:52:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356731769382-153</Id><Topic><Title>Intel® Insider, Delivery Agent to Power New Entertainment Experiences for Ultrabook</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356731521434</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:52:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel and Delivery Agent will also deliver a compelling second-screen experience when the Intel Insider device is connected to a television using an HDMI cable or wirelessly via Intel®Wireless Display (WiDi). The Delivery Agent media player, powered by Intel Insider, will display relevant information and products about the programming on the PC’s screen while displaying the content in pristine, 1080p on the television at the same time. “Delivery Agent is tasked by the top media companies in the world with delivering a best-inclass commerce experience to their show viewers across all interactive platforms,” said Mike Fitzsimmons, Delivery Agent CEO. “Our relationship with Intel enables us to deliver a 1080p premium content offering, while, at the same time, bringing Delivery Agent’s complete commerce platform to market through Intel Insider.” “People are increasingly streaming and downloading movies and TV shows across all of their connected devices from a variety of online entertainment services,” said George Thangadurai, general manager of Intel’s PC Client Services division. “Delivery Agent’s commerce engine and TV content library helps make the Ultrabook an ideal device for watching online television and having a great second screen experience.”</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356731769382</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:56:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356731819414-154</Id><Topic><Title>Don't worry 2 much about the CLIFF, the mini Plan will go though the House Sunday evening</Title><Username>songliu002</Username><Timestamp>1356718319639</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:11:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There will be at least a "patch" to keep going things going. Obama won't allow his precious 47% tit suckers to get screwed.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356731819414</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:56:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356732047343-155</Id><Title>20.13 in AH ouchie.</Title><Msg>OBama ouchie.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356732047343</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:00:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356732701305-156</Id><Topic><Title>Futures down 219 and dropping INTC going to test 19.23 Monday</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356730188399</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:29:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The numbers look OK. My question was about the meaning. The Dow futures of 12796 on your paste are not exactly -229.31 down from todays Dow close of 12,938. If the DJI opens at your 12,796 number tomorrow AM, That is currently a drop of -142 and not -229 From CNBC .... FUTURES FAIR VALUE (89.11) Fair Val Close Cur Future Change 12866.11 12796.0 &amp;nbsp; -70.11</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356732701305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:11:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356733045322-157</Id><Title>INTC @ 19.15 AH?? Did they warn?</Title><Msg>Not sure if I'm reading this right.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1356733045322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:17:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356733056662-158</Id><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Msg>These things have become clear in recent weeks: 1.) ARMs fabrication roadmap is in serious trouble. Enough that they are seriously contemplating an almost impossible jump of two process levels to 14/16nm FinFET due to the marginal returns that would result from a complex and expensive move to planar 20nm. 2.) Intel can move into major foundry work while maintaining reasonable margins and dramatically improving the bottom line and EPS. 3.) Intel can move into major mobility market share while maintaining reasonable margins and dramatically improving the bottom line and EPS. 4.) Intel has a dramatic roapmap for 2013 and we will be hearing a lot more details at CES in January and at the World Mobile Congress in February. 5.) Intel will be making major tablet and smartphone inroads in 2013 with LTE smartphones coming to the US early in the year. 6.) Intel's superior technology,fabrication, manufacturing and capacity will lead to some major industry-changing deals in 2013. 7.) Intel is preparing to take the lead in the power efficiency race in 2013 while continuing its significant lead in performance. 8.) Intel is going to have some major surprises and developments for us in 2013, particularly in the area of entertainment. "Intel’s relationship with Delivery Agent adds to the growing offerings of premium HD content from Intel Insider-enabled services, including Best Buy CinemaNow*, Hungama Digital Media*and WB* Shop." Delivery Agent is the leader in multi-channel commerce for the largest global media companies and an Intel Capital portfolio company. 9.) 2013 will be a watershed year for Intel in terms of traction for its mobility strategic plan. 10.) The fiscal cliff market adjustment represents a great opening to build or add to an Intel position. There has never been a better time to invest in Intel.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356733056662</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:17:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356733274456-159</Id><Topic><Title>INTC @ 19.15 AH?? Did they warn?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1356733045322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:17:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw it do 20 .12 ....did not see anything that low. They are down more than most, not sure what is going on. A broker may have got wind of a data point or warning, I don't know.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356733274456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:21:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356733290075-160</Id><Topic><Title>Futures down 219 and dropping INTC going to test 19.23 Monday</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356730188399</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:29:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorts make up facts. No surprise that they would throw math under the bus too. Just more Wall Street corruption in play. If the SEC doesn't investigate the big Wall Street firms for what they have done to Intel, it must mean that the jails are already full...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356733290075</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:21:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356733481100-161</Id><Title>20.09</Title><Msg>what is going on ??</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356733481100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:24:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356733610243-162</Id><Topic><Title>20.09</Title><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356733481100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:24:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The usual Wall Street manipulation in AH. What else?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356733610243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:26:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356733693231-163</Id><Topic><Title>Futures down 219 and dropping INTC going to test 19.23 Monday</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356730188399</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:29:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>make up facts ------------- That's really funny! Can one really "make up facts," Peckerwood??? Maybe make up things and then present those things as facts? DUHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHB!!!!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356733693231</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:28:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356733836568-164</Id><Title>In the Meantime</Title><Msg>I love the idea of the Wall Street defective excuses for human beings getting their taxes raised. I'll take my lumps. Off the fiscal cliff we go. No retreat, no surrender...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356733836568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:30:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356733976413-165</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356733056662</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and the funny part is none of it matters. They can't deal with ARMH. see ya at 9.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1356733976413</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:32:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356733988560-166</Id><Title>Imagine</Title><Msg>Imagine lying on your deathbed thinking you wasted your adult life bashing Intel and trying to run the US economy into the dirt. Such will be the end of the life of Lucy/Coinmaker. And now it's another day closer...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356733988560</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:33:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356734087122-167</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356733056662</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"and the funny part is none of it matters. They can't deal with ARMH. see ya at 9." [Yeah, that's what AMD said. We'll see ARM at 9...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356734087122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:34:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356734228834-168</Id><Topic><Title>In the Meantime</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356733836568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:30:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll take my lumps ------------------ Lumps??? INTC beats the #$%$ out of you every day! HI-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356734228834</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:37:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356734289755-169</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356733056662</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mistake to think ARMH threat is like AMD.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1356734289755</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:38:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356734846512-170</Id><Title>The One Man Shill Show</Title><Msg>Will be bashing Intel from his deathbed with intravenous feeds of bile and venom. The problem with Lucy is that he wakes up every day with the feeling that the world is a tuxedo and he is a pair of brown shoes....</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356734846512</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:47:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356734868618-171</Id><Topic><Title>Teen angel, can you hear me?</Title><Username>alan_unable_son</Username><Timestamp>1056569496000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2003-06-25 15:31:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Teen angel can you see me? Are you somewhere just below, where many claim you cannot go? -------------------------------------------------------- I think we may still have a 45rpm copy of that hanging around in the archives somewhere.</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1356734868618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:47:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356734881822-172</Id><Topic><Title>Intel® Insider, Delivery Agent to Power New Entertainment Experiences for Ultrabook</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356731521434</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:52:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you wasted time to tell us this #$%$ ? thanks ....</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356734881822</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:48:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356734929776-173</Id><Topic><Title>Imagine</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356733988560</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:33:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imagine staying up all night pumping a stock, night after night, for years only to see the stock go lower and lower, year after year. Hey, Buttplug, I thought you had me on ignore. HI-HO WEAVERINO! TOOOOO FUNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1356734929776</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:48:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356734945018-174</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356733056662</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"mistake to think ARMH threat is like AMD." [Yeah, you're right. AMD is scrappier...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356734945018</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:49:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356735061160-175</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356733056662</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes they are crappier.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1356735061160</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:51:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356735295073-176</Id><Topic><Title>Intel® Insider, Delivery Agent to Power New Entertainment Experiences for Ultrabook</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356731521434</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:52:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"you wasted time to tell us this #$%$ ? thanks ...." [Now that's funny. Do you ever read any of the total #$%$ you post up? But you're right. I know you short cretins absolutely hate any post that discusses technology or performance or trends because you have no idea what any of it is about. You're much too busy saying weighty things like, "Eek, eek, the sky is falling...] [Oh, here is one of your weighty posts: "ARMH is just getting started in servers." You're a genius, Gump...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356735295073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:54:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356735526301-177</Id><Topic><Title>20.09</Title><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356733481100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:24:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe margin calls SELLS I am not worrying. Monday, it could go $1.00 higher if whole market RALLIES.</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356735526301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:58:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356735775821-178</Id><Title>Intel $20.20 AH</Title><Msg>And more sheep have been shorn...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356735775821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:02:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356735786457-179</Id><Topic><Title>Intel® Insider, Delivery Agent to Power New Entertainment Experiences for Ultrabook</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356731521434</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:52:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow pretty sensitive.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356735786457</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:03:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356735827470-180</Id><Title>Bought 1,000 @ $20.32</Title><Msg>I know it closed lower, but I will sell when it goes above $20.75.</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356735827470</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:03:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356735872238-181</Id><Topic><Title>The One Man Shill Show</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356734846512</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:47:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>appreciate your comments. It helps to counterweight all the baloney from Lucy and his multitude of aliases. Although buyers / sellers originated from Yahoo posts have no effect on Intel price, hate to see some newbie base his sale on Lucy's constant barage of #$%$.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356735872238</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:04:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356735876400-182</Id><Topic><Title>20.09</Title><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356733481100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:24:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah they could make a deal and you would likely be right.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356735876400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:04:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356735978773-183</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356733056662</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>such insight, why did you post this drivel ????</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1356735978773</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:06:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356736150218-184</Id><Topic><Title>Futures down 219 and dropping INTC going to test 19.23 Monday</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356730188399</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:29:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like you don't like the truth, Just keep losing money all the way down from 29.25 when you didn't sell trying to prove me wrong. its your fault you didn't sell not mine</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356736150218</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:09:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356736318771-185</Id><Topic><Title>The One Man Shill Show</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356734846512</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:47:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>exactly my point to attlte4g</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356736318771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:11:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356736416517-186</Id><Topic><Title>Over 14,000 $22.50 call contracts traded today... speak well for upward motion...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1356576877025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 21:54:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thank you</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356736416517</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:13:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356736441553-187</Id><Topic><Title>Futures down 219 and dropping INTC going to test 19.23 Monday</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356730188399</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:29:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What we now know is that some longs may be deficient in certain areas of logic. up is down and all that.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356736441553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:14:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356736807707-188</Id><Title>How about FUTURE done 700 points????????</Title><Msg>even better if 900 points down That will guarantee AAPL trading at $1.25</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356736807707</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:20:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356737181306-189</Id><Title>what things we know now, not for longs to read. Longs stay out. Go away longs.</Title><Msg>Dimtel's price has dropped faster than a dress on prom night. Dimtel forgot that people are mobile. Dimtel has just heard about heat and power and not to waste them. Dimtel does not like win8. . Dimtel has just heard about LTE. Dimtel, I once loved you myself, but it was not to be. Dimtel ohh how I curse thee.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356737181306</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:26:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356737524591-190</Id><Topic><Title>what things we know now, not for longs to read. Longs stay out. Go away longs.</Title><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356737181306</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:26:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>idiot</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356737524591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:32:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356737658590-191</Id><Title>anyone seen the Delivery Agent ?</Title><Msg>evidently you can not watch TV on your lappie without it. oooooo, and it must be an Intel computer too they say. ahhhhh</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356737658590</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:34:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356737732951-192</Id><Topic><Title>Mandy on CNBC</Title><Username>simpleawright</Username><Timestamp>1356725874668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:17:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>step away from yo mirror.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356737732951</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:35:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356737822485-193</Id><Topic><Title>what things we know now, not for longs to read. Longs stay out. Go away longs.</Title><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356737181306</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:26:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As usual the only thing you know how to do is call names. You have no logic, arguments, knowledge facts or analysis. Why don't we just stipulate that you have posted ten or twenty times a day calling Intel a bunch of names and then you can stop posting all together...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356737822485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:37:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356738180935-194</Id><Topic><Title>Mandy on CNBC</Title><Username>simpleawright</Username><Timestamp>1356725874668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:17:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>quip from a dip</Msg><Username>simpleawright</Username><Timestamp>1356738180935</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:43:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356738226355-195</Id><Title>The GOP nimnnutts in the House of reps are NUTS!</Title><Msg>They are playing chicken with a Pres that has 4 years while these idiots have only 2. Worse is the fact that he is not running again and these losers are. It does remind me of the Johnny rebs who were yelling and screaming about their nation and their rights. Kind of like the crazed teabaggers in the GOP. Never mind that you end up slaughtered with your homes burned and your women raped. It was the cause right Johnny. Well OB is in DC and you idiots cannot send a Rebel army to burn down his house this time. In fact, most of the rest of the nation thinks you are nuts. What? You thought you could fool him again like you have so many times in the past? Well--looks like not. His offer today was 250,000 for the taxes and he is not interested in your threats. If you want to take the nation into meltdown with this budget and then the debt ceiling, he will simply wait for the nation to go into meltdown and then declare marshal law and suspend the constitution as did Lincoln. At that time, he can arrest you without a trial teabaggy boys. I think a few of you would look good being tortures at gitmo. But it is all worth it for you because you want your country back right? When the Dow goes down 40% and their are people hating you everywhere you walk--I bet you fat old white men will not be so brave. But a special thanks GOP nummmmnuts for wrecking your party. Oh yeah--Apple-Intel</Msg><Username>amdsuckks</Username><Timestamp>1356738226355</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:43:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356738536590-196</Id><Topic><Title>what things we know now, not for longs to read. Longs stay out. Go away longs.</Title><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356737181306</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:26:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallass do you own Yahoo ? I think not. Are you a moderator ? I think not again. Are you a overly sensitive odd little man/boy ? I think so. When I say stay out of my post if you are long, do just that and we will be fine. Don't come in here crying cause ya pick losers.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356738536590</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:48:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356738547202-197</Id><Topic><Title>what things we know now, not for longs to read. Longs stay out. Go away longs.</Title><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356737181306</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:26:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I told you to stay away, and look now you are all upset.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356738547202</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:49:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356738874179-198</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356733056662</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We know now you are lacking in man areas. I mean many areas.</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1356738874179</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:54:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356739049871-199</Id><Title>Over the cliff. GOP meltdown</Title><Msg>Obummer will get all he wants and you rightwingers will be so so angry at your elected GOP Congress people. Hey---you elected them so EAT IT!</Msg><Username>amdsuckks</Username><Timestamp>1356739049871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:57:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356739523078-200</Id><Topic><Title>Over the cliff. GOP meltdown</Title><Username>amdsuckks</Username><Timestamp>1356739049871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:57:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is for FMLA, SS, Welfare, Public and free everything, Going greek style, ouch. pass the plate. Calling 250k rich, now that is funny. DPRK is his model.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356739523078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 19:05:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356740019461-201</Id><Topic><Title>Intel $20.20 AH</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356735775821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:02:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what a POS</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356740019461</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 19:13:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356740150872-202</Id><Title>will Intel be a teeny bopper again ???</Title><Msg>teen angel ?</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356740150872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 19:15:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356740257962-203</Id><Topic><Title>Will Intel Lead a Television Revolution in 2013?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356730696239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:38:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TVs ....giant snooza.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356740257962</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 19:17:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356740438870-204</Id><Topic><Title>Over the cliff. GOP meltdown</Title><Username>amdsuckks</Username><Timestamp>1356739049871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:57:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A democrat and your money are soon parted.</Msg><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1356740438870</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 19:20:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356740507341-205</Id><Topic><Title>ultrabooks on list of biggest product flops....go Intel !!</Title><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356703749059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:09:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no logic, just calling names and being child like. Intel is a great co. and a #$%$ stock all in one, like a ultrabook yoga. Can we all agree your best posting days are in the past ?</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356740507341</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 19:21:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356741261462-206</Id><Topic><Title>Over the cliff. GOP meltdown</Title><Username>amdsuckks</Username><Timestamp>1356739049871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:57:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HAAA HAAA Yeah the stock market did great under 8 years of GW Bush your republican pres. OH? It crashed? What? The reeaestate market crashed too? What? He started two wars and borrowed to finanace both of them? Funny how NO one in the GOP gave a rat's about the debt until a black man dem was pres. But what would we expect out of a party and nutjob group of idiots who vote for same. I mean after all, they impeached Clinton for having a #$%$ and then being forced to answer questions under oath about same. He lied. Repub trash in the house impeached him. GW Bush starts a war in iraq for no reason and he is fine. But oh well---if you like losing money in the markets--back the GOP.</Msg><Username>hothectors</Username><Timestamp>1356741261462</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 19:34:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356741809854-207</Id><Topic><Title>Over the cliff. GOP meltdown</Title><Username>amdsuckks</Username><Timestamp>1356739049871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:57:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you like losing money via the paycheck taxes ...vote demo...n . If you like taking care of others vote demo. If you think free education is good for minorities ..vote demo. Pretty much if you liked the same policies Hitler and Stalin and Castro embrace vote demo. They work so well.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356741809854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 19:43:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356741886613-208</Id><Title>aintezbeingreen and dominateamerika</Title><Msg>Two more Nuff aliases. This guy really is nuts. My new years wish is for him to fall asleep on an active set of railroad tracks and hopefully he uses one of the rails as a pillow.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356741886613</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 19:44:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356742245642-209</Id><Title>Futures way down if the market was to open now it would be down 329 points</Title><Msg>Futures way down if the market was to open now it would be down 329 points</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356742245642</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 19:50:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356742437957-210</Id><Title>Tanking, Tanking, Tanking Intc will test 19,23 Mondayl</Title><Msg>Tanking, Tanking, Tanking Intc will test 19,23 Mondayl</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356742437957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 19:53:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356742548366-211</Id><Topic><Title>Over the cliff. GOP meltdown</Title><Username>amdsuckks</Username><Timestamp>1356739049871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:57:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Public schools are the main heart of American education. Once you get out of big cities, public schools are fantastic. You say minorities? You have a problem with educating a young child unless they are white do you? Shame on you.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey7</Username><Timestamp>1356742548366</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 19:55:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356743263409-212</Id><Topic><Title>Over the cliff. GOP meltdown</Title><Username>amdsuckks</Username><Timestamp>1356739049871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:57:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What I was saying was PUBLIC education has failed minorities. I am a minority ! We need choices, not gov. education monopoly. Choice and competition lead to a better product ...not education or post office or health care gov. monopolies. Imagine only one car co. !</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356743263409</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 20:07:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356743275239-213</Id><Title>Futures posted on a Fri. night have absolutely no relevancy- ( futures market is closed)</Title><Msg>Reopen at 7PM Sun EST once Asia markets reopen.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356743275239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 20:07:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356744909096-214</Id><Topic><Title>Futures posted on a Fri. night have absolutely no relevancy- ( futures market is closed)</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356743275239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 20:07:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DOH! That explains why my numbers did not add up. thanks</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356744909096</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 20:35:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356746098539-215</Id><Topic><Title>aintezbeingreen and dominateamerika</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356741886613</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 19:44:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wishing death on someone, is that normal or just how you deal with stuff ? Anyway I never take the train.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356746098539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 20:54:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356747157719-216</Id><Topic><Title>Futures posted on a Fri. night have absolutely no relevancy- ( futures market is closed)</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356743275239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 20:07:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>blow hard jerry, has absolutely no relatives that will claim kin with him. Jerry, futures are a measure of sentiment you nitwit. They change quickly and are traded lightly. By trading day they could be as green as you. Good Luck ...you are gonna need it from what I see. Don't let a train hit cha.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356747157719</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:12:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356747244937-217</Id><Topic><Title>In the Meantime</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356733836568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 17:30:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Waldo, plenty of tech geek speak, but zero technical trading skills. great call of his yesterday about how INTC shorts were going to get hammered. Only fools hold semi stocks as long term investments. No excuse for being an old fool, and constantly blaming Wall Street when his beloved INTC goes down.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1356747244937</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:14:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356747854854-218</Id><Title>INTC's chart very similar to BBY's chart</Title><Msg>going down, down every day.....</Msg><Username>trade_4_somegreen</Username><Timestamp>1356747854854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:24:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356747970620-219</Id><Title>Looks like jerry.blown is going to lose a lot more money come Monday morning. INTC just might open down 1-2 dollars, Sleep will Jerry</Title><Msg>Looks like jerry.blown is going to lose a lot more money come Monday morning. INTC just might open down 1-2 dollars, Sleep will Jerry</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356747970620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:26:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356748043430-220</Id><Topic><Title>Don't worry 2 much about the CLIFF, the mini Plan will go though the House Sunday evening</Title><Username>songliu002</Username><Timestamp>1356718319639</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 13:11:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep a partial deal is likely to be a reality, the question remains how will the market react?</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1356748043430</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:27:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356748143230-221</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like jerry.blown is going to lose a lot more money come Monday morning. INTC just might open down 1-2 dollars, Sleep will Jerry</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356747970620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:26:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you drunk posting jerk wad?? Flu cccck you!!!</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1356748143230</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:29:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356748195214-222</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like jerry.blown is going to lose a lot more money come Monday morning. INTC just might open down 1-2 dollars, Sleep will Jerry</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356747970620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:26:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Japan will sell off INTC because windows 8 computers are not selling. Then EURO will sell off INTC because windows 8 computers are not selling and the clowns in DC screwed things up.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356748195214</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:29:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356748371670-223</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like jerry.blown is going to lose a lot more money come Monday morning. INTC just might open down 1-2 dollars, Sleep will Jerry</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356747970620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:26:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like your going to lose a lot of money come Monday to, Sleep will</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356748371670</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:32:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356748561364-224</Id><Title>Futures are tanking INTC should open down 1-2 dollars come Monday. Dow down maybe 400-500</Title><Msg>Futures are tanking INTC should open down 1-2 dollars come Monday. Dow down maybe 400-500</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356748561364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:36:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356748715048-225</Id><Topic><Title>Futures are tanking INTC should open down 1-2 dollars come Monday. Dow down maybe 400-500</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356748561364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:36:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time to put you on ignore, pal.</Msg><Username>livingsez</Username><Timestamp>1356748715048</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:38:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356751409714-226</Id><Topic><Title>Futures posted on a Fri. night have absolutely no relevancy- ( futures market is closed)</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356743275239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 20:07:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yup</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1356751409714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 22:23:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356751828997-227</Id><Topic><Title>Futures are tanking INTC should open down 1-2 dollars come Monday. Dow down maybe 400-500</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356748561364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:36:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is up with you coinmaker, why do you spend so much time postinh your stupid comments.Use your time productively or are you unemployed trying to get even with humanity?</Msg><Username>garoseme</Username><Timestamp>1356751828997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 22:30:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356751960537-228</Id><Title>cliff deal within reach per google news</Title><Msg>Could be a big green new year .</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356751960537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 22:32:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356752504462-229</Id><Topic><Title>Futures are tanking INTC should open down 1-2 dollars come Monday. Dow down maybe 400-500</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356748561364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:36:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like you don't like the truth.Sleep will it looks like you are going to lose a lot of money come Monday also</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356752504462</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 22:41:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356752589635-230</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like jerry.blown is going to lose a lot more money come Monday morning. INTC just might open down 1-2 dollars, Sleep will Jerry</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356747970620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:26:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To is not the same as too, and will isn't even close to the same as well. Frankly I'm surprised you didn't use the word loose, grammar is not your strong point, then again neither is stock picking.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1356752589635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 22:43:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356753694855-231</Id><Title>Marsavian/Alex</Title><Msg>Saw this in the comment secetion of SA article....what would you say to this?: Intel's reliance on the CPU's it makes is all but total. So the question is can Intel remain such a large revenue company with the Desktop market being added to the endangered species list? Think about it, their profit margin is about 3 times that of AMD on every chip they sell, and they sell about 3 times as many, they all but completely dominate the market while AMD get by on the scraps left over. Making chips for Tablets and Mobile Phones will not yield anywhere near the revenue a $300 CPU does, but a fraction of that, in fact. And they will never have it all to themselves. If anyone thinks Intel will muscle ARM out of the way like they did with AMD, Think harder. Think they can remain unchanged, unchallenged filling the same boots selling chips for $20 a piece? Think again. Intel have a much longer way to fall than AMD, that can only mean they will hit the ground so much harder.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1356753694855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 23:01:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356753929543-232</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian/Alex</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1356753694855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 23:01:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what I been saying.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356753929543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 23:05:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356755403101-233</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian/Alex</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1356753694855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 23:01:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What this author doesn't account for is the way Windows 8 convolutes the mix. With Windows 8, the line between tablet and laptop/desktop completely blurs since the OS fully supports both platforms. Secondly, as you can see, Intel is bringing down the power consumption of its elite core series chips down to tablet levels. What we are going to see is desktop and laptops being replaced by a slew of touch enabled form factors all combining the features of laptops with tablets with touch. From the consumer's perspective, they are buying devices that have all the power and functionality of a desktop/laptop with the added convenience of a tablet. Its a win-win for the consumer and Intel. Since we're starting from the laptop/desktop end, you can expect them to pay the same price that they were used to before. Since we're also supporting the tablet form factor with a hybrid design, the total size of the market grows to include the tablet market.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1356755403101</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 23:30:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356755435399-234</Id><Title>Jerry the Blower has no relevancy</Title><Msg>His parents disavow any knowledge of him. Brother and sister say he aint kin to them either.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356755435399</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 23:30:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356755856911-235</Id><Topic><Title>Will Intel Lead a Television Revolution in 2013?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356730696239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:38:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many times they gonna do the computer TV thing ? fail after fail. I don't think Apple can even do it. Intel sure as hell can not do it. They could not even do a phone or a tab.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1356755856911</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 23:37:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356757138267-236</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian/Alex</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1356753694855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 23:01:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who are you? weren't you the one thrashing Intel just yesterday?</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1356757138267</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 23:58:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>