<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350705722613-1</Id><Topic><Title>February 23, 2009</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350696522864</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:28:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got to love those Bush wars and tax cuts. _________________________________ Hey Einstein (Wallisweaver) Bush added 5 trillion in debt in 8 years and that's with 2 wars. Obama has added almost 6 Trillion in just 4 years and didn't even do a war. Obama has added more debt in half the time as bush!!!!!!!!!!!!! STAGGERING...but you'll vote for him like many will because they only care about your party winning, at any cost.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350705722613</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 00:02:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350705994580-2</Id><Topic><Title>Im a PC. Heres why</Title><Username>bull_v_fighter</Username><Timestamp>1350700181601</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 22:29:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ulbrabook convertibles are going to change the world, and sounds like you'll buy and love one as you'll have a kick #$%$ laptop with Intel inside and it will be able to convert to a Windows tablet whenver you feel like acting like a kid and playing with a toy. Why would anyone buy anything else once those come out?</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350705994580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 00:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350709129724-3</Id><Title>Intel's dividend yield is in top five Dow 30 stocks.</Title><Msg>And very close to being in top 4. Plus, Intel's ability to pay its dividend is the strongest out of all the Dow stocks. Making Intel the best dividend play.</Msg><Username>viperjk99</Username><Timestamp>1350709129724</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 00:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350716388920-4</Id><Topic><Title>Im a PC. Heres why</Title><Username>bull_v_fighter</Username><Timestamp>1350700181601</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 22:29:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good one attglte...thought you wre a short.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350716388920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 02:59:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350716671760-5</Id><Topic><Title>Im a PC. Heres why</Title><Username>bull_v_fighter</Username><Timestamp>1350700181601</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 22:29:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you'll have to stay with windows 7.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350716671760</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 03:04:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350724322289-6</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, 14M shares dumped in 5 minutes.</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1350480975053</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lower lows every day = stay away for now.</Msg><Username>borderescalade</Username><Timestamp>1350724322289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 05:12:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350733237991-7</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT better offer dual boot</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350679458490</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:44:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Start menu has pretty much always sucked, we just got used to it...I think Windows 8 will be a SMASH success, the younger generation loves their tablets and smartphones so much, they should latch right onto Windows 8... It will also be easier for people who are computer 'handicapped' (I work with SEVERAL) of them... Also, if your a real techo, you will do everthing at the command line and that is well supported with PowerShell... So Windows 8 is a hit with the techies, a hit with the clueless and a hit with the younger generation... It will be a SMASH hit...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350733237991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 07:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350733370258-8</Id><Topic><Title>intel should buy amd</Title><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1350688642783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 19:17:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buying AMD would send INTC down to the low teens... number 1, number 2 - AMD has NOTHING that Intel needs... They'd be better off letting AMD die the slow death that it has been...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350733370258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 07:42:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350733675272-9</Id><Topic><Title>easy way to get rich</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1350693015705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 20:30:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would have down myself well to have sold off on Tuesday when it hit 22.40 and then taken your advice and turned right around and shorted the crap out of it... At this point though, it's such a high dividend for the money and the ex-div date is right around the corner, I think if it starts going up again it won't stop till it gets around 22.70 or so, till after the ex div date... and if Window 8 is shown to be a huge success by then, it may just continue to climb... however it Windows 8 pcs are left collecting dust on store shelves, then it will probably fall back down to the mid teens... We'll see I guess...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350733675272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 07:47:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350734378288-10</Id><Topic><Title>Pumper's Holiday?</Title><Username>freakquently</Username><Timestamp>1350677344247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:09:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They'll be back Monday when it goes back up by at least 30 cents at close, but reaching a high of right around $22 at some point during the day. I'm second guessing myself for now scrounging together some funds and buying it when it hit $21.23 on Friday, I was watching and sat on my hands, I think the next 2 weeks will be the TELL all as to where we're headed by the end of the year. If we end near the high 22s or better by the end of the next 2 week, then I say 25 by the end of the year, however if we stay down in the low 22s or lower by the end of the next 2 weeks then I say 17 to 18 by the end of the year... We'll see...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350734378288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 07:59:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350735789501-11</Id><Title>$24 PUT options cost are rising, does this also indicate a rising stock price?</Title><Msg>PUT options 24.00 NOV 2012 - 2.95 24.00 DEC 2012 - 2.99 24.00 JAN 2013 - 3.05 Looks positive to me, only 10 cents, but at least it may signal a upward trend...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350735789501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350736479853-12</Id><Topic><Title>$24 PUT options cost are rising, does this also indicate a rising stock price?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350735789501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:23:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the price difference is because they have different time value. it's like insurance a 2 year insurance will cost more then 1 year. etc.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350736479853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:34:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350736638858-13</Id><Title>PC upgrade cycle</Title><Msg>Microsoft's Windows 8 is the latest version of the popular PC operating system and it is expected to be launched on October 26, 2012. In the past, a new release of Windows has created an upgrade cycle, as it often motivates consumers and businesses to buy new PCs and software. Conversely, it is not uncommon for buyers to hold off on buying a new PC or software if they know a new version will soon be available. This can lead to soft sales in the short term, but that can create pent-up demand once the latest version is released. That is why Microsoft could see stronger sales in the coming quarters. (from seekingalpha)</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350736638858</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:37:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350736794195-14</Id><Topic><Title>PC upgrade cycle</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350736638858</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow, I didn't know that! wow! idiot</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1350736794195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:39:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350737014642-15</Id><Topic><Title>PC upgrade cycle</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350736638858</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My thoughts too of course... and Windows 8 is the 1st 'fresh' user interface since windows 95, I think it will be a big hit...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350737014642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:43:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350738486316-16</Id><Topic><Title>PC upgrade cycle</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350736638858</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are a known #$%$ by now, you posts baseless staff and when Alex challenged your post you went back to your corner as you should.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350738486316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 09:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350738524921-17</Id><Topic><Title>PC upgrade cycle</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350736638858</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I also believe it will be big success. Windows 8 is really a unique and even revolutionary. I love the metro style, I used it on windows phone and welcome it on PC</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350738524921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 09:08:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350738716013-18</Id><Title>TODAY'S BARRON'S COVER STORY- 'BYE-BYE, PCS'</Title><Msg>Preview- "Bye-Bye, PCs" By Tiernan Ray As the PC era wanes, Dell and HP will fade from view. Tablets, smartphones, and big data will drive Apple, Google, and EMC</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1350738716013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 09:11:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350739466139-19</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's dividend yield is in top five Dow 30 stocks.</Title><Username>viperjk99</Username><Timestamp>1350709129724</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 00:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nov 5 is the next expiration day</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350739466139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 09:24:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350739621597-20</Id><Topic><Title>PC upgrade cycle</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350736638858</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Early look at Windows 8 baffles consumers Early taste of Windows 8 baffles consumers, as Microsoft ditches familiar look and feel By Peter Svensson, AP Technology Writer | Associated Press – 15 hours ago.. . NEW YORK (AP) -- The release of Microsoft's Windows 8 operating system is a week away, and consumers are in for a shock. Windows, used in one form or another for a generation, is getting a completely different look that will force users to learn new ways to get things done. Microsoft is making a radical break with the past to stay relevant in a world where smartphones and tablets have eroded the three-decade dominance of the personal computer. Windows 8 is supposed to tie together Microsoft's PC, tablet and phone software with one look. But judging by the reactions of some people who have tried the PC version, it's a move that risks confusing and alienating customers. Tony Roos, an American missionary in Paris, installed a free preview version of Windows 8 on his aging laptop to see if Microsoft's new operating system would make the PC faster and more responsive. It didn't, he said, and he quickly learned that working with the new software requires tossing out a lot of what he knows about Windows. "It was very difficult to get used to," he said. "I have an 8-year-old and a 10-year-old, and they never got used to it. They were like, 'We're just going to use Mom's computer.'" Windows 8 is the biggest revision of Microsoft Corp.'s operating system since it introduced Windows 95 amid great fanfare 17 years ago. Ultimately, Windows grew into a $14 billion a year business and helped make former Chief Executive Bill Gates the richest man in the world for a time. Now, due to smartphones and tablets, the personal computer industry is slumping. Computer companies are desperate for something that will get sales growing again. PC sales are expected to shrink this year for the first time since 2001, according to IHS iSuppli, a market research firm. The question is whether the new version, which can be run on tablets and smartphones, along with the traditional PC, can satisfy the needs of both types of users. "I am very worried that Microsoft may be about to shoot itself in the foot spectacularly," said. Michael Mace, the CEO of Silicon Valley software startup Cera Technology and a former Apple employee. Windows 8 is so different, he said, that many Windows users who aren't technophiles will feel lost, he said. Microsoft is releasing Windows 8 on Oct. 26, and it doesn't plan to cushion the impact. Computer companies will make Windows 8 standard on practically all PCs that are sold to consumers. Speaking to Wall Street analysts on Thursday, Microsoft's chief financial officer Peter Klein said he isn't very concerned that user confusion could slow the adoption of Windows 8. When Microsoft introduces new features, he said, people eventually realize that "those innovations have delivered way more value, way more productivity and way better usability." That's going to be true of Windows 8 too, he said. Instead of the familiar Start menu and icons, Windows 8 displays applications as a colorful array of tiles, which can feature updated information from the applications. For instance, the "Photos" tile shows an image from the user's collection, and the "People" tile shows images from the user's social-media contacts. (Microsoft is licensed to use AP content in the Windows 8 news applications.) The tiles are big and easy to hit with a finger — convenient for a touch screen. Applications fill the whole screen by default — convenient for a tablet screen, which is usually smaller than a PC's. The little buttons that surround Windows 7 applications, for functions like controlling the speaker volume, are hidden, giving a clean, uncluttered view. When you need those little buttons, you can bring them out, but users have to figure out on their own how to do it. "In the quest for simplicity, they sacrificed obviousness," said Sebastiaan de With, an interface designer and the chief creative officer at app developer DoubleTwist in San Francisco. Technology blogger Chris Pirillo posted a YouTube video of his father using a preview version of Windows 8 for the first time. As the elder Pirillo tours the operating system with no help from his son, he blunders into the old "Desktop" environment and can't figure out how to get back to the Start tiles. (Hint: Move the mouse cursor into the top right corner of the screen, then swipe down to the "Start" button that appears, and click it. On a touch screen, swipe a finger in from the right edge of the screen to reveal the Start button.) The four-minute video has been viewed more than 1.1 million times since it was posted in March. "There are many things that are hidden," said Raluca Budiu, a user experience specialist with Nielsen Norman Group. "Once users discover them, they have to remember where they are. People will have to work hard and use this system on a regular basis." Mace, the software CEO, has used every version of Windows since version 2.0, which came out in 1987. Each one, he said, built upon the previous one. Users didn't need to toss out their old ways of doing things when new software came along. Windows 8 ditches that tradition of continuity, he said. "Most Windows users don't view their PCs as being broken to begin with. If you tell them 'Oh, here's a new version of Windows, and you have to relearn everything to use it,' how many normal users are going to want to do that?" he asked. The familiar Windows Desktop is still available through one of the tiles, and most programs will open up in that environment. But since the Start button is gone, users will have to flip back and forth between the desktop and the tile screen. There's additional potential for confusion because there's one version of Windows 8, called "Windows RT," that looks like the PC version but doesn't run regular Windows programs. It's intended for tablets and lightweight tablet-laptop hybrids. Budiu believes the transition to Windows 8 will be most difficult for PC users, because Microsoft's design choices favor touch screens rather than mice and keyboards. Alex Wukovich, a Londoner who tried Windows 8 on a friend's laptop, agrees. "On a desktop, it just felt really weird," he said. "It feels like it's a tablet operating system that Microsoft managed to twist and shoehorn onto a desktop." Not everyone who has tried Windows 8 agrees with the critics. Sheldon Skaggs, a Web developer in Charlotte, N.C., thought he was going to hate Windows 8, but he needed to do something to speed up his 5-year-old laptop. So he installed the new software. "After a bit of a learning curve and playing around with it a bit more, you get used to it, surprisingly," he said. The computer now boots up faster than it did with Windows Vista, he said. Vista was Microsoft's most recent operating-system flop. It was seen as so clunky and buggy when released in 2007 that many PC users sat out the upgrade cycle and waited for Windows 7, which arrived two and a half years later. Companies and other institutions wait much longer than consumers to upgrade their software, and many will keep paying for Windows 7. Many companies are still using Windows XP, released in 2001. Colin Gillis, an analyst at BGC Financial, is optimistic about Windows 8, pointing out that it's snappy and runs well on PCs with limited processing power, making it suited for compact, tablet-style machines. But he also notes that through Microsoft's history, roughly every other operating-system release has been a letdown. Intel Corp. makes the processors that go into 80 percent of PCs, and has a strong interest in the success of Windows. CEO Paul Otellini said Tuesday that when the company has let consumers try Windows 8 on expensive "ultrabook" laptops with touch screens, "the feedback is universally positive." But he told analysts that he doesn't really know if people will embrace Windows 8 for mainstream PCs. "We'll know a lot more about this 90 days from now," he said.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1350739621597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 09:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350751937395-21</Id><Topic><Title>Pumper's Holiday?</Title><Username>freakquently</Username><Timestamp>1350677344247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:09:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe they injured their wrists?</Msg><Username>semiconductorguy</Username><Timestamp>1350751937395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 12:52:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350752069697-22</Id><Topic><Title>$19 support nothing till than......</Title><Username>febru3012</Username><Timestamp>1350673826390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sell Short and make money.</Msg><Username>borderescalade</Username><Timestamp>1350752069697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 12:54:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350752696400-23</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Deliberately Sets the ARM Surface RT Price Too High</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350520653506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess again, Chump. Do you ever get tired of yourself? It's a good sign for Redmond. Microsoft is reporting that its Windows RT Surface tablet Relevant Products/Services's $499 model sold out in a single day of pre-orders. The next batch is supposed to ship out within three weeks.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1350752696400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350753479254-24</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Deliberately Sets the ARM Surface RT Price Too High</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350520653506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Posted: 2012-10-19 @ 12:50pm PT Speculation related to Microsoft Windows 8 and associated devices has been anecdotal with very few getting their facts straight. Windows RT screams enterprise. You get the benefit of the lower cost for Windows RT devices and extended battery while also being able to still access x86 applications from the Windows RT tablets using the RemoteApp feature in Windows Server 2012. You can remotely stream x86 applications via the updated RemoteApp feature baked into Windows Server 2012.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1350753479254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:17:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350753659937-25</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Deliberately Sets the ARM Surface RT Price Too High</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350520653506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Talk about a DELUSIONAL, self-serving and deceiving subject line. Denial is very dangerous, Wallchump. Heck, you're just a typical lying Liberal.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1350753659937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:20:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350753908204-26</Id><Topic><Title>$24 PUT options cost are rising, does this also indicate a rising stock price?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350735789501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:23:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mystk7 is correct. There is the TIME VALUE but the SMALL difference is due to several things in this particular case: 1. DEPTH INTO THE MONEY 2. LOW BETA ... Intel stock price is not expected to be volatile. small trading range 3. OPTION MARKET MAKER PREPARING FOR EX-DIVIDEND. 0. TIME VALUE OPTION MONSTER has a good chart that shows TIME VALUE visually. select QUOTE INTC in the window which will have VIX STRATEGY SEEK The chart shows the time value as time TIME PASSES and it shows the PROBABILITY as you get farther away from the STRIKE VALUE. 1. DEPTH INTO THE MONEY. The primary purpose of options is RISK REDUCTION and the PUT is insurance on the down side. If someone owned (bought) the puts in GOOG they were protected from the $70 drop. The SELLERS or WRITERS/SELLERS of those GOOG put options absorbed the DROP (not loss since they wanted to own the shares). The depth in the money is like the DEDUCTABLE on insurance. The higher the PUT strike, the more risk the buyer is assuming. He will sell and close out before expiration since it was just insuance. 95% of option expire worthless.... guess why .... those that are not worthless get closed. As a byproduct of someone buying an "insurance premium", those wanting to buy the shares cheaper can simply WRITE or SELL the option and the premium reduces the effective cost. 3. OPTION MARKET MAKER PREPARING FOR EX-DIVIDEND. The option market maker and/or someone is preparing for an ex-dividend arbitrage game. The option market maker prepares each day. A dividend drop pricing SHOULD show up EQUALLY in the put and call options. It does for FAR OUT option expiration months. However, as dividend day approaches the premium shifts into the PUT and out of the CALL. An UNCHANGED stock will show a dividend drop on ex-dividend day. It then trades from that point. All CALL OPTIONS that have no premium on the day before ex-dividend will be exercised early. The person who sold the option will lose the shares and dividend. _____________________ If you look $3 deep into the CALLs at $18 for the same months, with the price leaning to make the ITM calls more pricy by 26 cents ($21.26 stock price), you would expect the CALLS to be 26 cents higher than the calls. CALL options with $18 strike. 18.00 NOV 2012 - $3.25 18.00 DEC 2012 - $3.25 18.00 JAN 2013 - NONE there is a $17.50 CALL options with $15.00 strike 15.00 NOV - $6.25 15.00 DEC - $6.25 15.00 JAN 2013 - $6.25</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350753908204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:25:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350753929120-27</Id><Title>Ultrabooks that convert to Tablets will deem The Surface Tablet "unbuyable" within 9 months</Title><Msg>Booyaaaaaaaaaaa.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350753929120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:25:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350754205261-28</Id><Title>AAPL solution</Title><Msg>Everyone knows by now that AAPL and Samsung don't play nice together in the sand box. After the lawsuits, AAPL has no choice but to find another fab for their devices. TSM immediately comes to mind, but they don't have the latest technology (they're still having problems with 28nm supply) and QCOM and AAPL have each reportedly tried to pay TSM sums like 10B to increase production for them and were turned down. The only other alternative is INTC which said they would make ARMH processors for a select few manufacturers if the conditions were right. To date that hasn't happened even though NVDA has publically asked them too. You can bet AAPL has asked them and were turned down for some reason. AAPL will be in a world of hurt if they don't secure fab production shortly because you know Samsung will pay them back for the lawsuits. If AAPL were smart, they would offer to buy 30% of INTC shares at $30.00/share. This would give them a big voting block of shares and they would be able to secure several seats on the BOD to champion their interests. AAPL has their own hedge fund located in Las Vegas and reportedly has 130B in assets. Buying 30% of INTC would cost 30% of 5 billion shares = 1.5 billion x $30.00 = 45 billion. This would take the INTC PE from 9 to</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350754205261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:30:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350755147243-29</Id><Topic><Title>Ultrabooks that convert to Tablets will deem The Surface Tablet "unbuyable" within 9 months</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350753929120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:25:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ultrabooks are said to finally hit the 699$ price next year and the floodgates will open, especially with 22nm, Windows 8 and Touchscreen covertible. I'll pre-order one.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350755147243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350755973094-30</Id><Topic><Title>February 23, 2009</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350696522864</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:28:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis is "Einstein"? He is a doofus like Lucy!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! WHORHEY did not fire up the Iraq war until half way through his term so he did not get the full BENEFIT of its effect. WHORHEY did not get all the cuts for the rich in place until half way through. Same with Medicare Part D costs. THEN IN 2008, just months before the end of his destruction of America, WHORHEY tanked the economy and brought on the FINANCIAL CRISIS. He destroyed normal REVENUE. OBAMA has had the FULL BENEFIT of the BUSH spending burden for 4 years PLUS BUSH financial crisis revenue destruction for 4 years. BUSH had his spend burden for 4 years PLUS his revenue destruction for ZERO years. BUSH today would be IDENTICAL to Obama. If ROMNEY were elected in 2008, it would be IDENTICAL. Anyone who thinks that ROMEY will be better for America than Obama is rationalizing. STAGGERING that you have such a shallow understanding of economics and shout so loud. RUSH .... is that YOU???? Those voting for ROMNEY are the ones who only care about their party winning. They don't even know what he stands for today. Which ROMNEY are they or YOU voting for? Generous ROMNEY donations .... to his personal foundation which ONLY HE donates to and to SUPER PACS supporting ROMNEY. The American people just get to pay for the tax deductibility of those donations.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1350755973094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:59:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350756009968-31</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>douglasinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1350733223265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 07:40:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks, I tried this out just now and it is nice.</Msg><Username>frozencustardking</Username><Timestamp>1350756009968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 14:00:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350758001492-32</Id><Title>PC is dead? LAUGHABEL: Dell XPS Convertible Ultrabook?Tablet just on TV - Pre orders taken now</Title><Msg>The dominoes are starting to fall. Dell’s XPS 12 Convertible Ultrabook – A Windows 8 Laptop and Tablet in One Lionel Menchaca, Chief Blogger 19 Oct 2012 3:15 PM As many of you are already aware, we recently started taking preorders for several of our machines with Windows 8. Out of our new products, one that has probably generated the most buzz was the XPS 12, a convertible Ultrabook that combines the power of a laptop with the convenience of a tablet. Converting from one to the other is a snap. The vibrant full HD 12.5” display rotates via an elegant flip hinge mechanism providing a smooth, seamless transition. In other words, you can convert from laptop mode to a tablet in seconds. Take a look at this quick video overview to see what I mean: Our engineering and design teams started with the same approach that has made the XPS 13 such a success: to build a solid, high-performance product by using premium materials and merging them with the latest available technology. Premium materials help make the system look great, but our design teams also chose materials for real functional benefits in terms of weight and durability. The XPS 12 starts at 3.35 pounds thanks to design choices like carbon fiber found on the back of the panel and on the base of the system. In addition to keeping the system light, the carbon fiber base also keeps the base comfortably cool when you’re using it on your lap. Our design teams chose machined aluminum for the frame because of its rigid properties, providing a solid framework for the flip hinge panel design. Corning Gorilla Glass is bonded to the panel for added rigidity. I recently got a chance to spend a little time with one, and I can say I noticed a couple of things right off the bat—that Windows 8 touch interface works really well, and that this machine offers some pretty solid performance because it is a full-blown laptop. Just as reviewers like Walt Mossberg have noted, touch performance in Windows 8 is stellar. It’s clear that the operating system was built with touch as one of the primary ways of interacting. Coupling that with the 10-finger capacitive-touch display results in snappy performance in a number of tasks. So whether you’re scrolling through the Windows 8 home screen, scrolling up or down a web page or pinching and zooming on images, you’ll notice the responsiveness. Update from Lionel: Click on either of the images below to see a larger version. To see more pictures, take a look at the XPS 12 Convertible Ultrabook album on Dell's Google+ page. XPS 12 convertible Ultrabook running Windows 8 Since the XPS 12 is based on Intel’s Ivy Bridge technology with processor options up to the Core i7 and the integrated HD 4000 graphics, it makes sense that performance is solid across any laptop-specific tasks you need to tackle. Productivity tasks like editing a presentation or a Word doc are as quick as you’d expect. Same goes for watching videos or streaming videos on services like Netflix or Hulu. Beyond the effectiveness of touch and the great overall performance I noticed, there’s a lot to like about the screen as well. The -full HD (1920 x 1080) display supports –wide viewing angles up to 170 degrees, which means that the screen looks great from almost any angle. In other words, you can look at it from the side and still see the slick Windows 8 tile interface in great detail. The brightness and clarity of the display is noticeable as well. It’s rated at a brightness level of 400nits. The glass integrated touchpad builds on the multi-touch gesture capability that we first introduced with the XPS 13. And since this machine is designed for Windows 8, our teams worked hard to deliver a consistent Windows 8 touchpad experience on the XPS 12 and other products. In a future post, I’ll sit down with a key member from that team to explain Dell’s approach in more detail. Dell XPS 12 convertible Ultrabook in tablet mode The XPS 12 utilizes a built-in 47-watt 6-cell battery. Based on our labs updated tests using the new MobileMark 2012 industry benchmark, users can expect –up to 6 hours, 7 minutes* of battery life in typical use, according to our labs’ testing. For customers in the United States, the XPS 12 comes with Americas Best Warranty, which includes one year In-Home Service after Remote Diagnosis, and one year Premium Phone Support. See previous link for more details. Business customers who buy the XPS 12 can opt for our ProSupport service. XPS 12 configurations will vary by region, but all configs come with SSD drives. Those drives work together with technologies like Intel Smart Response, Rapid Start and Smart Connect technology for fast boot times, and keeping your email inbox current, even when the system is in sleep mode. The fact that the XPS 12 runs the 64-bit version of Windows 8 in all configurations means you can run many of the applications you’re used to running in Windows 7. But it also means you can run Windows 8 apps (the ones that like Live Tiles in the screenshots above) either in tablet mode or laptop mode. We’re also including an app called “Getting Started with Windows 8” – a video tutorial designed to help you navigate the most basic operations in the new Windows 8 user interface. This includes basics like shutting down the system, pinning an app and accessing Charms. The XPS 12 is currently available for preorder in several countries like the United States and Canada, UK, France and Germany. It will be available in more countries soon. Pricing for customers in the United States starts at $1,199.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350758001492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 14:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350758197345-33</Id><Title>Idiots like Lucy can just watch "Getting started with Windows 8"</Title><Msg>We’re also including an app called “Getting Started with Windows 8” – a video tutorial designed to help you navigate the most basic operations in the new Windows 8 user interface. This includes basics like shutting down the system, pinning an app and accessing Charms.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350758197345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 14:36:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350758425460-34</Id><Title>Intel best Long Term Dividend Investment</Title><Msg>They've never been in a better position to keep paying and INCREASE the Dividend. See Yahoo news.</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1350758425460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 14:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350761744403-35</Id><Title>Motorola Droid Razr i smartphone review.</Title><Msg>Motorola played a big part in the early success of Android, with its Droid devices catapulting Android into the mainstream, especially in the US. Although Motorola has struggled to compete with the likes of Samsung and HTC in the UK, the Razr i could signal a change of direction. Instead of relying on chip firms like NVIDIA and Qualcomm - Motorola is the first high-end manufacturer to strap an Intel processor inside its handset. We've previously seen one of these Medfield-based Atom chips in the Orange San Diego, but the Z2460 used in that handset has been upgraded to the Z2480 in the Razr i. It's still a single-core part with Hyper-Threading, but the clock speed has been raised from 1.6GHz to 2GHz. This makes it one of the fastest phones we've ever seen. Performance The Razr i's theoretical power translated to decent benchmark performance. In GeekBench the Razr i scored 981 – higher than the 709 scored by the HTC One X, but lagging behind the 1,387 result of Samsung’s Galaxy S3. The Razr i performed well in other benchmarks, too. The Intel processor overhauled the Samsung’s quad-core Exynos chip in the SunSpider benchmark, completing the test in 1,052ms – quicker than the 1,430ms of the Samsung. Using an Intel chip provides plenty of power as expected when bench-marking, but it does translate to excellent real-world performance. Android was slick in use, with no hint of juddering when opening the app drawer, navigating menus or switching between homescreens, and games ran largely without issues – we noticed the tiniest of framerate drops in graphical intensive apps such as Reckless Racing 2 and Dead Trigger, but it’s not enough to stop us playing. Battery life We’re willing to live with the slight performance issues though as the Razr i has stunning battery life – the best result we’ve ever seen. For our intensive battery test we set corporate email, Gmail, Facebook and Twitter accounts up to push content to the phone throughout the day, and we also carried out a range of tasks – including browsing the web and watching a forty minute video. Brightness was cranked up to maximum, Wi-Fi turned off, and battery saving modes were also disabled. Motorola’s phone is the third handset to last beyond the 12 hour mark in our test, and it’s the longest-lasting Ice Cream Sandwich device we’ve tested. After twelve hours the Razr i still well over a third of battery power remaining (34 per cent). This beat the Samsung Galaxy S3, which had 27 per cent remaining at 12 hours and left the iPhone 5 for dead as the Apple device ran out of juice completely after 10 hours. Display It's got good power and top-tier battery life, but the Razr i isn't as expensive as the priciest handsets. The screen is one area where the budget has obviously been cut: the 4.3in panel is physically smaller than the 4.8 screens included on other phones, and the resolution of 540 x 960 means the Motorola can't compete on a pixel-by-pixel basis, either - its 256ppi is no match for the 306ppi of the Samsung. Pixels are visible if you look closely, but the Motorola redeems itself elsewhere. The AMOLED screen’s brightness level of 219cd/m2 is reasonable, even if it can’t match the 240cd/m2 of the Galaxy S3. That’s partnered with the perfect contrast provided by the AMOLED panel, and it makes for a screen’s punchy, with accurate colours. The handset itself doesn’t break much new ground, but build quality is good throughout, and its 8.3mm girth is 0.3mm thinner than the Samsung. The styling won’t be to everyone’s taste, with exposed screws and Kevlar backing lending the Razr i an industrial feel. Durability has been improved across the entire handset thanks to Motorola’s water-repellant Splash-Guard coating, and this is one of the toughest Android handsets on the market. Android needs updating The presence of the dated Ice Cream Sandwich, inevitably, comes as a disappointment – while Motorola says that Jelly Bean will make its way to the device, it’s given no indication of dates. Despite this, Motorola has made Ice Cream Sandwich work extremely well on the Razr i, making small tweaks rather than sweeping changes. The lockscreen is home to a neat circular widget that unlocks the phone directly into the caller, text-messaging and camera apps depending on which are selected, and there’s another circular widget – literally called Circles – that takes centre-stage on the homescreen. It’s made from a trio of circular graphics that provide time, weather and battery information, as well as some notifications. Swipe down on each of these circles and they flip over, serving up additional information. The Smart Actions app is well-conceived and executed, too. Taking after third-party Android apps like Tasker, it allows you to set specific rules for the phone in order to change its behaviour. A host of rules are included by default: one reminds you to charge the handset if the battery dips below 50 per cent in the evening, for instance, and another uses the phone’s GPS to turn ringtones off when you’re at the office. It’s easy to create your own. Customisable “triggers” can use all manner of settings around the device in order to start or stop actions, and dozens of different effects can be used in order to alter the phone’s behaviour. Camera The inclusion of an 8-megapixel camera won’t turn any heads, but quality is reasonable – it captures colours that aren’t a million miles away from the bright, accurate tones of top-end handsets, and detail is good, too, with detail that’s close to the levels managed by the Galaxy S3. The camera’s software is impressive, too. The phone goes from its standby mode to the camera application in just over a second, and takes one and a half seconds to take the first shot. Elsewhere, there’s a decent HDR mode for brightening up shots, and a 10fps burst mode too. Conclusion It’s technically a mid-range phone, but Motorola’s latest continually punches above its weight thanks to stunning battery life, good performance and a reasonable screen. If high-end phones are just too large or expensive, and battery life is important, this is an excellent choice.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1350761744403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 15:35:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350765233068-36</Id><Title>Seasonal pricing of INTC</Title><Msg>According to the historical pricing of INTC, the worst month is October. Nov, Dec, and Jan are the best months to own INTC. If you are going to own it, then this month would be the best time to buy it.</Msg><Username>tlee22202</Username><Timestamp>1350765233068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 16:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350768071571-37</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Deliberately Sets the ARM Surface RT Price Too High</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350520653506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can remotely stream x86 applications via the updated RemoteApp .. ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------ LOL. that's a bad solution at best, creating a bottleneck and not efficient. The Intel version of MS tablet will be adopted by companies and will roll to the customers as a default.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350768071571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 17:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350768547122-38</Id><Title>AMD going bankrupt will allow Intel much better pricing power.</Title><Msg>Of course Intel picks up the 20 % unit share, but better is the increase in ASPs. Intel. Shorty with big institutional Auto selling pushed Intel down but it is only temporary this time. Phone chips sell in volume in 2013 and server sales bounce again. Net incomes well past 4 billion a quarter are coming in late 2013 and then to 5 billion a quarter or more in 2014. Joe #$%$bucket wallstreet GOPTArds will be over their crying soon as they except that Obummer wins again. The Blacks, Hispanics, and Asians along with a core of 35% of the white votes is more than enough to make Rombo two sides go down. The voter turnout on election day will be your sign that your GOP #$%$mwackks have lost to Obummer. Huge voting lines in Ohio, Penn, Michigan, Illinois, Iowa, Wisconsin, and Florida will have Fuxeeed up news into hysteria. Hannity bad wig boy will sheet his pants. Rushfatttbaugh will call for a recount. HAAAA HAAAAA Obummer wins every state he won the last time including Indiana. He adds on Arizona in a stunning bit of bad news for Fuxeddd up news fans. You believe those plucked up polls? They see a black face and they say he is not a likely voter and do not count him. Let me clue you--he will vote. He hates you whiitetrash GOP #$%$ and he will vote. He would vote for Satin as long as he was a dem and had a black face. Obummer is no sating and so he will cry and call for everyone to vote and they will. Every black church in America will line their people up to vote. It is over Rombo. That 47% you hate THREW YOU DOWN AND STEPPED ON YOU. YOU #$%$ scccumbage rich anti American jerkooofff can move now. Try Mexico--your grandpa ran there--OH? They hate you too? Well it is Utah then.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1350768547122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 17:29:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350769972137-39</Id><Topic><Title>AMD going bankrupt will allow Intel much better pricing power.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1350768547122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 17:29:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rambling, incoherent, hateful drivel from a pseudo-politician bully on a financial board. AMD will more likely get outside funding for partial ownership, like what Intel is doing with Sharp, which will allow them to keep building the x86 chips. AMD is the only company in the world other than Intel who can build a combo product: ARM+x86. Or put the two in the bender and build a hybrid part. The 47% are the poor who are concentrated in the Republican, right to work southern states. They are already disenfranchised and will not make any impact on the voting. The 47% are the military who will mistakenly think that Romney stands with them. Noone knows how it will turn out. Anyone who correctly predicts the outcome is just as lucky as Noriel Robini was to predict the SP500 bottome. I do find it hard to believe that Romney and Ryan can avoid providing some real answers to questions on taxes, social issues. I find it hard to believe the Whitehouse botching the handling of the Sept 11 embassy attack. I do expect both sides to provide amazingly stupid answers to simple questions. Anyone who thinks that any significant legislation can be passed without 60 US Senators in agreement is ignorant of the process. That is the reason that so little gets done. Rand Paul has the support of Kentucky voters and can follow his scortched earth voting record. The Earth is over 5,000 years old. Women are people too. I think that most men are people. A majority of Republicans and Democrats could agree on legislation if the extremists were not in control. That includes Social Security and medicare modifications. That includes tax revenue and spending policies.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1350769972137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 17:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350770607071-40</Id><Topic><Title>AMD going bankrupt will allow Intel much better pricing power.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1350768547122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 17:29:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"..Women are people too. I think that most men are people..." -------------------------------------------------- speaking of hateful drivel you seem to do well in that department.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350770607071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 18:03:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350770739085-41</Id><Topic><Title>$19 support nothing till than......</Title><Username>febru3012</Username><Timestamp>1350673826390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Short the top and be patient.</Msg><Username>rolsondonald</Username><Timestamp>1350770739085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 18:05:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350771436401-42</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Deliberately Sets the ARM Surface RT Price Too High</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1350520653506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you know how many MSFT built? There were probably some buyer who purchased multiple units (probably 100's) for close examination. Apple, Samsung, Intel, AMD, Google, HP, DELL, teardown labs, consultants, ..... Few went into the retail market. Those that went into retail hands are already on Ebay. There are already several hundred advertised on EBAY as new at $999. Those were probably purchased to make a quick profit by flipping them before becoming widely available.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350771436401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 18:17:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350771744558-43</Id><Topic><Title>AMD going bankrupt will allow Intel much better pricing power.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1350768547122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 17:29:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are right. What was I thinking???????????? Men are people too.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1350771744558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 18:22:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350774651621-44</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL solution</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350754205261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:30:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This would take the INTC PE from 9 to</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350774651621</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350774706173-45</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL solution</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350754205261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:30:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This would take the INTC PE from 9 to</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350774706173</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350774821129-46</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL solution</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350754205261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:30:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This would still leave the price below peer companies like TSM, which has a PE=17 (This is why they couldn't buy a portion of TSM as the PE would climb to a PE=25 which would be a losing proposition). This would also leave AAPL or some other competitor room to increase bidding to $40.00/share where they would be at a PE=17 and equal to the likes of TSM and others. This would force INTC to make ARMH processors and utilize all of their plant capacity and continue the fab they just moth balled due to too much capacity. This would also dramatically increase their earnings per share and increase return to INTC and AAPL's bottom line. This would also give AAPL a manufacturing edge that GOOG, QCOM, NVDA and Samsung don’t have. Let’s face it Samsung with Galaxy III is making a mockery of AAPL’s superiority and will erode their cult following and premium pricing if they don’t do something soon to restore it.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1350774821129</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350775295533-47</Id><Topic><Title>$24 PUT options cost are rising, does this also indicate a rising stock price?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350735789501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:23:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Puts seem more appealing than calls, as you never really have to purchase the stock, if I understand that right...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350775295533</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350775365655-48</Id><Title>Divident</Title><Msg>when is the ex divident date?</Msg><Username>starbauch</Username><Timestamp>1350775365655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:22:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350775420307-49</Id><Title>Liar, liar, pants on fire</Title><Msg>The Quote of the Decade: "The fact that we are here today to debate raising America's debt limit is a sign of leadership failure. It is a sign that the US Government cannot pay its own bills. It is a sign that we now depend on ongoing financial assistance from foreign countries to finance our Government's reckless fiscal policies. Increasing America's debt weakens us domestically and internationally. Leadership means that, "the buck stops here.' Instead, Washington is shifting the burden of bad choices today onto the backs of our children and grandchildren. America has a debt problem and a failure of leadership. Americans deserve better." ~ Senator Barack H. Obama, March 2006</Msg><Username>paulcluz</Username><Timestamp>1350775420307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350775795309-50</Id><Topic><Title>Divident</Title><Username>starbauch</Username><Timestamp>1350775365655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:22:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>11/5/2012</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350775795309</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:29:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350777501524-51</Id><Topic><Title>$24 PUT options cost are rising, does this also indicate a rising stock price?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350735789501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:23:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you thinking of BUYING or SELLING them? I am generally an optimistic person. I follow stocks that I think are going to appreciate. I am conservative (I think I am). I like the time decay of option premium being my friend rather than my enemy. I prefer to sell put options about 60 to 90 days out that are near the money. I tend to sell them at the $1 range and close them out at a profit if they drop substantally to the sub-50cent range. I don't hold below 25 cents. I am bad about closing them out for a loss if they appreciate. I just roll them out a could months for credit. I hope you can be more displined about when to buy and exit than I am. There is a Yahoo Group that is pretty good that someone on the board suggested named: CoveredCalls-NakedPuts_OptionStrategies Account approval. You will need to get account approval to trade options. Level 0 is conservative and only covered options can be traded but check. If you sell a call or a put, sufficient cash is reserved to cover the exercise, even if exercise is not planned or actually happens. Level 0 is easy and is approved upon request, even for IRA accounts. Levels beyond are approved based on your experience. You can possibly get it raised and talk to the broker. Simple bearish bets: buying a put or selling a call. both are generally, bets that the stock will not go up. Simple bullish bets: buying a call or selling a put. both are generally, bets that the stock will go up. In combination, call or put options can be bearish, bullish or neutral bets.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1350777501524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:58:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350777565163-52</Id><Topic><Title>Liar, liar, pants on fire</Title><Username>paulcluz</Username><Timestamp>1350775420307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We will be greeted as liberators ..." The quote of the millennium.</Msg><Username>phil_mccrakkin</Username><Timestamp>1350777565163</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:59:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350778421298-53</Id><Topic><Title>$24 PUT options cost are rising, does this also indicate a rising stock price?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350735789501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:23:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd consider buying the right to sell the stock at the higher price... the assumption being that the stock price is going to decline... as of right now... I've all my funds tied up in INTC at an average of 22.60, don't intent to take the loss on that anytime soon.... I could scrap together enough to margin another $7,000 worth, but would only consider that if it dropped to $21 or less... I'm hoping to be able to sell out what I hold right now around $23.60, but it seems far away at this point as I watch it go down down down, but I'm optimistic about the coming month... I believe we'll see some good up stream in November and maybe even more in December... great stock to own for the long run... far TOO many idiots calling the PC dead, and not looking at the fact that the PC is actually evolving and no where near dead... my only large fear right now is a recession or a deep recession, which seems like a possibility at the rate our once great nation accumulates debt. Anyway, as always thank you very much for helping me understand by sharing you wealth of knowledge. I've learned a lot and hope to learn more.</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350778421298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 20:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350790168694-54</Id><Topic><Title>$24 PUT options cost are rising, does this also indicate a rising stock price?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1350735789501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:23:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. TIME VALUE OPTION MONSTER has a good chart that shows TIME VALUE visually. select QUOTE INTC in the window which will have VIX STRATEGY SEEK The chart shows the time value as time.. ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Alex, i managed to see the chart and it shows a trend thru diff strike prices. Is there a way to see a chart of how a specific strike changed value over time. ? for example i would like to see the chart of prices of QQQ DEC 60 price from the begining of the year. is there such an online tool that you used? ( i guess i also can ask my brokerage firm if they provide it)</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1350790168694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 23:29:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>