<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353824576053-1</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more EVIL than Liberals?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353814323179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:32:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many people are more than SHOCKED at the disgusting Republican behavior. They lost a big chunk of those voters because of their efforts to limit voting and other medieval views. Everyone knows that there is federal laws relating to voting are directed at protecting rights in the absence of state voting laws. This is just more conservative fake outrage. Why not put energies into avocating fixes instead of faking the anger. How about ANYONE with an IQ of less than 80 cannot vote. That way you would still be able to vote. I guess it makes sense for the government to decide who gets to vote or not. That is what you are advocating. RIGHT?? For example in Vermont, there are only 4 rules qualifying a voter: 1. U.S. citizenship 2. Vermont residence 3. 18 years or older (by election day) 4. Voters must take the voter’s oath on, or before, election day (stating that the person will vote his or her conscience and not be told how to vote by another person) #4 would filter out those who are real incompetent in Vermont. IN TEXAS: You are eligible to register to vote if: •You are a United States citizen; •You are a resident of the county where you submit the application; •You are at least 18 years old on Election Day; •You are not a convicted felon (you may be eligible to vote if you have completed your sentence, probation, and parole); and •You have not been declared by a court exercising probate jurisdiction to be either totally mentally incapacitated or partially mentally incapacitated without the right to vote. In TEXAS you must be declared mentally incapacitated without rights to vote. Vermont seems tougher than Texas.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1353824576053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 01:22:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353827353230-2</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more EVIL than Liberals?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353814323179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:32:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because we re-elected President Obama… Did you teabaggers happen to notice that 5 of the last 6 Presidential elections have seen the Dem win the popular vote 5 times? White Trash like limbuttt and the gang on Fuxed news look even stupider. Forbes also looks like a dufffasss bag for predicting an easy Rombo win. In fact, almost all you rightwing trash look stupid--nothing new there. Because we re-elected President Obama… We are not going to have a Supreme Court that will overturn Roe v Wade. There will be no more Samuel Alitos or Antonin Scaleas added to this court. Nazi8 #$%$m We are not going to repeal health reform. EVER Nobody is going to kill Medicare and make old people in this generation or any other generation fight it out in the open market to try to get themselves health insurance. We saved your grandma. We are not going to give a 20% tax cut to millionaires and billionaires and expect programs like food stamps and kids’ health insurance to cover the cost of that tax cut. Wallstreet #$%$ have to pay. We’re not going to make you clear it with your boss if you want to get birth control under the insurance plan you’re on. We are not going to redefine rape. We are not going to amend the US Constitution to stop gay people from getting married. We are not going to double Guantanamo. We are not eliminating the Dept. of Energy, or the Dept. of Education, or Housing at the federal level. We are not going to spend $2 trillion on the military that the military doesn’t want. We are not scaling back on student loans because the country’s new plan is that you should “borrow from your parents.” We are not vetoing The Dream Act. We are not self-deporting. We are not letting Detroit go bankrupt. We are not starting a trade war with China on inauguration day in January. We are not going to have as president a man who once led a bunch of friends to run down a scared gay kid to hold him down and forcibly cut his hair off while that kid cried and screamed for help, and there was no apology, not ever. We are not going to have a Secretary of State John Boulton. We are never bringing Dick Cheney back. We are not going to have a foreign policy shop stocked with architects of the Iraq war. We had the choice to do all that as a country, and we said NO. Rombo was not the problem--you idiotttts who backed him are the problem but a minority problem.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1353827353230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 02:09:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353827623514-3</Id><Title>Is there anything more funny than a crybaby loser GOP?</Title><Msg>Pathetic--But funny they are.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1353827623514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 02:13:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353828845755-4</Id><Topic><Title>Broadwell in 2013 now that 14nm roadmap bumped forward?</Title><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1353728775300</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 22:46:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to not know what you are talking about. Clovertrail is dual core with two threads per core. A15 is quad.core. Silvermont will be quad core no hyperthreading and it will be out of order execution. Just the quad core aspect will boost the integer by 60% and double foating poin. The out of order will also substantially boost performance along with other archetectuaral changes. The 22nm will allow for higher clock speeds if desired. It will kill A15 on performance and power. Intel will have 14 nm in 2014 and ARM will have no substantial improvemnet. ----- No. The A15 on geekbench is dual core. The 60% numbers are from Intel and they are comparing against Clovertrail V Silvermont. That 60% is everything, IPC, memory, clock, 2 real extra threads. Geekbench is a multithreaded benchmark, so when the A15 goes quad, it'll improve it's performance numbers. Today, the A15 has double the floating point and the same integer performance of Clovertrail even with less running threads (2 hyperthreads of Clovertrail). Silvermont is due in 2014, not sure when Airmont @14nm will arrive. ARM isn't standing still:) Before Silvermont arrives, they'll be going quad A15, then the A7/A15 hybrids and you'll likely see the next gen arch. in 2014, perhaps even a node shrink. ---- It is over when Intel adds LTE. Except for a few possible big cell phone manufacturers, everyone will convert product line to Intel reference designs.. ---- Nope, it wont be:)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1353828845755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 02:34:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353848205513-5</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more EVIL than Liberals?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353814323179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:32:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think I'm going to print that and put it on my refrigerator door.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353848205513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 07:56:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353848323172-6</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more funny than a crybaby loser GOP?</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1353827623514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 02:13:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>funny and well worth making fun of.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353848323172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 07:58:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353848618482-7</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Cannot Survive The Graphics War Like This</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353799245945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 18:20:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you really think about the structure of an ARM chip business, so distributed that it has built in inefficiencies and costs that make competition with a dedicated vertically integrated Intel impossible. Intel's achilles heal we have seen...not making a decision to get into a game early enough..but once they are in they win because of the innate structure of the business. They are alos really really good at what they do. There are no new chip players like never before.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353848618482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 08:03:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353851039968-8</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more EVIL than Liberals?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353814323179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:32:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nicky you are an idiot no matter which stock you choose to bash and short at the bottom, I guess you truly are a bottom feeder.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1353851039968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 08:43:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353851304476-9</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suspect that a sizable number of Quadros solds in Workstations are used as gpgpus due to many workstation app vendors doing gpgpu ports. Phi will expand the market due to the sheer amount of x86 HPC code already out there that can be easily recompiled and accelerated. $1-2bn Phi revenue within 3 years will be the result I suspect.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353851304476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 08:48:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353852582381-10</Id><Title>INTC building their own phone and other HW?</Title><Msg>I was on vacation last week and saw the news about Paul resigning in May. I have to admit I was spooked but now I am wondering if this move means more than meets the eye. If they bring in someone who is familiar with building own HW (smartphones, tablets, PC convertibles and maybe servers) then it would definitely mean that Intel is moving in this direction. Anyone familiar with the agreement between INTC and Motorola? Is there anything in there preventing INTC from building and selling their own HW?</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1353852582381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 09:09:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353852741664-11</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more funny than a crybaby loser GOP?</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1353827623514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 02:13:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's funn is A) you talking to yourself with your cornhole, monkey and flumoxed aliases and B) the fact that you never respond to any of the pathetic tactics and cheating of Liberals........like a true Liberal POS you just say "You lost!" Weasel.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353852741664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 09:12:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353855738429-12</Id><Topic><Title>INTC building their own phone and other HW?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1353852582381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 09:09:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, who would be a good CEO for INTC if they are serious about building their own consumer HW products?</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1353855738429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:02:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353857119278-13</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more funny than a crybaby loser GOP?</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1353827623514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 02:13:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am my own alias, s#iT h o l e .</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353857119278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:25:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353857633860-14</Id><Topic><Title>INTC building their own phone and other HW?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1353852582381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 09:09:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is highly doubtful, Intel competing with their customers?? They are not Microsoft!</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1353857633860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:33:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353857693613-15</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Cannot Survive The Graphics War Like This</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353799245945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 18:20:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They got in mobile, they just did not have the patent protection they are use to and got out played. They look good because they have played patent protection well. They can not block young upstarts with fresh ideas that have little to lose and a lot to gain.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1353857693613</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:34:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353858040109-16</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more EVIL than Liberals?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353814323179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:32:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>decipiles? What are those, one tenths of a pile?</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353858040109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:40:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353859457677-17</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Phi will expand the market" Hope so !!!!! Would like to see attention, and drama, brought back to floating point...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1353859457677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 11:04:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353860002910-18</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more funny than a crybaby loser GOP?</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1353827623514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 02:13:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am my own alias, s#iT h o l e . ___________ Your a total liar, but it's in your blood.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353860002910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 11:13:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353862680148-19</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more EVIL than Liberals?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353814323179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:32:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sad people like you vote. You live in your own reality. Far removed from reality.</Msg><Username>arthor_arthor</Username><Timestamp>1353862680148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 11:58:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353863797280-20</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phi is a niche. Selling one million units a year would mean something like one in every fifteen server CPUs would be a Phi - that probably won't happen for a long time. Phi looks like a defensive product, an attempt to keep GPGPUs at bay, but initially may not even be making a net profit. Of course, supercomputing is the one area where Wallis's dream of a huge fabrication win really means something. The trouble is, even if they win the same 94% of the supercomputing CPU market Intel has in the overall server market it isn't enough to pump up the stock price. Intel either figures out mobile computing or IMO there's a good chance they will be a future division of Qualcomm or some other company that has. Unless Intel's market cap goes up in two years Apple will be able to buy them, for cash.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1353863797280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 12:16:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353863963715-21</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more EVIL than Liberals?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353814323179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:32:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is there anything more EVIL than Liberals? ------------------------------------------ Anyone/everyone who publicly pumped Intel at 29 is far more evil.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353863963715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 12:19:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353865940687-22</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more EVIL than Liberals?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353814323179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:32:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Romney will save you,” he said to me out of the blue. “What do you mean?” “I voted for him for president and now he’s saving me.” I was taken aback by these words, since Henry had no idea who Romney was, or what a president might be, and would be unable to fill out a registration form let alone get to the polling place by himself. So I asked him how he knew that and how he had registered and cast his vote. In halting, impeded speech he told me that Fox News filled out “the papers” to register him to vote, Fox News told him how Romney cared for him, even taught him the Romney Mormon chants, and then took him to the polling place to vote. Fox News did the same for all of the mentally disabled patients in their care, approximately 6000000 in all. Teapigs your 15 minutes is so over even youe won party is trying to wash you off the bottom of their shoe</Msg><Username>asswipesforbush</Username><Timestamp>1353865940687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 12:52:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353866242312-23</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AAPL is overated , the stock dropped from 700$ to 500$, people realizing APple products are pure hype . Surface with Intel chip is the new king.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1353866242312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 12:57:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353867023245-24</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you on crack? A "lot of other players"? You have Nvidia and you have Intel. That's it. AMD's products are not suitable due to a lack of software support.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1353867023245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:10:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353869688257-25</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Texas TACC Stampede will be configured with 6,400 Dell DCS Zeus compute nodes, each with two 2.7 GHz E5-2680 Intel Xeon (Sandy Bridge EP) processors. It is targeted to have 6,400 PHI. They have connected 1 PHI for each Sandy Bridge EP. The PHI bandwidth probably makes it impractical to connect more than 1 per CPU. I don't know what the real phyical limit is. The population of sockets is not, however, limited to servers. There are workstations too. Gamers? Is Intel working with game developers? There will also be substantial price elasticity. The PCI add in board will find additional installations as they are able to drop the price. Workstations are also targets. The Intel C and Fortran compilers will make it easy for people to build code that take full advantage of the PHI and capture near 100% of its compute capability. MATLAB, simulations, modeling, ... I have an Intel Core i7 Ivy Bridge desktop and I have been watching for PHI to hit retail and drop to my price point. I am cheap so it will be awhile but I can put it on my Wish list.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1353869688257</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:54:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353869711357-26</Id><Topic><Title>US Stocks Rise Sharply in Black Friday Retail Rush</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353692174390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 12:36:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reports that Black Friday sales slumped. I swear I think that if you do the opposite of Wallisweaver, you'll be rich.</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1353869711357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:55:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353869988758-27</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more funny than a crybaby loser GOP?</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1353827623514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 02:13:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a guy who writes letters to the SEC because his stock is not doing what he thinks it should is also pretty funny.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1353869988758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:59:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353870243294-28</Id><Topic><Title>US Stocks Rise Sharply in Black Friday Retail Rush</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353692174390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 12:36:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What numbers are you looking at? Did they compare the online sales too? Online was up 20%. Did they compare the Thanksgiving day sales too? A number of sales were pulled forward out of the Friday numbers. I had to laugh at the article saying some of the Black Friday deals were up to 100% off. Hard to increase revenue with those 100% off bargains.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1353870243294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:04:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353870441271-29</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more funny than a crybaby loser GOP?</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1353827623514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 02:13:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>disgusting. you are representative of the large minority of our citizenry that are unthinking uneducated tribalistic retrogrades. you are an ugly human being. you live in fear, fear mainly of others, xenophobia. you are the kind of person that joins lynch mobs, or berates people who are gay, or deformed, or in anyway different from yourself. you are a classic paranoid pd. you accept no responsibility to make the system or the human condition better, you just hurl your childish epithets at the world, like molatov cocktails, then run back into your bunker to hide. You are a sociopath. You are a modern day republican, dwelling in the first millenium. you are simply disgusting.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353870441271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:07:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353870542818-30</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more EVIL than Liberals?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353814323179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:32:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are a classic sociopath.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353870542818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:09:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353870631135-31</Id><Title>att4gte classic sociopath</Title><Msg>his last name is Gobbler. He was mistakenly released doing time as serial child molester when a state turkey pardon went bad.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353870631135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:10:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353870819443-32</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything more funny than a crybaby loser GOP?</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1353827623514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 02:13:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a guy who writes letters to the SEC because his stock is not doing what he thinks it should is also pretty funny. ------------ ABSOLUTELY! THUMBS UPPPPPPPPPP!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353870819443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:13:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353871392706-33</Id><Title>DID YOU EVER SEE WALLIS MAKE THESE COMMENTS?</Title><Msg>"Wait for a pullback to buy" or "Take a little off the table here" or "I think Intel may be overbought"</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353871392706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:23:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353871943615-34</Id><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Msg>Sensible people must assure that the House is no longer controlled by these vermin after next election. There can be so sensible policies from the US Gov't with them around. It is also the imperative of the Democratic party to ensure that Mitch O'Connell never returns to the US Senate.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353872452409-35</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is Mitch McConnell, not O'Connell. What policies would you like to see in place and why. Calling people vermin and asking for eradication is harsh.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1353872452409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:40:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353873034411-36</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, so now it's only $1-2bn. Phi is defensive play for a niche, what may get to be a big niche due to exa-scale computers, but I worry more about the next three years. Phi will still be footnote in Intel's revenue picture, and mobile will still be where the war is won or lost. Phi is to Intel as the Corvette is to GM.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1353873034411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:50:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353874107756-37</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pay the bills, unlike the debacle a year and a half ago when they tried to squeeze all programs by trying to block the debt ceiling increase. And now we have a fiscal cliff to drag the market under. I hope Obama simply allows the Bush tax cuts to expire and can blame it on these white trash tea baggers. Then we can start working back to Clinton's surpluses. And I hope O'Connell gets the heave-ho.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353874107756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:08:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353874604675-38</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Phi is defensive play for a niche' No it is a disruptive product for a disruptive market and it is high profit, $1K+ for each chip. Intel would have to sell 100 Medfield phone chips to get that. It brings a scale of improvement to vectorized x86 code of about 5-10. An order of magnitude. Until the existing server/workstation market fully appreciates what it will bring to their existing code none of us know big the upgrade cycle it creates could be but it might snowball into an avalanche eventually. Haswell, Clovertrail and Phi will be Intel's bright rising stars in 2013. Haswell will be lapped up equally by gamers and ultrabook users as it simultaneously improves ultimate performance and power consumption. Clovertrail brings the iPad form factor to fully functional Windows PCs and Phi will reignite the Workstation/HPC market.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353874604675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:16:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353875119803-39</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not limiting government spending appears to be what got Greece in its insolvency. But, I am not an expert.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1353875119803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:25:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353875257312-40</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It is Mitch McConnell, not O'Connell. What policies would you like to see in place and why. Calling people vermin and asking for eradication is harsh." [People who put political gain over the welfare of the country are vermin. The short crowd would crash the economy in a second if they made an extra fifty cents. They're vermin. Wall Street defrauds the average investor with the application of money, leverage and media spin. Why can't they work for a living and earn money the old-fashioned way - by working for it? They're vermin. Those people who get out of bed every day trying to destroy something instead of building something up. They're vermin...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353875257312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:27:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353875475059-41</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Not limiting government spending appears to be what got Greece in its insolvency. But, I am not an expert." [You think austerity is the answer but so far austerity is making things worse. You can't apply austerity until you first fuel economic growth... ]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353875475059</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:31:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353875794876-42</Id><Topic><Title>US Stocks Rise Sharply in Black Friday Retail Rush</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353692174390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 12:36:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Reports that Black Friday sales slumped. I swear I think that if you do the opposite of Wallisweaver, you'll be rich." [Lucy, if you have gotten rich (doubtful from your negative attitudes on Intel all the way from 17.67 to 29+), then you should buy yourself a backbone. Maybe then you would have the courage to just post under a single ID. Girly-boy...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353875794876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:36:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353875872449-43</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, when they tried to clean up GREED in the Soviet Union and a lot of other countries, they murdered anyone who did not play properly. Everyone hates greed, but it is an essential part of our progress and survival as individuals. Countries with freer economies have done better then countries with central planners that are planning for the so called greater good. Hilter thought killing 6 million people was for the good of the Germans and the world. Stalin the same, and so on.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1353875872449</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:37:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353875883931-44</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No sensable boards until fools like you quit posting stupid tit for tat OT GD politics, go have another vodka.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1353875883931</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:38:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353876381471-45</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not limiting gov. spending got them in a mess. Greece has no money. You don't think anything over time spending needs to be cut in Greece ? Severe austerity would probably create a mess and suffering, to that I agree.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1353876381471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:46:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353876411302-46</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Well, when they tried to clean up GREED in the Soviet Union and a lot of other countries, they murdered anyone who did not play properly." [Where did you learn your Russian history? They never tried to clean up greed. They tried to limit it to the ruling class. No different than modern-day Republicans who would sell their souls for another tax cut for the rich...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353876411302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:46:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353876541219-47</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not having a GDP got them in trouble. The white trash are going to sink our GDP with their "austerity" policies, which only help billionaires get more billions.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353876541219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:49:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353876599183-48</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Communism is the anti greed creed. Stay on subject without demonizing people please.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1353876599183</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:49:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353876629364-49</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>go start with your own vermin and take your task to att4gte. Like I say, nothing will improve until we rid ourselves of republican vermin.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353876629364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:50:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353876634446-50</Id><Topic><Title>US Stocks Rise Sharply in Black Friday Retail Rush</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353692174390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 12:36:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you are no longer ignoring me, kweerbait. And in that case, please tell me if "Intel is good for 30" I think you said that 30 is a "slamdunk" and if you're having lots of fun "plowing" through the high teens and low 20s.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1353876634446</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:50:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353876921653-51</Id><Title>Black Friday</Title><Msg>Black Friday sales online top $1 billion for 1st time: comScore Shoppers spent record $1B online on Black Friday Black Friday mania in consumer tech Online sales jumped on Thanksgiving, Black Friday Black Friday shopping hits a new record Total spending over Black Friday weekend hit a record $59.1 billion, up from $52.4 billion last year. The number of shoppers in store and online ... Online shopping powered Black Friday Black Friday's online sales jumped 21% over last year, the Financial Times reported. Shopping on mobile gadgets also increased, with ...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353876921653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:55:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353877111211-52</Id><Title>BORN DEAD</Title><Msg>ULTRABOOK</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1353877111211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:58:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353877718719-53</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Communism is the anti greed creed. Stay on subject without demonizing people please." [Well that's one interpretation. In its ideal form it was promoted as "from each according to his or her abilities, to each according to his or her need. There has never been a communist society or government on the planet. Certainly what happened in the Soviet Union wasn't a communist society. It was lip service. In short there never will be a communist society except on a very, very limited basis as it runs contrary to human behavior. People are capable of altruism but there will never be a nation of altruists. Just look at the rich in the US. They never think they have enough. Even worse they think they deserve more. The best that can be done is to keep the rich from ravaging the middle class. It's a constant battle. For the last thirty years the rich in the US have gotten richer while the poor have gotten poorer...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353877718719</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:08:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353878119690-54</Id><Topic><Title>Black Friday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353876921653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:55:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad PC sales probably didn't see much of a boost. Being an Intel shareholder right now has made me all kinds of pessimistic. I'm almost starting to believe the "PC is dead" propaganda...</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1353878119690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:15:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353878726229-55</Id><Title>INTEEN INTURD SMELLWETHER SMELLTEL</Title><Msg>better names than Intel, imo. Other suggestions for new names, Walldork? Hi-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1353878726229</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:25:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353878759990-56</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't think the poor are better off in the U.S. vs. North Korea? If you work hard for something you or your children don't deserve it ? Capitalism sucks for sure, Socialism sucks way more IMO. We only have imperfect choices. Democracy sucks until it is compared to any other election system. I really am not an expert in economics, but I don't think I would be motivated to work very hard if the govt. just took it to give to some one else. I don't think I would work hard if my job was guaranteed, but that is just me.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1353878759990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:25:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353878937114-57</Id><Title>Trending</Title><Msg>Trending Up US Employment US Housing US Consumer Sentiment Chinese Economic Recovery Intel's Mobility Strategy for 2013 Intel: Haswell Intel:Clovertrail Intel:Phi "[Phi] is a disruptive product for a disruptive market and it is high profit, $1K+ for each chip. Intel would have to sell 100 Medfield phone chips to get that. It brings a scale of improvement to vectorized x86 code of about 5-10. An order of magnitude. Until the existing server/workstation market fully appreciates what it will bring to their existing code none of us know big the upgrade cycle it creates could be but it might snowball into an avalanche eventually. Haswell, Clovertrail and Phi will be Intel's bright rising stars in 2013. Haswell will be lapped up equally by gamers and ultrabook users as it simultaneously improves ultimate performance and power consumption. Clovertrail brings the iPad form factor to fully functional Windows PCs and Phi will reignite the Workstation/HPC market." Comments immediately above from marsavian Trending Down Wall Street's constant propaganda war against Intel</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353878937114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:28:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353879238332-58</Id><Topic><Title>Trending</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353878937114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:28:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that you in the "secret to stay asleep" advertisement on the right margin of the page. I'm sure it's difficult to sleep when you're so far UNDERWATER in your INTC position, effwad.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1353879238332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:33:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353880088039-59</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You don't think the poor are better off in the U.S. vs. North Korea?" [I'm a staunch capitalist, butkus. Just not of the variety that believes the rich should be able to use their advantages to arbitrarily crush the middle and lower classes. I believe in a level playing field. What in your nutcase brain caused you to think the discussion was about poor in North Korea???] "If you work hard for something you or your children don't deserve it ?" [Yeah, people who work hard should benefit. Dunno why those on Wall Street can't just work hard instead of trying to manipulate their way to wealth. As far as your kids go, let them earn their own way. Leaving them big bucks will ruin their lives...] "Capitalism sucks for sure, Socialism sucks way more IMO. We only have imperfect choices. Democracy sucks until it is compared to any other election system. I really am not an expert in economics, but I don't think I would be motivated to work very hard if the govt. just took it to give to some one else. I don't think I would work hard if my job was guaranteed, but that is just me." [Who do you know that has a guaranteed job? We don't have a socialist society but we do have some aspects such as taking care of old people and little kids. You really don't think we should take of old people and little kids? Or provide an education to young people? Because those are all forms of socialism. If you hate socialism then you hate Social Security. Do you hate Social Security?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353880088039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:48:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353880814280-60</Id><Topic><Title>Black Friday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353876921653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:55:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gamers and people with real computing or business to do buy PCs. Airheads, some kids and people who can afford both buy tablets. Tablets are great but are no replacement for a heavy-duty fully-loaded high-powered PC. It's like the difference between a Harley and a tricycle. If you want to be a lucy who wouldn't know what to do with a high powered computer, then go hang with the tricycle crowd. Nevertheless, note that Intel doesn't make PCs. Intel makes processors and has the most advanced technology, fabrication and manufacturing in the world. During 2013, Intel will demonstrate the viability of their approach across the complete processor market, including mobility...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353880814280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:00:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353881227161-61</Id><Title>Five Ultrabooks to Looks for on Cyber Monday</Title><Msg>Laptops: Best Ultrabooks (Updated November 20, 2012 5:17 AM PST) Dan Ackerman Senior editor Scott Stein Senior editor The latest hot buzzword, "ultrabook" is actually a trademarked Intel marketing term applied to thin laptops that meet certain size and component requirements. For this list, we're considering officially labeled ultrabooks, as well as other laptops, such as Apple's MacBook Air, that follow the same design aesthetic. Apple MacBook Air (13-inch, Summer 2012) This year's MacBook Air opts for gradual improvements rather than anything revolutionary, but lowered prices continue to make it the go-to mainstream recommendation for any MacBook owner-to-be. Price: $1,011.54 - $1,199.99 (check prices) 4 stars ExcellentRead full review Lenovo IdeaPad Yoga 13 The Lenovo IdeaPad Yoga 13 is a convertible touch-screen laptop/tablet that most importantly doesn't compromise the traditional laptop experience. Price: $1,099.00 - $1,399.95 (check prices) 4 stars ExcellentRead full review Lenovo ThinkPad X1 Carbon The business-oriented Lenovo ThinkPad X1 has a few quirks, but is otherwise a very impressive business-oriented ultrabook with strong crossover potential. Price: $1,149.00 - $1,474.43 (check prices) 4 stars ExcellentRead full review Dell Inspiron 14z (June 2012) Dell has managed to give a very upscale feel to its mainstream Inspiron 14z, a 14-inch ultrabook that comfortably juggles price, design, and performance. MSRP: $899.00 4 stars ExcellentRead full review HP Envy Spectre XT A high-end laptop at a mainstream price, the HP Envy Spectre XT gets much of the look and feel right, with only a few missteps. Price: $964.95 (check prices)</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353881227161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:07:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353881536909-62</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe in a mixed economy, I don't think most people are mature enough to save when they are young. I would prefer Individual accounts over SS though. Education's biggest quality issue is it is a govt. monopoly for the poor and some middle class. The rich can afford private schools or the best public schools. I believe vouchers and competition would help the poor. Competition and profit/loss make a better school than more money to a bad school IMO. I am a British immigrant and have waited in so many NHS lines it is funny ...so not a fan of Universal Health Care and it ain't cheap. Why do you think attacking people strengthens your argument.? I am not a Butkus or a nut job or a teabagger. I even voted for Obama though he is not my perfect candidate. I enjoy discussing and learning, I don't see any need to belittle someone. Thank you.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1353881536909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:12:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353881680570-63</Id><Title>INTEL TO DO AWAY WITH DRAM IN PCs</Title><Msg>semiaccurateDOTcom/2012/09/07/intel-to-do-away-with-dram-in-pcs/ Can someone give more insight into this? and what does it mean for INTC?</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1353881680570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:14:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353881998490-64</Id><Topic><Title>Five Ultrabooks to Looks for on Cyber Monday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353881227161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:07:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many of the new laptops are so thin and light and faster and so so much cheaper, or get cloud computer and utilize the cloud if that works for you, or a tablet. Can not see the value in an Ultra expensive book as my teenagers call them. Just my opinion though...and my teenagers.</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1353881998490</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:19:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353882091165-65</Id><Title>Lenovo ThinkPad Edge E430 Small Business Laptop</Title><Msg>You can buy a ThinkPad for $483.12. That's less than an iPad for full computing capability. And with a third generation Intel processor. Available in black brushed aluminum with chrome accents or soft-touch black or red Durable drop-down hinges Dolby® Advanced Audio™ v2 HDD express cache mSATA capable 5GB of free cloud storage through Lenovo Cloud Storage powered by SugarSync Integrated 720p HD camera Three USB 3.0 ports, 4-in-1 card reader Active Protection System™ Lenovo Solutions for Small Business powered by Intel Small Business Advantage Spill-resistant AccuType keyboard Fingerprint reader</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353882091165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:21:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353882324817-66</Id><Topic><Title>Five Ultrabooks to Looks for on Cyber Monday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353881227161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:07:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Can not see the value in an Ultra expensive book as my teenagers call them. Just my opinion though...and my teenagers." [And that's why you and your teenagers should be sitting with the tricycle crowd. You wouldn't know what to do with real computing power. Congratulations on admitting it. No reason to be bashful about computer illiteracy. After all - it exists everywhere on Wall Street...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353882324817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:25:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353882369106-67</Id><Topic><Title>Five Ultrabooks to Looks for on Cyber Monday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353881227161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:07:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The best Ultrabook is the Samsung 13.3" Series 9. The weight comes in at 2.6 pounds with the 13.3" screen. Amazon has it for $1200 with Win 7 or for $1300 with Win 8.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1353882369106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:26:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353883319503-68</Id><Topic><Title>No rational market until Republicans are eradicated</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353871943615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I believe in a mixed economy, I don't think most people are mature enough to save when they are young. I would prefer Individual accounts over SS though. Education's biggest quality issue is it is a govt. monopoly for the poor and some middle class. The rich can afford private schools or the best public schools. I believe vouchers and competition would help the poor. Competition and profit/loss make a better school than more money to a bad school IMO. I am a British immigrant and have waited in so many NHS lines it is funny ...so not a fan of Universal Health Care and it ain't cheap. Why do you think attacking people strengthens your argument.? I am not a Butkus or a nut job or a teabagger. I even voted for Obama though he is not my perfect candidate. I enjoy discussing and learning, I don't see any need to belittle someone. Thank you." [Individual retirement accounts would have gutted everyone's retirement during the Bush administration. And this is why they are a bad idea. Most people have no idea about investing their own money. So, let's not do something insanely stupid for the masses in order to provide a capability for a few people like you. Not to mention that Wall Street absolutely loves to manipulate the investments of the average investor into nothingness. It's like their favorite activity. Witness what they have done to Intel's stock price. How many average investors do you think got totally screwed by this latest Wall Street mugging? Wall Street's predictions for last quarter were totally wrong and yet they still forced the stock price down. How will this kind of thing work for the average investor? It won't.] [Making profits and providing quality education are 2 different things. Just like making profits and providing quality healthcare are 2 different things. All vouchers will do is gut public education in order to increase corporate profits.] [So, you love American health care. It's the most expensive in the world and only about 27th in quality and you love it. And you have to pay for it. One can only wonder why. You obviously can afford health care. But wait until you get turned down for a life-saving operation in spite of having health insurance. Happens all the time in the US. You'll be on the next plane back, anxious to join the NHS waiting lines...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353883319503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:41:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353883329598-69</Id><Topic><Title>Five Ultrabooks to Looks for on Cyber Monday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353881227161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:07:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To get the Ivy Bridge processor here are the model numbers: Samsung 13.3" Series 9 with Win 8, NP900X3C-A05US Samsung 13.3" Series 9 with Win 7, NP900X3C-A01US So the models with X3B are the Sandy Bridge processors and will be $200 cheaper.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1353883329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:42:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353886196944-70</Id><Title>A. Easa</Title><Msg>Hey man, what's the deal? You recently wrote an article on Seeking Alpha that was pro-Intel, then one just days later that was negative Intel. Now you say your are long but worried. Seems really unprofessional to me.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353886196944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 18:29:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353886461965-71</Id><Topic><Title>Five Ultrabooks to Looks for on Cyber Monday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353881227161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:07:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 14 inch HP ENVY Ultrablook with Win8 Touch, Intel Core i3 is on dealnews for $550.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1353886461965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 18:34:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353888109198-72</Id><Title>Is this yet more bad news for Intel?</Title><Msg>Weekend tech reading: Haswell to be Intel's last swappable CPUs? By Matthew DeCarlo On November 25, 2012, 1:44 PM EST Intel’s Haswell could be last interchangeable desktop microprocessors As personal computers become smaller, their flexibility is decreasing. According to a media report starting from code-named Broadwell generation of processors, Intel Corp. will only offer mainstream desktop chips in BGA packaging, which will eliminate upgrade options as well as increase risks for PC makers. Both Intel and Advanced Micro Devices supply two different desktop platforms these days, making a very clear difference between mainstream and high-end desktop. X-bit Labs</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1353888109198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 19:01:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353888147853-73</Id><Title>Well the profits margins Intel has made in the past will be cut IMO</Title><Msg>I believe a lot of the margin and market strength comes from the X86 patent expansion as the technology is updated. ARMH has nullified this protection with its very fast growing architecture. I personally believe Intel is in competitive landscape like it has never seen. Mr. Market appears to agree. I believe it failed in mobile because it could not use the leverage of the patents.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1353888147853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 19:02:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353891652422-74</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi - Intel's very overlooked $2k wildcard</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1353493844004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 05:30:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is this disruptive market? How is Phi a disruptive product? Intel's policy is clear - they will only expose the x86 instruction set in their products. If they are to respond to GPGPUs, and they need to, they needed a highly threaded CPU with vector units to provide competitive floating point processing, and, surprise! That's what Phi looks like. If that isn't defensive then I don't understand what a defensive product is. As for the $1K margins on each chip, that appears to be a pipe dream. There is already word in the press that Intel is selling the co-processor BOARDS for $400 to the TACC. I'd be surprised if they're making any money at all at that $400 price point. That's in the range of the price for a simple 10 gigabit Ethernet adapter, not 240 x86 threads on a board, and this makes your original assertion, that these are $2K chips, look rather naive. The on-going Intel pumpers, you, Eassa, and Wallis, look like mere fanboys. Intel is a company that has learned to play one game, and while they weren't looking another game became more important. Phi is a defensive play in the old game. Truth be known, I'm not much of a fan of the GPGPU scenario. I think it's an overly complicated burden on software for the sake of utilizing some hardware that happens to have a cost-performance advantage for a little while. Making life difficult for software development is always a dumb idea. Nonetheless, Phi seems unlikely to be a major revenue or profit win for a long time. Only the most stubborn longs will see Phi a win. In the next two years either Intel wins in tablets and phones or we will all be holding stock worth about 50% less. (And by the way, I don't think the answer is just sell CPUs into those markets either.)</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1353891652422</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:00:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353891865120-75</Id><Topic><Title>A. Easa</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353886196944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 18:29:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What article are you referring to that was negative on Intel?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1353891865120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:04:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353892015762-76</Id><Topic><Title>Is this yet more bad news for Intel?</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1353888109198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 19:01:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is this bad news? This means Intel is focusing more on reducing platform power in general, which can only mean good things.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1353892015762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:06:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353892357380-77</Id><Topic><Title>A. Easa</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1353886196944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 18:29:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spoken like the true paranoid pd that you are.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353892357380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:12:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353892396716-78</Id><Topic><Title>att4gte classic sociopath</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353870631135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:10:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes..the worst kind...</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1353892396716</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:13:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353892867756-79</Id><Topic><Title>Is this yet more bad news for Intel?</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1353888109198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 19:01:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For "mainstream desktops" there is zero CPU upgrades. Gamers, overclockers and other real high end users might upgrade their CPU, but a barebones system today is same/cheaper price than an Intel retail CPU. This will reduce the prices or profit headroom for PC manufacturers as they are able to remove an expensive socket from their parts list and auto assemble the CPU.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1353892867756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:21:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353893988205-80</Id><Title>Hope Apple gets Samsung products banned in the U.S.</Title><Msg>Samsung is killing all the industries its in by undercutting everyone with this pricing. They really messed up Sony on TV's, and are trying to do the same thing in the cellphone market.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1353893988205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:39:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353895965065-81</Id><Topic><Title>Hope Apple gets Samsung products banned in the U.S.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1353893988205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:39:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SAMSUNG WILL DESTROY APPLE!!!!!!!!!!!! AND INTEL!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>nk499</Username><Timestamp>1353895965065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 21:12:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353896695798-82</Id><Topic><Title>Is this yet more bad news for Intel?</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1353888109198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 19:01:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Due to the market trends towards low-power microprocessors, Intel will offer various Broadwell multi-chip modules – which will contain Broadwell CPUs with integrated memory controller, graphics core, etc. and Wildcat Point input/output controllers – with various thermal design power envelopes, e.g., 10W, 15W and 47W/57W, according to the report. ------------------------------------- this actually good for Intel, new is better than upgrade from profit POV. you guys need to read the whole article to realize that</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1353896695798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 21:24:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353901516494-83</Id><Title>Trending</Title><Msg>Trending Up US Employment US Housing US Consumer Sentiment Chinese Economic Recovery Intel's Mobility Strategy for 2013 Intel: Haswell Intel:Clovertrail Intel:Phi "[Phi] is a disruptive product for a disruptive market and it is high profit, $1K+ for each chip. Intel would have to sell 100 Medfield phone chips to get that. It brings a scale of improvement to vectorized x86 code of about 5-10. An order of magnitude. Until the existing server/workstation market fully appreciates what it will bring to their existing code none of us know big the upgrade cycle it creates could be but it might snowball into an avalanche eventually. Haswell, Clovertrail and Phi will be Intel's bright rising stars in 2013. Haswell will be lapped up equally by gamers and ultrabook users as it simultaneously improves ultimate performance and power consumption. Clovertrail brings the iPad form factor to fully functional Windows PCs and Phi will reignite the Workstation/HPC market." Comments immediately above from marsavian Trending Down Wall Street's constant propaganda war against Intel Psychotic short shills with self-esteem issues endlessly creating new user IDs</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353901516494</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 22:45:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353901914300-84</Id><Title>Lenovo Announces New Tiny HTPC</Title><Msg>Lenovo has today announced the IdeaCenter Q190, a powerful HTPC featuring a third generation Intel Ivy Bridge i3 processor, a 1TB hard drive with a 24GB SSD cache, and 8GB RAM. The Q190 will be very small; some sources quote a total device width of 22mm although Lenovo has not yet listed the full dimensions. The system can be outfitted with the Windows 8 OS and boasts a 7.1 channel audio output, full HD graphics, as well as the option of a Blu-ray drive. The tiny device also packs in Ethernet connectivity, HDMI output (as well as legacy support via VGA), USB 3.0, and a card reader. The device is expected to be released around January 2013 and could be yours for as little as $349. As well as this, Lenovo has also announced several new all-in-one PCs, ranging from the $349 Lenovo C240 with an 18.5” touchscreen to the $549 C540 with a 23” touchscreen. Lenovo has certainly been working hard over the last couple of months considering the amount of new technology being released.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353901914300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 22:51:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353902244951-85</Id><Title>“world’s smallest full-function desktop PC”</Title><Msg>[Pretty cool!] Lenovo has announced its new IdeaCentre Q190, as well as new additions to the C-Series all-in-one line. The IdeaCentre Q190 is touted as the “world’s smallest full-function desktop PC,” making it an excellent option for those in the market for an entry-level, space-saving computer. The C-Series additions, meanwhile, give shoppers looking for an all-in-one PC a variety of options. The IdeaCentre Q190 measures in at a measely 22mm in width (less than 1-inch), and features full HD graphics, an optional Blu-ray drive, and a max of 7.1 surround sound, making it an excellent option for a home theater system. Inside you’ll find Intel Core i3 processors, with the system running Windows 8. The tiny computer will be available in January starting at $349. The C-Series all-in-one computers each offer up to 1TB of hard drive space, with the exception of the C540, which offers up to 2TB. You can get up to 8GB of RAM, and will have access to a 720p HD webcam, the Lenovo Education portal, and Dolby Advanced Audio V2. The C340, C440, C540, C345, and C445 models are all running Windows 8. The C240 and C245 models have an 18.5-inch display, and have a starting price of $349. The C340 ($499), C440 ($519), C540 ($549), C345 ($479), and C445 ($499) models are specifically optimized for entertainment, and come with Lenovo Dynamic Brightness System and Lenovo Eye Distance System, which lets the user know if they’re too close to the screen. The C340 and C345 have 20-inch displays, the C440 and C445 have 21.5-inch displays, and the C540 has a 23-inch display. The C240 and C245 will be available in November, while the rest will be available in January.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353902244951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 22:57:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353902621447-86</Id><Title>Acer Aspire S7 Review</Title><Msg>[Those with low-end computing needs or knowledge need not be bothered with the following review...] The larger of the two big-hitters in the Acer Aspire S7 series Ultrabooks sits here on our desk like a high-powered glass-covered knife, ready to bring the best we’ve seen in touchscreen-toting Windows 8-optimized notebook action to the market. This machine has been delivered to our doorstep in its most powerful configuration, all $1,649 USD of it – complete with a 3rd Generation (Ivy Bridge) Intel Core i7-3517U Processor clocked in at 1.9GHz. The 13.3-inch display here is a beastly Full HD 1920 x 1080 pixel resolution widescreen CineCrystal LED-backlit bit of technology with 10 finger touch and a 16:6 aspect ratio. Now we’ve got to see if this is enough to match up with that price – or if after all is said and done, the price will be the last of your thoughts in this next-generation experience! From Slashgear</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353902621447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 23:03:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353903105597-87</Id><Title>Mobile shopping hits all-time high on Thanksgiving</Title><Msg>[Wait for it, wait for it. Soon there will be a Wall Street type to post up "Bah, humbug..." and to indicate the many reasons why the US and world economies are crashing, doom and gloom will never go out of fashion and why no metric exists that will disprove any of this. In the meantime technology continues to change everything around us except these cretins...] While Black Friday might be the only day where brick-and-mortar stores see the rush of shoppers, online establishments have been feeling the rush all week long, with many online retailers starting their Black Friday deals at the beginning of the week. However, Thanksgiving Day saw the most mobile traffic ever when it comes to shopping.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353903105597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 23:11:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353904535289-88</Id><Title>Shipments of ultrabooks, ultra-like models to double in 2013</Title><Msg>Shipments of ultrabooks and ultra-like notebooks are expected to double in 2013 as compared to the previous year as brand vendors are adjusting their product mix to cope with falling market demand, according to industry sources. Vendors are shifting more capacity to ultrabooks and ultra-like models as consumers are seeking products with more value-added, the sources noted, adding that declining prices will also help ramp up ultrabook sales. Ultrabooks will account for 10% of global notebook shipments in 2013, and ultra-like ones will make up another 10%, the sources estimated.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353904535289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 23:35:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353905060096-89</Id><Title>Cyber Monday: Five Best Deal Sites</Title><Msg>Five Best Deal Sites Alan Henry The holiday shopping season is revving up, which means it's time to search for some bargains so you don't go broke buying gifts for the people on your list. There are dozens of deal sites out there, but not all of them are useful when it's time to actually find discounts on things you actually want to buy. We asked you which sites you used, and this week we're taking a look at the top five, based on your nominations. Earlier in the week we asked you which deal sites you used to save money. You offered up plenty of options, and we tallied up your votes, but sadly we only have room for the top five. Slickdeals Slickdeals is so popular and well known that at my last job, most of my colleagues in our IT group (and out of it, honestly) had Slickdeals as our browser homepages. We never wanted to miss a deal, and new ones were breaking and expiring all day. Slickdeals is largely community powered, with members floating up coupon codes and sales available at retailers all over the web for the community to see and take advantage of, and it's not just on technology and electronics: apparel, local deals at nearby shops, travel and vacation packages, it's all there. Or you can hop right to your favorite online retailer and see what they have to offer before you click purchase. The forums are active and lively, and the deals never stop. Dealnews The Dealnews network of sites, including DealMac and the old DealRAM and DealCam (which have now been absorbed into Dealnews) offer daily, regularly updating deals from around the web on computer equipment, home electronics, apparel, and much much more. Almost nothing escapes Dealnews's eye: monitors and displays, TVs and home entertainment gear, headphones and audio equipment, GPS systems, even sunglasses and clothing are all available. The backlog of deals is huge, and you just have to search for the product you're interested in to see what deals are active in that area and which ones have recently expired. They also get a ton of exclusive deals you'll only find at Dealnews, and an excellent collection of holiday and Black Friday bargains. I'm pretty sure half my gear I got thanks to Dealnews, and they're always worth a check for bargains before you start shopping. Woot! Woot started off as the original daily deal site, and since being purchased by Amazon back in 2010, has expanded its empire to not just daily technology deals, but deals on wine, kids clothing and toys, technology and home electronics, independently designed t-shirts and apparel, and more. They've also launched Deals.Woot, a community powered site full of bargains on virtually any item you can think of, from lingerie to computer components, all upvoted or downvoted by the community so you only see the deals that actually save you money. The other Woot sites also go out of their way to offer more than just one deal a day, with many offering exclusive bargains and super-deep discounts for limited times, most notably their repeated and regular discounts on Gunnar glasses. Fatwallet Fatwallet is another deal site that's been around for a long time, but they're worth a check before you go shopping online to make sure you're not missing a coupon code or a retailer that has the item you want on sale. Fatwallet covers major retailers and niche ones, in categories that are largely electronics and computer gear, but also include apparel, cosmetics, jewelry, and local deals in your community. Fatwallet's biggest resource is its community though: its active forums are full of regularly churning deals that appear, make it big all over the web, and then vanish when the coupon code has been used up or every other deal site on the web links to their forum threads. The site boasts millions of members, and the while the front page is great, the forums are where the magic happens. BradsDeals While many deal sites focus on technology deals and electronics discounts, BradsDeals offers up discounts, price alerts, and coupon codes on other items we all buy: clothing, apparel, toiletries and small electronics (shavers, razors, etc), and jewelry. The site has a wealth of coupon codes for popular retailers and big box stores with names you'd recognize, and even offers printable coupons as well so you can run to a brick-and-mortar store when you don't want to wait for shipping. If you've felt that other deal sites are huge electronics stores with tiny household sections and other departments, BradsDeals will fix that for you—think of more like a traditional department store, just only stocked with discounts and coupons you can use anywhere you want to shop.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1353905060096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 23:44:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>