<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348114561160-1</Id><Topic><Title>What's all this IBM 14nm talk? They won't even half 20nm for a couple of years, best case !!</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348080172603</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neck and neck.....wha???</Msg><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1348114561160</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:16:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348114583437-2</Id><Topic><Title>close at the low you POS</Title><Username>scott4usa</Username><Timestamp>1348084742797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:59:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK. No more posts.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348114583437</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:16:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348118031390-3</Id><Topic><Title>What's all this IBM 14nm talk? They won't even half 20nm for a couple of years, best case !!</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348080172603</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neither IBM nor TSMC has a solid litho roadmap - everything is in flux ... SOI? trigate, EUV? the foundry manufacturing roadmap (TSMC, UMC, Samsung, Gloflo) is totally fragmented - IBM is everything but a leader. The gap between Intel and the foundries that you are seeing today is a result of the fact that there was no significant demand for foundry fabrication resources 5 years ago yeah right - LOL - what about XLNX and ALTR?</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348118031390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 01:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348118382067-4</Id><Title>TSMC to offer only one process at 20-nm Dylan McGrath</Title><Msg>TSMC to offer only one process at 20-nm Dylan McGrath 4/17/2012 10:40 PM EDT SAN JOSE, Calif.—Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. Ltd. (TSMC) will offer only one process at the 20-nm node, a change from the multiple processes that the foundry giant has offered customers for the past several nodes, a TSMC executive said Tuesday (April 17). Speaking at TSMC's annual technology symposium here, Shang-yi Chiang, executive vice president and co-chief operating officer at TSMC, said the firm might also offer an 18- or 16-nm process node after 20-nm if lithography technology is not available to make 14-nm devices cost effectively. Chiang said the TSMC initially planned to offer two 20-nm processes, presumably a high performance process and a low-power process. Both processes would have featured high-k metal gate (HKMG) technology. But, after some development, TSMC determined that there was not a noticeable performance difference between the two 20-nm processes, Chiang said. Because 20-nm linewidths are so small, approaching fundamental physical limits, there isn't much room for tweaking design rules to specify different gate lengths and other requirements, Chiang said. TSMC offers four processes at the 28-nm node: a high performance process, a low power process, another low power process with HKMG and a high performance process geared for mobile applications. TSMC expects its 20-nm HKMG process to be in production next year. In 2015, TSMC wants to commence production at the 14-nm node, adding FinFET 3-D transistors. But the semiconductor industry is waiting on extreme ultraviolet (EUV) lithography, which has been delayed several times. To date, no power source has been developed to provide the power and stability necessary to enable volume production at sufficient throughput. Lithography tool vendor ASML Holding NV is working with several power source developers on the technology and has pledged to make available tools with sufficient throughput later this year for commercial chip production in 2013 and 2014. But many in the industry remain skeptical that EUV will be available in time to support the aggressive roadmaps of TSMC and other leading-edge chip manufacturers. Chiang also noted that lithographers have made a great deal of progress on the 193-nm immersion lithography to the point where it could be a commercially viable alternative at 14-nm. However, Chiang said, 193-nm immersion might require triple-patterning on some layers and double patterning on many layers in order to achieve adequate image fidelity, which would make it too costly for volume production. Chiang said TSMC is "thinking very carefully" about whether to offer an 18- or 16-nm process. "If we choose this node, we will have to offer it to customers for 10 years," Chiang said.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348118382067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 01:19:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348118640659-5</Id><Topic><Title>What's all this IBM 14nm talk? They won't even half 20nm for a couple of years, best case !!</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348080172603</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At this stage in the game, keeping your options open makes sense. They don't need to decide on these right away. They can wait and identify the emergent winner and their decision to wait is also dictated by the demand which appears to be predominantly low power SOC. I wouldn't consider XLNX and ALTR as significant demand compared to the PC industry that Intel was feeding. What we have now is comparable.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1348118640659</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 01:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348118902373-6</Id><Topic><Title>What's all this IBM 14nm talk? They won't even half 20nm for a couple of years, best case !!</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348080172603</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Fast forward and you see the foundries neck and neck with Intel." *** Every day you offer your opinion with nothing to back it up. Why do you bother? I'm thinking you're the fanboi's father, he's out drunk someplace and you are trying to cover for him...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348118902373</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 01:28:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348119291416-7</Id><Topic><Title>I need a Xeon Phi optimized compiler for Lattice C 2.1, which I purchased legitimately in 1989. I think Lattice 'C' is the future, since they</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1348107974571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:26:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can also use a Xeon Phi as a heater...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1348119291416</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 01:34:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348126300219-8</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to offer only one process at 20-nm Dylan McGrath</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348118382067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 01:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Based on market trends in high volume devices, it makes sense to have only one process targeting low power ARM based SOCs. This way you have smartphones, tablets and some PCs and cloud servers covered, a large enough market to feed into. Complexity in producing chips is increasing as the node progresses. Narrowing down your scope helps tame it somewhat. I think he makes some interesting points on cost of production and how that influences choice of process. Blindly going after a higher resolution node doesn't make business sense (Moore's law is over-rated).</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1348126300219</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 03:31:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348139795235-9</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to offer only one process at 20-nm Dylan McGrath</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348118382067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 01:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>..and horse drawn carriages have advantages over motor vehicles....gasoline engines are overrated.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348139795235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:16:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348144515814-10</Id><Title>misery loves company..</Title><Msg>i bought hi, and dont have the nads to sell. down 13000 so far. this is going to be my dividend "investment". hehe, looks like more downside to come.</Msg><Username>sharppolly</Username><Timestamp>1348144515814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:35:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348148223451-11</Id><Title>Globalfoundries Moves to Match Intel’s Transistors and Timing and I would like to cure cancer</Title><Msg>not going to happen!</Msg><Username>fmsg35</Username><Timestamp>1348148223451</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:37:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348148526926-12</Id><Topic><Title>I need a Xeon Phi optimized compiler for Lattice C 2.1, which I purchased legitimately in 1989. I think Lattice 'C' is the future, since they</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1348107974571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:26:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love watching INTC pimps get what they deserve after ruining so many startups and churning out #$%$ 386 derivatives for half a century. If I remember correctly, I sold my AMD at $40 or thereabouts. Way overvalued at those prices, but it was a nice swing trade. What was so funny about AMD is that they had a two year lead on INTC when it came to 64-bit technology, but Microsoft kept 64-bit under wraps to allow stinky pants INTC to catch up because they had wasted so much time on Merced errr ummmm I mean Itanic.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1348148526926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348148572979-13</Id><Topic><Title>What we know about Vinnie_bagodonitz (also known as Lucy Nuff, Too funny, etc)</Title><Username>vinnie_bagofhotwind</Username><Timestamp>1347979014823</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:36:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, I guarantee Lucy/Vinnie is sitting in some tiny cubible right now at a #$%$ Bank banging out Cobol code. ROFL !</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1348148572979</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:42:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348149480454-14</Id><Topic><Title>I need a Xeon Phi optimized compiler for Lattice C 2.1, which I purchased legitimately in 1989. I think Lattice 'C' is the future, since they</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1348107974571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:26:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what do you say about aapl then ?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348149480454</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:58:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348149542504-15</Id><Title>HPQ drops 3+%. Really?</Title><Msg>For what while Intc, AMD and even Dell down less than 1%?</Msg><Username>coolheadwarmblood</Username><Timestamp>1348149542504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:59:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348149565417-16</Id><Topic><Title>What's all this IBM 14nm talk? They won't even half 20nm for a couple of years, best case !!</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348080172603</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you blow intc up and here we are</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348149565417</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:59:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348149743135-17</Id><Topic><Title>Hey People,</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348075257732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lying pos</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1348149743135</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348149828564-18</Id><Title>Obama tells Letterman that debt is "fine" short-term, LOL! He basically said that debt is fine under his administration and then someone else can deal with it. What a #$%$</Title><Msg>People starving while he's up late night hobknobbing with Letterman, a known adulterer. Unreal how pathetic this country is becoming.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348149828564</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348150313994-19</Id><Title>KhitchD'uh Says</Title><Msg>KhitchD'uh says Moore's law is over-rated. Hahahahahahahahaha. The shill has spoken...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348150313994</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:11:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348150532898-20</Id><Title>Apple Maps Broken Now</Title><Msg>A casualty of the fight with Google. Could Apple actually someday decide that suing everyone, fighting with everyone might be a bad idea? Just another day of Wall Street's largest firms trying to erode the economy and beat Intel down. Scumbags...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348150532898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:15:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348150565819-21</Id><Title>OB will win re-election so quit your crying Teabagger nimrods.</Title><Msg>Debt? Like the Congress gives a sheet? It does not matter what budget OB would put in front of those clowns because they would not pass it anyway. The GOP wants to increase military spending while the Dems want to cut it. The Dems will not cut Medicaid and Medicare in a huge way as the GOP want. Neither one has introduced a budget that would balance the budget. The Ryan so called plan the idiots in the GOP voted for in the house would not balance the budget for thirty years according to independent looks. Oh well--funny you on the right never cared about a balanced budget for 8 years of Bush yearly massive deficit spending. if you on the right really cared, why in heck do you vote for those idiots who hold House seats who are republicans clowns who do not balace the budget. Nominate GOP who will vote for a balanced budget. The only guy who would have done it who ran for Pres was Ron Paul and yur GOP trashed him and laughed at him on Fuxed up news. All true.</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1348150565819</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:16:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348150913127-22</Id><Title>We are not living in a Post PC world</Title><Msg>We are not living in a Post PC world Todd Bradley who is executive vice president of HP’s printing and personal systems group, is quite emphatic that we are not living in a post-PC world. In an interview with PC World, Bradly said that it was “just wrong” to think that the PC has had its day. He said that when a kid goes to college, they need a PC. Businesses who want their employees to be productive, need a PC. Bradley said that the size of the PC market was huge and even if there is a place for tablets, they will not be the big enchilada for a while. He was also a little sniffy about HP moving to make Windows 8 Arm based tablets. Apparently the maker of expensive printer ink will be making tablets that run on the x86 platform. It will use both Intel and AMD architecture because it was a lot more robust and established than things Armish. HP sees x86 chips delivering one of the best experiences in the short term and near future. While it will develop ideas with its partners in the ARM ecosystem, its first tablets will be based on the x86 architecture. From Fudzilla</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348150913127</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:21:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348151019575-23</Id><Title>ITC to investigate Apple's patent infringement</Title><Msg>Motorola might have a case The US ITC said it will investigate if Apple has nicked Motorola technology in its iPhones, iPods, iMacs and tablets. Motorola is asking for import bans on just about every iOS device, including the Mac OS X computer, claiming Apple's iMessage technology infringes a Motorola patent. On the whole, Motorola names seven patents, all of which are allegedly infringed upon by some or all of these iOS devices: the iPod Touch, iPhone 3GS, iPhone 4, iPhone 4S, and all three generations of the iPad. Presumably, the iPhone 5 will be complained about later. This patent, filed for in 2001 and issued in 2006, covers a "System for providing continuity between messaging clients and method therefor." Motorola said that Apple's iMessage client for iOS and Mac OS X violates a claim in that patent covering "A plurality of messaging clients within a messaging communication system for providing continuity between the plurality of messaging clients comprising: a first messaging client, for establishing a first communication connection including a plurality of client data with a message server; and a second messaging client for receiving the plurality of client data from the first messaging client and for establishing a second communication connection including the plurality of client data with the message server." iMessage provides a common messaging client between iOS and Mac OS X devices, with users being able to "start a messaging conversation on an OS X Mountain Lion device such as a MacBook Air, and continue the conversation on another device running the 'iMessage' messaging client on iOS 5 software, such as an iPhone 4S." This idea did not spring fully formed from the head of Steve Jobs but was already invented by Motorola, the ITC was told. Motorola said that iMessage on the MacBook Air "establishes a first communication connection via WiFi or LAN or otherwise resulting in the exchange of data with Apple's message server." The iMessage messaging client on the iPhone 4S can establish a second communication via WiFi or 3G that results in the receipt of data from Apple's message server." The ITC announcement that it will open an investigation into "certain Apple iPhones, iPods, iPads, and Apple personal computers” is a sign that the ITC thinks the claim might have legs. From Fudzilla</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348151019575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348151154731-24</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to offer only one process at 20-nm Dylan McGrath</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348118382067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 01:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, gonna let their customers pay 100% of the R&amp;D for any tuned process</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1348151154731</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:25:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348151318495-25</Id><Title>Forbes: Globalfoundries has 14nm finfets and production</Title><Msg>article in Forbes 9/20/12. Is this for real?????</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348151318495</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:28:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348151365003-26</Id><Title>Intel's Embedded Framework Gains Traction at DESIGN East</Title><Msg>Microcontroller makers and software developers welcomed Intel to the embedded software party following the PC giant’s announcement of a framework for embedded middleware. Intel announced last week its Intelligent Systems Framework to secure, manage and aid connectivity for embedded systems. It uses a combination of code from its McAfee and Wind River divisions along with Intel’s VPro management software for PCs. The framework intends to smooth a path for a growing class of sensors that gather and communicate data as part of an Internet of Things. Because it is tied to use on x86 processors, it is likely to see most widespread use on gateways and hubs, becoming a de facto standard that end nodes based on microcontrollers will need to support.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348151365003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:29:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348151495940-27</Id><Title>Why are you queuing fanboys?</Title><Msg>Samsung is having a lot of fun at Apple's expense. For a while now it has been running adverts which take the mickey out of Apple fanboys who slavishly buy what ever Apple tells them. This time it has run a series of adverts which show Apple fans queuing for what they have been told is the latest technology. The only problem, as the adverts point out, is that there is little in the new Apple 5 which has not been on Samsung, or Android phones for months or years. The Samsung III has a bigger screen, and also runs LTE which appears to be Jobs' Mob's thunder well and truly taken. That means that people are queuing outside Apple stores waiting for a product whose spec is already outclassed by rivals. Samsung als took a shot at the iPhone 5 this weekend, running full-page ads in newspapers saying "it doesn't take a genius ..." It listed features of the iPhone 5 and the Galaxy S III, with the Samsung phone's list nearly twice as long. The ad concludes: "The next big thing is already here." You can check out the cheeky ad after the break. From Fudzilla</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348151495940</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:31:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348151704692-28</Id><Title>To $17</Title><Msg>This POS will slide down to $17. PCs are a dying breed, increasingly everyone is workling on tablets and Intel is way behind in tablet technology, they cannot catchup with Apple and Samsung.</Msg><Username>wankhede99</Username><Timestamp>1348151704692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348151778472-29</Id><Topic><Title>To $17</Title><Username>wankhede99</Username><Timestamp>1348151704692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should have just said "I'd LOVE to get a chance to buy Intel at 17" instead of throwing in the lies.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348151778472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348152027114-30</Id><Title>ARMs Fabrication Is Okay. Really...</Title><Msg>The attempts to make us believe that ARMs fabrication is okay go on and on. The thing is - it isn't okay. No matter what the latest shill posters and the media say (without support, logic or details of course). And the article today saying GloFlo has decided to match Intel's pace and technology. Why do they let the marketing departments write this swill? Well, because what else are they going to do? ARM has 28nm production. And not much of that. They tell us they are just around the corner from FinFET and 14nm production yet they haven't even rolled out 20nm production and no one knows when they will. "When TSMC started ramping up its 40/45nm production capacity, it took 5-6 quarters to have the process contribute 10% to company revenues, Chai pointed out. As for 65nm, the period was shorter but still longer than three quarters allowing the process to account for 10% of TSMC's revenues." So the problems started a long time ago with ARM fabrication. If you can't roll out 45nm production quickly how are you going to deal with 14nm and EUV? The ARM fabrication crisis is real and getting worse. But don't tell Wall Street. Because they think everything is peachy keen...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348152027114</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:40:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348152162985-31</Id><Title>Intel working on direct to OEM foundry deal with Cisco</Title><Msg>Says Piper Jaffray just before immediately reverting to form and trying to beat Intel to pulp. Scumbags...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348152162985</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:42:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152204657-32</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Globalfoundries has 14nm finfets and production</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348151318495</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:28:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, but hype: CHIP SHOP Globalfoundries has launched its 14nm process node that uses FinFET 3D transistors. Intel stole a march on the industry with its 22nm Tri-gate process node, a subset of FinFET technology, however Globalfoundries is the first to announce a 14nm process node that uses 3D transistors to fab chips. The firm markets its 14nm process node as "extreme mobility" and is pitching it towards mobile system-on-chip (SoC) vendors. Globalfoundries said its 14nm process node uses parts of its existing 20nm process node and fabs FinFETs that the firm tries very hard to say are not the same as the 3D transistors that Intel has marketed so cleverly in the past year. According to the company, its 14nm FinFET process node is particularly well suited to SoCs, exactly the type of chips vendors such as Qualcomm and Nvidia are trying to get TSMC to produce on its 28nm process node. TSMC told The INQUIRER last week that it doesn't expect to meet demand on its 28nm process node until the end of 2013, and that leaves Qualcomm, which has already called out TSMC over its production capacity, few options for cutting edge process node technology. We have heard for some time that Globalfoundries could receive inquiries from disgruntled TSMC customers and the launch of the firm's 14nm process node, which is clearly pitched at SoC vendors, might trigger some interest. Globalfoundries might have launched its 14nm process node but it is far from ready to churn out production chips. The firm said its Fab 8 in Saratoga County, New York is producing test silicon and customer tape-outs are expected in 2013, meaning that any major delays will give any advantage Globalfoundries might have gained back to TSMC. µ</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1348152204657</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:43:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152309886-33</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Globalfoundries has 14nm finfets and production</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348151318495</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:28:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC's complete blunder has brought new life to the fabs... The fabs have become more aggressive...competition is good !!! but we'll see if they deliver...and those yields..</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1348152309886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:45:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152489068-34</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Globalfoundries has 14nm finfets and production</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348151318495</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:28:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"article in Forbes 9/20/12. Is this for real?????" *** Of course not. They don't have 28nm in volume, don't have 20nm at all and they want us to believe now they will skip all of that and move to FinFET, EUV and 14nm. If anyone believes this is going to happen in less than 4 or 5 years, I have a bridge, a watch and some swampland that you are going to be very interested in...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348152489068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:48:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152493498-35</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to offer only one process at 20-nm Dylan McGrath</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348118382067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 01:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blindly going after a higher resolution node doesn't make business sense (Moore's law is over-rated). So why did TSMC and Samsung follow (opposite of leading) Intel buying a hefty stake $ billion stake in ASML if not for Moor's law. 20 years ago a 386 laptop sold for $6000!!!!</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348152493498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152523119-36</Id><Topic><Title>Hey People,</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348075257732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I interpreted the question from kblank657: "like the weaver "chump" one. No offense meant to orig. weaver" as: "did the person who created the weaver "chump" alias intend to offend weaver?" My answer to the kblank657 question was: The person who created the "weaver chump" alias intended to offend weaver. One of my many problems seems to be that I am unable to write a message clearly enough so you can understand it. I am long Intel. I am short Intel put options (bullish .... to make it very clear). I think Intel is a good company. I think that Intel has missed some opportunities (and will make mistakes in the future like everyone else). I think that Intel will recover and take a good chunk of new markets. I am not a shill. I wish i had sold at $29 so I could buy back cheaper. I am not devastated that I did not sell at $29. I have missed many market and stock peaks and bottoms in the past. I will miss the peaks and bottoms in the future. I share what knowledge and opinions I have. I don't offer my opinion as fact and expect people to verify (or at least audit) what I say. I like messages of yours that point out news and inform. I might be "passive aggressive" but I don't think so. I don't care for messages on politics, religion and ones focused on personal attacks. Oh crap!!! Did I just say all that??? Cheers Of course all that is just the opinion of ..... A. Dums.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348152523119</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:48:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152548936-37</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Globalfoundries has 14nm finfets and production</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348151318495</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:28:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Plus they would need about $20 billion in capital. Like GloFlo is going to raise that...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348152548936</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:49:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348152774828-38</Id><Title>Note to Dumas</Title><Msg>Thank you for the clarification. For some reason some messages come up without a reply button...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348152774828</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:52:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152803632-39</Id><Topic><Title>Globalfoundries Moves to Match Intel’s Transistors and Timing and I would like to cure cancer</Title><Username>fmsg35</Username><Timestamp>1348148223451</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:37:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>with their 1 fab plan,t Ha ha ha ha ha</Msg><Username>fmsg35</Username><Timestamp>1348152803632</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152973874-40</Id><Topic><Title>Keep Your Eyes On $23.02</Title><Username>wilder_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1347907500878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:45:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you listen to Wilder or did you listen to Wally?</Msg><Username>wilder_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1348152973874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:56:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348153145116-41</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Globalfoundries has 14nm finfets and production</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348151318495</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:28:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you read the guy's relationship at the bottom. A Complete HYPE. Atleast 20BIL capital requirement. What is he smoking???</Msg><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1348153145116</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:59:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348153763927-42</Id><Topic><Title>This group of stock braniacs nailed INTC in advance of everyone.</Title><Username>allenjoe3624</Username><Timestamp>1348152473271</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:47:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These guys are on a volcano hot streak nowadays. I don't think that they will discontinue or slow down just yet.</Msg><Username>stanleyanthony36</Username><Timestamp>1348153763927</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348153787425-43</Id><Title>Jim Chanos Says SELL ALL PC Related Stocks</Title><Msg>07:55 EDT HPQ, DELL, MSFT Jim Chanos expects PC-related companies to remain under pressure 07:54 EDT MSFT, HPQ, DELL Jim Chanos recommends short position in PC-related companies Chanos is speaking on CNBC. That said, he is long ORCL and MSFT.</Msg><Username>wilder_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1348153787425</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:09:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348153913163-44</Id><Topic><Title>Obama tells Letterman that debt is "fine" short-term, LOL! He basically said that debt is fine under his administration and then someone else can deal with it. What a #$%$</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348149828564</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Knock that sh.t off. This is a message board for Intel stock, not for you to post your illiterate political posts. Go somewhere else because no one wants you on this site.</Msg><Username>ldemoss</Username><Timestamp>1348153913163</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:11:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348154335340-45</Id><Topic><Title>Obama tells Letterman that debt is "fine" short-term, LOL! He basically said that debt is fine under his administration and then someone else can deal with it. What a #$%$</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348149828564</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who put you in charge, buttwad?</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348154335340</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:18:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>45</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348154596725-46</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Globalfoundries has 14nm finfets and production</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348151318495</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:28:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It seems like they say they are using the 20nm process node and 20nm process transistor spacing to build some 14nm transistors on it. Whatever they have in 2014 will be measured on die size, power consumption and costs. GF does not have the best track record. Intel has plowed the road at 22nm and ramped Ivy Bridge production rapidly. From GF blog ... Architecting Advanced Technologies: Not All FinFETs are Created Equal Posted on September 20, 2012 By Gregg Bartlett</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348154596725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:23:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348154934124-47</Id><Topic><Title>Obama tells Letterman that debt is "fine" short-term, LOL! He basically said that debt is fine under his administration and then someone else can deal with it. What a #$%$</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1348149828564</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then where is the bash the worst president Obama board because we need one</Msg><Username>fmsg35</Username><Timestamp>1348154934124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:28:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348155795044-48</Id><Topic><Title>This group of stock braniacs nailed INTC in advance of everyone.</Title><Username>allenjoe3624</Username><Timestamp>1348152473271</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:47:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi and thanks. I hadn't registered yet. Completing this task as soon as possible.</Msg><Username>johnronald600</Username><Timestamp>1348155795044</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:43:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348156274721-49</Id><Title>Intel buying back shares cheap when nobody's watching. Check today's Yahoo news. You gonna listen to an Analyst that says sell at the bottom of the COMANY itself, that's buying shares with CASH</Title><Msg>??????????????</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348156274721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348156400411-50</Id><Topic><Title>Intel buying back shares cheap when nobody's watching. Check today's Yahoo news. You gonna listen to an Analyst that says sell at the bottom of the COMANY itself, that's buying shares with CASH</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348156274721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Share count dropping, EPS will rise out of this world in due time. Losers.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348156400411</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:53:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348156513040-51</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes: Globalfoundries has 14nm finfets and production</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348151318495</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:28:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jul 31, 2012 – And as part of its strategy, TSMC has accelerated its finFET roadmap. Rival GlobalFoundries is considering a plan to offer dedicated modules ... Firms Rethink Fabless-Foundry Model By Mark LaPedus As chipmakers move toward 20nm designs, finFETs and 3D stacked devices, the industry is beginning to re-think the fabless-foundry model....... GlobalFoundries and Samsung have yet to change their finFET strategies. GlobalFoundries still plans to roll out a finFET at the 14nm node in the fourth quarter of 2014 or first quarter of 2015, according to Kengeri.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348156513040</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:55:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348156784840-52</Id><Topic><Title>Attention all tech people</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348087981231</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:53:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not tech but Financial stuff Regular dividend announcement; If Intel follows the past couple years, they should announce a 22.5 cent dividend approved by the BOD in the next few days. They just increased to 22.5 from 21 last quarter so I don't see them increasing it. If they did increase, it would be a surprise. More money tossed into the share buy-back bucket by the BOD is likely as part of the dividend announcement.. EU $1.45bil fine court appeal process completed on July 8th. The court has yet to issue their ruling. The original 500 page ruling and fine against Intel was not warranted (IMO) but will not likely be overturned. I would expect the fine to be reduced.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348156784840</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:59:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348157188648-53</Id><Topic><Title>Intel buying back shares cheap when nobody's watching. Check today's Yahoo news. You gonna listen to an Analyst that says sell at the bottom of the COMANY itself, that's buying shares with CASH</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348156274721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get to the top da**it.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348157188648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:06:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348157828803-54</Id><Topic><Title>Intel buying back shares cheap when nobody's watching. Check today's Yahoo news. You gonna listen to an Analyst that says sell at the bottom of the COMANY itself, that's buying shares with CASH</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348156274721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly. They buy in the shares with company cash to support the share price, then they issue more stock options to insiders with ZERO strikes, and said insiders, whenever possible, exercise those ZERO strike options and immediately dump the stock. Lather, rinse, repeat ... In other words, the insiders are running an ATM for themselves at the expense of the regular shareholders since the number of shares outstanding never reduces by anything meaningful despite all that cash being used to buy in the shares. THAT'S what you dumba zzes should be writing to the SEC about --- it should be illegal (but isn't) for the insiders to sell stock while the company is buying stock at their direction. Write the letters!</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1348157828803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348158003330-55</Id><Topic><Title>Intel buying back shares cheap when nobody's watching. Check today's Yahoo news. You gonna listen to an Analyst that says sell at the bottom of the COMANY itself, that's buying shares with CASH</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348156274721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the number of shares outstanding never reduces by anything meaningful despite all that cash being used to buy in the shares" Wrong, but I don't expect you to do any research/tell the truth as you a just another Lucy_Nuff alias. I have your alias count well over 100 now. What percentage of shares have they retired over the last 10 years, big shot?</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348158003330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:20:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348158061464-56</Id><Topic><Title>Intel buying back shares cheap when nobody's watching. Check today's Yahoo news. You gonna listen to an Analyst that says sell at the bottom of the COMANY itself, that's buying shares with CASH</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348156274721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis alias "intc_inside" desperately trying to keep his pumper message at the top of the message board. Glad I was able to help you out, Pumpwad!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348158061464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:21:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>44</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348158206239-57</Id><Topic><Title>Intel buying back shares cheap when nobody's watching. Check today's Yahoo news. You gonna listen to an Analyst that says sell at the bottom of the COMANY itself, that's buying shares with CASH</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348156274721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong again, I 've called Wally out publicly. Check my post history and Guess again, chump.nuff.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348158206239</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:23:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348158630120-58</Id><Title>ARM "architecture"..........LMFAO Trash architecture, smoke and mirrors</Title><Msg>Snipped below from a SA article posted today: Even ARM Isn't Selling Custom Designs The big misconception that people have is that ARM's designs somehow lead the device vendors to have more customized designs than competing Intel solutions. To understand how ARM's business works, it is key to understand the two types of ARM licensees: Fully Custom: In this case, the chip designer is simply licensing the right to make an ARM compatible CPU, but will take on the responsibilities of actually doing the design work that ends up defining the chip in terms of performance, power consumption, etc. Examples of companies doing so are Apple , Qualcomm, Applied Micro (AMCC), and Marvell (MRVL) System-On-Chip Customization: In this case, the licensee uses a fully-designed ARM processor core and then builds a system-on-chip around the core. In no case is ARM Holdings itself selling custom designs; it has a standard set of cores that the system-on-chip designers can either use or not use.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348158630120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:30:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348158758353-59</Id><Topic><Title>Intel buying back shares cheap when nobody's watching. Check today's Yahoo news. You gonna listen to an Analyst that says sell at the bottom of the COMANY itself, that's buying shares with CASH</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348156274721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel RSU tax sales process makes it look like the employees are rolling over options. Intel incorporates RSU stock options into the compensation packages of most of its employees. In response to financial reporting rule changes, Intel to the RSU shares which do have a strike price of $0. When the RSU vest, the owner is responsible for taxes on the gains from $0 to market price for that tax year. Most employees have elected the option to sell shares to pay for the tax payments. The executives who must file the SEC FORM 4 to report these insider tax sales make it look like they are just rolling the shares over. The Form 4 must be read to understand the difference.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348158758353</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:32:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348158785385-60</Id><Topic><Title>Intel buying back shares cheap when nobody's watching. Check today's Yahoo news. You gonna listen to an Analyst that says sell at the bottom of the COMANY itself, that's buying shares with CASH</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348156274721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What percentage of shares have they retired over the last 10 years, big shot?" Less than 10%. Now how about some questions for you: How many billions did they spend in so doing, and what was the company's resulting average price per share for the retired shares? In the meantime, how much money did the insiders reap off this wicked scam they are perpetrating on unsuspecting dopes like you? (Or are you merely a shill and not a dope?)</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1348158785385</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:33:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348159040420-61</Id><Topic><Title>Intel buying back shares cheap when nobody's watching. Check today's Yahoo news. You gonna listen to an Analyst that says sell at the bottom of the COMANY itself, that's buying shares with CASH</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348156274721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What percentage of shares have they retired over the last 10 years, big shot?" Less than 10%. Now how about some questions for you: How many billions did they spend in so doing, and what was the company's resulting average price per share for the retired shares? In the meantime, how much money did the insiders reap off this wicked scam they are perpetrating on unsuspecting dopes like you? (Or are you merely a shill and not a dope?) __________________________________ #$%$ clown. Alexander, easily the best poster on this board just explained it for you since you can't comprehend anything. Stand down, little girl.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348159040420</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:37:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348159250140-62</Id><Title>Long on INTC? Play options short term?</Title><Msg>Thoughts on the Oct earnings from INTC and if you think the stock price has taken into account the negative news about the earnings report</Msg><Username>xyankeesx</Username><Timestamp>1348159250140</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:40:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348160979949-63</Id><Topic><Title>Long on INTC? Play options short term?</Title><Username>xyankeesx</Username><Timestamp>1348159250140</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Q3 results will very close to the revision. I expect results to meet or slightly exceed forecasts. Q4 forecast by Intel will be ignored by the analysts. There is a big player messing around with the options and many times arbitraging dividend. Friday's weekly calls show some vertical option spread activity on the order of 10k to 30k shares. Check out the even dollar Friday 9/22 strike prices. Lots of volume and open interest.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348160979949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:09:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348161032023-64</Id><Title>Wally's FAVOURITE COLOR is RED</Title><Msg>Intel is ALWAYS RED and Wallis ALWAYS LOVES Intel. Did you ever see Wallis say "take a little off the table" or "wait for a pullback to buy?"</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348161032023</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:10:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>44</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348161882012-65</Id><Topic><Title>This group of stock braniacs nailed INTC in advance of everyone.</Title><Username>allenjoe3624</Username><Timestamp>1348152473271</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:47:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Geez. Fokking doing this now. I did not remember this guy. Heard a lot of superior things.</Msg><Username>stanleyanthony36</Username><Timestamp>1348161882012</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:24:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348162016539-66</Id><Topic><Title>Long on INTC? Play options short term?</Title><Username>xyankeesx</Username><Timestamp>1348159250140</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>9/22 INTC120922C00022000 is in the money though, do you think the hit from bad news is already baked in? I love the INTC stock and dividend, and you're right no one is touching them and they didn't even start getting into mobile yet</Msg><Username>xyankeesx</Username><Timestamp>1348162016539</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:26:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348162835531-67</Id><Topic><Title>Globalfoundries Moves to Match Intel’s Transistors and Timing and I would like to cure cancer</Title><Username>fmsg35</Username><Timestamp>1348148223451</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:37:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>with the 1 plant that gave amd so much headaches.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1348162835531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:40:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348162988150-68</Id><Title>Fox news poll out today. swing states Rush is not even pumping Rombo today</Title><Msg>Fox News released a new poll Thursday showing that President Barack Obama leads Mitt Romney in three battleground states, topping off a week of bad-news polling for the Republican presidential nominee in toss-up states. The poll, which covered Ohio, Virginia and Florida, shows Obama leading the former governor by seven points in both Ohio (49 to 42 percent) and Virginia (50 to 43 percent). In Florida, Obama leads by five points (49 to 44 percent), which is within the poll's margin of error. Obama won all three states in 2008, marking the first time Virginia voted for a Democratic president since 1964. In Michigan and Wisconsin, Obama has also opened up a lead against his rival: A CNN poll puts him up eight points in Michigan (52 to 44 percent), and one from Marquette Law School has Obama leading Romney by 14 points in Wisconsin (54 to 40 percent). In August, Obama led Romney in Wisconsin by only three points. New York Times pollster Nate Silver notes that Obama tends to do better against Romney in polls that include cell phones and use live interviewers instead of automated questions. (About a third of U.S. households are cell phone-only.) Silver writes that Obama has shown a clear lead in the 16 cell phone-inclusive polls of seven top battleground states taken since the convention. (The Fox, CNN and Marquette Law School polls all included cell phones.) On average, he's shown a 5.8 percentage point lead in these surveys. The exception is Colorado, where Obama and Romney are neck and neck. But there's some evidence that the "bounce" Obama has enjoyed since the Democratic National Convention in Charlotte, N.C., may be dissipating. The Romney campaign has pointed to the Gallup national tracking poll, which found Romney and Obama in a dead tie this week, and a recent Rasmussen poll showed Romney leading Obama by three points in New Hampshire. Our poll tracker, which averages all national polls, has Obama leading by a little under four points.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348162988150</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348163406085-69</Id><Topic><Title>Fox news poll out today. swing states Rush is not even pumping Rombo today</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1348162988150</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so you're spamming the INTC message board why?</Msg><Username>xyankeesx</Username><Timestamp>1348163406085</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:50:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348163733825-70</Id><Topic><Title>This group of stock braniacs nailed INTC in advance of everyone.</Title><Username>allenjoe3624</Username><Timestamp>1348152473271</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:47:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol. All of you are novices. this newsletter is in all probability the most effective go to resource for volatile stocks.</Msg><Username>johnronald600</Username><Timestamp>1348163733825</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:55:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348164697907-71</Id><Topic><Title>This group of stock braniacs nailed INTC in advance of everyone.</Title><Username>allenjoe3624</Username><Timestamp>1348152473271</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:47:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great report inside the site i signed up</Msg><Username>jerryrick96</Username><Timestamp>1348164697907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348166304269-72</Id><Topic><Title>Wally's FAVOURITE COLOR is RED</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1348161032023</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:10:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally better hire the elevator repair man to get this back to the 24 level, 29 may have been the top for years to come, similar to the other rally top post March 03 of 34.00 eight years ago.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348166304269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:38:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348166420176-73</Id><Topic><Title>Long on INTC? Play options short term?</Title><Username>xyankeesx</Username><Timestamp>1348159250140</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It depends on what your goals are. The option expires tomorrow so there is not much premium but not much time and it would be a gamble. Intel has bounced off $23 and I could see them trade it down to below $23.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348166420176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:40:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348168579803-74</Id><Title>$25 is in view</Title><Msg>It will be here before the end of the year.</Msg><Username>goofy_investor</Username><Timestamp>1348168579803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348168636418-75</Id><Topic><Title>This group of stock braniacs nailed INTC in advance of everyone.</Title><Username>allenjoe3624</Username><Timestamp>1348152473271</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:47:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well this stock wont make you rich thats for sure</Msg><Username>jerryrick96</Username><Timestamp>1348168636418</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:17:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348168712858-76</Id><Topic><Title>$25 is in view</Title><Username>goofy_investor</Username><Timestamp>1348168579803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't be afraid of making money. Buy INTC and make good money.</Msg><Username>goofy_investor</Username><Timestamp>1348168712858</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348168801532-77</Id><Title>Reversing yesterday trend</Title><Msg>It will go higher before the close.</Msg><Username>goofy_investor</Username><Timestamp>1348168801532</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:20:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348168953136-78</Id><Title>Program traders are keeping it down</Title><Msg>But not anymore.</Msg><Username>goofy_investor</Username><Timestamp>1348168953136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:22:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348169551076-79</Id><Title>intc is skyrocketing</Title><Msg>it is</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348169551076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:32:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348169624368-80</Id><Topic><Title>Intel buying back shares cheap when nobody's watching. Check today's Yahoo news. You gonna listen to an Analyst that says sell at the bottom of the COMANY itself, that's buying shares with CASH</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348156274721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When the RSU vest, the owner is responsible for taxes on the gains from $0 to market price for that tax year. Most employees have elected the option to sell shares to pay for the tax payments." Alexander, I respect your postings. The thing to look at with respect to the above, is that more often than not, the insiders sell exercise and sell their entire vesting, and believe it or not, they are not taxed at 100%, so the explanation falls short. You need only look at the reported insider transactions to see I am not making this up. In any case, I stand by my position that the practice should be against the law. Only the insiders have any reason to support the current practice. Write the letters!</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1348169624368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:33:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170245237-81</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, this is an old-fashioned dump</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347028575983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 10:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Where's support, $23?" So far.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1348170245237</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:44:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170525742-82</Id><Topic><Title>$25 is in view</Title><Username>goofy_investor</Username><Timestamp>1348168579803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why</Msg><Username>xyankeesx</Username><Timestamp>1348170525742</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:48:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170552825-83</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, this is an old-fashioned dump</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347028575983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 10:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it would be a bigger problem if they did get into mobile technologies and they were taking a dive like this ... this is room for growth for them</Msg><Username>xyankeesx</Username><Timestamp>1348170552825</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:49:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348170599250-84</Id><Title>What does this insider know that eludes Wallus Weener?</Title><Msg>Check out the insider activity of SODHANI ARVIND (yahoo won't even permit a link to its own site, which is rediculous, so you'll have to go to "Insider Transactions", then click on the name of the above insider to see his activities of the past 2 years). Very inspiring confidence. Need more examples? Click on some other names. These guys seem to think the future of Intel is not nearly as attractive as the proverbial bird in the hand (and a free bird at that). You want to defend this practice? Write the letters!</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1348170599250</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:49:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170653875-85</Id><Topic><Title>Long on INTC? Play options short term?</Title><Username>xyankeesx</Username><Timestamp>1348159250140</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like the Oct 22 or 23 put on this one ... thoughts?</Msg><Username>xyankeesx</Username><Timestamp>1348170653875</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:50:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170789581-86</Id><Topic><Title>$25 is in view</Title><Username>goofy_investor</Username><Timestamp>1348168579803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Entirely possible that the stock will bounce from current $23 support back up to around the 50 day SMA, which is currently declining from just above $25. And, of course, $25 is in view in the rearview mirror as well.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1348170789581</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:53:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348171045531-87</Id><Topic><Title>$25 is in view</Title><Username>goofy_investor</Username><Timestamp>1348168579803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so you like the call</Msg><Username>xyankeesx</Username><Timestamp>1348171045531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348171687764-88</Id><Title>My heavens the NAZI closed on the Devils number</Title><Msg>DAGGER</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1348171687764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348171839688-89</Id><Topic><Title>$25 is in view</Title><Username>goofy_investor</Username><Timestamp>1348168579803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"so you like the call" Got no problem with it, that's for sure. I am involved in the financial markets for one reason: to make money. All this "religious" and "patriotic" crap that posters like Wallus try to evoke about the company is just that: crap, just as is all the now overdone press about the "death of the PC". Sentiment creates price movement, which creates opportunity to profit. The rest is noise. "News" itself is irrelevant; it's the price reaction to it that tells the story.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1348171839688</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:10:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348175614950-90</Id><Title>Intel announced partnership with Cisco, sees 1 billion per year bump. HUGE!</Title><Msg>Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) is readying itself to partner with Cisco Systems, Inc. (NASDAQ:CSCO) through which arrangement it would manufacture the latter’s custom processors, according to Piper. Further, Intel believes that such a deal could bring $1 billion per year.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348175614950</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348175772450-91</Id><Topic><Title>Intel announced partnership with Cisco, sees 1 billion per year bump. HUGE!</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348175614950</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deals like this just prove that INTEL is trusted by big-name customers AND that more and more deals like this will pop up as Intel keeps making faster processors that take up less power. If others don't want to use the cutting-edge manufacturiing facilities that Intel has coming online, no worries as they'll be plenty of business.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348175772450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:16:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348176820788-92</Id><Topic><Title>Long on INTC? Play options short term?</Title><Username>xyankeesx</Username><Timestamp>1348159250140</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am very guilty of shorting puts on Intel. The dividend is nicely reflected in the premium when compared to the premium on the calls. I am long puts now. Nov $25 and Jan $26. I just rolled out the $25 to Nov because the premium dropped below a dime. I got caught in the down draft but I am OK. I tend to sell ATM where the premium is highest ... The OCT $22 with a premium of 22 cents and $23 with a premium of 54 cents both look OK here. After the sell off, I might even go to Oct $24 with a premium of $1.10 or Nov $23 with a premium of 84 cents or a Nov $24 at $1.45. The one month OCT - NOV includes some extra premium for the dividend price adjustment. It really depends on what you are comfortable with. I don't worry letting them expire and will usually close early at a profit or roll out when preimum thins do a dime but I expected Intel to hold at $25. So how much is my guidance worth??? 8-)</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348176820788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:33:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348177018618-93</Id><Topic><Title>Long on INTC? Play options short term?</Title><Username>xyankeesx</Username><Timestamp>1348159250140</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I am long puts now." I meant that I had a position. I WRITE puts and I am SHORT the puts. sorry</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348177018618</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:36:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348178862347-94</Id><Topic><Title>Intel announced partnership with Cisco, sees 1 billion per year bump. HUGE!</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348175614950</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These was a Piper opinion about Intel and not announced by Intel. It Intel revenues are $50bil then represents a 2% revenue source and the margins are probably either "in line" or lower than current Intel margins. IF this does become a deal, it will be important to look at the mix of processes that it covers. I suspect that it will soak up some 32nm fab.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348178862347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 18:07:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348183121397-95</Id><Title>Intel to take big stake in SHARP.</Title><Msg>Thoughts?</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348183121397</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348183829974-96</Id><Title>What was the purpose of the warning?</Title><Msg>It seems that the warning was a wrong move on part of the management? The timing was horrible - HP and Dell just had missed earnings and Intel took a big hit. Warren Buffet disclosed that BH sold all of Intel. Analysts came out of the woodwork and downgraded the whole PC sector and then just to confirm the worst fears Intel warned. As a result Intel stock kept going lower in opposite direction from the market. Why did Intel warn? If they didn't the stock might have recovered with the market but now no one wants to touch it with a 6 ft poll. What is the best that can happen now? Intel meets it's lowered guidance? Stock will not recover then - at best will stay flat. On the opposite if Intel misses it's lowered guidance, even by a little bit - it'll be a bloodbath for the exit even from a long term value investors, not just day traders. I've been scratching my head on decision to warn and can't understand it. Anyone?</Msg><Username>bubbagumphere</Username><Timestamp>1348183829974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:30:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348183982889-97</Id><Topic><Title>What was the purpose of the warning?</Title><Username>bubbagumphere</Username><Timestamp>1348183829974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:30:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As a fellow foolish commentator points out, the announcement is classic Intel. The company has a long history of waiting until a few weeks before its earnings announcement – the next one is scheduled for October 16 – and then lowering guidance. When actual earnings results are then reported in line with the original expectations, the company can declare the figures “an earnings beat” and watch shares rise by much more than the lowered guidance cost them. This is a classic game of Wall Street expectation management, and one at which Intel excels</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348183982889</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:33:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348184434066-98</Id><Topic><Title>What was the purpose of the warning?</Title><Username>bubbagumphere</Username><Timestamp>1348183829974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:30:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you believe that meeting lowered guidance will result in shares rise? I don't have such a high expectations. The shares are down over $2.50 since warning. They could've been up by buck or two with the raising market so we could've been up $4 compared to where we are now. How is this "managing expectations" working out for Intel? Do you think it will rise by $4 in case of meeting reduced guidance? - In my opinion it has a bigger chance of going down after earnings then up.</Msg><Username>bubbagumphere</Username><Timestamp>1348184434066</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:40:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348185078324-99</Id><Topic><Title>What was the purpose of the warning?</Title><Username>bubbagumphere</Username><Timestamp>1348183829974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:30:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bubba, Intel LOVES buying shares cheap and could care less about your day to day worrying. You should know that by now.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348185078324</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:51:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348185894080-100</Id><Topic><Title>What was the purpose of the warning?</Title><Username>bubbagumphere</Username><Timestamp>1348183829974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:30:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes they love buying share cheap but unfortunately it doesn't reduce a share float or increase shareholders value as they turn around and grant these shares to employees, leaving shareholders holding the bag. I am long for the last 7 years and barely breaking even on a share price. Yes of course there is dividend but it only reached $0.22 now it was much smaller back then - $0.08. My patience is wearing thin. I want to believe into mobile story and give it another 6-12 month to see how it develops, but at the first sign that Mobile story is breaking down I will take my loss and run for the exit, as I suspect many longs such as myself will do. I gave management more than enough time to increase my shareholder value and missed a lot of other opportunities. That is why I question if management/BOD is really adequate and start asking questions regarding their decisions - namely Warning in a horrible micro climate.</Msg><Username>bubbagumphere</Username><Timestamp>1348185894080</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:04:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348186089327-101</Id><Topic><Title>What was the purpose of the warning?</Title><Username>bubbagumphere</Username><Timestamp>1348183829974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:30:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" the company can declare the figures “an earnings beat” and watch shares rise by much more than the lowered guidance cost them." If the BTE earnings always cause the shares to jump by more than the lowered guidance takes them down, one might reasonably expect the stock to have advanced over the last ten years, no? And yet, the shares have NOT advanced over the last decade. In fact, these shares were north of $70 a little over ten years ago. Got any more of that "foolish" analysis to share with us?</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1348186089327</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:08:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348187065064-102</Id><Title>Oracle's sales miss seems to have some good news for Intel.</Title><Msg>Here's a part of the report regarding Oracle. "The company is pushing sales of its high-end Exadata and Exalytics machines, which use Intel Corp. (INTC) chips. Sales of high- end engineered systems more than doubled, co-President Mark Hurd said in the statement. Sales of servers using Sun’s Sparc chip are waning, though."</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1348187065064</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:24:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348187954496-103</Id><Title>Key ingredient to Intel's ultrabook success.</Title><Msg>First of all, no other tablet maker will do well against iPad with ARM based processors. But the ultrabook can create less of a need for tablets altogether provided that the difference between one with a convertible touch screen tablet capability costs around $200 more than one without. People over time will want the best of all worlds. Apple's apps, Google's apps, and Windows full capabilities. A one time ownership of an Apple smartphone is good enough for enjoyment of Apple's apps for the most part. No real need to upgrade a smartphone. Just use the wifi capabilities until the phone breaks. Second, many should be looking for the vast selection of Android based smartphones to get access to the many perks that Google will provide for daily useage. Finally, an ultrabook with Windows 8 software should rap up the experience of mobility by having a fully functional sleek and lightweight laptop with conversion to a tablet that has the main functions that can be satisfied through only touch capabilities. As Apple said, with over 250,000 total apps available, the average user has about 106 total apps. So Microsoft could easily satisfy most of its customer based with around 10,000 of the most popular apps. Most of Apple's apps seem very childish and hardly ever used. Or used once to try it out and placed in permanent storage if not totally discarded. This will be key for ultrabook's success and I think Intel knows this along with its partners. The most successful tablet maker second to Apple is Samsung. Same company that build tablets for Apple. Yet they still only have 2.4 million quarterly sales. This pales in comparison to the number 5 PC seller, Acer, which sells over 6 million unit in a quarter.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1348187954496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:39:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348188445069-104</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to offer only one process at 20-nm Dylan McGrath</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348118382067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 01:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because they think there's some money to be made in higher resolution chips and investing in ASML improves the chances of the equipment keeping pace with the demand. They could be wrong though. If the cost/wafer doesn't reduce as it has been in the past, they likely wont find many customers at the higher resolution. Intel's taken a risk in lining up so much fab capacity at the higher res nodes. They may get outpriced by lower resolution chips that have good enough performance.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1348188445069</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:47:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348188718193-105</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle's sales miss seems to have some good news for Intel.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1348187065064</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:24:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ain't nobody gonna get rich buy and holding INTC. on the good news front, it outperformed the SMH today, another non buy and hold, down over 14 percent from the May highs, and well below the lofty heights of $45.00 reached on the rise post March of 2003.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1348188718193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:51:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348190387974-106</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle's sales miss seems to have some good news for Intel.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1348187065064</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:24:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Highest performance = High end Intel server chips = high margin for both companies. Oracle Database servers X2-8 (Sun Fire X4800) [4] 8 × Ten-Core Intel Xeon E7-8870 Processors (2.40 GHz) ************************* 2 TB Memory. Disk Controller HBA with 512MB Battery Backed Write Cache. 8 × 300 GB 10,000 RPM SAS Disks 8 × QDR (40Gbit/s) Ports 8 × 10 Gb Ethernet Ports based on the Intel 82599 10GbE Controller 8 × 1 Gb Ethernet Ports 1 × ILOM Ethernet Port 4 × Redundant Hot-Swappable Power Supplies 3 × 36 port QDR (40 Gbit/s) InfiniBand Switches Oracle Exadata Storage Servers X2-2 2 × Six-Core Intel Xeon L5640 (2.26 GHz) Processors ************************* Exadata Smart Flash Cache 384 GB System Memory 24 GB Disk Controller Disk Controller HBA with 512MB Battery Backed Write Cache InfiniBand Connectivity Dual-Port QDR (40Gbit/s) InfiniBand Host Channel Adapter Power Supplies Dual-redundant, hot-swappable power supply Remote Management Sun Embedded Integrated Lights Out Manager (ILOM) Disk Drives 12 × 600 GB 15,000 RPM High Performance SAS or 12 × 3 TB 7,200 RPM High Capacity SAS Integrated Lights Out Manager (ILOM) Ethernet port</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348190387974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 21:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348192347779-107</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle's sales miss seems to have some good news for Intel.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1348187065064</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:24:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ain't nobody gonna get rich buy and holding INTC. ________________ How rich did you get buying Intel at 19.58 and selling it at 19.78 for a paultry 20 cent agains at max capital gains taxes, idiot. Even funnier, yoiu told all Longs at the time that they were idiots for not selling under 20.......right before it went up 50 percent. You were NOWHERE to be found during that entire runup, and that makes you a Grade-A coward for coming back now.</Msg><Username>wdblueball</Username><Timestamp>1348192347779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 21:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348192782493-108</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to offer only one process at 20-nm Dylan McGrath</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348118382067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 01:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They may get outpriced by lower resolution chips that have good enough performance." *** Um, do you know the difference between a processor and a monitor?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348192782493</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 21:59:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348193072095-109</Id><Topic><Title>Key ingredient to Intel's ultrabook success.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1348187954496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:39:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ARM tablet market is definitely going to be affected by the price points of Ultrabooks and laptops. For near the price of a spendy Apple tablet or perhaps even less you can now buy a functional computer in Ultrabook or laptop form. And more form factors are on the way. Why buy such a limited product when you can get so much more value and use?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348193072095</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:04:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348193348620-110</Id><Topic><Title>Key ingredient to Intel's ultrabook success.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1348187954496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:39:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I want to see the commercials for the convertibles rammed down our throat like they are doing right now with the available Ultrabooks. I think the tide will start to turn once they mass market these and people begin to see that they can get EVERYTHING they need all in one purchase. A slender, solid laptop with touchscreen. The next generation will all be carrying them.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1348193348620</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:09:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348193597954-111</Id><Title>Intel Biological chips.........Intel's a 10,000 pound Gorilla about to wake up</Title><Msg>Brave new biometric world: Intel helps diagnose Lupus, arthritis Sylvie Barak 9/20/2012 8:56 PM EDT Intel inside is about to take on a whole new biological meaning, as the worlds of information technology and biomedical science collide. Intel Chief Technology Officer Justin Rattner says the firm’s research and development teams are making breakthroughs using semiconductors to synthesize and study disease-associated proteins. Rattner said people didn’t expect to see Intel in the biomedical field, but described the ongoing research being done alongside Stanford University’s medical center as "very important." A paper on the study has already been published in Nature of Medicine journal. The researchers have been synthesizing short segments of biological proteins, called peptides, on silicon wafers using some of the same methods used in semiconductor manufacturing, including sequential steps of light exposure and photolithography. The chip, dubbed an Intel array by researchers, can analyze thousands of protein interactions simultaneously, allowing it to detect those associated with certain diseases and their variations. This in turn makes it easier for doctors to determine what drugs would be most effective for a particular patient, #$%$ various therapies and for researchers to design ever more-effective drugs. Understanding how proteins interact within the human body is something that has historically taken a lot of time, so this research is something of a breakthrough in terms of getting results in at very high speeds. Diagnosing diseases like Lupus used to be very hard, sometimes taking years, but Rattner said this new system allows doctors to take blood samples and have results back "literally in a matter of minutes." Rattner called the progress a "brave new world by anybody’s measure," noting that it's not just a question of collecting the data and crunching some numbers, but having information technology and biotechnology physically meet. "That’s very exciting," he said. "We’re getting to the point where information technology and biotechnology are getting up close and personal and it just promises great things for healthcare," he added. Another disease that could be more decisively diagnosed and treated using this method is arthritis. With over 30 different types of arthritis, doctors can have a tough time knowing which particular variation a person is suffering from. "Most doctors will never actually know which one a patient has, until we can identify the different types of proteins associated with the different types of arthritis," Rattner explained. The best most patients can currently hope for is to get a prescription for anti-inflammatories, but Rattner said in the near future, physicians would be able to know exactly what type of arthritis they are dealing with, and which specific treatments are needed to treat it. "That’s what this fusion of information technology and biotechnology will give us," he said.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1348193597954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:13:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348193779360-112</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to offer only one process at 20-nm Dylan McGrath</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348118382067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 01:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They may get outpriced by lower resolution chips that have good enough performance. Do you understand the difference between an IDM process and a foundry process and how it relates to Moore's law? Top Five Design and Manufacturing Challenges at 20nm 5. More DFM to the rescue Is Moore’s Law slowing down? “The answer is that it is not for the memory and processor IDMs, but definitely for the foundries,” said G. Dan Hutcheson, president of VLSI Research Inc. “The alarming thing about it is that the ability of foundries to convert their process development and tool investments into revenues has been steadily declining since 130nm. The importance of 130nm is that’s when process and design began to be recoupled. The result was the rise of DFM, which didn’t exist before then.”</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348193779360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348194091522-113</Id><Topic><Title>What was the purpose of the warning?</Title><Username>bubbagumphere</Username><Timestamp>1348183829974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:30:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel did the responsible thing by warning. A lot of companies warned without getting mugged the way that Intel did. Any company that suffers the unrelenting attacks that Wall Street's largest firms and hedge funds mounted on Intel are going to show the effects. A coordinated effort using money, leverage and the media will produce these results. The whole question is whether this type of wholesale manipulation is going to be allowed. Wall Street firms need to earn their money rather than use sleazy tactics to mug small and medium sized investors. Their efforts are at the best extremely unethical and at the worst illegal. The coordinated appearance of these attacks at least suggest the possibility of collusion. Intel investors need to demand an accounting from Wall Street. Why does Wall Street continue to attack one of America's best companies? *** A comment from Fudzilla on Wall Street: "The cocaine nose jobs of Wall Street have been spluttering into their espressos after Texas Instruments announced that it is set to beat their low end estimates. Wall Street had smuggly declared that since TI was operating in a weaker economy it must be suffering from poor orders. However it seems that TI didn't get the memo."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348194091522</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:21:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348194474106-114</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to offer only one process at 20-nm Dylan McGrath</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1348118382067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 01:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I might not understand that difference, but the foundries do. For a long time, chip design companies have been working closely with foundries to ensure their designs get good yields when manufactured. This is nothing new and neither the foundries nor the chip design companies are stupid. Intel's claim that they have an integration advantage is baseless.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1348194474106</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:27:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348194973498-115</Id><Topic><Title>ARM "architecture"..........LMFAO Trash architecture, smoke and mirrors</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348158630120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:30:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmm, doesn't the Atom have no less than eight bridges between the core and the RAM? Umm, yeah, it does. What a piece of Bush.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1348194973498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348196020316-116</Id><Topic><Title>intc is skyrocketing</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348169551076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:32:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>starting</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1348196020316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:53:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>