<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-09"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347164739396-1</Id><Title>Do tablets really mean "the death of the PC"?</Title><Msg>Or will the same things happen to the PC after what happened with the smartphone craze. PC's still grew after many said that the smartphones will create no real need for computer upgrades. So what has the growth of the tablet, or more specifically, the growth of the iPad done to PC sales. Have they cannibalized PC sales. Let's see if this is true. Apple was the first to introduce a tablet with the iPad. Then Samsung along with other and Amazon followed. Apple first sole iPad back in Q3 of 2010. So PC sales did not compete against tablets in Q2 of 2010. At that time, about 83.3 million PC units were sold in Q2. Since then, iPad sales have grown to 16.5 million units in Q2 of 2012, while total tablet sales have grown to 24 million units. Amazon's Kindle fire which seems to be helping their stock hit all time highs, was a mere 1.2 million units. And what has happened to the PC sales? Total PC sales for Q2 of 2012 was 87.4 million units. So PC sales actually grew in Q2, even with it maturity and worldwide slowdown in GDP growth. Specifically, the stall in growth of Europe. So does this mean tablets are cannibalizing PC sales? I guess not since the growth of tablets to 24 million units per quarter should have taken a big chunk of PC quarterly sales. PC sales actually grew by about 4 million units during that period. And the tablet market share for anybody but Apple is pretty sad. Take the so called popular Kindle by Amazon. Number 3 in sales yet only 1.2 million units sold. The last place PC seller Asus sold over 6 million units, or five times Kindle Fire sales. And Kindle sold 1.2 million units at a price that was way below cost. This is what they call tablets cannibalizing PC sales? Oh, by the way, all other vendors besides the top five sold a total of 36.5 million units. So more vendors seem to be successful in PC sales while only Apple seems to be successful in tablet sales.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1347164739396</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 00:25:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347172503770-2</Id><Topic><Title>Do tablets really mean "the death of the PC"?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1347164739396</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 00:25:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are absolutely right, and thanks for a great post. No serious writer, composer, executive, scientist, engineer, student, etc etc is going to replace a PC with a tablet. The physical keyboard/mouse is the optimal user interface and the feature ensemble on PC's, particularly next gen "ultrabooks" will outpace and outgame the tablet. If you need to be in tablet mode an ultrabook offers that option, but also allows you to go back to being a grown-up in PC mode.. If you want to switch op systems to, eg, ubuntu linux, PC's offer that option...tablets?. The massive arsenal of professional software runs on PC's and a tablet would simply not be up to the task (try running and composing a symphony in Sibelius 6 on a tablet; or do Mathematica, or adobe photoshop, on a tablet, etc). Aside from being a novelty the functional flexibility and utility of tablets is so limited that they will frustrate a wave of users who will return in the next cycle to the modern PC. I predict tablets will ultimate rejoin PC's as a "detachable screen" mode. This is the INTC vision of things and I believe it is correct. Regarding the "warning": We are seeing a confluence of effects on the PC market at this moment: (1) Windows 8 is pending, (2) China is slowing; (3) Europe is slow; (4) the AAPL novelty shop is peaking (5) An idiot is seeking the Presidency (6) a hoard of idiots who call themselves analysts are trying to wreck Intel. But remember, INTC is 30% PC's, 25% Servers, 15% Atoms in everything, 30% other. Only the PC part of this is getting rocked temporarily. Fasten your seatbelt and collect your dividend. We'll weather this and be back to the targets beyond $30 in no time. Intel is numero uno and will remain so indefinitely far into the future.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347172503770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 02:35:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347193394724-3</Id><Title>My average cost is now just a tad over 20 thx to the Dividend</Title><Msg>Thx Intel. Love watching all the new aliases pop up......broke daytraders that can't even spell the word "Dividend" let alone have money set aside to earn one............that and losers with no morals and no brain that think they can move a stock lower by bashing it on a dumb mesage board so they can buy low.</Msg><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1347193394724</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 08:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347196053630-4</Id><Topic><Title>Apple goes with TSMC 20nm 2014</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347159548090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Something to think about, all those iPads sold a starting a couple of years ago will be starting to have their batteries die in a year or two. Right now if you bought the original iPad2 it probably isn't holding the charge as long as it used to . The original iPad probably can't hold half it's charge by now. So what? If you have the skills to replace the batteries yourself it's under $50, to send it out to some no name service is $100. Or you can look into a new one. If by the end of 2014 there isn't something exciting like a TSMC 20nm processor in the newest iPad I don't think you'll see many consumers buying new ones nor getting their old ones fixed. Think the PC revolution is dead? Just wait until consumer throw out iPads in bulk. Something you spent over $500 a few years ago is a lot of money to just throw away.</Msg><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1347196053630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 09:07:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347198021269-5</Id><Topic><Title>Do tablets really mean "the death of the PC"?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1347164739396</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 00:25:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two very good posts. The change in the PC format has been a continuum since the 1980s Remember the "luggable" portables from Compaq? My first clamshell notebook weighed over 10 lbs! Changing formats in the name of this game. An A5X chip in a PC back in the 80s or 90s would have seems like a miracle, today it is too slow for any real contect creation. I bought my wife a full boat iPad (1 kilobuck) I tried it just for web surfing. I was so frustrated with it that I damn near "frisbeed" it off the deck. I got head of it on surfing to the point that I didn't know what I was waiting for.....and then it locked up! I think they have a real product with and entry level x86. Maybe more than an Atom. Maybe dual Atoms make a usable machine. I just bought a Macbook Air. I'm not interested in learning window 8. It's a torture learning Apple from PC. I think windows 8 will not provide the pop in PC buys this time. The format (Air, Ultrabook) will be hot once they get on some shelves. Another reason for the Air is that for $99 they transfer my data and I get as many one on one session as I can jam into a year. Windows needs to do something like this. For all the years I used a PC I felt like I was playing a video game without knowing the rules:) Tablets are toys until they get the performance up a few notches. I'm still holding onto the hope that Wed will bring a huge Apple/Intel announcement. I still can't see where Ottelini is scheduled for any appearance at the Developers Forum...Very strange.</Msg><Username>semiwiz2002</Username><Timestamp>1347198021269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 09:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347198614710-6</Id><Topic><Title>Apple goes with TSMC 20nm 2014</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347159548090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The post was for those that predicted Apple will be using INtel fabs... Maybe someday, but NOT till after the Paul Otellini era...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347198614710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 09:50:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347201488014-7</Id><Title>Dead Money Walking: Sell PC Players And Buy Apple Before It's Too Late at Seeking Alpha 08:36am EDT</Title><Msg>See today's Yahoo News for Intel</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347201488014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 10:38:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>29</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347201791092-8</Id><Topic><Title>Dead Money Walking: Sell PC Players And Buy Apple Before It's Too Late at Seeking Alpha 08:36am EDT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347201488014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 10:38:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That articles for guys like you who like to buy High (Cisco at 20 before it went to 13) and sell low (Intel at 20 before it went to 29). BTW, how's that 2 year disaster workin out for ya?</Msg><Username>lucyboycots_chickfillet</Username><Timestamp>1347201791092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 10:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347202097938-9</Id><Topic><Title>Dead Money Walking: Sell PC Players And Buy Apple Before It's Too Late at Seeking Alpha 08:36am EDT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347201488014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 10:38:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like Cramer's sister in law wrote that Article: "On 21 August the author suggested INTC a security to buy and hold forever. Very inconsistent with the current message two weeks later."</Msg><Username>lucyboycots_chickfillet</Username><Timestamp>1347202097938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 10:48:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347202503592-10</Id><Title>The "Big Q" has His Aliases Working Hard This Morning!</Title><Msg>Wallweeeeeeeenie: I'd like to see NO LESS than 50 thumbs down ratings for my "Dead Money" post. TOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347202503592</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 10:55:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>28</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347206228044-11</Id><Topic><Title>I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1293550442000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-12-28 10:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol....</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1347206228044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 11:57:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347206529123-12</Id><Topic><Title>Dead Money Walking: Sell PC Players And Buy Apple Before It's Too Late at Seeking Alpha 08:36am EDT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347201488014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 10:38:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol.... "On 21 August the author suggested INTC a security to buy and hold forever. Very inconsistent with the current message two weeks later."</Msg><Username>tooofunnny_suxwang</Username><Timestamp>1347206529123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:02:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347206943419-13</Id><Topic><Title>Dead Money Walking: Sell PC Players And Buy Apple Before It's Too Late at Seeking Alpha 08:36am EDT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347201488014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 10:38:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>current two weeks later ----------- Good one, WallDUH!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1347206943419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>41</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347209413152-14</Id><Title>Rombo Romney down 4% in Latest Raspukin(Rasmussen) Poll.</Title><Msg>Ras old boy had Romney up by 2 or 3 percent just a week ago. Guess the Clinton speech really ripped into Romney hard. Oh yeah--given that the rightwing trash have said the following Obummer was born in AfriKA Obam hates America He is European in his thinking He of course, says Trump, is not a citizen He is a communist Ob Will raise your taxes given these--it is entirely unlikely that any sheeeit the idiots on the right say now will help Romney to come back from this train-wreck. Of course--You rightwing nummmnuts are ready to shiiet yourselves but that morning after OB gets re-elected, you will be crying like little PUSHYYYYS. I want my country back. Why do they let women vote? My wife is a stupid ccccuuuunt for voting for OB and now she will not even screw me. No wonder Rush looks so dickessl. When you are a rightwing teabagging patriot like us, you never get any of the love juices from the ladies. Obummer</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1347209413152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:50:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347210681029-15</Id><Topic><Title>Even the Raspukken poll show Obummer up now by 2%</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1347134371254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today, Sunday, the Rasmussen poll has OB up 4% too.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1347210681029</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:11:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347211025287-16</Id><Title>There's a Reason</Title><Msg>There's a reason why Intel announced the reduction in the revenue estimate prior to the start of IDF on Tuesday and the imminent smartphone announcements. Just like with the last revenue warning, Intel is a master of managing the impact. This timing is designed to do the same thing. We've had the bad news, now we get the good news. And so the move back up begins. Not to mention the jobs numbers will likely generate more stimulus efforts when the Fed meets this week. And Windows 8 coming up in October which is a primary factor in the Q3 weakness as people are waiting to buy. In the meantime Wall Street's biggest firms will continue to do everything they can to prevent economic recovery as they have bet big on doom and gloom and literally can't afford to be wrong. They will continue their efforts to keep Intel's P/E ratio in the grossly under-valued range. Why do Wall Street's biggest firms constantly attack one of America's best companies? Let's get some answers. Send the letters...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347211025287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:17:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347211458170-17</Id><Topic><Title>There's a Reason</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347211025287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:17:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love ya, Wallis, but forget the letters. They're pointless. Like a letter to Grover Norquist to raise taxes.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347211458170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:24:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347211650351-18</Id><Title>Apple made the ipad to be a reader, (plus) to compete with amazon who made their reader first and apple played catch up to amazon</Title><Msg>They never made it to replace their real computers. they have never said that. The only people who say that are stupid analysts. It was made as a high end reader plus apps period! PC is here to stay the size of the screen alone is unproductive period! Compute Power is unproductive period! People who do real work on thier computers, laptops or desktops know what I mean, The rest of you go play with your $400.00 phones with $100.00 a month plans and $600.00 ipads. Really , their not for productivty work period!</Msg><Username>fmsg35</Username><Timestamp>1347211650351</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347211776779-19</Id><Title>Here's How Much</Title><Msg>Here's how much Wall Street has included in Intel's stock price for Lava, Orange, Motorola, Lenovo, MegaFon, ZTE and Karbonn smartphone business: Zero And here's how much Wall Street has included in Intel's stock price for the improvements in tablet sales will result from the same technology: Zero</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347211776779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347212220445-20</Id><Topic><Title>There's a Reason</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347211025287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:17:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not so. We must try out case in the halls of public opinion. All methods of getting the message out must be utilized. Big Wall Street firms are like cockroaches. They flee the light. The last thing they want is scrutiny of their unethical and perhaps illegal behavior. Send the letters. Copy the SEC. Follow them up with e-mails. Tell your friends and business associates not to do business with them. Send editorials to the WSJ, Fortune and Forbes saying this will not stand and Intel investors and shareholders have had enough. We demand to know why Wall Street's biggest firms continue to mount unwarranted attacks on one of America's best companies. Or you can sit back and do nothing. Your call...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347212220445</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:37:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347212808927-21</Id><Topic><Title>Apple goes with TSMC 20nm 2014</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347159548090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the usual fanboi distortion. Here's what was actually said: " (TSMC) is expected to get processor orders from Apple in 2014, after the company enters 20-nanometer manufacturing, predicted institutional investor UBS yesterday." The fanboi clearly has translated "is EXPECTED to get" into "has gotten" and clearly doesn't understand what the word "PREDICTED" means. But all that aside, this is great news for Intel. Apple not getting state-of-the-art technology until 2014!!! Wow, that's terrific news. Intel is going to own mobility by 2014. So if Apple doesn't upgrade until then and then only gets pathetic 20nm that gives Intel a huge competitive advantage. And that's if TSCM pulls it off by 2014, which is unlikely. Maybe 2015. Maybe later. After all, they are still struggling to master 28nm. If Apple wants to wait that long to move into 2nd rate technology, that's fine by me. Game over...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347212808927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347213287704-22</Id><Topic><Title>Apple made the ipad to be a reader, (plus) to compete with amazon who made their reader first and apple played catch up to amazon</Title><Username>fmsg35</Username><Timestamp>1347211650351</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:27:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well said. And the kindle is better as a reader..actually the early versions with the papyrus look and adjustable font. Cheap, great readers.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347213287704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347213472921-23</Id><Title>Romney Reverses Field on ObamaCare</Title><Msg>"Romney, who promised early in his campaign to repeal Obama's health overhaul, told NBC's "Meet the Press" that he would keep several important parts of the law." Now that's funny. First we're told it will end life as we know it and now we're told it has important and effective parts...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347213472921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:57:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347214059353-24</Id><Title>The death of the PC</Title><Msg>This assumption goes around every so often when there is a slower demand for PC's and hence chips. (and it never actually happens). Everything eventually rights itself. Businesses and people at home sitting at their desks aren't going to use their smartphones and tablets to do any serious computer work. Could probably find articles 3 to 5 years ago that have this same assumption in their headlines.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1347214059353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 14:07:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347214763645-25</Id><Title>INTC TESTS 23 TOMORROW</Title><Msg>Even though a huge honking $6 miss is already priced in and Intel is good fo 30. So what the heck is going on in here? Could WallDUH have been wrong??? Responsible replies only, PLEASE.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1347214763645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 14:19:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>43</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347215060752-26</Id><Title>NEXT BOARD MEETING</Title><Msg>Does anyone know date of next INTC BOD meeting? Thanks in advance.</Msg><Username>ronkaren69</Username><Timestamp>1347215060752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 14:24:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347215676212-27</Id><Topic><Title>Here's How Much</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347211776779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stock always falls during a hot summer and early in the fall. We'll be fine. New 10 year Highs next Spring.</Msg><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1347215676212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 14:34:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347216255710-28</Id><Topic><Title>Here's How Much</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347211776779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We'll be fine. New 10 year Highs next Spring. -------- So you're saying that if we buy now we'll be fine in 6 months? I hope you don't mind that I bookmarked your message, pumpwad.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1347216255710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 14:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>48</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347217225501-29</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Reverses Field on ObamaCare</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347213472921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:57:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We know who you wan to win. Tell it to your refrigerator over and over and spare the rest of us.</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1347217225501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:00:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347217430326-30</Id><Title>Intel one of the most undervalued oversold stocks out there</Title><Msg>but not for long</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1347217430326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:03:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347217628422-31</Id><Topic><Title>Intel one of the most undervalued oversold stocks out there</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1347217430326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:03:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SING IT, SISTER! TOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347217628422</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:07:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>25</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347217792151-32</Id><Title>You might be a lucy if...</Title><Msg>1.) If you dream of US economic devastation, then you might be a lucy. 2.) If you have a loose connection to your brain that causes you to hit individual keys repeatedly, then you might be a lucy. 3.) If you don't predict anything until after it happens, then you might be a lucy. 4.) If you are a pawn of the biggest firms on Wall Street, then you might be a lucy. 5.) If you have spent a lot of time in the fetal position on Intel's moves up, then you might be a lucy. 6.) If you don't know enough to discuss technology or fabrication, then you might be a lucy. 7.) If you are unable to hold down a real job, then you might be a lucy. 8.) If you got fired from Intel, or someone from Intel ran over your dog, then you might be a lucy. 9.) If you are a parasite on the US economy, then you might be a lucy. 10.) If you have more user IDs than brain cells, then you might be a lucy. 11.) If you have no life other than commenting on every down tick of the Intel stock price, then you are a lucy.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347217792151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:09:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347217908091-33</Id><Topic><Title>Intel one of the most undervalued oversold stocks out there</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1347217430326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:03:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Recommend getting out temp. if INTC gets to $25.25 or higher before FOMC announcement on Thurs. Buy back after another big dip then hold until just before div in Nov. Thank me later.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1347217908091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:11:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347218338033-34</Id><Topic><Title>You might be a lucy if...</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347217792151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:09:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You might be Wallis if: 1) If you post 24 x 7 x 365 on a public message board. 2) If you you NEVER SELL because you think that stocks only go up. 3) If you wear fishnet stockings and black patent leather stiletto-heeled pumps.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347218338033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>25</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347218526950-35</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Reverses Field on ObamaCare</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347213472921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:57:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since you have a hatred of rich people, you wouldn't like me, I could buy and sell you like a bag of dogfood.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1347218526950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:22:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347218836208-36</Id><Topic><Title>NEXT BOARD MEETING</Title><Username>ronkaren69</Username><Timestamp>1347215060752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 14:24:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IMO, "today". I have not found any public information that describes their meeting dates or information about what they discussed. The only "clue" that I could even point to would be the "dividend declaration date". That is the the DAY that Intel announces the dividend approved by the BOD and so it should be right after the BOD meets. There seems to be a historical trend for mid-September, similar to the SF IDF. I would guess that the BOD meets shortly before the San Francisco IDF to get an update on status, approve what is going to happen and what announcements to make. The historical dates taken from the NASDAQ dividend history page for Intel shows the Q3 dividend dates: 9/21/2011 9/23/2010 8/1/2009 10/27/2008 9/29/2007 9/12/2006 Historical dates of SF IDF from Wikipedia: San Francisco IDF 9/13/2011 9/13/2010 9/22/2009 8/19/2008 9/18/2007</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347218836208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:27:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347219725658-37</Id><Topic><Title>You might be a lucy if...</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347217792151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:09:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You might be Wallis if: 1) If you read and respond to Lucy's messages but say that you have Lucy on IGNORE. 2) If you claim to have only one alias.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1347219725658</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>47</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347220670330-38</Id><Title>WSJ- Intel's Emerging Problem with Chip Sales</Title><Msg>Intel's Emerging Problem with Chip Sales at The Wall Street Journal 03:49pm EDT</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1347220670330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:57:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>50</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347220851625-39</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ- Intel's Emerging Problem with Chip Sales</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1347220670330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:57:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lifted from the WSJ report- "Emerging markets aren't bailing out Intel anymore. Expect the stock to stagnate as a result."</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1347220851625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:00:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>55</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347222187798-40</Id><Title>Intel board completely ruined by 2 60+ year old dweebs</Title><Msg>One a psycho optimist, one a psycho pessimists. Both complete tools....Both Liberals. Par.</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1347222187798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347222201650-41</Id><Topic><Title>Here's How Much</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347211776779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well said Wally</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1347222201650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:23:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347222859683-42</Id><Title>WSJ trashes INTC, stagnet for 10 years</Title><Msg>INTC is dead money for years. I am so happy I dumped this POS last week. Sorry for the rest of you bagholders who didn't dump. INTC will be teenager next week. I'd probably buy some if it gets below $15 again.</Msg><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1347222859683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:34:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347223050042-43</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ trashes INTC, stagnet for 10 years</Title><Username>marcopubio</Username><Timestamp>1347222859683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:34:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny how you and NYK2OH show up at exactly the same time, after months away......remember when you two cried like little girls because you shorted Intel twice on the way to 29 and lost? you're the same guy, and you're a complete loser.</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1347223050042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:37:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347223191235-44</Id><Title>Romney says he would keep parts of Obama healthcare law HAA HAA</Title><Msg>Romney says he would keep parts of Obama healthcare law WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney, who has called for scrapping President Barack Obama's 2010 U.S. healthcare law, said in remarks aired on Sunday that he likes key parts of "Obamacare" despite his party's loathing of it and wants to retain them. Romney, who faces Obama in the November 6 election, has vowed throughout the campaign to repeal and replace the Obama healthcare law. But asked about the Obama healthcare law on NBC's "Meet the Press" program, Romney said, "Well, I'm not getting rid of all of healthcare reform." "Of course, there are a number of things that I like in healthcare reform that I'm going to put in place," Romney added. "One is to make sure that those with pre-existing conditions can get coverage. Two is to assure that the marketplace allows for individuals to have policies that cover their family up to whatever age they might like." Funny but I was sure he said he would repeal all of it? Yeah and you rightwing teabagging nimrods voted for him because he said as much in the primaries. But now he says he will not repeal all of it. HAAAA HAAAA I think Romney has SCREWED you Rush dumbaugh loistenning teabagging losers.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1347223191235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:39:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347223381203-45</Id><Topic><Title>Romney says he would keep parts of Obama healthcare law HAA HAA</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1347223191235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:39:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course he would keep Obamacare. He wrote it.</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1347223381203</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:43:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347223436265-46</Id><Topic><Title>Romney says he would keep parts of Obama healthcare law HAA HAA</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1347223191235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:39:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What happened to "I'll repeal ObamaCare on day 1!"?</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1347223436265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:43:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347223573022-47</Id><Topic><Title>Romney says he would keep parts of Obama healthcare law HAA HAA</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1347223191235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:39:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe the latest polls from both Gallop and Rasmussen showing him down 4% happened.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1347223573022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:46:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347223632046-48</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Reverses Field on ObamaCare</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347213472921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:57:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't hate anyone, bro. I just think the rich should take some of all that money that they use to buy and sell people like bags of dog food and pay their fair share. Should Romney be able to deduct watermelon for his horse or deduct his horse? I think not. Pay your way, bro. It's the right thing to do. Dodging taxes isn't. But you're right, I prolly wouldn't like you even if you were poor. People who talk about buying and selling other people are jerks...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347223632046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:47:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347224222200-49</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Reverses Field on ObamaCare</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347213472921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:57:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And being rich has made you so so happy.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1347224222200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347224678892-50</Id><Topic><Title>Intel board completely ruined by 2 60+ year old dweebs</Title><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1347222187798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll wait for the hothead-pothead, jobless, burdon-on-society, loser, known as herbal dooooooooosh to weigh-in on this one.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1347224678892</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 17:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>53</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347225461861-51</Id><Topic><Title>Romney says he would keep parts of Obama healthcare law HAA HAA</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1347223191235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:39:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's the man.......he has supporters like you that post on a message board and then respond to said post with two different aliases. Make no mistake about it: Liberals are misfits, freaks and lazy losers.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1347225461861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 17:17:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347225744648-52</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Reverses Field on ObamaCare</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347213472921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:57:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm happy. Besides, if money doesn't buy happiness, one can always rent some. Lastly, couldn't find "prolly" in the dictionary.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1347225744648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 17:22:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347228399589-53</Id><Topic><Title>The death of the PC</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1347214059353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 14:07:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right. If the PC was truly dying then Intel is investing over 10B to make fabs for products that people don't want anymore? I don't see the logic.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1347228399589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 18:06:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347228739888-54</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Reverses Field on ObamaCare</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347213472921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:57:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I just think the rich should take some of all that money that they use to buy and sell people like bags of dog food and pay their fair share" --------------------------------------------------------------- what is 'fair share' exactly ?? if they pay 40% is fair 50%? 70%? some would say that even 35% is more than enough, way punish success ? in addition most of the taxes are alreay paid by the rich while many american's don't pay at all, IS THAT FAIR ?? what's my motivation to work hard and be creative and take risks, i might as well just seat home and pay no taxes and enjoy cheap housing and free healthcare. Sounds good to me. lol</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1347228739888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 18:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347230090232-55</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Reverses Field on ObamaCare</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347213472921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:57:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"what is 'fair share' exactly ?? if they pay 40% is fair 50%? 70%? some would say that even 35% is more than enough, way punish success ?" *** Don't make me laugh. Mitt Romney is filthy rich and he pays thirteen percent. The rich aren't paying any of those numbers you presented. Billionaires pay less than their secretaries. But here is the rub. If the rich don't pay then the middle class has to. The middle class has been shrinking for the last 30 years because of the success of Republican administrations in making the rich richer. If the middle class goes then the country goes. And the rich along with it. The rich are so greedy that they would kill the goose that lays the golden eggs. Times are tough and still the rich push their responsibility down onto the middle class. I truly believe that if the tax rate for the rich were zero that the rich would say they need to be paid because they are such a wonderful benefit to American society. They're not. Pay your share and stop reducing the size of the middle class before you destroy the entire country...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347230090232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 18:34:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347231027330-56</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Reverses Field on ObamaCare</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347213472921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:57:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I'm happy. Besides, if money doesn't buy happiness, one can always rent some. Lastly, couldn't find "prolly" in the dictionary." *** You need a dictionary to figure out what "prolly" means??? It just goes to show you that there really isn't any correlation between intelligence and wealth. How did you make your money, Gump?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347231027330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 18:50:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347231780877-57</Id><Title>Intel's developer forum - what to expect</Title><Msg>From EETimes: If you think the biggest event of next week is the Apple press conference, you’re clearly not a chip-head. For those of us deeply embedded and ensconced in the world of semiconductor hardware, Intel’s yearly developer forum (IDF) held in San Francisco’s Moscone center is still a yearly highlight and this year won’t disappoint. We’ve been told that this year’s x(86)travaganza will revolve mainly around three topics; perceptual computing (or natural user interface), touch and convertible, and of course all the news around Intel’s low power 4th generation core processors, which are said to be doing better than expected. All in all, not a bad line-up. Let’s take a look at each in slightly greater detail.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347231780877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:03:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347231890769-58</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's developer forum - what to expect</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347231780877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:03:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At the Consumer Electronics Show (CES) in Las Vegas back in January, Intel already set the scene for its future perceptual aspirations with talk of voice recognition integration, but touch is the next big thing coming to Ultrabooks with Windows 8. Even touch, however, is just the beginning, with Intel making big bets on a not-too-distant future where embedded cameras and sensors (amongst other things) will recognize hand gestures, faces, and enable better voice processing, while allowing users to control their screens in more interactive, personalized ways. At IDF, Intel will apparently be showcasing several initiatives which will help enable hardware and software developers to drive perceptual computing aggressively into Intel platforms starting this year. If this is what peaks your interest, we’re told executive vice president and general manager of Intel’s mobility group, David (Dadi) Perlmutter, will be discussing it at greater length during his keynote on Tuesday September 11.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347231890769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347231964238-59</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's developer forum - what to expect</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347231780877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:03:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Touch and convertible to the PC Touch is coming to the ultrabook in a very big way, and Intel is betting that people will fall in love with it. The firm says that overwhelmingly its research has shown that when people were given an ultrabook with touch, they automatically used the feature in 80 percent of their applications, even claiming to feel a better emotional connection to their device. Microsoft Windows 8, of course, is specifically designed with touch in mind, and OEMs are refreshing their systems with touch capabilities in time for this coming holiday season. Intel will be touting 40 touch-enabled ultrabook design wins in the pipeline, which insiders say consumers should expect to see before this year’s end.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347231964238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:06:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347232060208-60</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's developer forum - what to expect</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347231780877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:03:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Convertibles and 4th generation cores For those who like a bit of a blend, melding ultrabook laptops with tablets, Intel believes its new convertible designs have the potential to bring the best of both worlds together in one platforms. We’re told there will be a number of new designs coming out -- some recently released last week at IFA in Berlin and many to be found onsite at IDF. The new convertibles are showing up in all shapes, sizes and SKUs, differentiating themselves with a plethora of sliders, swivels, flip screens, dual screens and more. Indeed, the focus for this holiday season appears to be strongly based around personalization, with a lot of choices depending on personal preference. Intel has a number of ultrabook systems in convertible designs on the way from OEMs including Asus, Dell, Lenovo, Panasonic, Sony and Toshiba, which will all be on display at IDF. On the tablet front, Intel has over 20 design wins from leading OEMs based on its next generation Atom SoC (Clover Trail), with a number of them in convertible designs. Sources say this is just the first step for convertibles, as Intel pushes towards its next generation Intel Core processor family, and arguably the most exciting news of the show.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347232060208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:07:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347232143174-61</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's developer forum - what to expect</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347231780877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:03:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4th generation Intel Core processor family Last year Intel set out to reinvigorate the industry around ultrabooks and said it would cut the mainstream mobile processor design power in half to enable this new category of laptops. The firm intercepted a product cycle half way through in 3rd generation Intel Core to bring power down from 35 watts to 17 watts, resulting in thinner, more innovative computing devices, represented by the touch and convertible designs available already today. Intel is purportedly pleased with these initial systems, and is getting ready to ramp things up another notch. Initially the firm had said its 4th generation Intel Core processor SoC (due out in 2013) would be the first chip built from the ground up with the ultrabook in mind. Now, the firm is saying that it’s going even better than originally expected. Indeed, things are going so well on the technical side that the firm is even said to be making more changes in its flagship core roadmap, starting with the 4th gen core in 2013, to help OEMs make even thinner and lighter designs. Specifically, we’re told, Intel will be introducing a new line of low power chips targeted to operate at around 10 watts initially, while offering other 4th Gen Core processor benefits like high performance, low idle power, single-chip packaging, and new graphics and security capabilities. Intel is said to be “really excited” about the possibilities this will open up for more innovation in the PC. And let’s face it, in an increasingly mobile world, the PC sorely needs a facelift. If IDF delivers, and I believe it will, it should be a great show this year.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347232143174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347232425589-62</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Reverses Field on ObamaCare</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347213472921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:57:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mystk7, that's why businesses aren't hiring. Why bust your butt to pay what some jackasses call "fair share"? Obama has no idea how to run a business or what a business owner goes thru to run his business.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1347232425589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:13:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347233108757-63</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Reverses Field on ObamaCare</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347213472921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:57:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally, Im far from being rich but i tend to understand how business people work and it's not like what you imagine, aka "fair". Who decides what's far and how much ?? you ? Obama ? who and by what criteria? in addition if you are talking about passive income from investment or dividends, do you think that if rich guy loses on investment that government will give him or participate in that loss? they are paid for taking risk same with business risk. BTW, rich people can shelter their money outside use and there is nothing you can do about it.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1347233108757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:25:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347233133818-64</Id><Topic><Title>The lower Intel goes, the higher the dividend paid</Title><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1347128801748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:26:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so busy they are working 6 shifts overtime? so busy working they announced an earnings shortfall for the 2nd time in 4 quarters.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1347233133818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:25:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347233199526-65</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Reverses Field on ObamaCare</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347213472921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:57:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Money is first for most people like Romney even if they talk about god a lot!</Msg><Username>batmantran</Username><Timestamp>1347233199526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:26:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347233476513-66</Id><Topic><Title>Read on internet somewhere- rumor</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1347080704101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 01:05:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Analyst : joe battipaglia, huh? maybe i don't understand this part. Joe R.I.P.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1347233476513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:31:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347233561430-67</Id><Topic><Title>I will explain how Intel failed and how they will never recover.</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347070091151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 22:08:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD, LOL!!!!</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1347233561430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347233656739-68</Id><Topic><Title>The republicans have a plan to fix the economy.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1347065410192</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 20:50:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Solyndra will lsave the country. more gov't jobs, more debt, now that's a great plan.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1347233656739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:34:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347235882001-69</Id><Title>AS LONG AS OBAMA IS PRESIDENT ALL COMPANIES WILL SUFFER.</Title><Msg>Obama is againts all companies. The companies cannot grow. The companies don't hire. We have to get rid of obama. That is very simply. Vote obama out in november. Anybody would be better.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347235882001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 20:11:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347237628116-70</Id><Topic><Title>AS LONG AS OBAMA IS PRESIDENT ALL COMPANIES WILL SUFFER.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347235882001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 20:11:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obama is againts all companies. The companies cannot grow. The companies don't hire. We have to get rid of obama. That is very simply. Vote obama out in november. Anybody would be better." *** Funny the head of Costco said just the opposite. Do you have more business experience than he does?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347237628116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 20:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347237831493-71</Id><Topic><Title>AS LONG AS OBAMA IS PRESIDENT ALL COMPANIES WILL SUFFER.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347235882001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 20:11:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah but Obama gets the "idiot" vote and this country has so many of them that he'll get re-elected. For instance, Wallisweaver spends day and night on this board pumping Intel AND Obama. Have you ever seen anything dumber? His logic is that QE3 will lift Intel to the stars.......4 more years of Obama and Intel will be under 10/share. it's just unreal how dumb Liberals are. Mind-boggling.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1347237831493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 20:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347237993476-72</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P500 next 1214:Morgan Stanley</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1347236143791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 20:15:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>buffet_graham_Fudd posts doom and gloom on multiple message boards as his doom and gloom masters order him. "Take the markets down" command the big Wall Street firms. The US economy must be destroyed. We have predicted it. Make it so...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347237993476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 20:46:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347238651914-73</Id><Title>What's Fair</Title><Msg>The question of what is fair is pretty easy. What's fair is a distribution of taxation that allows the middle class to grow. We haven't had that in 30 years. So the middle class is getting rubbed out. You damage the middle class beyond a certain point and the US economy will collapse. We are nearing that point and still the rich just can't get enough tax cuts. Just because you want a tax cut doesn't mean it's fair. How do we know the tax rate is already fair to the rich? Because they keep getting richer and every day own more and more of the wealth in America. The rich are not suffering. But the middle class sure is. Go ahead. Destroy the middle class. And the rich will go down with it...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347238651914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 20:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347238781770-74</Id><Title>Flashcrash</Title><Msg>Flashcrash: Just another lucy ID...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347238781770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 20:59:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347238869354-75</Id><Title>U know, why WB sold out INTC...insider info?</Title><Msg>why he would sell before warning.</Msg><Username>shares245</Username><Timestamp>1347238869354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 21:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347239549906-76</Id><Topic><Title>AS LONG AS OBAMA IS PRESIDENT ALL COMPANIES WILL SUFFER.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347235882001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 20:11:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Yeah but Obama gets the "idiot" vote and this country has so many of them that he'll get re-elected. For instance, Wallisweaver spends day and night on this board pumping Intel AND Obama. Have you ever seen anything dumber? His logic is that QE3 will lift Intel to the stars.......4 more years of Obama and Intel will be under 10/share. it's just unreal how dumb Liberals are. Mind-boggling." *** Yeah, I'm sure you're right. Let's check and see how the stock market did under the previous administration. The ones that used tax cuts and deregulation to lift the economy and the market up. Oh, pretty good. The market only lost half its value under Bush. I bet Romney could duplicate that performance. After all, he's planning on using the exact same approach...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347239549906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 21:12:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347239901487-77</Id><Title>Jobs rut tips scales in favor of Fed stimulus</Title><Msg>From Reuters: The Federal Reserve looks set to launch a third round of bond purchases this week to try to drive borrowing costs lower and breathe more life into an economy that is not growing fast enough to lower unemployment. Despite political opposition and some internal dissent, economists said a weak report on jobs growth for August was likely enough to convince the U.S. central bank a looser monetary policy was needed. "The Federal Reserve will ease again," said Sung Won Sohn, an economics professor at California State University Channel Islands in Camarillo, California. "There are too many people without jobs and the unemployment rate is too high at this stage of an economic recovery." [IDF and more stimulus. Prolly not enough to get Wall Street largest firms to put their "Bash Intel" campaign on hold. Write the letters...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347239901487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 21:18:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347240229836-78</Id><Title>Dissapointed to see Wally posting meaningless non-Intel stuff.......Here's a Q and A with Otellini</Title><Msg>Intel's Otellini: 'I don't think there is a tablet or phone-centric world' On the eve of his developer's conference, Intel's CEO explains why traditional computers are king, and cautions 'the ARM guys have to live under the same laws of physics that we do.' By Tom Spring, PCWorld Sep 9, 2012 8:00 pm</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347240229836</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 21:23:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347240527404-79</Id><Topic><Title>Jobs rut tips scales in favor of Fed stimulus</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347239901487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 21:18:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All those middle class people you talk about would find jobs if he had a President that didn't terrify every business owner in the country. Even Paul O. blasted Obama! You just don't get it.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347240527404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 21:28:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347241138845-80</Id><Topic><Title>AS LONG AS OBAMA IS PRESIDENT ALL COMPANIES WILL SUFFER.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347235882001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 20:11:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And from what country are you posting your nearly incomprehensible giberish?</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1347241138845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 21:38:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347241582521-81</Id><Topic><Title>I will explain how Intel failed and how they will never recover.</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347070091151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 22:08:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ummm, you completely missed the point. Maybe that's why AAPL has kicked you to the shoulder of the information superhighway? Embarrassed you? Made fools of you? INTC alienate vendors and so-called partners for years. While they strung them along, they were planning to kill them off. And it worked, they went to work for AAPL and others who actually had a vision. How ironic that you are telling Vinnie about life. Vinnie predicted the demise of the great borg ten years ago and guess what ... Vinnie was right. While AAPL stock went up 30x, INTC flounders in the 20's as an also ran, a commodity producing fab factory with a sketchy roadmap.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347241582521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 21:46:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347242163619-82</Id><Topic><Title>AS LONG AS OBAMA IS PRESIDENT ALL COMPANIES WILL SUFFER.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347235882001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 20:11:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok, got it. Wallisweaver knows more about what's good for businesses than Paul Otelini. With that pedigree, I'm amazed that you are a 61 year old message board addict instead of a 1 percenter?</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1347242163619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 21:56:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347243426172-83</Id><Topic><Title>AS LONG AS OBAMA IS PRESIDENT ALL COMPANIES WILL SUFFER.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347235882001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 20:11:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am currently buried with work Seven contracts lined up, turning smaller jobs away. Under Bush, I almost had to close. The entire world was in a freefall when that dummy and the heart attack king were screwing up the entire planet. So bad, he wasn't even invited to the RNC. Ditto for heart attack and the pit bull with lipstick. All failures. Nobody wants to be associated with them. They are poison.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347243426172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 22:17:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347244485492-84</Id><Topic><Title>I will explain how Intel failed and how they will never recover.</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347070091151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 22:08:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vinnie youre a sad little F*** who thinks he knows a lot but you have no clue and nooo patience. do some research and stop going around spamming message boards preaching your crappy beliefs. Another thing INTEL DOES NOT ONLY MAKE COMPUTERS...THEY MAKE COMPUTER CHIPS and the HARDWARE FOR THEM AS WELL UNLIKE MANY OTHER TECH COMPANIES. This gives them some diversification which will always be needed for any company producing computers. There will always be a need for such products so im sorry to say to you that INTEL WILL BE HERE FOR AWHILE. Next, R and D is #$%$ incredibly important for companies like intel....technology doubles every 6-7 #$%$ years and they have to stay on top of their #$%$ and ahead OR AT LEAST WITH THEIR COMPETITION...even if it mean copying them a little. Furthermore Intel has only experienced weaker sale for their computer because of the increase demand for TABLETS...WHICH THEY DONT MAKE. SO once again and on behalf of everyone on this board #$%$ off and learn how to make rational comments instead of coming in and blasting a company that has been around for sometime and has managed to maintain a significant portion of its market while also keeping up with the rise of new competitors.</Msg><Username>kgavru01</Username><Timestamp>1347244485492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 22:34:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347244735882-85</Id><Topic><Title>I will explain how Intel failed and how they will never recover.</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347070091151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 22:08:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and another thing...Intel has just contacted to meet with "tablet experts" which might indicate future plans to enter the tablet market.......you dingleberry</Msg><Username>kgavru01</Username><Timestamp>1347244735882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 22:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347246264062-86</Id><Topic><Title>Dissapointed to see Wally posting meaningless non-Intel stuff.......Here's a Q and A with Otellini</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347240229836</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 21:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets face it...Paul O. has been a total bust. he was 2 years late to mobile &amp; he bet the farm on ultrabooks without a software platform to take advantage of it. Need new blood or else INTC will drift back to $20.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1347246264062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 23:04:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>