<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-18"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347941460843-1</Id><Topic><Title>Analysts seem to be controlling stock prices.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1347850060598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 22:47:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just wanted to add a little more accuracy to the comparison of guiding lower than expected by Apple and Intel. Apple's guidance was actually for $7.65 EPS, which is a bigger difference than what Intel guided down. Apple's guidance was 26% lower than expectations by analysts on average between 60 to 90 days ago when the stock traded near $570. So relatively speaking, both Intel and Apple gave the same dissapointing guidance compared to analysts' expectations. Yet Apple has so far risen about 23% while Intel stock has dropped about 14%. In the meantime, while people's nipples are getting hard for the iPhone 5, I will be waiting for the first American version of an Intel smartphone. I'm guessing it will be a Motorola.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1347941460843</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347941666249-2</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola Mobility to announce first Intel-based device 5am ET</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347940781714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 23:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel replacing ARM chips. Gonna be hard for the fanbois to spin this one...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347941666249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:14:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347942142206-3</Id><Title>Dell already making ultrabooks very affordable.</Title><Msg>They start at $599 at Dell website. Nice sleek look for only $599 with i3 processors that runs circles around a tablet. Another note worth repeating, an iPad is not a computing device. It's simply an entertainment device. A PC or laptop or ultrabook can be an entertainment device as well while tablets can hardly be productive. The ultrabook will soon provide a tablet form factor as well. The need to buy a seperate tablet device could be unnecessary in the next year or so. Only those that do not want to do any computing whatsoever or be productive at all may choose a cheap tablet over a PC or ultrabook.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1347942142206</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:22:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347942923978-4</Id><Topic><Title>Analysts seem to be controlling stock prices.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1347850060598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 22:47:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[We're just waiting on LTE to arrive. Shouldn't be long...] At its annual investor day, Intel reiterated that its first dual-core smartphone processor, the "Medfield" Z2580, is coming later this year and will be offered with Intel-branded 4G LTE silicon. And to drive home its commitment to phones, CEO Paul Otellini said that phone chip development will move ahead at "twice the rate of Moore's Law." Put another way, chip development that would ordinarily take six years will be carried out in three. "They have a real chance...if they choose to get aggressive," said Anand Shimpi of chip review site Anandtech. [Intel has chosen to get aggressive...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347942923978</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:35:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347943898595-5</Id><Title>When Does Intel get LTE?</Title><Msg>The first thing to realize is that the number of devices that require HSPA+ eclipses number of devices that require LTE. Therefore, Intel not having LTE now hurts in the US market but doesn’t have any appreciable impact in the rest of world. In 2013, this will start to change and Intel will need to deliver on a strong LTE solution to ensure they can continue to grow their footprint in 2013. Intel was clear at their recent investor meeting on this by saying they would ship their discrete LTE solution, the XMM 7160 by the end this year and ramp in 2013. Looking Ahead Many forget that Intel’s Infineon arm supplied Apple with wireless chips for years. They aren’t rookies in mobility, but Intel won’t get full industry credit until their SoC are in a major US brand with leading wireless technologies. Intel will get that chance in 2013, and it will be interesting to see what percentage of Motorola’s high end business will be in reach. Even more interesting is Apple, who uses discrete wireless chips, not integrated into the SoC. Given Infineon’s previous relationship with Apple, we may yet see Intel silicon inside future Apple mobile devices in the next year or two. From Forbes [And this is how lame Wall Street is, along with the media knownothings. Because of the revenue warning they have assumed that Intel is doing nothing, that Intel's mobility strategy isn't working and, of course, that Intel will soon be filing for bankruptcy. Instead we find out that Intel is ramping mobility at twice the normal pace. And their normal pace is one that ARM can't possibly match. We find out that Intel is starting smartphones in the rest of the world while they complete their LTE capability. We find out that Intel is already producing 14nm chips that are better than anything ARM will have for four years. And tomorrow we start to see Intel replacing ARM chips in smartphones. Intel will ramp the US smartphone business in 2013. And not a single analyst knows anything about any of this. Or at least is afraid to breathe a word of it lest they break the covenant with the rest of Wall Street's big firms to keep Intel in a trading range. Well, guess what? Intel is going to have the last word and it will be time to set up the dunking tank for all of the Gus Richard scumbags on Wall Street...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347943898595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:51:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347946537437-6</Id><Title>the only reason they pulled this stock back from 27 is</Title><Msg>to double it from 23</Msg><Username>raygeo2003</Username><Timestamp>1347946537437</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 01:35:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347951727820-7</Id><Title>IT IS OUR OBLIGATION TO OUR CHILDREN TO VOTE OBAMA OUT IN NOVEMBER.</Title><Msg>Obama is ruining everything for our children. It is are obligation to vote him out in november.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347951727820</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 03:02:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347954309571-8</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola Mobility to announce first Intel-based device 5am ET</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347940781714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 23:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good info. Also a really funny screen name...Did you write the Countdown to Mephisto?</Msg><Username>qniform</Username><Timestamp>1347954309571</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 03:45:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347955465467-9</Id><Topic><Title>When Does Intel get LTE?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347943898595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:51:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From a 2011 announcement: "LTE is a fast growing market driven by the increasing demand for such mobile broadband services as multimedia broadcasting, music and video streaming and high-speed mobile Internet. It is expected to become the worldwide mobile standard for high-speed Internet due to its high data throughput and high spectral efficiency. However, LTE is faced with the challenge of a strongly fragmented regional frequency landscape. This calls for major RF innovation to create a low-power modem platform that can cover all the diverse frequency plans fitting to portable devices. Intel Mobile Communications is leveraging its proven leadership in RF and meets this challenge by offering the XMM 7060 platform." Started shipping late last year. Sounds like they're on it...</Msg><Username>qniform</Username><Timestamp>1347955465467</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 04:04:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347956578345-10</Id><Title>Medfield</Title><Msg>Kitchdee makes some excellent points in the "processor wars" thread. There's no question that Intel was late to the mobile game (rather than writing the rules like they usually do). However, as someone said in another thread (sorry, forget who to credit) their chip ecosystem is probably going to save them. Their Penwell SoC is OK, but the real competitive position is represented by the SoC and surrounding chip population. Can other players cobble together competing architectures? Probably, but I wouldn't bet on them competing very effectively on price...</Msg><Username>qniform</Username><Timestamp>1347956578345</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 04:22:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347958862817-11</Id><Title>Obama The Marxist !!!</Title><Msg>Dreams from My Real Father ~ A Story of Reds and Deception At age 18, Barack Obama admittedly arrived at Occidental College a committed revolutionary Marxist. What was the source of Obama's foundation in Marxism? Throughout his 2008 Presidential campaign and term in office, questions have been raised regarding Barack Obama's family background, economic philosophy, and fundamental political ideology. Dreams from My Real Father is the alternative Barack Obama "autobiography," offering a divergent theory of what may have shaped our 44th President's life and politics. In Dreams from My Real Father, Barack Obama is portrayed by a voice-over actor who chronicles Barack Obama's life journey in socialism, from birth through his election to the Presidency. The film begins by presenting the case that Barack Obama's real father was Frank Marshall Davis, a Communist Party USA propagandist who likely shaped Obama. Much More in the Book!</Msg><Username>robertnupstatecarolina</Username><Timestamp>1347958862817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 05:01:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347959327874-12</Id><Title>Motorola live cc</Title><Msg>livestream[dotcom]/motorolamobility</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347959327874</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 05:08:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347960485315-13</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola live cc</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347959327874</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 05:08:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2 GHz, 40% larger battery, 4.3" edge to edge screen, nfc, wide European launch in October.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347960485315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 05:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347960940149-14</Id><Topic><Title>Dell already making ultrabooks very affordable.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1347942142206</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:22:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two things I've learned: (1) never invoke conspiracy when stupidity will explain something; (2) there are lots and lots of stupid people out there. To the point, the analysts aren't in conspiracy to sink INTC...they have simply bought the stupid line that tablets beat PC's. And, there are lots of stupid people buying them.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347960940149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 05:35:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347961081597-15</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola live cc</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347959327874</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 05:08:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>anandtech[dotcom]/show/6307/motorola-hits-2ghz-with-intel-powered-razr-i</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347961081597</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 05:38:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347961776447-16</Id><Topic><Title>Dell already making ultrabooks very affordable.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1347942142206</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:22:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC is near a generational bottom here, not sure though whether it's going to be around $23 or the 600 day adjusted moving average of just over $22. Wallis lays it on thick but he is basically right that 14nm will be the inflection point with ARM although it will be as much about the excellent designs of Haswell and Airmont than the 14nm process itself, it's never been just about the fabrication but it sure helps to showcase great designs. 14nm 5W Haswells and 1-2W Airmonts will be asking serious questions of 20nm ARM processors in 2014 which they just may not be able to answer.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347961776447</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 05:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347961969876-17</Id><Topic><Title>Dell already making ultrabooks very affordable.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1347942142206</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:22:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>correction: I meant to write 14nm Broadwell as that is the 14nm shrink of 22nm Haswell.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347961969876</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 05:52:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347965026063-18</Id><Topic><Title>When Does Intel get LTE?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347943898595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:51:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot to mention that Intel's base bands are manufactured by TSMC and contain an ARM CPU...</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1347965026063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 06:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347965164673-19</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS OUR OBLIGATION TO OUR CHILDREN TO VOTE OBAMA OUT IN NOVEMBER.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347951727820</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 03:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are crazy if anything our kids will benefit more then we will</Msg><Username>funtoday89</Username><Timestamp>1347965164673</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 06:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347967851650-20</Id><Title>second top-ten smartphone maker to introduce an Intel-based mobile phone</Title><Msg>Intel (INTC) Corp.’s effort to land chips in smartphones is getting a boost from Google Inc. (GOOG)’s Motorola Mobility, which plans to start selling devices featuring Intel processors in Europe and Latin America next month. Motorola Mobility plans to sell the Razr i in the U.K., France, Germany, Argentina, Brazil and Mexico, the companies said today. The handset is the first to boast a 2-gigahertz version of Intel’s Atom processor, which is designed to speed up such tasks as taking pictures and toggling between applications. Motorola Mobility becomes the second top-ten smartphone maker to introduce an Intel-based mobile phone, after China’s ZTE Corp. (000063) released one in Europe this month. While Intel is establishing a beachhead in mobile chips after a decade of failed attempts to persuade phone makers to use its products, it doesn’t expect material sales from the effort until 2013. Intel has less than 1 percent of the market for mobile- phone processors, said Will Strauss, an analyst at Forward Concepts Co., a Mesa, Arizona-based research firm. Intel lags in mobile chips behind Qualcomm Inc., Samsung Electronics Co. and Apple Inc. Its new device will square off against Apple’s iPhone 5, which goes on sale in parts of Europe on Sept. 21, as well as other, more established brands. Not all of Intel’s announced partners end up bringing Intel-based phones to market. That was the case with Nokia Oyj (NOK1V) and LG Electronics Inc. (066570)</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347967851650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 07:30:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347968881103-21</Id><Title>Wallis, intc_inside, and others...</Title><Msg>Your informed posts and counterattacks on the analysts is the best thing we've got going for the INTC pps aside from fundamentals. This is much more effective than letters to CEO's and politicians that go straight into the circular file. Keep up the good work, and indeed, expand to comment on the idiots who write negative drivel for Seeking Alpha, and other miscreant blogs.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347968881103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 07:48:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347968997190-22</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS OUR OBLIGATION TO OUR CHILDREN TO VOTE OBAMA OUT IN NOVEMBER.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347951727820</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 03:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GFY..idiot.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347968997190</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 07:49:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347969979128-23</Id><Title>I have an iPhone too.</Title><Msg>I have the very first generation 16 GB iPhone with aluminum casing. My contract with AT&amp;T was expired over 2 years ago. Still have the same iPhone which I use as an entertainment device when I'm bored. I see no reason in upgrading to a new iPhone. My experience with the AT&amp;T/iPhone combination during the latter part of the 2 year contract was the worse I've had in making calls. I have access to all the apps that Apple offers, so I don't need a new portal to access them. The current iPhone works just fine in WiFi locations to download. But during the last four years, I've had the need to upgrade my laptop to a netbook and a seperate desktop with a larger screen. And to add another desktop to the house. And currently, I have more of a need to add an ultrabook to the mix than I do in having a smartphone, although, I am game to having a non iPhone smartphone within the next 6 months. I don't see the reasoning at all that a smartphone and tablet combo will replace the need for a laptop or desktop.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1347969979128</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 08:06:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347970081573-24</Id><Topic><Title>When Does Intel get LTE?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347943898595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:51:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot to mention that Intel's base bands are manufactured by TSMC and contain an ARM CPU... _______________ You forgot to mention that LTE is a documented disaster and that Intel needs to save Apple from the mess TSMC and ARM are making.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347970081573</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 08:08:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347970495302-25</Id><Topic><Title>I have an iPhone too.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1347969979128</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 08:06:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nor do I. Tablets are for the poor lesser beings that co-inhabit this grossly overpopulated planet.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1347970495302</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 08:14:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347972974000-26</Id><Title>INTC,New cpu 4 mobile and x86,Dividend Yield</Title><Msg>INTC,New cpu 4 mobile and x86,Dividend Yield - Good Future growth and Leader of the CPU Market - News - Intel's powered mobile handset - News - Intel's Haswell chips 2012 Dividends ------------------ Declared Date Record Date Payable Date Amount Type 07/26/12 08/07/12 09/01/2012 0.2250 Regular Cash 03/22/12 05/07/12 06/01/12 0.2100 Regular Cash 01/25/12 02/07/12 03/01/12 0.2100 Regular Cash</Msg><Username>palstkinfo</Username><Timestamp>1347972974000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 08:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347974258056-27</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS OUR OBLIGATION TO OUR CHILDREN TO VOTE OBAMA OUT IN NOVEMBER.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347951727820</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 03:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is are obligation to vote him out in. The alternative is worse. Just remember the previous President that took over a surplus and left us in ruins.</Msg><Username>gerdfricke</Username><Timestamp>1347974258056</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:17:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347974266165-28</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS OUR OBLIGATION TO OUR CHILDREN TO VOTE OBAMA OUT IN NOVEMBER.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347951727820</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 03:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is are obligation to vote him out in. The alternative is worse. Just remember the previous President that took over a surplus and left us in ruins.</Msg><Username>gerdfricke</Username><Timestamp>1347974266165</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347974607555-29</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>Stocks were overbought after last week's rally. So it wasn't surprising to see some backing and filling. A little pullback could bring worries back in the market allowing stocks to climb a wall of worry. Expect some consolidation as the economic data dominates the week. Let stocks work off their overbought condition before stepping in. Oil tanked in late trading yesterday on rumors of an oil release from the strategic oil reserves. Volume was very thin, thats because the retail investors are shunning the market. The High Frequency Trading is taking a toll on this market. The Analysts grading of the stocks, the info of the grades being fed to the hedge funds and mutual funds even before the investor gets a glimpse of it and looses out is also driving the retail investor away by the droves. The excuberance of this QE3 and ECB soap opera has driven the markets to oblivion but the fundamentals will catch up pretty soon so stay nimble and quick. have a nice day</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1347974607555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:23:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347974642122-30</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS OUR OBLIGATION TO OUR CHILDREN TO VOTE OBAMA OUT IN NOVEMBER.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347951727820</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 03:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry for the unintended double reply.</Msg><Username>gerdfricke</Username><Timestamp>1347974642122</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:24:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347974855318-31</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola Mobility to announce first Intel-based device 5am ET</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347940781714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 23:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's called the Razor i. Has a 4.3-inch screen, single core 2-GHz Atom Z2480, takes 10 photos per second. Battery reportedly delivers 20 hour of mixed-use on a single charge. It looks very nice. Targeted for Latin America and Europe. The phone is compatible with T-Mobile's U.S. network. Intel's work in mobile is finally beginning to show results. I expect the pace to substantially accelerate.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1347974855318</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347975525846-32</Id><Title>Oops, we completely screwed the dog in the mobile market</Title><Msg>Oh well, no sweat. It'll come around again in another 50 million years.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347975525846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:38:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347975692986-33</Id><Title>Pimps, stock price is about valuation GOING FORWARD</Title><Msg>INTC has NO SIGNIFICANT PRESENCE in the mobile space. They NEVER HAVE. Going forward, AAPL and others completely OWN THIS SPACE. Get it?</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347975692986</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347975930154-34</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola Mobility to announce first Intel-based device 5am ET</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347940781714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 23:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>another day, another downgrade, target price way up there at 24.00</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1347975930154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:45:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347975933732-35</Id><Topic><Title>When Does Intel get LTE?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347943898595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:51:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot to mention that LTE is a documented disaster and that Intel needs to save Apple from the mess TSMC and ARM are making. ------ So Apple are going to move from QCOM's baseband (28m@TSMC which contains an ARM core) which does LTE today, to Intel's future LTE baseband (40nm@TSMC which also contains an ARM core)? Mess? Intel use TSMC and ARM... LTE is a mess, but it's a standards thing...</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1347975933732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347976019909-36</Id><Title>Big Step for Intel in Mobility</Title><Msg>Motorola wasn’t quite done with its announcements for the month. The Google-owned smartphone maker announced three new versions of the Razr earlier this month, but took the wraps off a fourth Thursday. The Motorola Razr i is notable not only because of its edge-to-edge screen and long battery life, but also because of its 2Ghz processor, which is made by a relative newcomer to the smartphone field — Intel. The phone is pegged for a release in Britain, France, Germany, Argentina, Brazil and Mexico in October; at this time, no U.S. launch plans have been announced. The announcement is the product of a partnership Intel and Motorola announced in January and is a big step for Intel, as it expands its horizons.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347976019909</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:46:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347976212239-37</Id><Title>Motorola unleashes Intel-powered RAZR i on Euroland</Title><Msg>2GHz Medfield meets RAZR M Rumours of an Intel-based Motorola handset have been swirling around for weeks and now the phone is finally official. The Motorola RAZR i is basically a RAZR M with a 2GHz Intel chip inside. The 2GHz Medfield processor takes the place of Qualcomm’s S4 in this Euro phone and it is basically the first big Intel phone launch in Europe. The rest of the spec remains unchanged, a 4.3-inch edge-to-edge screen in a tiny Kevlar coated package, with a 2000mAh battery and 8-megapixel camera. Of course, the big news here is the processor, so let’s stick to that. Engadget reports that the chip is optimized for browsing, with a special emphasis on Java. Gaming should also benefit from the new chip, but we still have to see how the Medfield compares to Krait in real life tests. It’s not a Nexus, but the RAZR i comes with an unlocked bootloader, NFC and Android Beam support, but it is still unclear whether the phone will launch with Android 4.0 or 4.1. The RAZR M was demoed with Jelly Bean, but launched with ICS. In any case, both phones will probably end up running Jelly Bean in a couple of months one way or the other. From Fudzilla</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347976212239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:50:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347976262301-38</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola Mobility to announce first Intel-based device 5am ET</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347940781714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 23:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It has been interesting. I was surprised when Yahoo let me take it. I cannot sign off using it without Yahoo deleting the message. It started as a pun on the writer "Alexandre Dumas".</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347976262301</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347976515374-39</Id><Title>INTEL DOWNGRADE</Title><Msg>Intel (INTC) downgraded at RBC from Outperform to Sector Perform, RBC Capital said. $24 price target. PC market faces near-term headwinds.</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1347976515374</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:55:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>32</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347976700629-40</Id><Title>The danger Intel's Haswell poses to Nvidia and AMD</Title><Msg>Intel’s next-generation architecture, codenamed Haswell, isn’t just another “tock” in Intel’s tick/tock cadence; it’s a serious threat to both AMD and Nvidia. For the first time, Intel is poised to challenge both companies in the mainstream graphics market while simultaneously eroding Nvidia’s edge in the GPGPU business. Its low-power, 10 Watt TDP ULV parts will challenge the price/performance ratio of AMD’s second-generation Brazos SoC (codenamed Kabini) as well as any ARM-based Windows 8 notebooks that companies like Qualcomm might bring to market.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347976700629</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:58:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347976900663-41</Id><Title>Haswell’s GPU turns the screws on Nvidia, AMD</Title><Msg>Haswell’s GPU is a tweaked version of the cores currently deployed in Ivy Bridge. What’s really changing is the shader loadout; Intel will offer Haswell in 10, 20, and 40-shader flavours (GT1, GT2, and GT3). The chip will also be offered in variants that include up to 128MB in on-package RAM, a feature that provides the GPU with a small dedicated pool of memory. Intel isn’t talking much about the GPU changes, but the company has stated that the new GT3 configuration offers “up to 2x” the performance of Ivy Bridge’s HD 4000 graphics. Even a conservative take on that promise spells trouble for AMD and Nvidia. According to figures from Anandtech, Trinity’s GPU is an average of 18 per cent faster than Llano’s across a range of 15 popular titles. Compared to Sandy Bridge, Trinity was almost 80 per cent faster. Against Ivy Bridge, it’s just 20 per cent faster. Given what we know of Haswell’s GPU shader counts and performance targets, it shouldn’t be hard for Intel to deliver a 30 to 50 per cent performance boost in real-world gaming. If it does, Trinity goes from the fastest integrated GPU on the market to an also-ran, and AMD loses the superior graphics hole card it’s been playing since it launched the AMD 780G chipset four years ago. Sunnyvale has virtually no room to manoeuvre. The company’s 28nm Kaveri APU, with its next-generation graphics core based on the HD Radeon 7000 and the new Steamroller CPU reportedly has yet to tape-out. That means it could be the tail end of 2013 before we see the chips, assuming that production goes smoothly. AMD will likely offer a “Trinity 2.0” update to stem off Haswell’s onslaught, but slightly higher clocks aren’t going to be enough to keep Intel from matching AMD’s performance. AMD’s last bastions are the markets Intel doesn’t really want. It’s an unsustainable position for any company that dreams of challenging the market leader; AMD literally can’t afford the R&amp;D it would take to catch up to its erstwhile rival. You won’t find Nvidia gloating – well, not much. Intel’s literature makes it plain that the company absolutely intends to minimise the value of separate GPUs by incorporating performance where it can and driving the adoption of ever-smaller form factors where it can’t. Barring a major screw-up, it’ll be Haswell, not Kaveri, that crosses the “good enough for enthusiasts” line first. The chip’s 10 Watt power envelope won’t directly compete with any potential Tegra 4-based tablets – that’s what Bay Trail, Intel’s out-of-order 22nm Atom SoC is for. No, Haswell won’t drive AMD out of business or frighten Nvidia into dumping Tesla – but unless Intel completely blows its roadmap, it’ll drive both companies further towards the margins of computing. For AMD, that move is very literal; the company is being forced into the low-end products that Intel doesn’t want to bother with. For Nvidia, it means scrambling to convince OEMs to allocate space for discrete GPUs at a time when Intel’s marketing dollars and consumer preferences are aligned against it. Enthusiast preferences, Intel’s historically weak driver support, and Nvidia’s own brand recognition will help, but the IT industry is littered with the bones of companies that treated their brand as an unassailable bulwark rather than a sand castle. Enthusiasts that care about performance tend to follow it, wherever it goes. From ITProPortal</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347976900663</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:01:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347976937986-42</Id><Topic><Title>Pimps, stock price is about valuation GOING FORWARD</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347975692986</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:41:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Motorola just launched an Intel phone with an Intel chip that REPLACED a Qualcom chip. It's all over today's yahoo news. Vinny, I see where you endlessly pumped AMD at 40 and used to work for Intel and couldn't get it done.</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1347976937986</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:02:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347977393434-43</Id><Title>Wall Street: Dumb and Dumber</Title><Msg>AMD on the ropes. Wall Street doesn't notice. Intel releases a smartphone replacing ARM chips. Nor is there any media coverage to speak of. Intel now has smartphones in most of the world and prepares for a major US roll-out in 2013. Wall Street doesn't notice. Intel prepares to push AMD and Nvidia out of the graphics business. Wall Street doesn't notice. Apple releases a disappointing iPhone 5 that's just good enough. Wall Street goes crazy. Wall Street: Dumb and Dumber Send the letters...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347977393434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:09:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347978025245-44</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street: Dumb and Dumber</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347977393434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:09:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Waldo, getting poorer and poorer lately. Analysts a perfect 10, Waldo a perfect zero.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1347978025245</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:20:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347979014823-45</Id><Title>What we know about Vinnie_bagodonitz (also known as Lucy Nuff, Too funny, etc)</Title><Msg>He went to a second rate school, fudged on his resume and got a job at Intel. They quickly found out that he was a fraud, but he got out just in time and landed a job at AMD. He got nowhere there either, as Intel destroyed AMD and left it barely alive. He takes his vengence out on the Intel board and is nothing but a Techy loser with an Associates degree, no love-life and a laughable golf game suited only for the far end of the driving range. BLOOP !</Msg><Username>vinnie_bagofhotwind</Username><Timestamp>1347979014823</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:36:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347979241334-46</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL DOWNGRADE</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1347976515374</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:55:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You realize they do this to move stock right? Can't make money unless you create volitility. Mark it.. INTC will be over 25 by Oct.. Look at the 2 year history.</Msg><Username>verioinc</Username><Timestamp>1347979241334</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:40:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347979279620-47</Id><Topic><Title>Oops, we completely screwed the dog in the mobile market</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347975525846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:38:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch for news in the coming month!!</Msg><Username>verioinc</Username><Timestamp>1347979279620</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347979393626-48</Id><Topic><Title>What we know about Vinnie_bagodonitz (also known as Lucy Nuff, Too funny, etc)</Title><Username>vinnie_bagofhotwind</Username><Timestamp>1347979014823</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:36:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Usually people that have this much of a vendetta against a company they either worked for them or lost big time money from them. I laugh at losers like that.</Msg><Username>verioinc</Username><Timestamp>1347979393626</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347979445879-49</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street: Dumb and Dumber</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347977393434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:09:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LetterBoy: The INTEL management team JUST WARNED and Wall Street heard and is heeding that WARNING. You must have missed it. You were probably busy with your letter-writng campaign.</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1347979445879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:44:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>28</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347979578832-50</Id><Title>Intel ready for another LEG DOWN: below 20$ Soon</Title><Msg>Sell any pop -------------- eom ------------------------------------------------</Msg><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1347979578832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:46:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347980287181-51</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell’s GPU turns the screws on Nvidia, AMD</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347976900663</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:01:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The real place that Haswell is unmatched, imho, is mobile. If they double mobile graphics and pop 10% for CPU tasks at the same wattage, it just crushes video cards. The reason is efficiency. That is a huge jump in graphics performance, and is up in the revolutionary regime, not evolutionary.</Msg><Username>tesoro2day</Username><Timestamp>1347980287181</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:58:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347980754863-52</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola unleashes Intel-powered RAZR i on Euroland</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347976212239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem here is graphics. They aren't even close to Iphone 4S, and Iphone 5 has twice the graphics performance of the 4S, according to Apple. So, we likely have a slightly inferior CPU (Medfield to A6) at the same process, with a crippled GPU comparatively, but higher wattage. Folks, Medfield is DOA, outside of very cheap emerging market applications, imho. The DC updated graphics version should do much better in tablets, but it will suck the wattage in comparison, I suspect.</Msg><Username>tesoro2day</Username><Timestamp>1347980754863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:05:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347981455900-53</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street: Dumb and Dumber</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347977393434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:09:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All true, but nothing speaks louder than results. When Intel's competitive advantage begins to show in marketshare and financial statements analysts will jump on board and they'll consider themselves geniuses for it. The Razr i is an attractive product and is likely to do well. However the Razr i is a small sample of the Intel mobile products yet to come.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1347981455900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:17:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347981553025-54</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola unleashes Intel-powered RAZR i on Euroland</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347976212239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good thread. I also think it demonstrates another factor germaine to stock picking - there are people who would never buy an Apple product just like there are those who will buy them at any price....</Msg><Username>qniform</Username><Timestamp>1347981553025</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:19:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347982153813-55</Id><Title>Trolls</Title><Msg>Plonking trolls apparently isn't enough - I have to block those who feed them as well, before the interesting messages are visible...</Msg><Username>qniform</Username><Timestamp>1347982153813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:29:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347982354168-56</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola unleashes Intel-powered RAZR i on Euroland</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347976212239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True. I used to be one of those types. After watching my Android crash, chew battery life, hang up on me when my cheek hit it, etc., I finally took the plunge and bought an IP4 on Ebay. I will probably never go back. Iphone to Android is very much like Lexus to Chevy; there simply is no comparison in quality. As more people experience what I did, Apple will grow or Android will have to get a lot better. We'll see how it plays out.</Msg><Username>tesoro2day</Username><Timestamp>1347982354168</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:32:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347983294538-57</Id><Title>BARRON'S ARTICLE ON TODAY'S DOWNGRADE OF INTEL</Title><Msg>see yahoo news.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347983294538</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:48:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>28</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347984112154-58</Id><Title>Motorola RAZR i review - Hands on with the fastest smartphone ever</Title><Msg>expertreviews[dot_co_uk]/smartphones/1294753/motorola-razr-i-review-hands-on-with-the-fastest-smartphone-ever ATOMIC POWER Inside, we were told by an Intel representative, that this handset uses the same capable Intel Atom Z2460 chipset as the San Diego, but this time it's running at up 2GHz. That makes it the fastest smartphone ever in pure clock speed. It's only a single-core, but it uses Intel's venerable Hyper Threading technology to provide two virtual cores. In practice it feels very fast, and test bore that out with a SunSpider JavaScript score of an all-time best score of 1,065ms. That compares well to the 1,326ms we got from the San Diego, and the 1,600ms scores that most top-end ARM-based devices get. Now Java performance isn't everything in a phone, but its a key element and one Intel has nailed - even the top Android handsets feel slow in comparison. Intel claimed: “Our single core architecture outperforms dual core products”, and we're convinced.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347984112154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:01:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347984183600-59</Id><Topic><Title>BARRON'S ARTICLE ON TODAY'S DOWNGRADE OF INTEL</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347983294538</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:48:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Barron's article describes the RBC downgrade of Intel. It appears that RBC is a little late to the game. Intel is green/unchanged while the rest of the market is red. Analyst Moves: INTC, MPC This morning, RBC downgraded shares of Intel (INTC) from outperform to sector perform as headwinds from the PC sector could weigh on earnings. With the downgrade, RBC set a price target of $24 per share.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347984183600</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:03:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347984673854-60</Id><Topic><Title>Has ARM won the processor wars? Hardly!</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347844824985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's the licensees for the ARM 64 ISA that will attack x86 from every direction..." Interesting, what do you think ARM 64 will offer that will be such a threat to Intel? It can't be nearly as good, or as good or a little bit better than Intel. It has to be night and day in order to make an impact. What will that killer thing will bring it to it's knees?</Msg><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1347984673854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:11:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347984703511-61</Id><Topic><Title>BARRON'S ARTICLE ON TODAY'S DOWNGRADE OF INTEL</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347983294538</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:48:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More evidence of the analyst herd following mentality. Oops, look like the herd just had a direction change. Time to change direction.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1347984703511</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347985771324-62</Id><Topic><Title>Has ARM won the processor wars? Hardly!</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347844824985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"what do you think ARM 64 will offer that will be such a threat to Intel?" World support... "It can't be nearly as good" Doesn't have to be... just good enough... "What will that killer thing will bring it to it's knees?" World support...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347985771324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347986075677-63</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola RAZR i review - Hands on with the fastest smartphone ever</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347984112154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:01:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesomoe. I say Motorola is going to introduce an Intel-based phone next year in the U.S. that changes the industry forever.</Msg><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1347986075677</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347987050719-64</Id><Title>Support</Title><Msg>Sitting right at support now. Let's see which way it goes.</Msg><Username>northtower91</Username><Timestamp>1347987050719</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:50:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347987115082-65</Id><Topic><Title>What we know about Vinnie_bagodonitz (also known as Lucy Nuff, Too funny, etc)</Title><Username>vinnie_bagofhotwind</Username><Timestamp>1347979014823</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:36:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol....</Msg><Username>nuff_cuffedandstuffed</Username><Timestamp>1347987115082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:51:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347987345100-66</Id><Title>Buy SHF</Title><Msg>huge potential</Msg><Username>drhollars</Username><Timestamp>1347987345100</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:55:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347987575717-67</Id><Title>Apple spent $500M to say ‘f*** you’ to Intel</Title><Msg>Apple spent $500M to say ‘f*** you’ to Intel Apple’s A6 processor is the result of years of effort that has its roots in Apple’s efforts to achieve independence from its chip suppliers. As noted in a post by Anandtech, the evidence is growing that Apple took the added trouble of not only designing its own ARM-based chip, it also created a customized core (the central processing brain inside the chip) for the A6. This is according to a post by Lynley Gwennap, head of The Lynley Group, a chip market consultancy. Gwennap believes the A6 has a dual-core design running at 1.2GHz. Gwennap says that Apple has spent $400 million on chip company acquisitions and probably another $100 million on four years of chip development, bringing its total investment to $500 million. That’s probably a small price to pay for independence from chip manufacturers, who would charge Apple a 30 percent margin or more on every processor they sell. Apple’s independence movement stretches back to its $278 million acquisition of PA Semi in April 2008. This kicked off an attempt to become independent of chip suppliers such as Intel and Samsung. PA Semi’s team was a veteran group of chip designers led by Dan Dobberpuhl, who led the development of Digital Equipment’s StrongArm processors in the 1990s. PA Semi created a PowerPC processor under the leadership of Jim Keller and Pete Bannon. But Apple’s deal with Intel to use x86 chips in the Macs disrupted PA Semi’s plans. Within a month of acquiring PA Semi, Apple secretly signed an architecture license with ARM that allowed the company to develop its own ARM-compatible CPUs (central processing units). Under then-CEO Steve Jobs, one team worked on the Apple A4 chip using an ARM CPU chip core, while another began defining the microarchitecture for a new CPU. In March, 2010, Dobberpuhl left Apple, as did PA Semi chief operating officer Leo Joseph and vice president of system architecture Mark Hayter. Keller and Bannon continued to work on the chip development and hired Gerard Williams, an ARM fellow and the technical lead for the ARM Cortex-8 and Cortex-15 CPUs. Apple could have chosen an ARM Cortex-A9 or A-15 for the A6 core, but it had the chops to do a more efficient, precisely defined core that did exactly what Apple wanted it to do and no more. In early 2010, the team finished the microarchitecture design (akin to the blueprints) and began the physical design phase, where it laid out the exact structure of the chip. To bolster its physical design skills, Apple bought chip design firm Intrinsity for $120 million in April 2010. That gave Apple more talent to finish the A6, which was completed last summer. Gwennap now expects Apple to use the A6 through 2013 and then launch a new CPU design in 2014. That one could be based on the 64-bit ARMv8 instruction set. Gwennap says he believes that Samsung is building the A6 in a 32-nanometer manufacturing process. (In that respect, Apple is not completely independent. It designs the chips, but has to rely on Samsung to make them). Gwennap said the A6 is similar in complexity and performance to the ARM Cortex-A15 and the Krait CPU that appears in Qualcomm’s newest chips. To hit a 2X performance gain over the iPhone 4S (as Apple claimed at its press conference), Gwennap says Apple had to move to the two CPU cores at 1.2 gigahertz. Apple also said the A6 processor is 22 percent smaller than the A5. The A6 is 22 percent smaller than the A5, which means the chip size is about 96 square millimeters. That’s a fairly small size, which means the chip is manufacturable and lower in cost. The size is bigger than simply taking the Apple A5X processor (used in the new iPad) and shrinking it from a 45-nanometer manufacturing process to a 32-nanometer manufacturing process, which would normally result in a chip size of 82 square millimeters. To get to that larger size of 96 square millimeters, Gwennap said that Apple must have added a more powerful custom CPU core as well as a better image processor for the camera. And that is the nature of chip design. For more explanation of the significance of this, see the passage on Moore’s Law at the bottom *. Williams has become Apple’s chief CPU architect, while Keller left to join Advanced Micro Devices. But Gwennap believes that Apple is just getting started with CPU design.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347987575717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:59:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347988041247-68</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola RAZR i review - Hands on with the fastest smartphone ever</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347984112154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:01:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The new Razr i is an unlocked phone. No doubt they will be imported to the U.S and used with T-Mobile's network. T-Mobile's HSPDA delivers about 10Mbps/3Mbps. Most smartphone users won't notice the difference between that and LTE and 3G is still the best phone to have for international travelers.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1347988041247</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347988043972-69</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola RAZR i review - Hands on with the fastest smartphone ever</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347984112154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:01:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The new Razr i is an unlocked phone. No doubt they will be imported to the U.S and used with T-Mobile's network. T-Mobile's HSPDA delivers about 10Mbps/3Mbps. Most smartphone users won't notice the difference between that and LTE and 3G is still the best phone to have for international travelers.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1347988043972</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:07:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347988164079-70</Id><Title>Anybody watch CNBC yesterday?</Title><Msg>They said they were going to discuss how changes in Dividend taxes would effect the economy, but I missed what they said.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1347988164079</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:09:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347988848615-71</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola RAZR i review - Hands on with the fastest smartphone ever</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347984112154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:01:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are a couple of problems here. One is that even with the high clock, it isn't going to be the fastest on a lot of CPU tasks, and second, they put the watts into the CPU. For instance, IP4s has much better graphics; you can just imagine what the IP5 will do. I think we should look at this as MOT throwing INTC a bone at 32nm to obtain most favored nation status for the next generation when it comes out next year.</Msg><Username>tesoro2day</Username><Timestamp>1347988848615</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347988918781-72</Id><Title>Bad news keeps on coming</Title><Msg>Daily bad news, the gift that won't stop giving. If anyone wants to predict how a stock will move, do the opposite of what I do. The reason Intel is moving down, is because I bought it @$25. Wouldn't be surprised it eventually goes to zero. Now, if I sell it, it would immediately move up quite substantially.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1347988918781</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:21:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347989289405-73</Id><Topic><Title>Apple spent $500M to say ‘f*** you’ to Intel</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347987575717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, let's look at it. Two years of IOS devices, so what do you think? Maybe 200-300 million devices? So that investment cost Apple $2.50 or less a chip. Apple likely saves $10-30 per chip, so they are really saving billions by doing this. As of now, they have been producing the top performing chips available anywhere, so that pays a premium. The only way I see Intel getting Apple's business, is for Intel to produce chips that put Apple in a corner--either put Intel inside or you will lose market share. That day could be coming, but it sure doesn't look to be any time soon. The A6 looks pretty competitive right now, but we should learn a lot more soon. GLTA longs.</Msg><Username>tesoro2day</Username><Timestamp>1347989289405</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:28:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347989539938-74</Id><Topic><Title>Bad news keeps on coming</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1347988918781</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:21:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then sell that sucker. naw....jus kidding....it will be fine...</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1347989539938</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:32:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347990268646-75</Id><Topic><Title>Bad news keeps on coming</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1347988918781</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:21:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Need more time to see how the chip design battle shakes out, especially ARMH v INTC. Will INTC put SSD on their board? If so, whose? How will they exploit the ubiquitous android based device market? It has an attractive yield but is it an MSFT dynosaur? Actually I have a limit buy at $20.50</Msg><Username>mikecstrong</Username><Timestamp>1347990268646</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:44:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347990817006-76</Id><Topic><Title>Apple spent $500M to say ‘f*** you’ to Intel</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347987575717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a bigger rebuff to NVDA, QCOM and TI than Intel. Intel did not have a low power solution at the time Apple needed and Apple spent $278m for PA Semi. At that time, QCOM, NVDA and others had low power parts that would solve Apple's needs, didn't they? Apple likes to control their supply chain and I expect that they will continue to be independent. It makes sense. The only reason they went to Intel for MAC was because Intel had much lower power than IBM could not offer with their Power parts. It would not surprise me to have the MAC go ARM for some (and maybe all) of their models. They, like many ARM vendors, has company infrastructure that will provide inertia and keep them in the ARM camp for some time.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347990817006</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347990933539-77</Id><Topic><Title>Bad news keeps on coming</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1347988918781</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:21:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Almost seems as if there's a carefully orchestrated campaign to hammer down the price to help all those short. Every scrap of news is either a downgrade or some negative trumped up story? It's almost as if everyone is saying that anyone investing in Intel should go ahead and just slit your throat so as not too worry. There is no hope only despair. Intel will go in the same direction as the horse and buggy.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1347990933539</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:55:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347991059765-78</Id><Topic><Title>Bad news keeps on coming</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1347988918781</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:21:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it will be fine... ----------- Will it will be fine in six months? Is Intel is GOOD FOR $30? TOOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1347991059765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>29</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347991067888-79</Id><Topic><Title>Apple spent $500M to say ‘f*** you’ to Intel</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347987575717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Original poster threw his entire life away to bash Intel and pump ARM and Nvidia. lol</Msg><Username>getsome_nads</Username><Timestamp>1347991067888</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347991363268-80</Id><Title>MIPS sale at an advanced stage</Title><Msg>September 18, 2012 1:15 pm MIPS Technologies sale moves forward By Mark Andress, Sarah Cohen and Louise Bleakley dealReporter -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- The sale process for MIPS Technologies (NASDAQ: MIPS) is now at an advanced stage, a source familiar and an industry source claiming knowledge of the situation told dealReporter. In April, news reports circulated saying that the licensor of embedded processor intellectual property (IP) had retained an investment bank to explore strategic options. This news service reported in May that JP Morgan had been hired. JP Morgan declined to comment. MIPS said it does not comment on speculation surrounding the potential sale of the company. MIPS’ shares are currently trading around USD 7.20, up from USD 5 in early April. MIPS is receiving interest from about a half a dozen bidders, the first source said. Semiconductor and related companies that are seeking to expand their IP portfolios are participating in the process, he noted. Manufacturers like Intel (NASDAQ: INTL) and Qualcomm (NASDAQ: QCOM, and IP “trolls” like Acacia Research Group and RPX Corp. (NASDAQ: RPXC) are the “types of companies” in the auction, the first source said. The industry source said a customer of the Sunnyvale, California-based company has “aggressively” sought buyers for MIPS to ensure it remains in “good hands” so it will have access to its IP in the future. This source said a customer of the Northern California company found two companies willing to move forward with a bid, adding that he believed the interested suitors are “not from Asia or the Americas”. In an August research note, Benchmark analyst Gary Mobley said that after meeting with management and other stakeholders in MIPS, he had concluded the company would be broken up and sold within the next four months. He named Imagination Technologies (IGNMF.PK), ARM Holdings (NASDAQ:ARMH), Ceva (NASDAQ:CEVA), and Synopsys (NASDAQ:SNPS) as possible buyers. However, one industry banker said he did not expect MIPS customers to buy the company. The industry banker said Broadcom (NASDAQ:BRCM), MIPS’ biggest customer, may have sought a buyer for MIPS given fears that Intel could buy it and limit access to its technology. In that likelihood, an industry executive said Broadcom would not have much trouble ramping up production of competitor ARM’s products to compensate for a MIPS loss. Broadcom declined to comment. The system manufacturers that rely on MIPS-based chips for their products have much more at stake because its products have considerable software to drive the MIPS-based chips, he said. Nokia Siemens Networks, which uses Cavium’s (NASDAQ:CAVM) MIPS-based chips in its network equipment, could be a customer anxious to see MIPS remaining in good hands, added the executive. A person familiar with the company said it is relatively simple for customers using MIPS’ products in the mobile market to switch architectures. They only need to take some time “recompiling” for a new architecture. However, in deeply embedded systems, such as micro-controllers, if some of the software code is written in the assembly language then the code would need to be completely rewritten. This process would involve the risk of mistakes in rewritten code, which could lead to outsized costs, the person noted. In its annual report, MIPS lists its two biggest customers as Broadcom and Cavium, each accounting for more than 10% of 2011 revenue. Customers that buy MIPS chips or systems-on-chips include Alcatel-Lucent (NYSE: ALU), Cisco Systems (NASDAQ: CSCO), and ZTE. -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- For more information or to inquire about a trial please email sales@dealreporter or call Europe/EEMEA: +44 (0)20 7059 6160 Americas: +1 212 686-3076 Asia-Pacific: +852 2158 9714 ..</Msg><Username>fastmoneypete</Username><Timestamp>1347991363268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 14:02:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347991751015-81</Id><Title>Clover Trail WILL support Linux</Title><Msg>Intel Clover Trail Will Support Linux After All By Michael EndlerInformationWeek September 18, 2012 11:48 AM 10 Tablets To Shake Up 2012 (click image for larger view and for slideshow)Intel has clarified that Linux does indeed play a role in the chipmaker's plans for its forthcoming Clover Trail line of Atom processors. "The current version of Clover Trail supports Windows 8 tablets," spokeswoman Kathryn Gill wrote in an email, "[but] Intel has plans for another version of this platform directed at Linux/Android." The statement reverses a claim made during last week's Intel Developers Conference (IDF), where representatives from the Silicon Valley-based giant asserted that the new chips would be exclusive to Windows 8. Those comments ostensibly confirmed earlier reports that active Clover Trail efforts did not include porting Google's popular OS. Though Gill could not comment on platform specifics--"stay tuned," she said--the revised road map makes clear that the next Atom generation isn't about excluding Android as much as prioritizing Microsoft's much-hyped new offering. The Clover Trail system-on-a-chip (SoC) is similar to the Medfield platform with which Intel has slowly been establishing a presence in the ARM-dominated mobile processor market. Like the current chip, Clover Trail uses a 32-nm architecture--but the upcoming version jumps from one core to two and includes more powerful graphics processing. [ They're here, but does anyone care? See Nokia Windows Phone 8 Devices Arrive With Thud. ] Just as crucially, Clover Trail also promises improved battery life that could allow Windows 8 tablets to match the low power consumption of their ARM-based rivals. At least 20 Clover Trail-fueled devices are slated to hit the market soon after Microsoft begins shipping the new OS at the end of October. Because Medfield devices currently rely on Android, eyebrows raised when Intel said the new SoC would support only Windows products. With the company declining to explain its strategy, speculation ranged from the current version of Linux being ill-equipped for the chip's power-management functions to possible contractual agreements with Microsoft. With the revelation that multiple Clover Trail versions are planned, however, Intel's approach now makes perfect sense, according to Gartner analyst Sergis Mushell. "No two SoCs are the same," he said in an interview. "It's very important for the OS to be fully integrated and optimized for each chip." He said that the form factor revolution is no longer the dominant factor for businesses and consumers, as many manufacturers now offer appealing shapes and sizes. The key, rather, is "which one is going to perform better?" It consequently makes sense to focus on one OS at a time, and to add support for others later, said Mushell. Mushell noted "it could be a business move rather than a technology move," but that "it frankly doesn't matter." Outside of a few parties, such as Apple and Samsung, few tablet makers have achieved true success, he said. "What else is there to have a stake in? Windows is it." Put another way, Android devices already have a base in the marketplace: ARM. Lacking a clear means of differentiating Intel-based Android products from those already available, it makes sense for Intel to consolidate eggs, at least for now, in the Windows 8 basket. With several different versions of Windows 8 available, a Microsoft-focused attitude could allow Intel to stand out in an emerging market space, rather than to simply add to an established one. It won't be long before industry watchers can see how Intel's plan shakes out: the Windows 8 app store went live earlier this month, and Microsoft, which waffled last week on whether it would patch a Flash vulnerability prior to shipping the new OS, announced on Monday that it will launch Windows 8 with a New York event on Oct. 25, one day ahead of the general release.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347991751015</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 14:09:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347994181072-82</Id><Topic><Title>Clover Trail WILL support Linux</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1347991751015</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 14:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This quote below gave me a chuckle. Noone at IDF said that Clovertrail was Win8 exclusive. It does however, make for more interesting reading. I suspect that Intel has disclosed Clovertrail to MSFT in a way they could not with the Linux community. My guess is that vanilla Linux would "run" on Clovertrail with some "basic" drivers but needs some new drivers and possibly kernel changes to take full advantage of the low power modes. I think that Intel does not want to release internal Clovertrail design choices before introduction. I am pretty sure they have "Linux" running on Clovertrail already inside Intel. "The statement reverses a claim made during last week's Intel Developers Conference (IDF), where representatives from the Silicon Valley-based giant asserted that the new chips would be exclusive to Windows 8. Those comments ostensibly confirmed earlier reports that active Clover Trail efforts did not include porting Google's popular OS. Though Gill could not comment on platform specifics--"stay tuned," she said--the revised road map makes clear that the next Atom generation isn't about excluding Android as much as prioritizing Microsoft's much-hyped new offering."</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1347994181072</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 14:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347994586195-83</Id><Topic><Title>Apple spent $500M to say ‘f*** you’ to Intel</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347987575717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good points, Alex! I do think Intel has a virtual army of engineers working on this in Texas and elsewhere. And, I expect Intel to start throwing some serious punches in low power some time next year. The thing that I have been saying for the last several years is that Intel benefits tremendously regardless of how many LP chips they sell. Performance per watt is now being emphasized all over the company with tremendous expertise being developed, so Haswell and beyond are going to do better because of Intel's LP efforts. It is synergistic, and the roadmap changes for 13 and 14 show me they are laser focused on the problem now. It just takes them three years to get the Tick-Tock momentum going. I think it starts ticking next year. If Apple does move the laptops to ARM, I think they will be back. However, a Quad core A6 at 2-2.5ghz would be a beast...well up into laptop performance levels.</Msg><Username>tesoro2day</Username><Timestamp>1347994586195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 14:56:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347994674223-84</Id><Title>INTC downgrade</Title><Msg>Another rocket scientist analyst announces (after a 15 percent drop in share price) that the stock isn't worthy of a higher rating. These guys should start predicting sports outcomes after the games are over. Useless analysis at its finest!!</Msg><Username>bcjt51</Username><Timestamp>1347994674223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 14:57:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347995579230-85</Id><Title>Apple spent 500M to say F**u to NVIDIA</Title><Msg>See below.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1347995579230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 15:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347996252922-86</Id><Topic><Title>Apple spent $500M to say ‘f*** you’ to Intel</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347987575717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are such a two-year old. I don't blame you for being frustrated though. Intel is preparing to drive a stake through Nvidia's graphics business. ARMs fabrication roadmap is a disaster. Over half the people in the US were unhappy with the new iPhone. And today Motorola is replacing ARM chips with those by Intel in a new smartphone release. It's not going well, is it, fanboi? In regards to your silly statement that Apple did chip design to send a message to Intel, it's a figment of your adolescent personality. First of all, it's chump change for Apple and they would throw it away in a heartbeat if they needed to in order to do a deal with Intel. And here's the thing you and Wall Street don't seem to be able to comprehend: It doesn't make any difference who designs them - someone still has to build them and the ARM foundries are going to be spending the next five years dealing with their fabrication debacle. Intel has built for the future while ARM (and Apple) are trying to live off the past. When has that ever worked in technology? Dunno, why don't you ask RIMM?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347996252922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 15:24:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347996932644-87</Id><Topic><Title>Apple spent $500M to say ‘f*** you’ to Intel</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1347987575717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The size is bigger than simply taking the Apple A5X processor (used in the new iPad) and shrinking it from a 45-nanometer manufacturing process to a 32-nanometer manufacturing process, which would normally result in a chip size of 82 square millimeters. To get to that larger size of 96 square millimeters, Gwennap said that Apple must have added a more powerful custom CPU core as well as a better image processor for the camera. And that is the nature of chip design." *** This could also be called "why fabrication is important". Otellini tried to explain it to analysts in one of the conference calls. You add more capability to processors and they get bigger. Did everyone get that? Wall Street, are you listening? They get bigger. So, unless you shrink the die size, you get big, fat, hot processors like the one in the new iPad. This, of course, is why ARM is in trouble as their fabrication will coast to a stop after 20nm, assuming they ever get there. And this is why Intel has such a huge advantage going forward as they have a clear path to 14, 10, 7 and 5nm die sizes. You want the big, fat, hot, slow ARM processor or you want the state-of-the-art from Intel. It's not a tough call. But you do have to be smarter than Gus Richard to grasp it...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347996932644</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 15:35:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347999655868-88</Id><Title>Who Are the 47 Percent Who Don't Pay Income Taxes?</Title><Msg>Well, half of them are elderly. And there are the 3,000 people who made more than $2,178,866 in 2011 (putting them in the top 0.1 percent of taxpayers), and yet paid no federal income taxes. Deadbeats...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347999655868</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 16:20:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348000327294-89</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola RAZR i review - Hands on with the fastest smartphone ever</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1347984112154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:01:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM supporters like to say the PC is dead because the tablet delivers "good enough" performance to substitute for the desktop. I happen to disagree with the premise but the "good enough" factor certainly applies to smartphones. At some point soon Intel will achieve enough graphics performance to satisfy 99% of the tasks people use smartphones for, just like embedded graphics in its third generation Core CPU's do for laptops.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1348000327294</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 16:32:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348002637676-90</Id><Topic><Title>Who Are the 47 Percent Who Don't Pay Income Taxes?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1347999655868</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 16:20:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And of course, they all did pay taxes, state, local, payroll via employers if any, sales, etc., not to mention large pending estate taxes for the rather more elderly. The taxes these people pay tend to be much larger percentages of their meager incomes than Mr. Romney's total (these various "incidental" taxes are very regressive) . Hmmmm... and wasn't it Romney who had $100 Million in his IRA and paid less than 15% in IRS taxes for many a year. Most of the 47% are eaking out an existence without medical insurance (until and if Obamacare kicks in), undereducation (have you looked at college tuitions lately, and also wondered what you're getting for that?) and most have served their country with distinction in the armed forces (or lost sons and daughters who have). DID MR ROMNEY SERVE HIS COUNTRY IN THE ARMED FORCES? In fact, Democrats have served at almost twice the per capita rate that republican have. Of the 47% are amongst the 20% poorest people we call "poverty." But, to quote one of Mr. Romney's relatives, "LET THEM EAT CAKE."</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348002637676</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 17:10:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348003078698-91</Id><Title>I hear the beginning of a rumbling sound....</Title><Msg>It's the early stages of panicky feelings in the guts of INTC analysts, CEO's and minions of ARMH, and shorts who read about RAZR i today. Just a kind of "out of sorts" feeling, and many will be hitting the local bars and saloons on the way home from work this evening so as not to bring their negativity home to their tenuous marriages. It's a nagging feeling, and many will not sleep so well tonight. They won't know quite why. But it's a rumbling sound.."sounds like a freight train in the distance," and it's getting louder by the day.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1348003078698</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 17:17:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348006166416-92</Id><Topic><Title>What we know about Vinnie_bagodonitz (also known as Lucy Nuff, Too funny, etc)</Title><Username>vinnie_bagofhotwind</Username><Timestamp>1347979014823</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:36:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's pretty funny. I laugh at people who completely missed the mobile computing revolution and whose stock is stuck in the $20's for the rest of time. The only smart INTC employees are the ones who bought AAPL stock.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1348006166416</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 18:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348006266106-93</Id><Topic><Title>Oops, we completely screwed the dog in the mobile market</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1347975525846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:38:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>alstanap, go scrounge some iPhone iv's from the dumpster.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1348006266106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 18:11:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348006864464-94</Id><Title>Here's Vinnie_baguhdonitz aka Lucy_nuff LOVING AMD at 40, LOL!</Title><Msg>Re: This is great By vinnie_baggadonitz . 8 years 5 months ago . Permalink Go to topic AMD is super strong today, considering the DJIA is in the toidy. Hey, Vincent ... learn how "don't" without a semicolon ... it'll really impress the ladies. BTW, the INTC chart looks friggin awesome if you turn your monitor upside down. Where'd you get that cool alias? VB</Msg><Username>vinnie_bagofhotwind</Username><Timestamp>1348006864464</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 18:21:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348007538734-95</Id><Title>Lucy_Nuff aka Vinny_baguhdonitz VERY LONG AMD from 40</Title><Msg>LOL! By vinnie_baggadonitz . 8 years 7 months ago . Permalink Go to topic Got it .. I do it a little differently. I have a cash account that I daytrade shorts with very specific chart patterns. Sometimes one a day, sometimes two, sometimes none. Then, I have a long account (stuffed with AMD and other things) that's like watching turtle races. I rarely touch it. Anyhow, I like your post about enjoying every day. Nobody ever went to the pine box wishing they'd spent more time at work. BTW, WIND and CAMP were one day moves, so save some time and don't bother looking into them. Best luck .. VB</Msg><Username>vinnie_bagofhotwind</Username><Timestamp>1348007538734</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 18:32:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348008559992-96</Id><Title>The Intel Jinge followed by a Smartphone commercial with Intel inside will drive the haters INSANE!</Title><Msg>LMAOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1348008559992</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 18:49:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348009087525-97</Id><Topic><Title>Here's Vinnie_baguhdonitz aka Lucy_nuff LOVING AMD at 40, LOL!</Title><Username>vinnie_bagofhotwind</Username><Timestamp>1348006864464</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 18:21:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, if you had as many stock options as I had, you'd be laughing at INTC-bots, too. Hey, do you have a compiler optimized for Turbo PASCAL on the Xeon Phi? I have an old version of PONG I'd like to spruce up.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1348009087525</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 18:58:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348009342764-98</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS OUR OBLIGATION TO OUR CHILDREN TO VOTE OBAMA OUT IN NOVEMBER.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347951727820</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 03:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a disaster for whole country. He has to be voted out. We will have to regroup and hopefully achieve prosperity in our country again. We only can hope romney can accomplish it. With 47% people not paying any taxes it will not be easy, but it can be done. People need jobs to pay taxes. With obama more people will be unemployed. As i said it is our obligation to vote obama out of the office.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1348009342764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 19:02:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348012379803-99</Id><Title>First ARM chips officially replaced by Intel chips today IN Getanid61's own back yard. Intel says F*&amp;% You to Getanid61 and ARMH</Title><Msg>Daggerrrrrr</Msg><Username>magicjackassss</Username><Timestamp>1348012379803</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 19:52:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348014318444-100</Id><Title>This is a simple concept many have difficulty understanding-</Title><Msg>Why do many so called rich people only pay 15% in taxes? IT IS BECAUSE THEIR MONEY IS INVESTED AND THEIR INCOME IS IN THE FORM OF DIVIDENDS. DIVIDENDS ARE TAXED AT A LOWER RATE THAN ORDINARY INCOME. (hope this puts to rest the idiots who are always crying that rich people pay a lower rate. If you want them to pay more, have congress increase the tax rate on dividends!)</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348014318444</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:25:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348016097018-101</Id><Title>Mr. East said Intel couldnt make a smartphone CPU...LOL</Title><Msg>The Motorola Razr is a top-of-the-line phone &amp; its Intel's 1st attempt. Wait until Clovertown 22nm SoCs early next year.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1348016097018</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:54:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348016398511-102</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS OUR OBLIGATION TO OUR CHILDREN TO VOTE OBAMA OUT IN NOVEMBER.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347951727820</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 03:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, you are a pro-wealthy Mormon. Thanks for that rant.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1348016398511</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348016705760-103</Id><Topic><Title>This is a simple concept many have difficulty understanding-</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348014318444</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally's gonna get what he wants........Rich paying more taxes, taking their money out of stocks as a result and Intel going to 15.</Msg><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1348016705760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 21:05:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348017319730-104</Id><Topic><Title>This is a simple concept many have difficulty understanding-</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348014318444</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt Romney hides money in off shore accounts, where the tax rate is really low. Rich people hire people to evade tax laws. It's an old game Stop with the verbal diarrhea. If you think rich people are philanthropic, send them money and see what happens. In Oregon, INTC managers often buy so-called hazelnut farms in order to get around the land restrictions. Common knowledge. Half the grade 10's and above are, "hazelnut farmers." Get off the soap box.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1348017319730</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 21:15:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348020389787-105</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. East said Intel couldnt make a smartphone CPU...LOL</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1348016097018</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:54:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I want an Intel Razr. When are they coming to the U.S. ? Next year on 22nm ?</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1348020389787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:06:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348021594184-106</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. East said Intel couldnt make a smartphone CPU...LOL</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1348016097018</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:54:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am pretty sure you mean Clover Trail Clovertown (dumb Intel code names) was a 2006 65nm Xeon server chip.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1348021594184</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:26:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348022412828-107</Id><Title>Great video n AMD...</Title><Msg>Yes I knw INTC longs you are eating AMD's lunch. However, for a trade TheContrarianTrader lays out a really good trade thesis so although I can't share you can do a search since the video is on his home page/blog.</Msg><Username>blewthroughstop</Username><Timestamp>1348022412828</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:40:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348022609158-108</Id><Topic><Title>This is a simple concept many have difficulty understanding-</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1348014318444</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt that you know any more about Mitt's financials than anyone else. You know what has been released and what you "think" you know. Many of those "tax evasion consultants" make recommendations that ultimately result in IRS assessments and followup tax bills. Romney either paid no taxes or his 2009 taxes are under audit or have been assessed extra taxes. I really think that Romney moved his residence to the Cayman Islands and did not file taxes in the US. I want to see his long form. "Common knowledge" ? It MUST be common knowledge if you know it. You sound like a nut farmer too.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1348022609158</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:43:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>