<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-06"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354783997804-1</Id><Title>If you are long INTC and worried - Listen to Paul Otellini at the Bernstein Conference</Title><Msg>The audio is at the intcDOTcom website. I recommend listening to the whole thing but if you are strapped for time, then listen to the part where he talks about Intel's manufacturing process...beginning at the 34 minute mark. Very interesting and clearly shows how confident he is in Intel's lead in the manufacturing process and the advantages it brings.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354783997804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 03:53:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354784405222-2</Id><Topic><Title>If you are long INTC and worried - Listen to Paul Otellini at the Bernstein Conference</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354783997804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 03:53:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, I think it was a slip-up on his part when he said: "And our foundry customers aren’t going to announce that they’ve moved until they’ve moved because it would hurt them at their previous suppliers. So for obvious reasons, this has been a lower-profile kind of deal."...He backed up really quick right after that and started to talk more generically from there on. Judge for yourself.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354784405222</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 04:00:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354785554418-3</Id><Topic><Title>10W to 13W, with a twist</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1354753729197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 19:28:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting numbers. For comparison, the A15 in the Nexus 10. ARM ARMv7 @ 1.70 GHz ,1 processor, 2 cores Integer Processor integer performance 1776 Floating Point Processor floating point performance 3963 Memory Memory performance 2758 Stream Memory bandwidth performance 1052 Although the A15 is only 2 threads, Ivy Bridge kills it on memory bandwidth and Integer performance but not in float. Will be interesting to see what the power consumption of the A15 is in reality.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1354785554418</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 04:19:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354786352315-4</Id><Title>Buy intel after it spends the $6B</Title><Msg>on an aquisition</Msg><Username>scott4usa</Username><Timestamp>1354786352315</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 04:32:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354800366400-5</Id><Title>'Round n round she goes, where she stops, only the manipulators know...</Title><Msg>The big boys with the money, are ripping it up everyday... while the average fella is left bleeding on the floor...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354800366400</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 08:26:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354800624501-6</Id><Topic><Title>POS down again</Title><Username>pq.8989</Username><Timestamp>1354760538973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 21:22:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Manipulation... also Q4 2012 and Q1 2013 don't look good, but somewhere around Q2 and Q3 2013, things will start to look better</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354800624501</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 08:30:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354801697386-7</Id><Title>Low stock price = More shares retired = High Stock price when economy expands</Title><Msg>Intel is becoming a stronger company through all this mess. We aer down from 7 billion shares to 5 billion and if they retire 300m more, we'll obviously be down to 4.7 billion.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1354801697386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 08:48:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354801887708-8</Id><Topic><Title>10W to 13W, with a twist</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1354753729197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 19:28:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The single core floating performance difference is focused in the blur/sharpen image benchmark. I have not looked at the code to see how the geekbench compiler generated the code. hand typed so might have a typo Single core SCALAR Results Benchmark iPAD-ARM Lenovo-Intel Mandelbrot 648 1311 Dot Product 718 742 LU Decomposition 501 2510 Primality Test 2759 3740 Sharpen Image 2243 768 Blur Image 2674 1744 Lenovo Intel Single core vector Dot Product 3991 Multi core SCALAR Results, you have to normalize 50% to iPad favor Benchmark iPAD-ARM Lenovo-Intel Mandelbrot 1306 5294 Dot Product 1511 3117 LU Decomposition 918 2924 Primality Test 4108 7343 Sharpen Image 4441 2633 Blur Image 5320 5945</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354801887708</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 08:51:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354803899443-9</Id><Title>Intel's Ownership of McAfee Software</Title><Msg>Seems the namesake on the run and now seeking asylum in Guatemala isn't exactly good PR for the brand...???</Msg><Username>ibdtrader</Username><Timestamp>1354803899443</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 09:24:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354805280251-10</Id><Topic><Title>If you are long INTC and worried - Listen to Paul Otellini at the Bernstein Conference</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354783997804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 03:53:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I liked this part: "We are increasing the lead that we have in the industry..... We did High K 4 years ago @ 45 nm. People are barely figuring that out today. Trigate, we are at our 2nd generation. No one's figured that out. They aren't gonna figure that out." He actually said this. They aren't gonna figure that out.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1354805280251</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 09:48:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354805518805-11</Id><Topic><Title>If you are long INTC and worried - Listen to Paul Otellini at the Bernstein Conference</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354783997804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 03:53:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Question: " Why should investors buy Intel stock?" "It's a bargain... When you see traction with Window's based tablets, then the tablet argument goes away. When you see Intel based Android phones, that one goes away." So he is saying what kind of negative arguments are currently keeping the stock down and that Intel will eventually disspell those arguments. In the meantime, the stock is said to be a bargain by the CEO himself. And they usually don't comment on stock price at all. Must be so cheap that it warranted a statement like that from the CEO.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1354805518805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 09:51:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354806044088-12</Id><Topic><Title>10W to 13W, with a twist</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1354753729197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 19:28:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FROM ZDNET, SEPTEMBER 2012, ON THE INTEL IDF. Intel gave two Haswell demonstrations. In the first, he compared a Haswell-based Ultrabook to a reference system using an Ivy Bridge processor that consumes about the same power. The Haswell system delivered a 2x increase in graphics performance in the same power, he said. The difference in the graphics performance was obvious. This is especially significant because the current 3rd-generation Core processors, or Ivy Bridge, already delivered a significant increase in graphics. Perlmutter joked that this is something people expect from Intel but it is no "small exercise." In the second demonstration, Intel compared a current 17-watt Ivy Bridge systems to a 4th-generation Core processor running at half the power (about 7.8 watts in the demo). The Haswell system delivered the same level of performance, he said.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1354806044088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 10:00:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354806573652-13</Id><Title>Intel smartphones for less than $150 in India by mid-2013</Title><Msg>US-based chipmaker Intel Thursday said it would develop smartphones with its chips, priced Rs 7,000 onwards, in India in partnership with handset makers. The touch screen-based smartphones, based on Google's Android operating system, would be available in the market by the middle of 2013, Intel South Asia Managing Director, Sales and Marketing Debjani Ghosh said on the sidelines of INFOCOM 2012 here. In India at present, Intel has a partnership with Lava. 'Lava Xolo', which features Intel's mobile chip, was launched early this year. "The first handset with Lava that we launched was a premium one. We learnt that it was important to have a portfolio and offer choice to the user. We will not have entry-level handsets but our smartphone range will be priced upwards of Rs 7,000," she said. Ghosh, however, did not divulge whether the partnerships would be with homegrown or International equipment makers.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1354806573652</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 10:09:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354808854637-14</Id><Topic><Title>If you are long INTC and worried - Listen to Paul Otellini at the Bernstein Conference</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354783997804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 03:53:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"bacbacker" and "paul.ottelini" are both Wallis aliases. One alias sets up the questions and interest in the original messge and the other alias responds. This guy knows no bounds. Wallis is the KING OF PUMPERS! 24x7! HE NEVER STOPS!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354808854637</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 10:47:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354809469908-15</Id><Topic><Title>Here come the sellers, down on big volume</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1354737028477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 14:50:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL</Msg><Username>coinloser77</Username><Timestamp>1354809469908</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 10:57:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354809841866-16</Id><Topic><Title>Paid basher Lucy Nuff's aliases. Let's track him down and expose whoever it is that's paying him.</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349291135816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Notice how his posts stop abrubtly at 4PM EST as he clocks out and fights through traffic to get back to his Duplex.</Msg><Username>coinloser77</Username><Timestamp>1354809841866</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:04:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354810096186-17</Id><Topic><Title>Didja let Gold Man and Juhhny steal you're shares?</Title><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1354289436095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:30:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well didja, you pikers? Truly classic.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1354810096186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:08:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354810187846-18</Id><Title>Gamers rest easy, Intel's got your back</Title><Msg>Intel to continue making socketed CPUs for “foreseeable future” by Mark Tyson on 6 December 2012, 11:30 Recently we covered a news rumour emanating from Japan about Intel discontinuing support for socketed CPUs. It turns out that it was a tsunami in a tea-cup, as Haswell isn’t going to be Intel’s last range of swappable CPUs. This comes from the horse’s mouth, via an email from an Intel spokesman to Maximum PC. Intel’s email The rumour that Intel PCs would move to soldered on BGA CPUs only, following the Haswell line of chips, has been scotched. In an email, Intel spokesman Daniel Snyder told Maximum PC that “Intel remains committed to the growing desktop enthusiast and channel markets, and will continue to offer socketed parts in the LGA package for the foreseeable future for our customers and the Enthusiast DIY market”. Snyder ended his comment with a “however” statement, he wrote “However, Intel cannot comment on specific long-term product roadmap plans at this time, but will disclose more details later per our normal communication process.” The statement is reassuring but ultimately non-committal, but how far ahead can you expect a commercial enterprise to make commitments for? Businesses are there to make money, not merely to keep promises beyond that of a product guarantee or contractual agreement.</Msg><Username>coinloser77</Username><Timestamp>1354810187846</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:09:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354810241168-19</Id><Topic><Title>Paid basher Lucy Nuff's aliases. Let's track him down and expose whoever it is that's paying him.</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349291135816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he was trying to get there to stop the foreclosure auction.</Msg><Username>pumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1354810241168</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:10:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354811585388-20</Id><Title>Buyback</Title><Msg>They have not even announced the amount of buy back. This will be coming soon. Maybe cash payout or increase of dividend. Look out shorties!! Bottom is in.</Msg><Username>tmurphy227</Username><Timestamp>1354811585388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:33:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354811732580-21</Id><Title>Big foundry deal definitely coming</Title><Msg>I just listened to Paul Otellini at the Bernstein Conference....From the way he said it, one of the customer could be Apple....but it sounds like there will be MULTIPLE large customers. For sure some big foundry deal coming.</Msg><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354811732580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:35:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354812236092-22</Id><Title>If the market drops 1000 points how low will INTC go from here? anyone</Title><Msg>If the market drops 1000 points how low will INTC go from here? anyone</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1354812236092</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:43:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354812583111-23</Id><Title>Buy and hold here</Title><Msg>The volume has been high in the last month or so. I think whoever buys at his level will be awarded. I believe this is the lows for the next few years and with yield of 4.5%, whoever buys here won't be selling for a long time. With $6 Billion in buyback coming and more from the current program, the float will skrink substantially and stock will soar!</Msg><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354812583111</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:49:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354812630535-24</Id><Topic><Title>Big foundry deal definitely coming</Title><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354811732580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:35:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wildandwacky is a wild and wacky Wallis alias. wildandwallis! HI-HO Weaverino! TOOOOO FUNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354812630535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:50:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354812786261-25</Id><Topic><Title>If the market drops 1000 points how low will INTC go from here? anyone</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1354812236092</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:43:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would like to know, anyone have anything</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1354812786261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:53:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354812847140-26</Id><Topic><Title>Buy and hold here</Title><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354812583111</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:49:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think whoever buys at his level will be awarded. --------------- If I buy Intel shares today will I look fine in 6 months, Wallwad? TOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354812847140</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:54:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354812948443-27</Id><Topic><Title>Didja let Gold Man and Juhhny steal you're shares?</Title><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1354289436095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:30:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I truly wish I had sold much higher and bought back in below 20. I did buy more, but how do you call someone who sold for a profit and bought back more and cheaper shares a piker?</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1354812948443</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:55:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354812958361-28</Id><Title>keeb</Title><Msg>Hope you didn't miss your chance to pick up INTC at a great price. 4.6 % divvie and growing.</Msg><Username>soldi_reali</Username><Timestamp>1354812958361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:55:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354813245010-29</Id><Title>if Ivy Bridge can go down to 7W, how much can Haswell go?</Title><Msg>I'm not technical, but wouldn't Haswell be able to down further?</Msg><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354813245010</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:00:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354813268498-30</Id><Topic><Title>If the market drops 1000 points how low will INTC go from here? anyone</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1354812236092</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:43:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A 1,000 point drop on the DJI from $13,047 would be about 7%.Intel would drop about 7% too but probabably a little less due to dividend yield and buy back. 7% of $20.20 is $1.41 which would mean that Intel would drop to the $18.79 area on a 1:1 basis.. I suspect that buy back and short covering would probably stop its decline at $19.37.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354813268498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:01:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354813375445-31</Id><Topic><Title>Buy and hold here</Title><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354812583111</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:49:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think whoever buys at his level will be awarded</Msg><Username>wallisweiner</Username><Timestamp>1354813375445</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:02:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354813638474-32</Id><Topic><Title>If the market drops 1000 points how low will INTC go from here? anyone</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1354812236092</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:43:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1354813638474</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:07:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354813684413-33</Id><Title>Longs, we did it!</Title><Msg>Keep posting positive articles! The big boys are reading!!! Yesssssssss!</Msg><Username>kermit_the_hogg</Username><Timestamp>1354813684413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:08:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354813727710-34</Id><Topic><Title>Didja let Gold Man and Juhhny steal you're shares?</Title><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1354289436095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:30:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>STRONG agree. Juhhny has GOT to GO!</Msg><Username>jeangenou_pomme_verte</Username><Timestamp>1354813727710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:08:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354814321795-35</Id><Topic><Title>Big foundry deal definitely coming</Title><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354811732580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:35:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No matter who wrote it.....its true.....intc is a great hold here.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1354814321795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:18:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354814427794-36</Id><Title>What is the difference between these two symbols: AAPL and QQQQ?</Title><Msg>Is there a mistake at the exchange? I can't seem to find any discernible difference between these two issues. Any help would be appreciated. Best, KTH</Msg><Username>kermit_the_hogg</Username><Timestamp>1354814427794</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:20:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354814731563-37</Id><Topic><Title>Big foundry deal definitely coming</Title><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354811732580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:35:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'great hold'? is that like 'super average'? who gets excited about a hold rating? the bonus is the 'award' that someone mentioned here earlier. as a shareholder i'm looking forward to receiving a leg lamp from the company. that will be a 'major award'</Msg><Username>wallisweiner</Username><Timestamp>1354814731563</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:25:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354814911304-38</Id><Topic><Title>Didja let Gold Man and Juhhny steal you're shares?</Title><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1354289436095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:30:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"but how do you call someone who sold for a profit and bought back more and cheaper shares a piker?" I was referring to those who sold on the Gold Man downgrade when I used the term pikers.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1354814911304</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:28:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354815534692-39</Id><Topic><Title>All Bush Tax Cuts will Expire, thanks to GOP</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354734195405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 14:03:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am soooo happy when att4glte is spewing at me in here...then I know, at least at that moment, he's not out at some school yard trying to pick up some little boys to diddle.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354815534692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:38:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354815738047-40</Id><Title>After the manipulators are done we should close out the day around 19.50...</Title><Msg>Just sayin...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354815738047</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:42:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354816003193-41</Id><Topic><Title>Didja let Gold Man and Juhhny steal you're shares?</Title><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1354289436095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:30:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who's Juhhny???</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354816003193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:46:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354816375795-42</Id><Topic><Title>What is the difference between these two symbols: AAPL and QQQQ?</Title><Username>kermit_the_hogg</Username><Timestamp>1354814427794</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:20:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there is no qqqq</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1354816375795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:52:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354816937282-43</Id><Topic><Title>if Ivy Bridge can go down to 7W, how much can Haswell go?</Title><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354813245010</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:00:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FROM ZDNET, SEPTEMBER 11,2012 REPORTING ON THE INTEL IDF Intel gave two Haswell demonstrations. In the first, he compared a Haswell-based Ultrabook to a reference system using an Ivy Bridge processor that consumes about the same power. The Haswell system delivered a 2x increase in graphics performance in the same power, he said. The difference in the graphics performance was obvious. This is especially significant because the current 3rd-generation Core processors, or Ivy Bridge, already delivered a significant increase in graphics. Perlmutter joked that this is something people expect from Intel but it is no "small exercise." In the second demonstration, Intel compared a current 17-watt Ivy Bridge systems to a 4th-generation Core processor running at half the power (about 7.8 watts in the demo). The Haswell system delivered the same level of performance, he said. Perlmutter said that Haswell was designed with "mobility in mind" and is meant to work with everything from "sleek tablets" to Ultrabooks to "eventually" high-performance desktops and workstations. The first systems based on Haswell CPUs are expected to ship in the first half of next year.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1354816937282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:02:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354817387322-44</Id><Topic><Title>if Ivy Bridge can go down to 7W, how much can Haswell go?</Title><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354813245010</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:00:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm MUCH more interested in Conroe.</Msg><Username>kermit_the_hogg</Username><Timestamp>1354817387322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:09:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354817825512-45</Id><Topic><Title>If the market drops 1000 points how low will INTC go from here? anyone</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1354812236092</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:43:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>intel is already battered. will not drop as much as ultra high pe stocks like armh and fb.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1354817825512</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:17:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354817843799-46</Id><Topic><Title>After the manipulators are done we should close out the day around 19.50...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354815738047</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:42:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you so knowing?</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1354817843799</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:17:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354817915207-47</Id><Title>We need to go over the cliff to get the real cuts that are needed, CUT,CUT,CUT and CUT some more</Title><Msg>We need to go over the cliff to get the real cuts that are needed, CUT,CUT,CUT and CUT some more</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1354817915207</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:18:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354818021050-48</Id><Topic><Title>Didja let Gold Man and Juhhny steal you're shares?</Title><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1354289436095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:30:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Who's Juhhny???" Some guy who used to post here back in the day. Last we heard, though, he got an HVAC certificate from Apollo Collich under the tutelage of famed HVAC instructor Frank Dvorak got a job installing window fans with the Hair Bawl Dooooosh HVAC and Trading Group, Ltd. down in Kentucy.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1354818021050</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:20:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354818125762-49</Id><Topic><Title>After the manipulators are done we should close out the day around 19.50...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354815738047</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:42:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pivot point is still $19.87. R1 is $20.00 R2 is $20.15 I think it will close at R2 today, $20.15, since it has been trading around R2 and well above it.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354818125762</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:22:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354818322990-50</Id><Topic><Title>After the manipulators are done we should close out the day around 19.50...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354815738047</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:42:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, we both hope so, but the way these bstards manipulate the market, nothing would surprise me...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354818322990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:25:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354819070642-51</Id><Topic><Title>We need to go over the cliff to get the real cuts that are needed, CUT,CUT,CUT and CUT some more</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1354817915207</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:18:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flat cut 15% on everything to start, Cut 3 % next year , then if they save over 3% in fraud they don't get a 3 % cut next year and for every year after. So they have to work on get the fraud out of the system</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1354819070642</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:37:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354820665213-52</Id><Title>Where is "too funny" today?</Title><Msg>Surprised he hasn't dug up some article with a negative spin to insinuate that anyone holding is completely and totally screwed. He would gleefully add that we will see single digits soon. J. Blown</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354820665213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 14:04:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354821431368-53</Id><Topic><Title>We need to go over the cliff to get the real cuts that are needed, CUT,CUT,CUT and CUT some more</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1354817915207</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:18:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Start with $500 million in military cuts.</Msg><Username>psuedonym5</Username><Timestamp>1354821431368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 14:17:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354821436503-54</Id><Topic><Title>Where is "too funny" today?</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354820665213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 14:04:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's just cross our fingers and hope that the INTC rally continues... but I would really like to see a couple of plus $1 days...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354821436503</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 14:17:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354822012187-55</Id><Title>TSM &amp; INTC</Title><Msg>TSM = $16.97/share PE=16.48 Div=2.3% INTC = $19.91/share PE=8.69 Div=4.6%. TSM can’t make enough 28nm for customers and INTC has a surplus of 22nm. Which is at true fair value? If INTC had the same PE as TSM, INTC would be at $37.75/share and over 2.3% dividend. Feel free to sell, the big boys really want your shares. The street also has a buy rating on TSM. Could that be why Jimmy boy is so negative on INTC?</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1354822012187</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 14:26:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354822045011-56</Id><Topic><Title>Where is "too funny" today?</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354820665213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 14:04:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and about a zillion others. Probably not recommend buy at this time but wait until fiscal cliff plays out. If already in, then of course, hold. J. Blown</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354822045011</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 14:27:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354823547976-57</Id><Title>Intel to 1-Hunnert dollars +</Title><Msg>This will be fun.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354823547976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 14:52:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354824356201-58</Id><Topic><Title>Longs, we did it!</Title><Username>kermit_the_hogg</Username><Timestamp>1354813684413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:08:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>8-21-2012 was when the 50 DMA fell below the 200 DMA. It was all downhill from there. If INTC can just close above 20.20, buyers will start coming back in. The volume should really start picking up when it breaks the 50 DMA which is just a dollar away. Dec and Jan is the best seasonal time to own INTC shares.</Msg><Username>tlee22202</Username><Timestamp>1354824356201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:05:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354824440566-59</Id><Title>Intel No Longer a Teenager</Title><Msg>Lucy resumes the fetal position...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354824440566</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:07:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354824642546-60</Id><Title>$24-28 on this mini rally</Title><Msg>Very doable.</Msg><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354824642546</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:10:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354824654204-61</Id><Topic><Title>Intel No Longer a Teenager</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354824440566</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:07:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so how's it feel holding since 24.00 in 2010</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1354824654204</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:10:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354824668458-62</Id><Title>IEDM preview: The main attraction this year is a talk by Intel</Title><Msg>The main attraction this year is a talk by Intel on 22nm SoC technology using its 3-D transistors, generally known as FinFETs, for mobile processors. Intel's Ivy Bridge Core processors for laptops, desktops and servers already use this technology, but this will be the first time the company has talked in detail about how its 22nm technology with FinFETs will translate to Atom mobile processors for the increasingly important smartphone and tablet markets. Intel's current Atom processors are still stuck on the older 32nm planar technology, but in mobile the company has set an aggressive goal of shrinking its chips once a year. Although it is still playing catch-up to a host of ARM competitors, Intel insists that ultimately the best transistor will win, and this presentation may be the first indication of whether it can really deliver on this. From ZDNet</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354824668458</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:11:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354824732331-63</Id><Topic><Title>Paid basher Lucy Nuff's aliases. Let's track him down and expose whoever it is that's paying him.</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349291135816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Add wdblawgrow and harlan_titusville to the list.</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1354824732331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:12:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354824855810-64</Id><Title>Intel committed to socketed CPUs</Title><Msg>Told you it was a silly rumour Rumourmongers used to be better at what they did. Earlier this week we saw Nokia debunk daft rumours of a possible Android phone and now it’s Intel’s turn to kill an equally outlandish rumour. Last week it was reported that Intel could ditch socketed processors as early as 2014. For some reason the rumour got a lot of traction and Intel was eventually forced to respond. In a chat with Maximum PC, Intel spokesman Daniel Snyder said the chipmaker will remain committed to desktop enthusiast and channel markets and that it will “continue to offer socketed parts in the LGA package for the foreseeable future for our customers and the Enthusiast DIY market.” Snyder did note that Intel cannot comment on specific long-term product roadmaps, but even so it is quite obvious that Intel will continue developing LGA processors for some time, depending on how we interpret “foreseeable future.” Of course, the low-end market is a different story. Both Intel and AMD have been churning out cheap ITX boards based on Atom and Brazos chips for a couple of years now, but using the same approach with pricey high-end components would be very difficult indeed. From FudZilla</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354824855810</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:14:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354825470765-65</Id><Topic><Title>Intel No Longer a Teenager</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354824440566</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:07:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like to see this somehow nursed to $33.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354825470765</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:24:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354825529837-66</Id><Title>Intel Labs unveils stage 1 results of R&amp;D cooperation with ITRI</Title><Msg>Intel CTO Justin Rattner on December 4 unveiled the results of R&amp;D cooperation between Intel Labs and the Taiwan government-sponsored Industrial Technology Research Institute (ITRI). The partnership has developed a super-speed, power-saving experimental memory array which is expected to be applied to ultrabooks, tablets, smartphones and mega data centers for cloud computing.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354825529837</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:25:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354825723716-67</Id><Topic><Title>Intel No Longer a Teenager</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354824440566</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:07:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Like to see this somehow nursed to $33." [Are you crazy??? That will takes weeks!!!]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354825723716</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:28:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354825821834-68</Id><Topic><Title>We need to go over the cliff to get the real cuts that are needed, CUT,CUT,CUT and CUT some more</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1354817915207</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 13:18:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no 15% on everything and that would be about 120 billion on defense cuts, I mean 15% on everything</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1354825821834</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:30:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354825840334-69</Id><Title>Both deals make sense</Title><Msg>My colleague Peter Clarke has been hearing rumors Intel will make high-end router chips for Cisco. Turley is hearing rumors Intel might make Apple’s A series mobile applications processors. Both deals make sense. The Cisco and Apple chips are strictly for internal use only, so there’s no competitive threat for Intel. To the contrary, both Apple and Cisco have the potential to be much larger customers of Intel than they are today, potential a foundry relationship could nurture. From EETimes</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354825840334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:30:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354825883252-70</Id><Topic><Title>Intel No Longer a Teenager</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354824440566</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:07:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not a teen, at least for the moment, but it is still a MINOR in more ways than one! PUMP, PUMP, PUMP! PUMP IT UP, Walldork! HI-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1354825883252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:31:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354826141305-71</Id><Topic><Title>Where is "too funny" today?</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354820665213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 14:04:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is a #$%$. ( I mean that with all due respect, of course).</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354826141305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:35:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354826362995-72</Id><Topic><Title>Both deals make sense</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354825840334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:30:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple chips are strictly for internal use only, so there’s no competitive threat for Intel.???</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1354826362995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:39:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354827098497-73</Id><Topic><Title>$24-28 on this mini rally</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354824642546</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:10:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>by year end, yes very doable... however, unless something AMAZING happens... with the volatility in the market, it's just not going to happen... however seeing those prices by mid to end next year seems very plausible... however I think the congress and president intentionally intend to push us over the cliff, because they really WANT to raise taxes on everyone...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354827098497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:51:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354827210362-74</Id><Topic><Title>Both deals make sense</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354825840334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:30:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My colleague Peter Clarke ----------- Peter Clarke the fiction author? No surprise that you'd be friends with another writer of fiction. Fiction is another way of saying beeee-essss. Does Peter know about all the beeee-essss that you sling around here? TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354827210362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:53:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354827514565-75</Id><Topic><Title>Both deals make sense</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354825840334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:30:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey there, too funny- you're heroic and much loved (NOT!)</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354827514565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:58:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354827880994-76</Id><Topic><Title>$24-28 on this mini rally</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354824642546</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:10:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama, fool that he is apparantly seems to think "we can afford to go over the cliff". Must be nice to get lifetime benefits as an idealoque</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1354827880994</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 16:04:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354828067542-77</Id><Topic><Title>Paid basher Lucy Nuff's aliases. Let's track him down and expose whoever it is that's paying him.</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349291135816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think he's then trolling for the sixth graders at the local middle schools.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354828067542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 16:07:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354828116168-78</Id><Topic><Title>After the manipulators are done we should close out the day around 19.50...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354815738047</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:42:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You called that one, spot on!</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354828116168</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 16:08:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354828759508-79</Id><Topic><Title>After the manipulators are done we should close out the day around 19.50...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354815738047</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:42:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>50% luck. Intel honor the piviot point, R and S levels frequently but not always. Since it was trading above the R2, I just expected it so sink back to it. 50% guess. Intel trading seems to be strongly influenced by some programmed trading aglorithm. I don't thnk programmed trading is the same as manipulation. It seems to use Piviot point as rails for weighting its trading. I don't know whether it is the buyer or seller or both. Share buy backs can continue up to the last 10 minutes of trading since Intel has a market cap of more than $150m. Otherwise, the last hour would be off limits.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354828759508</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 16:19:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354828884236-80</Id><Topic><Title>Paid basher Lucy Nuff's aliases. Let's track him down and expose whoever it is that's paying him.</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349291135816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No such thing as a paid basher that I know of,he's just some mentally unbalanced old F with way to much time on his hands.Just ignore him,his signature stupidity gives everyone of his minted IDs away every time.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1354828884236</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 16:21:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354828898664-81</Id><Title>How to win the war on drugs....</Title><Msg>send Wall Street and the big bank boys to Gitmo. We certainly won't miss them, especially the analysts.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354828898664</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 16:21:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354829773538-82</Id><Topic><Title>After the manipulators are done we should close out the day around 19.50...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1354815738047</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:42:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hmmmm, maybe you are not in the know....lol</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1354829773538</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 16:36:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354830456598-83</Id><Topic><Title>10W to 13W, with a twist</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1354753729197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 19:28:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>' bringing 13W parts down to just 7W will degrade performance, but at least it’s possible.' The performance at 10w will be the same performance at 7W, the only difference is that the 7W variants will need a better cooling solution to reduce the max junction temperature from 105c to 80c. Also note these are just harvested Ivy Bridge dies still on the high performance 22nm process, these wattages could go even lower with Intel's upcoming 22nm SoC LP process if they needed to but they won't need to as 22nm Haswell and 14nm Broadwell are following on 6-18 month cadences to still compete against the same A15/A6/S4 ARM processors only just on 28/20nm . The lowly 1.1 GHz Pentium 2129Y will be the cheapest lowest power Ivy Bridge variant yet still have too much processing power for ARM's greatest processors in most meaningful applications, this is a serious competition only in the deranged mind of some dumb ANALysts, it will be a turkey shoot in reality as each new year's wave of Tick-Tock processors take aim and take out these brash ARM newcomers. http://seekingalpha.com/article/1048411-intel-s-latest-low-power-battle-plans?source=yahoo</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1354830456598</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 16:47:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354831298699-84</Id><Title>AMD sent to the Dinosaur Boneyard soon..</Title><Msg>then things will rock and roll</Msg><Username>trader.quick</Username><Timestamp>1354831298699</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 17:01:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354831747026-85</Id><Topic><Title>10W to 13W, with a twist</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1354753729197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 19:28:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>' bringing 13W parts down to just 7W will degrade performance, but at least it’s possible.' The performance at 10w will be the same performance at 7W, the only difference is that the 7W variants will need a better cooling solution to reduce the max junction temperature from 105c to 80c. Also note these are just harvested Ivy Bridge dies still on the high performance 22nm process, these wattages could go even lower with Intel's upcoming 22nm SoC LP process if they needed to but they won't need to as 22nm Haswell and 14nm Broadwell are following on 6-18 month cadences to still compete against the same A15/A6/S4 ARM processors only just on 28/20nm . The lowly 1.1 GHz Pentium 2129Y will be the cheapest lowest power Ivy Bridge variant yet still have too much processing power for ARM's greatest processors in most meaningful applications, this is a serious competition only in the silly minds of some dumb ANALysts, it will be a turkey shoot in reality as each new year's wave of Tick-Tock processors take aim and take out these brash ARM newcomers. http://seekingalpha.com/article/1048411-intel-s-latest-low-power-battle-plans?source=yahoo</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1354831747026</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 17:09:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354832098655-86</Id><Topic><Title>10W to 13W, with a twist</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1354753729197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 19:28:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>' bringing 13W parts down to just 7W will degrade performance, but at least it’s possible.' The performance at 10w will be the same performance at 7W, the only difference is that the 7W variants will need a better cooling solution to reduce the max junction temperature from 105c to 80c. Also note these are just harvested Ivy Bridge dies still on the high performance 22nm process, these wattages could go even lower with Intel's upcoming 22nm SoC LP process if they needed to but they won't need to as 22nm Haswell and 14nm Broadwell are following on 6-18 month cadences to still compete against the same A15/A6/S4 ARM processors only just on 28/20nm . The lowly 1.1 GHz Pentium 2129Y will be the cheapest lowest power Ivy Bridge variant yet still have too much processing power for ARM's greatest processors in most meaningful applications, this is a serious competition only in the silly minds of some dumbo ANALysts, it will be a turkey shoot in reality as each new year's wave of Tick-Tock processors take aim and take out these brash ARM newcomers as they pop up. http://seekingalpha.com/article/1048411-intel-s-latest-low-power-battle-plans?source=yahoo</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1354832098655</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 17:14:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354834338047-87</Id><Title>Get in &amp; fasten your seatbelts</Title><Msg>This stock is ready to take-off</Msg><Username>jsf34062</Username><Timestamp>1354834338047</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 17:52:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354835536477-88</Id><Topic><Title>Buyback</Title><Username>tmurphy227</Username><Timestamp>1354811585388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:33:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Borrowing money to pay dividends or buy back stock is not s bullish indicator.</Msg><Username>scott_1234567890</Username><Timestamp>1354835536477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 18:12:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354835751644-89</Id><Topic><Title>Buyback</Title><Username>tmurphy227</Username><Timestamp>1354811585388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:33:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everything thinks that borrowing money to buyback stock is bullish. Seems to me they all think Intel knows something the rest of us are just beginning to know.</Msg><Username>stok1mom</Username><Timestamp>1354835751644</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 18:15:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354836944141-90</Id><Topic><Title>Buyback</Title><Username>tmurphy227</Username><Timestamp>1354811585388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:33:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry mom and scott, but when interest rates are low you use your leverage if you are a huge company, and that's what they are doing. A great article was on SA yesterday detailing why it was such a stellar move to issue the bonds.</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1354836944141</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 18:35:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354836971147-91</Id><Topic><Title>Buyback</Title><Username>tmurphy227</Username><Timestamp>1354811585388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:33:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets see borrow at really low rates, buy back stock when its 50% off its highs and probably undervalued...... I dont see a problem with that.</Msg><Username>floaty123457</Username><Timestamp>1354836971147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 18:36:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354839608088-92</Id><Title>Yahoo Finance dividend information is WRONG. It's 22.5 cents per quarter.</Title><Msg>Please post correct information, Yahoo!</Msg><Username>nickster135796</Username><Timestamp>1354839608088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:20:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354839865807-93</Id><Topic><Title>10W to 13W, with a twist</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1354753729197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 19:28:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A15 core has fused multiply-accumulate. That's why it's so competitive on FPU performance. Haswell will double these synthetic figures.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1354839865807</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:24:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354839871388-94</Id><Title>Paul O on Wed about Apple?</Title><Msg>Regarding making chips for Apple, Otellini said: "That would be an interesting model. He added more color to the Intel as manufacturer for others idea: As you know it takes a while to move your designs over, to design them under our process, for us to be able to bring them in house and so forth and our foundry customers aren't going to announce that they've moved until they've moved because it would hurt them at their current suppliers." ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- SO--you will wake up one morning this summer and BOOM, Apple will announce it is making chips in Intel fabs.</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1354839871388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:24:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354840005659-95</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo Finance dividend information is WRONG. It's 22.5 cents per quarter.</Title><Username>nickster135796</Username><Timestamp>1354839608088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:20:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>duuuuuhhhhhhhhh. stupid iS as sTUpid DoEs. (hint: divide by 4...oh, I suppose you don't understand what that means)</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1354840005659</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:26:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354840536393-96</Id><Title>AMDroadkill and Flumoxed show up at the same time......</Title><Msg>Next, a cornholer will show up! Shocking! SMH......</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354840536393</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:35:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354841033645-97</Id><Title>Telegram for Getanid 16 - Intel dropping ATOM bombs on ARM microprocessors</Title><Msg>Intel prepping Atom bombs to drop on ARM microservers Roadmap is top secret, dual-core 'Centerton' Atom looms By Timothy Prickett Morgan • Get more from this author Posted in Servers , 6th December 2012 23:17 GMT To hear Intel Fellow Matt Adiletta tell it, Chipzilla not only invented the term microserver but saw the trend towards wimpy computing coming way ahead of the all this fawning over the ARM architecture and a half-dozen upstarts wanting to take big bites out of the Xeon server processor cash cow. When El Reg says "fawn", that's an intentional pun that harkens back to FAWN: A Fast Array of Wimpy Nodes, a paper published in May 2008 by a bunch of server geeks researchers at Carnegie Mellon University. That paper compared the energy profile and performance of x86 and ARM architectures, specifically for server nodes equipped with flash storage. It demonstrated how the combination of low-powered (in terms of both performance and electrical consumption) processors combined with flash could yield a 50X improvement over then-current x86 and hard-disk clusters fielding requests from a key-value store, and on the order of 4X compared to low-power x86 chips mated to flash. Subsequent papers published by the CMU researchers were done in conjunction with Intel Research, as you can see at the FAWN project. Adiletta, as it turns out, caught the microserver bug back in 2006, when it wasn't even called that yet. In 2007 his team at Intel created what he calls a "CPU DIMM" that was about the size of a folded wallet, as he explained in a conference call today with the press, that had either Atom or two-core Core desktop/laptop processors on them. It had a lot of pin and signal connectors and plugged into a memory slot, and Adiletta explained that he had shown it to none other than Sun cofounder and serial capitalist Andy Bechtolsheim to get his opinion. Bechtolsheim asked a lot of questions about thermals, performance, reliability, and other feeds and speeds, then was quiet for a bit, holding his hands in his head and rocking a little bit. "Geez, it just hurts my head to think about all of the opportunities this could provide if we can realize it," Adiletta recalls Bechtolsheim finally saying as he came out of his trance. Intel's point in hosting Thursday's meeting with journos and in telling this story about the meeting with Bechtolsheim is that the company wants to demonstrate that it has not been caught by surprise by either the advent of microservers or the movement of the ARM architecture from the smartphone and embedded spaces into the data center. In fact, the second generation of FAWN research at CMU compared x86 to ARM because Intel knew where the real competition would come from. El Reg notes that at this time Bechtolsheim was the CTO for servers at Sun Microsystems, which was nearly three years away from being thrown into the arms of Oracle after a catch-and-release by Big Blue. What Bechtolsheim did not do was launch microservers at Sun, but rather he invested his money in Arista Networks, where he became CEO in late 2008. Bechtolsheim likes to flip back and forth between systems and networking, and has his own kind of ticking and tocking going on. Adiletta, as the godfather of microservers at Intel, was trotted out to establish this creation myth in our psyches and to also to remind everyone that Intel is expected to launch its dual-core "Centerton" processor before the end of the year – than means soon, obviously – as the first server-class Atom processor. "Having more chefs in the kitchen helps, up to a certain point, depending on what is being served," Adiletta explained by way of metaphor to illustrate why Intel was enthusiastic about its impending Atom S Series of server chips and the possibilities they present. "We're very bullish on this segment." Maybe Intel's researchers were indeed enthusiastic about microservers, but their business managers were not so sure and absolutely did not want to upset the Xeon cash cow, particularly during the Great Recession. As Jason Waxman, general manager of the Cloud Computing Group at Intel, put it when microserver upstart SeaMicro launched a Xeon-based SM10000 cluster in January of this year: "SeaMicro is pretty modest. They were really the first company to push us hard on the Atom, and they are the first to develop a system that supports both Atom and Xeon." It's the interconnect, stupid genius A little more than a month later, floundering AMD, looking for some kind of salvation after having big handfuls of server market share ripped from it by Chipzilla, snapped up SeaMicro for $334m and is now working on an Opteron ARM processor due in 2014 with SeaMicro's interconnect fabric gluing them together into what amounts to a data center in a box. The assembled hacks pressed Adiletta for more details about the Atom S Series roadmap, and this hack in particular asked about the way that Intel would embed interconnects onto the chip as Calxeda has done with its EnergyCore EXC-1000 processors or Applied Micro Circuits has done with its X-Gene chips. As far as Calxeda is concerned, putting ARM cores and a distributed Layer 2 switch that scales to 4,096 nodes today and to over 100,000 nodes in a few years is the real engineering task with microservers – not welding an Ethernet NIC to an Atom processor. After having bought Ethernet chip maker Fulcrum Microsystems a few years back, Intel certainly could respond with something similar, but Adiletta was not there to provide an actual roadmap, but rather to establish Intel's cred in microservers and ramp up excitement for the Atom S Series. "This has been a classic question from the communications space for a long time: do you go distributed or do you do centralized," explained Adiletta when asked about integrated networking on the future Atoms. "Quite frankly," he said, "if you talk to comms folks, it is a religious argument. If you do centralized, then one of the nice things is how you can manage it and hop counts. Latency is interesting. There are pluses and minuses to both approaches. I wish I could go into some real technical details on this, but frankly I am quite bullish on what our approach is going to be." That wasn't a real answer, and Adiletta would have been taken out behind the Intel PR woodshed if he actually did answer the question. But what seems clear is that Intel is going to put Ethernet ports onto the future "Avoton" Atom S Series chips due in 2013, and will rely on its foundry advantages and tweaks to the Atom core (moving from in-order to out-of-order processing was one such change that Adiletta hinted at) to drive thermals down and performance up, and then haul out the old x86 compatibility saw that it's also using to help promote its Xeon Phi parallel x86 coprocessors in supercomputing. What Intel should probably do is embed an Atom S chip on a Xeon Phi, use the PCI slot for power only, slap an InfiniBand port on it, stick a boatload of SATA or SAS ports on it for hard disks or SSDs, and throw away the Xeon node for all but the most serious single-threaded work where a brawny core is required. (We are only half joking here.) "There is a lot of performance that we could gain by adding sophistication to our Atom cores," Adiletta said. "I like where we are. We have the right tools in the toolbox and the management support to go out and do this." Later in the Q&amp;A session, Adiletta said that the future Atoms would "show very, very good low-power idle power metrics," which of course is something that ARM chips can already boast. And looking at the low power states in Intel's future "Haswell" microarchitecture, you can be forgiven for thinking that Intel might be tempted to do away with Atoms altogether and just stick with Xeons in the next few years. For all we know, the lack of serious attention to Atom-based servers up until fairly recently could be another reason why CEO Paul Otellini is retiring next May. Perhaps Otellini wants some young blood to handle the shift that will turn the Atom into the new Xeon and the Xeon into the new Itanium, at least in hyperscale data centers and for more workloads as more and more software gets parallelized. Remember, after all, that it took the Core architecture to be spun up into a Xeon in Opteron drag to vanquish AMD, and it might take an Atom phone and netbook processor wrapped in Xeon drag to repel the onslaught of the ARMed rebels.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1354841033645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:43:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354841048032-98</Id><Topic><Title>Paul O on Wed about Apple?</Title><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1354839871388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:24:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know, how can you expect to keep it secret until the product ships? I think, once production starts the cat is out of the bag, at least 6 months before the product is released.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1354841048032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:44:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354841391839-99</Id><Topic><Title>Telegram for Getanid 16 - Intel dropping ATOM bombs on ARM microprocessors</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1354841033645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:43:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I mean "Getanid61 and ARM MicroSERVERS" Carry on...</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1354841391839</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:49:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354841825805-100</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo Finance dividend information is WRONG. It's 22.5 cents per quarter.</Title><Username>nickster135796</Username><Timestamp>1354839608088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:20:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, since I posted that message they fixed it. It originally showed a lower number yielding less than 4%. Someone screwing around at Yahoo.</Msg><Username>nickster135796</Username><Timestamp>1354841825805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:57:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354842167718-101</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo Finance dividend information is WRONG. It's 22.5 cents per quarter.</Title><Username>nickster135796</Username><Timestamp>1354839608088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 19:20:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the One year target was showing $29. Now it's been lowered. Yahoo's office needs to use a stronger password to stop people changing things or hire someone who types in the correct information in the first place.</Msg><Username>nickster135796</Username><Timestamp>1354842167718</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 20:02:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354842422975-102</Id><Topic><Title>Intel No Longer a Teenager</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354824440566</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 15:07:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you in your 20s? you may then.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1354842422975</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 20:07:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354842525037-103</Id><Topic><Title>What is the difference between these two symbols: AAPL and QQQQ?</Title><Username>kermit_the_hogg</Username><Timestamp>1354814427794</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 12:20:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>used to be, back to qqq</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1354842525037</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 20:08:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354842613398-104</Id><Topic><Title>Big foundry deal definitely coming</Title><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1354811732580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 11:35:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that must be why he wants out.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1354842613398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 20:10:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354847054463-105</Id><Title>Idiot Liberal Senator tries to board plane with Gun and AMO</Title><Msg>It just never stops with you Liberal freaks.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354847054463</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 21:24:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354848493067-106</Id><Title>Broadcom sees rising 20 nm costs amid handset push</Title><Msg>Wakeup call for QCOM et al - margins will contract</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1354848493067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 21:48:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354848758554-107</Id><Title>Wafer price sticker shock</Title><Msg>“Moore’s Law is going through an interesting phase,” said McGregor. “We use to have improvement in cost per transistor at every node, and at 28 nm it’s coming down, but in 20 or 14 nm it may even come up and that may be a shock for everyone."</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1354848758554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 21:52:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354851877651-108</Id><Topic><Title>Wafer price sticker shock</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1354848758554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 21:52:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wont matter for a while with the obscene amounts of profit the semiconductor industry makes per chip.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354851877651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 22:44:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354854549184-109</Id><Topic><Title>Wafer price sticker shock</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1354848758554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 21:52:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wont matter for a while with the obscene amounts of profit the semiconductor industry makes per chip. Margins won't matter - the new ARM spin? LOL it's about huge block of fix cost = fix cost absorption = large volume “We have been a generation or two behind others in the node we use, but we believe it makes sense to move closer to the leading edge,” McGregor said. “We won’t be the first in a process tech but we will get more competitive." “When we went to 65 nm, we moved the whole product portfolio, but that won’t happen going forward,” said McGregor. “We will be judicious, 28 nm will have long life and some products won’t make sense to move maybe ever and that is very different from the past."</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1354854549184</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 23:29:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354855131861-110</Id><Title>DECEMEMBER 7, 1941===PEARL HARBOR, HAWAII----PLEASE REMEMBER++++++++++++</Title><Msg>PASS THE WORD????????????????????????????????</Msg><Username>jondow69</Username><Timestamp>1354855131861</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 23:38:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354855945127-111</Id><Title>AMD , ashes,ashes all go down and the WS traders try to scalp a couple cents</Title><Msg>On Thursday, AMD said it had struck a deal with GlobalFoundries to amend its existing wafer supply agreement with the foundry, which was created mainly by spinning off AMD's manufacturing operation. Under a third amendment to the agreement, AMD will lower wafer purchase commitments for the fourth quarter of 2012 to about $115 million, and for fiscal 2013 to $1.15 billion.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1354855945127</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 23:52:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354856114905-112</Id><Topic><Title>Idiot Liberal Senator tries to board plane with Gun and AMO</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1354847054463</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 21:24:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ann Romney Might Be Taking This Loss Harder Than Mitt. Settle down Annie!!! Its over!!! TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYYYYYY!!!</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1354856114905</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 23:55:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>