<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351051268331-1</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351032791501</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 18:53:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mysty I think the question was have you compared your Intel, to ARM.......I got out of Intel and none too soon! IT has tanked, but ARM has prospered! Seems like that answers the questions for you since you dodged it!</Msg><Username>koroundiii</Username><Timestamp>1351051268331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:01:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351051302085-2</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351032791501</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 18:53:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Settle down, we can't all make the right choices all of the time.....</Msg><Username>oiledude</Username><Timestamp>1351051302085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351052564470-3</Id><Topic><Title>What Was Wrong with Mitt Last Night?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351050893223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 23:54:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazingly, he was having a tough time with his lying. BLINK-BLINK-BLINK-BLINK-BLINK There are some actions that people really cannot control that perform necessary functions and blinking is one of them. This action keeps the eyes moisturized but also protects the eyes from debris and bright lights. The average person blinks every 3-12 seconds and that can work out to 8-10 blinks per minute unless under stress or medical conditions. Under stress, while fabricating or while lying the rate of blinking may increase. When people lie there are physical actions that they make whether they know it or not.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351052564470</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:22:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351053201189-4</Id><Topic><Title>BUY BUY BUY</Title><Username>bull_no_bear</Username><Timestamp>1351039008840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:36:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>starting</Msg><Username>raygeo2003</Username><Timestamp>1351053201189</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351061706936-5</Id><Title>Surface vs Clovertrail</Title><Msg>'The only other user experience issue I have with Surface has to do with CPU utilization when using Office 2013. Surface, like all Windows RT tablets, comes with a free installation of Office 2013 Student &amp; Home Edition. Surface also happens to use a quad-core NVIDIA Tegra 3 SoC, featuring four ARM Cortex A9 cores running at up to 1.3GHz. At least for the Cortex A9 generation, I don’t know that Microsoft could’ve used anything slower. Simply typing quickly in Microsoft Word maxes the single threaded performance of Tegra 3’s ARM Cortex A9 cores. I’ve seen CPU usage a high as 50% when typing very quickly, but mostly it tends to sit between 20 – 40%. Switch to notepad and max CPU utilization drops to sub 10%. This says more about Office 2013 than the performance of NVIDIA’s Tegra 3, but there are not a whole lot of spare CPU cycles to go around with Surface. On the user experience side alone, the Clovertrail tablet is noticeably quicker than Surface. Surface isn’t slow by any means, but had it used Atom hardware it would’ve been even more responsive. The large files used in the workload do a great job of showing Atom’s memory controller advantages over that used by the Cortex A9. The results here likely overstate the Clovertrail performance advantage a bit (I’m not sure how much 1080p video transcoding you’re going to be doing on Surface as compared to web browsing) but the results tend to agree with what our browser based JavaScript tests show: Intel’s Atom Z2760 is considerably faster than Tegra 3 here. I understand that Microsoft needed a good launch vehicle for Windows RT, however I really would have liked to have seen an Atom version of Surface. An Ivy Bridge version is in the works, but it’s also a bit larger. An Atom version could retain the same chassis size/weight, but deliver tangibly better CPU performance. Again we’ll have to wait to see what battery life looks like for these Clovertrail tablets before really deciding whether or not Atom would’ve been a better fit.' anandtechDOTcom/show/6385/microsoft-surface-review/10</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351061706936</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351062875781-6</Id><Topic><Title>Surface vs Clovertrail</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1351061706936</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows users have from the beginning been brought up on a diet of high performance CPUs. As a logical progression, the Surface is no exception. Clovertrail based Windows 8 tablets are definitely the way to go for such performance craving users. Battery life is not as significant a factor for such users. This is in stark contrast with iPad users who are used to extended battery life at acceptable performance levels. There's a big difference in design philosophy here.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1351062875781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 03:14:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351063553234-7</Id><Title>WHY INTC EMPLOYEES VOTE FOR OBAMA WHO IS AGAINST THEM.</Title><Msg>I don't get it. My friend who works for intc told me he is voting for romney but would not tell anybody.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351063553234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 03:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351068942517-8</Id><Title>Strong earnings preview from MPartners - Reporting a Milestone quarter today after market</Title><Msg>- Interdigital ( NASDAQ:IDCC ) is about to explode, check out the reasons for the $45 Price target from MPartners ( last night ) - This quarter IDCC recognized revenue from its first batch of patent assets sold to Intel for $375M (announced in June 2012) and also received positive ruling from the CAFC regarding its appeal of a 2009 ITC decision in favor of Nokia with respect to two 3G essential patents. - The recent good news has been undermined by underperformance of its core 3G licenses. Particularly revenue from per unit licensees continued to erode because handset vendors in Japan, along with RIM, and HTC continued to lose market share to Samsung and Apple. Samsung and Apple are both fixed-term licensees where revenue streams are unaffected by volumes. OUTLOOK SHOULD BE SOLID We believe that due to the timing of asset sales, as well as license renewals and outcomes of litigation, that quarterly results are difficult to forecast. However, we should continue to see an annualized trend towards growth through licensing, partnerships, and asset sales. This is reflected in our sum-of-the-parts analysis below. Our estimate of cash includes our estimate incremental cash that resulted from the sale of the patents to Intel. We reiterate our BUY recommendation and our 12-month share price target of $45.00. Our estimate excludes licensing revenue from Nokia, Huawei, ZTE, and LG, which are all involved in litigation with Interdigital currently. Yesterday's the stock closed with a gain of 5% in the after hours trading. Calls are also very active lately</Msg><Username>patentsaddicted</Username><Timestamp>1351068942517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 04:55:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351073850972-9</Id><Topic><Title>What Was Wrong with Mitt Last Night?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351050893223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 23:54:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He looked calm, professional, presidential and respectful, four words very foreign to you Liberals. All you guys can do is look for dirt and try to make Mitt look undesireable since you can't run on anything you've accomplished. The sitting POTUS sitting there making sarcastic remarks during the most serious of times when he's accomplished NOTHING. I guess Obama thought he was still at the white tie dinner. Only in America do you have people standing by the side of a party that includes Nancy Pelosi, Barny Frank, John Edwars, Bill Mauer, Chris Matthews and on and on. I guess "crazy" is something Liberals can all associate with, so they flock to it.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351073850972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 06:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351073956345-10</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH-based Surface tablets utter trash and ARM Holdings is the problem.</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351041087785</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 21:11:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUMP</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351073956345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 06:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351075011363-11</Id><Title>Windows RT Disadvantages</Title><Msg>From CNET article: 1. Flash only works on web sites Microsoft approves 2. No legacy Windows apps. No Photoshop, No Google Chrome or none of the other 4 million apps written for x86. 3. Apps can only be purchased from Google Store. 4. Very limited selection of apps. Couple thousand vs x86 Windows of roughly 4 million 5. Some traditional Microsoft apps won't work with RT, not even Outlook or Windows Media Player. 6. Desktop mode is restricted to pre-installed Microsoft apps. 7. RT is for home and student use only. Requires commercial license to use RT's Office Apps for work. Not only is RT a waste of money it's an invitation for customer disappointment and frustration.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1351075011363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 06:36:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351079932710-12</Id><Topic><Title>What Was Wrong with Mitt Last Night?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351050893223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 23:54:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looked good to me. And he is up four to five percent in a couple of good polls. Eat your heart out. Romney did just what he intended to do in the debates. Mitt may just win this thing.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1351079932710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:58:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351080296352-13</Id><Title>Credit Suisse: Intel removed from U.S. Focus List.</Title><Msg>10/24/2012: Intel removed from U.S. Focus List at Credit Suisse.</Msg><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351080296352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351083360997-14</Id><Title>Tiglet you should buy ARMH, PE of 63</Title><Msg>Or Facebook.... your call.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351083360997</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:56:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351083926448-15</Id><Topic><Title>Windows RT Disadvantages</Title><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1351075011363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 06:36:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One can buy a laptop with 15.6" display, Ivy Bridge processor, lots of RAM, storage, USB3.0 and 64 bit W8 in the high $300 range and have full compatibility with all x86 software and use it for home or business. Windows RT is an expensive toy.</Msg><Username>publicservice100</Username><Timestamp>1351083926448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351084125007-16</Id><Title>Of course CNBC, Bank of America, etc. say to buy now........they are stuck from 38</Title><Msg>You are kidding yourself if you think they have YOUR best interest in mind.</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1351084125007</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:08:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351084561568-17</Id><Topic><Title>Of course CNBC, Bank of America, etc. say to buy now........they are stuck from 38</Title><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1351084125007</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:08:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>better than zell</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1351084561568</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:16:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351084984511-18</Id><Topic><Title>What Was Wrong with Mitt Last Night?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351050893223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 23:54:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's true that Mitt did a good job with the debates. He threw everything he had said for months - all that hard right crazy rhetoric he used to get the nomination - under the bus. And morphed into a moderate. The problem is that no one knows who Mitt really is or what he will do if elected. You want him elected because you think he was lying about being a moderate, right?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351084984511</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:23:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351085008337-19</Id><Title>UP UP AND AWAY... doubt it, but I can have hope in this hopelessness can I not?</Title><Msg>Up 14 cents in pre-market, hopefully that turns into good things when the market goes live...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351085008337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351085037887-20</Id><Title>Indiana Senate candidate says pregnancy from rape is God's intent</Title><Msg>Unbelievable...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351085037887</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:23:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351085185194-21</Id><Topic><Title>Credit Suisse: Intel removed from U.S. Focus List.</Title><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351080296352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why Yahoo does not allow posting links anymore!!!! The news is on theflyonthewall website.</Msg><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351085185194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:26:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351085277480-22</Id><Topic><Title>Indiana Senate candidate says pregnancy from rape is God's intent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351085037887</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:23:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's a politician right??? So what's the surprise??? Lie, Cheat, Steal - their 3 best qualities!</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351085277480</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:27:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351085552627-23</Id><Topic><Title>Credit Suisse: Intel removed from U.S. Focus List.</Title><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351080296352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's nothing on that site about that and all I found when Googling it was Credit Suisse reiterating outperform on Intel and a target of 35.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351085552627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351085663148-24</Id><Title>Over night FARMVILLE went up 25%, only in America</Title><Msg>OINK</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1351085663148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:34:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351085693706-25</Id><Topic><Title>Credit Suisse: Intel removed from U.S. Focus List.</Title><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351080296352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have the full subscription one, maybe you was looking at the free on.....</Msg><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351085693706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:34:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351085710695-26</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>elinorenea234</Username><Timestamp>1351081287634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks legit. Thank you for sharing this</Msg><Username>burgess_christina611</Username><Timestamp>1351085710695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:35:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351085815441-27</Id><Topic><Title>Credit Suisse: Intel removed from U.S. Focus List.</Title><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351080296352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have the full subscription one, maybe you was looking at the free on..... _________________________ Ahh, the perfect response to suck someone in to buying a subscription. You better hope it's true, because you've just been reported for possible defamation.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351085815441</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:36:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086472360-28</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>elinorenea234</Username><Timestamp>1351081287634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is no place for SPAMMER..this is REAL! awesome.....</Msg><Username>mckinney_lara552</Username><Timestamp>1351086472360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:47:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086544902-29</Id><Topic><Title>UP UP AND AWAY... doubt it, but I can have hope in this hopelessness can I not?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351085008337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, that was short lived... I should have stuck to day trading... this stock is frustrating... of course if I stick with it (yes I have no patience) I'll probably win big time in the long run...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351086544902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:49:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086616410-30</Id><Topic><Title>UP UP AND AWAY... doubt it, but I can have hope in this hopelessness can I not?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351085008337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how's that workin' for you ? 20 minutes in and it is flat lined</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351086616410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:50:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086687642-31</Id><Topic><Title>What Was Wrong with Mitt Last Night?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351050893223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 23:54:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or because of this ? The Quote of the Decade: "The fact that we are here today to debate raising America's debt limit is a sign of leadership failure. It is a sign that the US Government cannot pay its own bills. It is a sign that we now depend on ongoing financial assistance from foreign countries to finance our Government's reckless fiscal policies. Increasing America's debt weakens us domestically and internationally. Leadership means that, "the buck stops here.' Instead, Washington is shifting the burden of bad choices today onto the backs of our children and grandchildren. America has a debt problem and a failure of leadership. Americans deserve better." ~ Senator Barack H. Obama, March 2006</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351086687642</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:51:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086742239-32</Id><Topic><Title>Tiglet you should buy ARMH, PE of 63</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351083360997</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:56:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no need to buy, I own 1 already. your guess.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351086742239</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:52:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086758542-33</Id><Topic><Title>Tiglet you should buy ARMH, PE of 63</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351083360997</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:56:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and armh is pushing $33</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351086758542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:52:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086838127-34</Id><Topic><Title>What Was Wrong with Mitt Last Night?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351050893223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 23:54:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but they inherited it................................</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351086838127</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086901438-35</Id><Topic><Title>WHY INTC EMPLOYEES VOTE FOR OBAMA WHO IS AGAINST THEM.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351063553234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 03:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and of course you asked him why - - - - - -- nah, you're just fos</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351086901438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:55:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086963440-36</Id><Topic><Title>What Was Wrong with Mitt Last Night?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351050893223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 23:54:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>romney spits in your face 22-Feb-12 05:04 pm Two out of every three people receiving stock dividend payments are rich, many totally, incredibly rich and should be paying more taxes instead of us soaking the middle class. I'm sick of the deadbeat rich who are unwilling to carry their fair share of the load... wallisweaver</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351086963440</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:56:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086990911-37</Id><Topic><Title>UP UP AND AWAY... doubt it, but I can have hope in this hopelessness can I not?</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351085008337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's doing EVEN BETTER now... it's down 8 cents... yep suits me well... if I were shorting it...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351086990911</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:56:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087050794-38</Id><Topic><Title>LOL Dirtbag Liberals sending fake letters to Florida Republicans saying they aren't eligible to vote</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1351040212552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:56:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jesse, is that you?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351087050794</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:57:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087064013-39</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH-based Surface tablets utter trash and ARM Holdings is the problem.</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351041087785</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 21:11:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It seems MSFT can't tell the difference between trash and gold (well, silver, since I don't think MSFT has ever ascended to the gold). Their OS system releases are a crap shoot. Is Ballmer still the CEO? Ever since he did that gorilla dance on stage I have had a bad feeling about MSFT.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351087064013</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:57:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087069267-40</Id><Topic><Title>Over night FARMVILLE went up 25%, only in America</Title><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1351085663148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, should have dumped my intel and bought that stuff on friday... but WHO knew!</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351087069267</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:57:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087079486-41</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>elinorenea234</Username><Timestamp>1351081287634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope it contains great info. I just joined. Many thanks</Msg><Username>bates_anne556</Username><Timestamp>1351087079486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:57:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087127986-42</Id><Topic><Title>INTC (buy 21/sell 22) nov</Title><Username>mtgtr09</Username><Timestamp>1351033085380</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 18:58:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd be thrilled with $22 any time in Nov and especially if it is nov 2012.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351087127986</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:58:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087172377-43</Id><Topic><Title>LOL Dirtbag Liberals sending fake letters to Florida Republicans saying they aren't eligible to vote</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1351040212552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:56:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>liberal ca. is doing well, that's a great example of liberalism.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351087172377</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:59:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087228295-44</Id><Topic><Title>ARM, Chump Street and Getanid61</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351036457402</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 19:54:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>of course and never forget the $3 eps</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351087228295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087303644-45</Id><Topic><Title>Credit Suisse: Intel removed from U.S. Focus List.</Title><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351080296352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just now on CNBC with Jim Cramer......</Msg><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351087303644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:01:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087308214-46</Id><Topic><Title>ARM and Chump Street - What a Pair</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351035007174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 19:30:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>guess what, we are down a nickel again, armh 33, intc</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351087308214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:01:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087391745-47</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351032791501</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 18:53:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but with that 4% div i can make back the losses from 29 to 21 in , uh, in, oh #$%$, never mind, maybe in my life time?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351087391745</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087482238-48</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351032791501</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 18:53:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow, really? amazing you would think that way. 14 bill in your account? my account? just makes it even harder to watch Intel miss mobile for a decade. zero long term vision 10 years ago.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351087482238</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:04:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351087519276-49</Id><Title>junk is junk</Title><Msg>no power to go up and hold the gains</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351087519276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:05:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351087590624-50</Id><Title>ARMH &amp; QCOM are the winners.</Title><Msg>INTC &amp; AMD are the losers.</Msg><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351087590624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:06:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087627072-51</Id><Topic><Title>FB up 9% AH</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351024186203</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 16:29:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>having another hate p.o. moment? LOL</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351087627072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351087635703-52</Id><Title>Dirtbag Romney's Bain outsourcing 170 jobs in little town to China</Title><Msg>Exactly what they did every time, everywhere else..."bustout" a profitable, happy little company, charge tons of "service fees," and send hundreds/per bustout to the unemployment rolls. This time its in Freeport Illinois, the Sensata company. (google Freeport, sensata) If you believe this man stands for "jobs for Americans" and for any part of the middle class, let alone the bottom 47%, (heck, the bottom 98%) then I have bridge to sell you in NYC.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351087635703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:07:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087663804-53</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>elinorenea234</Username><Timestamp>1351081287634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finally! I found something informative.</Msg><Username>haynes_jeanette559</Username><Timestamp>1351087663804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:07:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087723978-54</Id><Topic><Title>Why INTC is UP today?</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1351017405081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:36:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>time to move to a bigger town. oh just maybe that the pc is losing ground to wireless devices and Intel has flopped in that arena for years now.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351087723978</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:08:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351087741482-55</Id><Title>Intel EVP Sells 25K Shares.</Title><Msg>Yahoo news: SODHANI ARVIND who is EXEC. VP; PRES. INTEL CAPITAL at Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC), sold 25,000 shares at $21.50 per share for a total value of $537,505.</Msg><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351087741482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:09:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087853396-56</Id><Topic><Title>Why INTC is UP today?</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1351017405081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:36:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why nov? do you expect a lot of people to buy PCs as gifyd and wrap them and stick them under their xmas tree or more ipads? $24 in Nov, i will be shocked.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351087853396</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:10:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087923010-57</Id><Topic><Title>Intel EVP Sells 25K Shares.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351087741482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:09:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, I said this yesterday... thanks for catching up..</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351087923010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:12:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351087928905-58</Id><Title>INTC</Title><Msg>Once again ARMH is up another 5% today on top of being up 10% yesterday. We were up a wopping 13 cents yesterday and are losing it today. I was always taught that he who has the best product and manufacturing wins. INTC may have the best manufacturing and fabrication, but ARMH has the best selling product and TSM is smart enough to produce the product that sells. This is why INTC is punished and ARMH and TSM are rewarded. Enough is enough, I implore you to contact investor relations and let them know you are sick of losing money and its time to change course or senior management.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1351087928905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:12:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087997491-59</Id><Topic><Title>Apple fanboys won't be able to retire</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351016351049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if my past tells you anything, not real well is your answer buy 05/15/98 INTC 400 $20.00 $8,000.00 sell 03/03/06 INTC 400 $20.10 $8,040.00</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351087997491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:13:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351088008402-60</Id><Topic><Title>junk is junk</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351087519276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would appear that way... I think next week will be a better showing of what's to come...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351088008402</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:13:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351088132549-61</Id><Topic><Title>Why INTC is UP today?</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1351017405081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:36:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it is way down, no need to beat it further. seems he was right</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351088132549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:15:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351088182394-62</Id><Topic><Title>Why INTC is UP today?</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1351017405081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:36:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. CDs, bonds.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351088182394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:16:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351088314820-63</Id><Topic><Title>Apple fanboys won't be able to retire</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351016351049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC has lost 40 Billion in stock holder value since 5-3-12. How much longer is the INTC BOD going to let this go on? Start producing ARMH processors at 22nm with excess capicity and we go to mid 30's in a heart beat.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1351088314820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:18:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351088671343-64</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation most excellent thing Since Sliced Bread..</Title><Username>kwinfred64</Username><Timestamp>1351081238774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:20:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'd like to see the rest of this.. has anyone watched</Msg><Username>vargasboris55</Username><Timestamp>1351088671343</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:24:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351088776149-65</Id><Title>The Entire page 1 of my Intel board</Title><Msg>No joke. Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 33 seconds ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 6 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 6 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 7 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 8 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 9 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 12 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 13 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 17 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 18 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 19 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 20 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 23 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 23 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 24 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 25 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 26 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 27 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 27 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 28 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 29 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 30 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 32 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 38 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 43 minutes ago</Msg><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1351088776149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351088854943-66</Id><Topic><Title>junk is junk</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351087519276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I told you so</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351088854943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:27:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351089162728-67</Id><Title>Watch CRUS</Title><Msg>nnnn</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1351089162728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:32:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351089239156-68</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>elinorenea234</Username><Timestamp>1351081287634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very informative. Thank you</Msg><Username>love_maria569</Username><Timestamp>1351089239156</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:33:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351090013959-69</Id><Title>Might as well call this now... below $21 this Friday...</Title><Msg>But will recover nicely next week... in the $22s by Mid next week... just my speculation...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351090013959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:46:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351090498677-70</Id><Topic><Title>junk is junk</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351087519276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Credit Suisse: Intel removed from U.S. Focus List.</Msg><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351090498677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:54:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351090576459-71</Id><Topic><Title>Intel EVP Sells 25K Shares.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351087741482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:09:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's on today's news.</Msg><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351090576459</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:56:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351090641475-72</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH &amp; QCOM are the winners.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351087590624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe Intel &amp; AMD should buy ARMH &amp; QCOM.</Msg><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351090641475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:57:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351090761467-73</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH &amp; QCOM are the winners.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351087590624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First inning isn't even over. You are the LOSER. You are also a d i p s_h_%_ T</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351090761467</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:59:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351090940101-74</Id><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Msg>OH MY... has anyone compared yahoo charts of INTC vs ARMH every yahoo chart option available 1D, 5D, 1M, 3M, 6M, YTD, 1Y, 2Y, 5Y, MAX just today, 11am EST, ARMH up over 4% ... how's INTC doing... keep the faith...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351090940101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351091160821-75</Id><Title>How I make easy money for a living</Title><Msg>Just short this junk every time when it goes up, it's that simple and works all the time! short short short!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351091160821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:06:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351091445449-76</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351090940101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH MY...does anyone bother to read your drivel? IGNORE****</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351091445449</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:10:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351091879955-77</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351090940101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let him keep posting this stuff. It gets archived, can never be changed and these old posts will be hilarious to bring back up in a few years......just as the AMD ones are. To use his own words. "You've declared game over before it's begun! Desperate !!!".</Msg><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1351091879955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:17:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351092108194-78</Id><Topic><Title>What Was Wrong with Mitt Last Night?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351050893223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 23:54:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tiglet2l : blink blink blink blink blink blink blink blink</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351092108194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351092432285-79</Id><Title>Trump Bombshell - Obama used and dealt coke in College</Title><Msg>OH MY !!!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351092432285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351092439241-80</Id><Title>Trump Bombshell - Obama used and dealt coke in College</Title><Msg>OH MY !!!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351092439241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:27:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351092495958-81</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351090940101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump Bump and Bump.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351092495958</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:28:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351092655499-82</Id><Topic><Title>Trump Bombshell - Obama used and dealt coke in College</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351092439241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:27:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>King Birther requests new crown.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351092655499</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351093134323-83</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>elinorenea234</Username><Timestamp>1351081287634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is better than DOTA!!! two thumbs UP!!!</Msg><Username>powers_carol565</Username><Timestamp>1351093134323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:38:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351093378107-84</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>elinorenea234</Username><Timestamp>1351081287634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure thing. Been receiving good alerts from them</Msg><Username>young_deborah573</Username><Timestamp>1351093378107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:42:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351093888723-85</Id><Title>High Noon, EST make sure to check Donald Trump's twitter !</Title><Msg>Story about Hussein Obama to be released.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351093888723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351093914488-86</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>elinorenea234</Username><Timestamp>1351081287634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this here.</Msg><Username>wright_vickie569</Username><Timestamp>1351093914488</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094201459-87</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>elinorenea234</Username><Timestamp>1351081287634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like these guys, they're really good.</Msg><Username>mullins_ashley574</Username><Timestamp>1351094201459</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:56:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094382276-88</Id><Topic><Title>Intel EVP Sells 25K Shares.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351087741482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:09:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He exercised a company option that was going to expire 11/25/2012. The strike price of the option was $20.23 and cost him $505k to exercise. He got $21.50 average for the sale and banked $31k cash for exercise/sell. It would have been important if he had kept shares since it would almost be an open market $500k buy since the option price was so high.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351094382276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:59:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094392743-89</Id><Topic><Title>Is INTC Ready to Break Out?</Title><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1351086375644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:46:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for this guys!</Msg><Username>libbylicyr356003</Username><Timestamp>1351094392743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:59:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094492984-90</Id><Topic><Title>How I make easy money for a living</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351091160821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:06:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just make sure you are done shorting it long before the end of November... sure up your wins, take the money and run before then... otherwise, you're going to be in the hurt zone... $23.50 by the end of November, $24 before the end of the year and $26 to $30 by some point next year...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351094492984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094594974-91</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>elinorenea234</Username><Timestamp>1351081287634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just joined. Heard a lot about these guys</Msg><Username>graham_natalie576</Username><Timestamp>1351094594974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094735418-92</Id><Topic><Title>High Noon, EST make sure to check Donald Trump's twitter !</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351093888723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trump is a real clown for wading into this stuff. He will do virtually anything for the attention. CAN STREAKING BE FAR BEHIND! TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOo FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351094735418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094873804-93</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351090940101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351094873804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:07:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094909219-94</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>elinorenea234</Username><Timestamp>1351081287634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds interesting. Let me try this.</Msg><Username>reeves_catherine585</Username><Timestamp>1351094909219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:08:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094990060-95</Id><Topic><Title>High Noon, EST make sure to check Donald Trump's twitter !</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351093888723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But Gloria Alred's venom is ok with you, right? Don't look in the mirror. You will see an old, shriveled up hypocrite that couldn't get a piece of #$%$ in a brothel.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351094990060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:09:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351095092529-96</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation most excellent thing Since Sliced Bread..</Title><Username>kwinfred64</Username><Timestamp>1351081238774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:20:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy, hold and get rich! Something is up and we will know soon!</Msg><Username>romanroman79</Username><Timestamp>1351095092529</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:11:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351095189868-97</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>elinorenea234</Username><Timestamp>1351081287634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great share. Many thanks</Msg><Username>cross_tara587</Username><Timestamp>1351095189868</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351095290208-98</Id><Topic><Title>High Noon, EST make sure to check Donald Trump's twitter !</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351093888723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TRUMPS big Obama Tweet? Charity donation based on college records and passport application release? TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351095290208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:14:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351095537876-99</Id><Topic><Title>High Noon, EST make sure to check Donald Trump's twitter !</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351093888723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pretty lame on The Donald's part. Thought it's also ludicrous that our President doesn't want the country he leads to know who he really is. LOL.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351095537876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:18:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351095590570-100</Id><Topic><Title>Is INTC Ready to Break Out?</Title><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1351086375644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:46:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great , i just subscribed!</Msg><Username>libbylicyr356003</Username><Timestamp>1351095590570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351095654081-101</Id><Topic><Title>High Noon, EST make sure to check Donald Trump's twitter !</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351093888723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROMNEY doesn't care. Why should you? ROMNEY doesn't think it is venom. Why should you? "Romney lawyer Robert Jones told Time Magazine: “This is a decades-old divorce case in which Mitt Romney provided testimony as to the value of a company. He has no objection to letting the public see that testimony." TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351095654081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:20:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351095869666-102</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>elinorenea234</Username><Timestamp>1351081287634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love it. thanks</Msg><Username>edwards_katie592</Username><Timestamp>1351095869666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:24:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351096037480-103</Id><Topic><Title>High Noon, EST make sure to check Donald Trump's twitter !</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351093888723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for confirming that it's ok with you for Liberals to try and dig up dirt, but its petty if Republicans supporters do it. Your life amounted to you being a hypocrite........good luck on that! LOL!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351096037480</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351096320026-104</Id><Title>FB shorts are being squeezed bad.</Title><Msg>..................</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351096320026</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:32:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351096641010-105</Id><Title>Credit Suisse: "Intel removed from U.S. Focus List."</Title><Msg>Today's quote.</Msg><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351096641010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:37:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351096768685-106</Id><Topic><Title>Credit Suisse: "Intel removed from U.S. Focus List."</Title><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351096641010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:37:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you already spammed that this AM. lmao</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351096768685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:39:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351096981547-107</Id><Title>Intel plans massive expansion to $3B D1X fab</Title><Msg>Paul and the rest of the Intel management are cluelessly spending billions of dollars without knowing where the demand is going to come from..... /sarcasm ============================ Intel Corp. on Wednesday announced it will expand it's $3 billion D1X research fab in Hillsboro, in a project that could double the size of the facility, now under construction. Intel spokesman Bill MacKenzie said the Santa Clara, Calif.-based chip maker (NASDAQ: INTC) won't disclose the size of the expansion or the amount to be invested, though he said it would be "comparable" to D1X. That suggests the entire project will approach $6 billion in cost and twice the originally planned square footage.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1351096981547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:43:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351097159262-108</Id><Topic><Title>Might as well call this now... below $21 this Friday...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351090013959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At some point next year, back up to $30... I'm not waiting till then, but for anyone looking to benefit for the long haul... there's a lot of cash to be made.. you can make even more buying and shorting, if you can guess the right highs and lows... best of luck to everyone...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351097159262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:45:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351097347473-109</Id><Topic><Title>Intel plans massive expansion to $3B D1X fab</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1351096981547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:43:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It sounds like good news for 2014 and beyond... for the short term, not so good...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351097347473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:49:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351097359550-110</Id><Topic><Title>Credit Suisse: "Intel removed from U.S. Focus List."</Title><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351096641010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:37:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>24.10.2012 | 14:00 (80 Leser) Schrift ändern: (0 Bewertungen) BörseGo · Mehr Nachrichten von BörseGo Credit Suisse streicht Intel aus der "US Focus List" Credit Suisse streicht Intel aus der "US Focus List" (© BörseGo AG 2012 - Autor: Tobias Krieg, Redakteur) © 2012 BörseGo 24.10.2012 | 14:00 (80 Leser) Schrift ändern: (0 Bewertungen) BörseGo · Mehr Nachrichten von BörseGo Credit Suisse streicht Intel aus der "US Focus List" Credit Suisse streicht Intel aus der "US Focus List" (© BörseGo AG 2012 - Autor: Tobias Krieg, Redakteur) © 2012 BörseGo</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1351097359550</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:49:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351097410260-111</Id><Topic><Title>Is INTC Ready to Break Out?</Title><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1351086375644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:46:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very informative. Thank you</Msg><Username>quianabbalf331833</Username><Timestamp>1351097410260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:50:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351098151162-112</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351090940101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump Intel Corp. on Wednesday announced it will expand it's $3 billion D1X research fab in Hillsboro, in a project that could double the size of the facility, now under construction. Intel spokesman Bill MacKenzie said the Santa Clara, Calif.-based chip maker (NASDAQ: INTC) won't disclose the size of the expansion or the amount to be invested, though he said it would be "comparable" to D1X. That suggests the entire project will approach $6 billion in cost and twice the originally planned square footage.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351098151162</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:02:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351098234714-113</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation most excellent thing Since Sliced Bread..</Title><Username>kwinfred64</Username><Timestamp>1351081238774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:20:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fine. I'll buy now and hold It and after sometime .That was good information.</Msg><Username>v.roman61</Username><Timestamp>1351098234714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:03:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351098256290-114</Id><Title>Intel CEO: ARM, QCOM &amp; NVDA are threats.</Title><Msg>10/24/2012: Intel CEO: Windows 8 brings both opportunities, challenges, AllThingsD says - Intel (INTC) CEO Paul Otellini said Microsoft's (MSFT) launch of Windows 8 brings with it a new set of opportunities to expand into new markets, along with the threats posed by competition from ARM-based chipmakers like Qualcomm (QCOM) and Nvidia (NVDA), reported AllThingsD.</Msg><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351098256290</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:04:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351098470010-115</Id><Topic><Title>Is INTC Ready to Break Out?</Title><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1351086375644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:46:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure thing. Been receiving good alerts from them</Msg><Username>quianabbalf331833</Username><Timestamp>1351098470010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:07:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351098561455-116</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351090940101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump. The expansion will also include building an office building, a manufacturing support building and a parking structure. Intel announced the development of D1X in October 2010 during a celebratory press conference at the company's Ronler Acres campus in Hillsboro. The facility is to be the company's most advanced research and development fab featuring 200,000-square-feet of clean room space. It's where Intel will develop its next generation of chip technology that won't likely hit the market until later in the decade. MacKenzie referred to original D1X project as Mod1. The expansion will feature a second module, called Mod2, that will be built onto Mod1. It will serve the same research and development function — in other words, it won't be a high-volume production facility. The expansion, MacKenzie said, simply adds additional capacity to that work. "It’s really just an extension of D1X," MacKenzie said.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351098561455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:09:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351098587666-117</Id><Topic><Title>Intel plans massive expansion to $3B D1X fab</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1351096981547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:43:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The expansion will also include building an office building, a manufacturing support building and a parking structure. Intel announced the development of D1X in October 2010 during a celebratory press conference at the company's Ronler Acres campus in Hillsboro. The facility is to be the company's most advanced research and development fab featuring 200,000-square-feet of clean room space. It's where Intel will develop its next generation of chip technology that won't likely hit the market until later in the decade. MacKenzie referred to original D1X project as Mod1. The expansion will feature a second module, called Mod2, that will be built onto Mod1. It will serve the same research and development function — in other words, it won't be a high-volume production facility. The expansion, MacKenzie said, simply adds additional capacity to that work. "It’s really just an extension of D1X," MacKenzie said.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351098587666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:09:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351098607211-118</Id><Title>BUMP</Title><Msg>The expansion will also include building an office building, a manufacturing support building and a parking structure. Intel announced the development of D1X in October 2010 during a celebratory press conference at the company's Ronler Acres campus in Hillsboro. The facility is to be the company's most advanced research and development fab featuring 200,000-square-feet of clean room space. It's where Intel will develop its next generation of chip technology that won't likely hit the market until later in the decade. MacKenzie referred to original D1X project as Mod1. The expansion will feature a second module, called Mod2, that will be built onto Mod1. It will serve the same research and development function — in other words, it won't be a high-volume production facility. The expansion, MacKenzie said, simply adds additional capacity to that work. "It’s really just an extension of D1X," MacKenzie said.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1351098607211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:10:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351100230161-119</Id><Topic><Title>Is INTC Ready to Break Out?</Title><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1351086375644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:46:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this here.</Msg><Username>luanarbhoj06666</Username><Timestamp>1351100230161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:37:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351100687902-120</Id><Topic><Title>High Noon, EST make sure to check Donald Trump's twitter !</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351093888723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I asked you ONE question in two different ways. I got no answer. ROMNEY doesn't care. Why should you? NOT ONLY does ROMNEY not care, FOX News, CBS, NBC, ABC, CNN, BBC don't care either. It is perfectly fine if Trump wants to do this. He is a clown from his birther work. Is it "important" for Trump to get the information? FOX News, CBS, NBC, ABC, CNN, BBC, .... do not have either (Trump or Alred) on their front page so neither is very important. You do not know my feelings about Gloria Alread and what she is doing. You do not know whether I think it is OK or NOT OK or I don't care. I just asked you why you cared about Alred's request and you made a bunch of assumptions and went off like a rocket. Take your meds and chill out. TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO EASYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYY!</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351100687902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351101107990-121</Id><Topic><Title>Is INTC Ready to Break Out?</Title><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1351086375644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:46:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like these guys, they're really good.</Msg><Username>luanarbhoj06666</Username><Timestamp>1351101107990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:51:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351101813371-122</Id><Title>Hard to see who Windows RT is for....</Title><Msg>Check out arstechnica. ...... A lot of enterprise-oriented features are omitted (just as they are from the base Windows 8 SKU). Windows RT can't join a domain, be a Remote Desktop host, or boot from VHDs, for example. It also has a few omissions of its own. In particular, it lacks Windows Media Player and Windows Media Center. Then there are the two major differences. First the big bonus feature: Windows RT comes with four Office 2013 applications. Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and OneNote all ship as an integral part of Windows RT. They're not quite full versions of those applications—they lack macros and certain other extensibility features—but they're very close. These applications run on the desktop, and although Microsoft has attempted to make those applications touch-capable, you'll really want a keyboard and pointing device to use them. And the big missing feature: Windows RT can't run third-party desktop applications. At all. Office is the only desktop application allowed. The only third-party applications allowed on Surface will be Metro-style applications bought from the Windows Store. In this way, Microsoft made the problem I alluded to much worse—developers can't even port their applications to run on ARM. At the same time, however, it also provided a platform for the creation of new, touch-friendly applications. There is one final wrinkle. The Office apps that ship with Windows RT are not licensed for use in any commercial fashion, whether for profit or otherwise. In a practical sense it's hard to see how this would ever be enforced, and it's inevitable that someone somewhere will end up breaking the rules, even if unwittingly. In fact, I daresay it's already happened: I'm sure some of the reviews of the Asus VivoTab RT and Microsoft Surface were written in whole or in part on Word in Windows RT. ........ So what about ARM's power advantage? That may still exist, but it's nowhere near as clear-cut as it was two years ago. Back then, Intel had nothing even vaguely comparable to the high-end ARM processors. But today it does, with its Medfield smartphone processor and Clover Trail tablet processor, both sold under its Atom brand. In the time it has taken Microsoft to bring Windows on ARM to market, ARM's once overwhelming battery life advantage has been erased. The ARM CPUs may still have a slight power use edge, but the difference will typically be dwarfed by the power consumption of the screen. The Intel processors, in turn, bring CPU performance that is probably best in class (or close to it), and most importantly of all the ability to run the full version of Windows 8 and existing Windows applications. The hardware could look identical to the user, but if it has Intel inside, the user experience will be quite different. Pricing still isn't known for all the Atom-powered Windows 8 PCs, but indications are that it won't be far off the price of the ARM machines.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1351101813371</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:03:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351102211542-123</Id><Topic><Title>Credit Suisse: "Intel removed from U.S. Focus List."</Title><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351096641010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:37:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>language!</Msg><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1351102211542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:10:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351102582269-124</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351090940101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351102582269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:16:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351102857219-125</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation most excellent thing Since Sliced Bread..</Title><Username>kwinfred64</Username><Timestamp>1351081238774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:20:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is true, on other blogs, major news…</Msg><Username>dickersonh73</Username><Timestamp>1351102857219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:20:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351103260377-126</Id><Topic><Title>Why INTC is UP today?</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1351017405081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:36:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you go through his ratings history, he always has two per Intel event. He keeps his reduce rating even if he raises his target. I think that it does not make any sense to raise the target and maintain the reduce. It must to him. Nomura Securities, Romit Shah, Intel ratings history. DATE RATING TARGET 10/17/2012 Reduce $19.00 @$21.79 10/9/2012 Reduce $22.00 @$21.90 9/12/2012 Reduce $22.00 9/10/2012 Reduce $22.00 @$23.26 7/18/2012 Reduce $25.00 @$26.21 7/12/2012 Reduce $25.00 7/10/2012 Reduce $25.00 5/10/2012 Reduce $25.00 4/23/2012 Reduce $25.00 @$27.45 4/18/2012 Reduce $23.00 @$27.95 4/10/2012 Reduce $23.00 1/20/2012 Reduce $23.00 @$26.38 1/18/2012 Reduce $21.00 @$25.39 1/11/2012 Reduce $21.00 1/10/2012 Reduce $21.00 12/13/2011 Reduce $21.00 @$23.56 10/19/2011 Reduce $18.00 @$24.24 10/12/2011 Reduce $18.00 9/6/2011 Reduce $18.00 8/19/2011 Reduce $18.00 8/17/2011 Reduce $18.00 @$22.81 7/21/2011 Reduce N/A 7/14/2011 Maintain N/A 5/18/2011 Maintain N/A 5/16/2011 Maintain N/A 4/29/2011 Maintain N/A 4/20/2011 Maintain N/A 4/18/2011 Maintain N/A 4/6/2011 Maintain N/A 12/10/2010 NewCoverage Buy</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351103260377</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:27:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351103682462-127</Id><Title>Options: SELLING JAN $21 CALLS</Title><Msg>There is a large number of JAN $21 call options being sold at $1.21. 30k contracts have traded so far. Selling the ITM calls encourages the option market maker to hedge (prepare for getting the shares in JAN) by shorting INTC. By holding the CALL sell order at a constant price, INTC is capped on the up side.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351103682462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351103911348-128</Id><Title>5 year support $19 will retest before end of year............</Title><Msg>hold off buy orders till than. yield will be over 5% . a really great investment with payout at only 30%..</Msg><Username>febru3012</Username><Timestamp>1351103911348</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:38:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351104334582-129</Id><Topic><Title>Hard to see who Windows RT is for....</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1351101813371</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:03:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two years ago starting a project for ARM made sense, but by the time RT was near there was no need as Intel had made such progress on energy efficient CPU's. Microsoft should have killed-off the RT project and launched with the x86 product line. RT tablets will not good for Microsoft or ARM as both brands will be associated with a product that is massively confusing to consumers and hugely limited in functionality.</Msg><Username>publicservice100</Username><Timestamp>1351104334582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:45:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351104557287-130</Id><Topic><Title>Hard to see who Windows RT is for....</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1351101813371</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:03:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's matter of months before MSFT declares that RT project is in dumps.</Msg><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1351104557287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:49:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351104802926-131</Id><Topic><Title>Hard to see who Windows RT is for....</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1351101813371</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:03:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree that the Intel version make more sense and add more value and performance. Microsoft is trying to prove they can do ARM but the goodies will be in the Intel pro version in 2 months.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351104802926</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:53:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351105093351-132</Id><Title>Whoa oh there she goes, watch out boy she'll chew you up</Title><Msg>Whoa oh there she goes, FB's a mannnnnnnn-eater.</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1351105093351</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:58:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351105129646-133</Id><Topic><Title>5 year support $19 will retest before end of year............</Title><Username>febru3012</Username><Timestamp>1351103911348</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:38:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry Jack, the bottom is in. I hear vaudeville is making a comeback..why don't you try out?</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351105129646</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351105313668-134</Id><Title>New 52wk low is coming.</Title><Msg>Technicals are bad, recession time.</Msg><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351105313668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351105601101-135</Id><Topic><Title>New 52wk low is coming.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351105313668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think it's time to throw on the iggy pile, Mr. stink.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351105601101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:06:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351105734665-136</Id><Topic><Title>Hard to see who Windows RT is for....</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1351101813371</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:03:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's matter of months before MSFT declares that RT project is in dumps." [Or maybe weeks. I did hear the initial run was bought out. I'm wondering who got all ten of them...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351105734665</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:08:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351105783996-137</Id><Topic><Title>New 52wk low is coming.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351105313668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tablets, Mobile are the future.....NOT PCs &amp; Servers.</Msg><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351105783996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:09:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351105915946-138</Id><Title>ARMH - new 52 week high... INTC new 52 week low</Title><Msg>keep the faith...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351105915946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351106009345-139</Id><Title>Apple unveils next-generation iMac with slimmer design and Ivy Bridge, starting at $1,299</Title><Msg>[Nice looking products...] Who said Apple's event was all about the little things? Apple just unveiled its first redesign to its iMac desktop in three years. The new all-in-one makes the widely expected leap to Intel's Ivy Bridge Core i5 and Core i7 processors, but also represents a much leaner and meaner replacement for the 2009-era template -- its edges are just 5mm thick, and it's constructed with "friction stir welding" as well as a gapless, less reflective display that's laminated together with the glass. Screen sizes remain the same and include both a 21.5-inch, 1080p model and a 27-inch, 2,560 x 1,400 model -- sorry, no Retina displays this year. They share 720p-capable front cameras with dual mics as well as NVIDIA's GeForce 600-era graphics, up to 32GB of RAM and a panoply of storage options that peak at 3TB of spinning storage, a 768GB SSD or what Apple calls a Fusion Drive that mixes both 128GB of flash with 1TB or 3TB of conventional storage (a hybrid drive, for those of us who've seen it before). There's no optical drive unless you plug in a USB option. The 21.5-inch model ships in November, and will set you back $1,299 for a 2.7GHz Core i5, 8GB of RAM and a 1TB hard drive; pony up for the 27-inch model at $1,799 and you'll get a 2.9GHz Core i5 as well as the same memory and storage. Apple's larger iMac doesn't ship until December, however, which will give some impulse buyers at least a brief respite. From Engadget</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351106009345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:13:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106092898-140</Id><Topic><Title>Options: SELLING JAN $21 CALLS</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351103682462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So the buyers are speculating that 22.21 is going to be a good or great price in January, so the assumption is that INTC will be selling for 23.00 or more by January... Sounds great!</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351106092898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:14:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351106113530-141</Id><Title>And Trump never used/dealt coke???????</Title><Msg>I got a bridge for sale in NYC.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351106113530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:15:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106154556-142</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351090940101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH MY... has anyone compared yahoo charts of INTC vs ARMH every yahoo chart option available 1D, 5D, 1M, 3M, 6M, YTD, 1Y, 2Y, 5Y, MAX just today, 11am EST, ARMH up over 4% ... how's INTC doing... keep the faith...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351106154556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:15:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106181230-143</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351090940101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ttt</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351106181230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:16:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351106259149-144</Id><Title>someone please outsource Trump asap</Title><Msg>the village idiot.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351106259149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:17:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351106309184-145</Id><Title>Recension worldwide.</Title><Msg>Humans are over 7 Billion, not enough resources for them, the world is doomed.</Msg><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351106309184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:18:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351106394061-146</Id><Title>it's Windows on Surface RT that's the greatest letdown of all...</Title><Msg>But it's Windows on Surface RT that's the greatest letdown of all, the lethal letdown, because it's not Windows 8, but Windows RT. You can't tell the difference by looking at them, but you certainly will once you use it. Windows RT is underpowered (everything opens and syncs slightly too slowly), under-functional (you cannot install a single app that's not available through the Windows RT app store, which offers a paltry selection), and under-planned (the built-in apps can't feel like Lite versions of something better). You'd be right to note that many of those limitations apply to the iPad as well, but no one could mistake iOS for OS X the way RT apes Windows 8. And even if it's a plight common to tablets, Microsoft—for better or worse—has hyped Surface RT as being so much more. In the end though, this is nothing more than Microsoft's tablet. And a buggy, at times broken one, at that, whose "ecosystem" feels more like a tundra. There's no Twitter or Facebook app, and the most popular 3rd party client breaks often. The Kindle app is completely unusable. There's no image editing software. A People app is supposed to give you all the social media access you'd ever need, but It's impossible to write on someone's Facebook wall through the People app, Surface's social hub; the only workaround is to load Internet Explorer. Blech. Something as simple as loading a video requires a jumbled process of USB importing, dipping in and out of the stripped-down desktop mode, opening a Video app, importing, going back into the Video app, and then playing. What. The app selection, overall, is worse than the already pathetic Windows Phone app fare, looking like the software equivalent to a barren Soviet grocery store. The difference is that Windows Phone, used in quick, informative bursts, skates by on the strength of its excellent with integrated features. At the moment, there's just not that much to do with Microsoft's über-tablet. Surface is weak because Windows RT is weak; a tepid tablet OS pretending to be a computer's. You can do work, yes. But productivity is limited to a "preview" (beta) version of Microsoft Office. It also hurts that Office requires plunging into Windows RT's Desktop mode, where users of actual Windows 8 are able to install a decade's worth of legacy software. Normally, this would compensate. But RT users can't install any of this older software. None of it. Desktop mode is entirely worthless in RT, a cruel tease of non-functionality. It'll only remind you of how much you can't do with your Surface, and is going to confuse the living hell out of most people who buy one—especially when Surface Pro, built on x86 architecture and perfectly compatible with all of those legacy programs, steps in a few months from now. From Gizmodo</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351106394061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:19:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106505914-147</Id><Topic><Title>Recension worldwide.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351106309184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel will be supported by its huge divident.</Msg><Username>divident_man</Username><Timestamp>1351106505914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106575128-148</Id><Topic><Title>it's Windows on Surface RT that's the greatest letdown of all...</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351106394061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should you buy it? No. The Surface, with an obligatory Touch Cover, is $600. That's a lot of money. Especially given that it's no laptop replacement, no matter how it looks or what Microsoft says. It's a tablet-plus, priced right alongside the iPad and in most ways inferior. That could change. Maybe there will be a new Touch Cover that retains the original's terrific physical qualities while actually allowing good typing. Maybe the quasi-vaporware Surface Pro, which eschews Windows RT in favor of the real-deal Win 8, will make all the difference, opening itself up to the open seas of PC software (for several hundred dollars more). Maybe the app store will look different in a month, or a year, and have anything to offer. Maybe. But remember that Windows Phone—which has swelled from mere hundreds, to tens of thousands, to over a hundred thousand app offerings over the past two years—is still a wasteland compared to iOS and Android. Poor precedent. Maybe Windows RT will be different. Maybe. But those maybes aren't worth putting money on. As much as it looked (and even felt) like it for a bit, the future isn't here quite yet. [WOA - DOA. No surprise that the ARM version is under-powered and over-priced...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351106575128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:22:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106821676-149</Id><Topic><Title>someone please outsource Trump asap</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351106259149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:17:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just "Village" sized ????</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351106821676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351106901695-150</Id><Title>China making slow, steady economic recovery</Title><Msg>China's economy is making a slow, steady recovery from its weakest period of growth in three years, a survey of purchasing managers signaled on Wednesday, with new orders and output at their highest in months. [China recovering. Economic news in the US is pretty good on housing, employment and consumer sentiment. Conclusion: Chump Street has gotten it wrong again. And hey Chump Street? Where is that huge honking miss that you promised us on Q3? There wasn't ANY. On revenues or earnings!!!]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351106901695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:28:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351107041394-151</Id><Title>October Surprise! Donald Trump Reminds Us He’s Worthless</Title><Msg>At long last, Donald Trump released his highly anticipated "October surprise" on YouTube today. Rumors were swirling for days about what the major announcement was going to be; the announcement that the animated toupe said was "bordering on gigantic." The only thing about it "bordering on gigantic" is Trump's boiling red face. The statement, as it was transcribed: "I have a deal for the president, a deal that I don't believe he can refuse, and I hope he doesn't. If Barack Obama opens up and gives his college records and applications, and if he gives his passport applications and records, I will give, to a charity of his choice—inner-city children in Chicago, American Cancer Society, AIDS research, anything he wants—a check, immediately, for $5 million."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351107041394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351107095097-152</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - new 52 week high... INTC new 52 week low</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351105915946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351107095097</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:31:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351107322943-153</Id><Topic><Title>Options: SELLING JAN $21 CALLS</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351103682462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not sure what you mean being sold, someone else buys them as well :) The open interest is low , only 5545. beside the MM will go for the max pain if possible, so far he wasn't able to do that with the Oct max pain which was 24</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351107322943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:35:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351107438832-154</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - new 52 week high... INTC new 52 week low</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351105915946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Enjoying the pain of others is beyond dispicable. But, go ahead and do what makes you happy.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1351107438832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:37:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351107847571-155</Id><Title>BUY MAGIC JACK...CALL</Title><Msg>Telephone Number Sharing Patent Might be the Most Valuable Telecom Patent Granted This Decade</Msg><Username>chkto40</Username><Timestamp>1351107847571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:44:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351108001853-156</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - new 52 week high... INTC new 52 week low</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351105915946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>getanid61 is a low life, no one takes him seriously. He bought NVDA when it was around 22$ and pump it all the way down, and with no divvy his pain doubled. lol</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351108001853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:46:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351108048625-157</Id><Topic><Title>China making slow, steady economic recovery</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351106901695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:28:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, Wallis, I know a lot about China and I can assure you the biggest lie out there is the notion that China is growing. If you want to believe commissars, then pick any number between 7 to 10% annual growth rate. If you want to believe the rate of electricity consumption it's 2% max (electricity production = consumption..you don't store electritricy; and that rate always outpaces GDP growth). With a rate of growth of electricity production in China of 2.1%, China's general economy is not growing at all. And, here's a simple quiz: unless you're Bain capital, what has China done for you? Compare Japan: first online with High speed rail; Walkman format that AAPL apes today; the high compression auto with tight bore cylinders; small print heads that HP ripped off....etc etc... and China???? cheap goods for less, and suck away american labor jobs. An don't be confused by 1.3 billion humanoids over there....1.1 billion are an eternally damned underclass that will never get out of the rice paddy, and will never have a delicacy other than boiled cat for lunch. China is neither growing nor is it a force to be reckoned with.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351108048625</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:47:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351108529632-158</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - new 52 week high... INTC new 52 week low</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351105915946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably this Friday... next week will be shades of grey... but I see light at the beyond...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1351108529632</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351108647802-159</Id><Topic><Title>someone please outsource Trump asap</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351106259149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:17:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Global village idiot.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351108647802</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351108963731-160</Id><Topic><Title>I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1293550442000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-12-28 10:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cisco tanked today. It's been a teeny-bopper ever since Lucy touted it.</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1351108963731</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:02:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351109411463-161</Id><Topic><Title>Options: SELLING JAN $21 CALLS</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351103682462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When I look at the BID SIZE and ASK SIZE, the BID SIZE or number of contracts for sale at the bid price says 50. The ASK SIZE says 2,310. Earlier it was 50 and 5,000. The implied volatility is low (22) meaning their is more selling pressure than buying pressure. These appear to be SELL TO OPEN and tomorrow the open interest will 37k.. BID/ASK is $1.15/$1.16 I don't give much weight to the MAX PAIN target. MAX PAIN was created before online trading, streaming quotes and before the commision cost dropped to near nothing. My theory is that the option market maker hedges his position immediately and therefore does not really care about the max pain. If he cannot match the ITM call sell to open with another buyer, he will take the other side with the price is right. When he takes the other side, he can get the shares or not. For the ITM calls he writes, he shorts the stock for the calls he bought. If INTC goes up, he gets the shares to fill the short. If Intel goes down, he is short and breaks even on the premium for buying the call. IMO, this is part of a dividend arbitraging that will play out on Nov ex-dividend day.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351109411463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:10:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351109688693-162</Id><Topic><Title>Options: SELLING JAN $21 CALLS</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351103682462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not exactly. It looks like they are trying to buy the NOV $19 calls for zero premium so they can exercise calls early and steal the dividend. The NOV $19 call premium at BID is zero. They will match those shares with zero premium in the money put options they buy. The put options at $24 and above for NOV, DEC and JAN are close to zero. IMO, shares will start going up when their is volume on ITM put options.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351109688693</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:14:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351110006880-163</Id><Topic><Title>High Noon, EST make sure to check Donald Trump's twitter !</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351093888723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Thought it's also ludicrous that [Mitt Romney] doesn't want the country he leads to know who he really is. LOL." You are a d-bag.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351110006880</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:20:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351111431568-164</Id><Topic><Title>High Noon, EST make sure to check Donald Trump's twitter !</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351093888723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROMNEY took a shredder to the official files documenting his work. ROMNEY took the hard drives from the systems when he left. ROMNEY BAIN documents are not public. ROMNEY Olympic documents do not exist because he took them with him. ROMNEY Govenor documents do not exist because he took the system hard drives on departure. ROMNEY took active and intentional efforts to avoid transparency. Obama has not. When Obama released a short form and long form official birth certificates, did that do anything or did those demanding the release simply say it was a forgery? Was it accepted? No. Did it change the story that Trump and the birthers chirped? No. Did it solve anything? No. Is there anyone in the Republican party officially requesting this? They are not shy about "speaking their mind". TRUMP is such a cheapskate that he would not pay off if the wager were satisfied. He donated $3.7m over a 20 year period. $165,000 per year average. Trump’s philanthropy over the past 20 years, which has been channeled through the Donald J. Trump Foundation. A TSG review of the group’s Internal Revenue Service returns dating back to 1990 reveals that Trump, the foundation’s president, may be the least charitable billionaire in the United States. How miserly is The Donald? From 1990 through 2009, Trump has personally donated a total of just $3.7 million to his foundation, which was incorporated in 1987. In fact, the billionaire is not even the largest contributor to his own charitable organization.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351111431568</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351111877530-165</Id><Topic><Title>it's Windows on Surface RT that's the greatest letdown of all...</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351106394061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seeing a lot of reviews that are negative on Windows RT. Almost all of them are asking customers to wait and go in for Windows 8 !!! I love it!!!!</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1351111877530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:51:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351112389020-166</Id><Topic><Title>Options: SELLING JAN $21 CALLS</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351103682462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The NOV $19 call premium at BID is zero. ----------------------------------------------------- Alex, i see BID 2.60 for NOV 19$ How could it be zero in the ops is 21.46? am i missing something? Also the NOV $24 is 0.02 while the put NOV 24$ is 2.6$ range ..</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351112389020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:59:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351113099306-167</Id><Topic><Title>Is INTC Ready to Break Out?</Title><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1351086375644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:46:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great share. Many thanks</Msg><Username>clairvnrh52236</Username><Timestamp>1351113099306</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:11:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351113172474-168</Id><Topic><Title>Is INTC Ready to Break Out?</Title><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1351086375644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:46:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you mean with acne?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351113172474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:12:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351113224055-169</Id><Topic><Title>High Noon, EST make sure to check Donald Trump's twitter !</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351093888723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>really worried about your Kenyan, eh ?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351113224055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:13:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351113315836-170</Id><Topic><Title>October Surprise! Donald Trump Reminds Us He’s Worthless</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1351107041394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:30:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>c_w's october surprise is rumored to be you in a hot tub with your husband to be</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351113315836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351113433417-171</Id><Topic><Title>Recension worldwide.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351106309184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah!!!! down 7 points on 1800 = 12.6k so, the dividenT will make that back how long after I am dead ?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351113433417</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:17:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351113495738-172</Id><Topic><Title>New 52wk low is coming.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351105313668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>really? thanks for the hot tip.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351113495738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:18:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351113663309-173</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation most excellent thing Since Sliced Bread..</Title><Username>kwinfred64</Username><Timestamp>1351081238774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:20:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we already know what's up, armh is up.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351113663309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:21:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351114027445-174</Id><Topic><Title>Options: SELLING JAN $21 CALLS</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351103682462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very interesting. I see two NOV options at $19. One has a bid of $2.60 (INTC121117C0001900) like you point out. The other has a bid of $2.46 (INTC121117C00019000). The latter was the one I was seeing on my streaming Schwab display. It is also the one seen on OptionMonster for the NOV monthly. CBOE has the $19 NOV call at $2.45 bid. Maybe the $2.60 one is a weekly that expires on next Friday. Don't know.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351114027445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:27:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351114033687-175</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - new 52 week high... INTC new 52 week low</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351105915946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for the faithful</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351114033687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:27:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351114059254-176</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351090940101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fyi..</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351114059254</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:27:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351114129273-177</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH vs INTC</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351090940101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just the facts... OH MY... has anyone compared yahoo charts of INTC vs ARMH every yahoo chart option available 1D, 5D, 1M, 3M, 6M, YTD, 1Y, 2Y, 5Y, MAX just today, 11am EST, ARMH up over 4% ... how's INTC doing... keep the faith...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351114129273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351115015119-178</Id><Title>Intel today released latest processor price list.</Title><Msg>Not one of the over 200 different processor chips dropped in price. Not one! Looks like demand continues to be relatively strong. Especially now that things don't look good for their only real competition, AMD.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1351115015119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:43:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351115562253-179</Id><Topic><Title>Intel today released latest processor price list.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1351115015119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:43:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not one of the over 200 different processor chips dropped in price. Not one! -------------------- Yeppp! Only the share price drops in price. TOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1351115562253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:52:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351115771943-180</Id><Title>worst case is $16 in 2013 recession</Title><Msg>until then we slowly drift down</Msg><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1351115771943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:56:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351116087296-181</Id><Topic><Title>High Noon, EST make sure to check Donald Trump's twitter !</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351093888723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not really. I am more worried about the United States. The Republicans bring too much social legislation for my taste. They are worried about Sharia law and yet try to impose their own version. The advisors that Romney has chosen scare me. They do not understand the middle east and will bury us. I do not know what Romney stands for this week, let alone next week or the week after. Whoever is elected, the obstructism will continue in the Senate. It will take 60 votes to override a secret hold and neither party will have 60 votes. If the Democrats win, nothing will change. If the Republicans win, I expect Democratic pay back. Whoever is elected President, they will have to deal with the political extremism. Romney could probably get more done trying to compromise with the Democrats than Obama could get done by trying to compromise with the Republicans.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1351116087296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351116101081-182</Id><Topic><Title>New 52wk low is coming.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351105313668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Plenty of time for a new 52 week low. about 51 weeks. some see one more rally in the markets left, then an ending to the 3 plus year bull market. The liklihood of INTC getting back to the lofty heights reached earlier this year anytime next year very doubtful . qqq's approaching rsi 30 on the daily charts, 65.00 has held so far, could see a bounce off that, but so far, the technicals suck, rsi and macd still firmly pointed downward. as for ARMH, seems most of the day was filled with sellers of ARMH, not buyers.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1351116101081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:01:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351116697877-183</Id><Topic><Title>Options: SELLING JAN $21 CALLS</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351103682462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not exactly. It looks like they are trying to buy the NOV $19 calls for zero premium so they can exercise calls early and steal the dividend. The NOV $19 call premium at BID is zero. They will match those shares with zero premium in the money put options they buy. The put options at $24 and above for NOV, DEC and JAN are close to zero. IMO, shares will start going up when their is volume on ITM put options. ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- ok,i see, (it takes few times to read due to my lack of experience with options): 1. they are buying NOV 19$ ITM that has zero premium 2. they are buying the 24$ (or above) close to zero premium- in order to protect from downside ... (?) 3. before expiration they will exercise the calls to get the divy and then they will ride the puts options.. hope i got it right</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1351116697877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351117471187-184</Id><Topic><Title>worst case is $16 in 2013 recession</Title><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1351115771943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:56:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, we've just seen the worst case: you arrived on the message board.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351117471187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:24:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351117581620-185</Id><Topic><Title>New 52wk low is coming.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1351105313668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not Servers ...... LOL</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1351117581620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351117821678-186</Id><Topic><Title>worst case is $16 in 2013 recession</Title><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1351115771943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:56:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>worst case will drift to $20....yesterday when Dow was down 230pts Intel held up - looks like we have hit the bottom</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1351117821678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351117879001-187</Id><Title>Obama gutting Intel and other semi firms.</Title><Msg>He is clueless of how to get 4+% growth. We are currently at a miniscule 1.5%.</Msg><Username>weightbayou</Username><Timestamp>1351117879001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:31:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351118426038-188</Id><Topic><Title>worst case is $16 in 2013 recession</Title><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1351115771943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:56:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>counter_insurgency_buffoon posted the same trash on the MSFT board,imagine that.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1351118426038</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:40:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351118962694-189</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BATATAGGLIA SAID LAST NIGHT</Title><Username>xtremeskier33</Username><Timestamp>955040744000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2000-04-06 13:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"that Intel was one of his FAVORITE picks. If its good enough for the Batman, its good enough for me." Well, I also require that it be good enough for Marc Haines. Has Me. Haines mentioned his opinion on INTC lately?</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1351118962694</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351119527472-190</Id><Topic><Title>worst case is $16 in 2013 recession</Title><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1351115771943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:56:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the markets are a very long way from "the bottom". the qqq's are a measley 7 percent off bull market highs. When this bull finally ends, if it hasn't already, the drop will be far more significant, and for INTC, worse.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1351119527472</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:58:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351119760310-191</Id><Topic><Title>worst case is $16 in 2013 recession</Title><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1351115771943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:56:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the markets are a very long way from "the bottom"." That's exactly what you were saying in March 2009 as I recall.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1351119760310</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:02:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351120370532-192</Id><Title>Young Women Voting Early Coast to Coast for Mitt Romney</Title><Msg>Surge in Women Voting for Mitt Romney for President of USA and Their Reasons By ladies_4_romney . Oct 24, 2012 2:37 PM Women Democrat Voters and Others are Switching to Mitt Romney in Ohio Michigan Florida Virginia Pennsylvania Wisconsin New York- New Jersey ( East Coast to West Coast ) The Democrat Ladies for Romney in all 50 States Ladies are Switching from Obama very Fast. Read this and you too will Change and become a "Romney Democrat" for a Stronger USA Economy and honest leadership. Women, Jewish Democrats and others are Switching to Mitt Romney for President. Women Review Debate 3 : First, Governor Mitt Romney Pasted the President Test, Ready to Lead USA. By USA_Jewish_Women 10 22 2012 Great Impression: Mitt Romney's Stunning Turnaround in Past 3 Debates after Huge Negative Ads. The Reasons for Change is Obama has Lost the Support and Respect with Women Voters and Others. People Notice: Most Men and Women are Turned Off Against Barack Obama most everywhere and Across All 50 States, Here is the the Review of Debate 3 on October 22, 2012 By a Jewish Women Focus Group of 7,890 Women Connecticut Across America Our Strong Plea for Change in the White House, Why? The following reasons listed bellow. Note: This review is a agreement amongst a Group of almost 8000 Women watching debates. During the Debate 3, President Barack Obama was Arrogant, Disrespectfully, Angry, Rude and Condescending to Governor Mitt Romney. Obama did not Act or Look Presidential. We Feel Governor Mitt Romney Pasted the Presidential Test and is Ready to Lead USA We Support Mitt Romney, found him to be a Smart, Respectable and Decent Gentleman. Governor Mitt Romney Looked Much More Presidential, Ready to be Commander-in-Chief. Mitt Romney said America Needs a Strong Economy in order to have a Strong Military for our National Security right now and the Future. ...... We All Agree. Women came away from this Debate with a Very Good Impression of Governor Mitt Romney, in that he would be a “ A Safe Pair of Hands.” in Foreign Policy and a Strong Economy. We Trust Him More. Obama lied about Libya on 9 11 ( a 8 hour fire fight, Obama watched did nothing) In Foreign Policy We feel Mitt Romney is Tough Enough to do what’s necessary, but laid-back enough not to do too much and get us into another war. Miit Romney Did Not attack President Obama's Policies, he Simply Pointed Out a Few Needed Improvements in a Very Respectable Way. During the debate Governor Mitt Romney Seemed More Like a Leader, Smart, Respectable, Thoughtful and Considerate. He looked and Acted more Like the New American President that our Nation and the rest of the World Needs so Disparately in These Troubling Economic Times. Governor Mitt Romney was Calm, Thoughtful, Relaxed, Steady, Looked Like A Smart Gentleman and More Presidential. Romney Looked and Acted as if he was Ready to Take the Job as Commander-in-Chief ASAP. President Barack Obama Looked more like a Very Disparate Candidate and Challenger, very Negative, Acted like a Disrespectful Attack Dog Instead of the President of the United States. Mitt Romney Expressed his Concern about Iran's Nuclear Threat that is 4 Years Closer and the USA Support of Israel, our Good Friend and Middle East Ally. The strained relationship with the Obama Administration. Tonight Romney Impressed the Ladies Very much, in that a Vote for Him is a Vote for American Security, Peace and Safety, a Strong Economy, a Strong Military, Millions of Higher Paying Jobs, Prosperity for the Middle Class and Others. and a Quiet Peaceful Life for USA and all People. The World is Much to Scary these days, Americans Aren’t Looking For a Scary Arrogant, Angry. Rude, Disrespectfully and Weak President. Barack Obama is Not the One to Lead us Any Longer Tonight we Came Away with the Feeling that President Barack Obama is extremely a more Scary Candidate then the President of USA. We are Concerned about America's Weaken Relationship with Israel, a Nuclear Iran, our Weaken Economy and the Huge 16 Trillion Dollars Debt, that in itself Threatens our National Security. Americans, Black, White, Latinos, Wake Up, USA Debt is Bigger than our Gross National Product. We Can Not Afford Four More Years of President Obama's Spending, Borrowing and lies. We Can Not Afford Another 5 or 6 Trillion Dollars in More Debt From China or Other Countries. Our Jewish Women's Focus Group of almost 8000 Democrats Therefore Proudly Endorse Governor Mitt Romney as the Next President of the United States of America. Vote for Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan Before It's to Late. Do it Now ....ASAP Public Notice: We Feel Strongly that President Barack Obama is No Longer Fit to Lead USA.</Msg><Username>political_gangsters</Username><Timestamp>1351120370532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:12:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351123708397-193</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation most excellent thing Since Sliced Bread..</Title><Username>kwinfred64</Username><Timestamp>1351081238774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:20:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have been through all the articles,found it very interesting to spend my money on. Thanks for bringing it into light.Hope for the best in times ahead.</Msg><Username>espinoza.flynn43</Username><Timestamp>1351123708397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:08:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351123926858-194</Id><Topic><Title>High Noon, EST make sure to check Donald Trump's twitter !</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1351093888723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama compromise? jobs billl was for more gov't jobs, more debt, you call that compromise? where was the compromise when Obama and his congress rammed thru an unread medical/health bill? you only seem to see it from the left. I say GWB was bad, Obama is bad. And what about the pipeline? what about the Boeing plant? what about the extreme favoritism for unions? We need a leader who plays it down the middle. I hate to even say it but Obama makes Slick look fantastic and I thought he was awful at the time. I argue with family members when they try to tell me Bush was good. No I tell them he was awful! Obama should have fixed the tax structure first and then tried to take on healthcare. People with jobs will pay more taxes, people without jobs can't. And people with businesses won't hire if they are threatened with higher taxes and that's where we are now. When Obama talks business, anyone who runs a busine big or small can tell he hasn't a clue what he is talking about. Go ahed and try to run a business and pay your employees well, provide medical, pay payroll taxes, EDD taxes, worker's compensation, pay, pay, pay, and see what is left over and how many hours a week do you work doing that? It isn't easy and then he says YOU !, YOU! didn't build that business!, the man is an #$%$ for that statement, he has no idea what it takes to run a business. I just think we need a change and I am not big on Bible huggers either and I think humans need regulation so I do see both sides. Being President is a no win job.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351123926858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:12:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351124026255-195</Id><Topic><Title>worst case is $16 in 2013 recession</Title><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1351115771943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:56:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so that's why I bght Intc about 12.00 way back then, what was I thinking? Not a very good buy. Outperformed by many miles would have been the SIRI .06.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1351124026255</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351124582121-196</Id><Topic><Title>Obama gutting Intel and other semi firms.</Title><Username>weightbayou</Username><Timestamp>1351117879001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:31:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WASHINGTON -- Two hours after the U.S. Consulate came under attack in Benghazi, Libya, the White House was told that a militant group was claiming responsibility for the violence that killed the U.S. ambassador and three other Americans. A State Department email sent to intelligence officials and the White House situation room said the Islamist group Ansar al-Sharia claimed responsibility on Facebook and Twitter, and also called for an attack on the U.S. Embassy in Tripoli.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351124582121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:23:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351124614692-197</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BATATAGGLIA SAID LAST NIGHT</Title><Username>xtremeskier33</Username><Timestamp>955040744000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2000-04-06 13:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe ? how old is that? cause you do know Joe is gone, don't you?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351124614692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:23:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351124689071-198</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BATATAGGLIA SAID LAST NIGHT</Title><Username>xtremeskier33</Username><Timestamp>955040744000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2000-04-06 13:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>April 2000</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1351124689071</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:24:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351127239662-199</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BATATAGGLIA SAID LAST NIGHT</Title><Username>xtremeskier33</Username><Timestamp>955040744000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2000-04-06 13:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"cause you do know Joe is gone, don't you?" What do you mean by "gone"? You mean he no longer appears on Squawk Box with Marc Haines?</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1351127239662</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351127689039-200</Id><Topic><Title>Young Women Voting Early Coast to Coast for Mitt Romney</Title><Username>political_gangsters</Username><Timestamp>1351120370532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:12:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent!!! This message needs to be at the top, so I'm bumping it...</Msg><Username>search616</Username><Timestamp>1351127689039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:14:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351128699522-201</Id><Topic><Title>worst case is $16 in 2013 recession</Title><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1351115771943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:56:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>longs should be asking what's the best case so they can get out with no losses, the overhead resistance is replete with buyers who thought they caught "the bottom". Intc is already in a bear market and the best chances to sell long gone.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1351128699522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351129772342-202</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation most excellent thing Since Sliced Bread..</Title><Username>kwinfred64</Username><Timestamp>1351081238774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:20:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For every times i buy my shares, i depend on your such contributions online because it give me full strength to invest more safely.thank you.</Msg><Username>nash.summers56</Username><Timestamp>1351129772342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:49:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351130204169-203</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BATATAGGLIA SAID LAST NIGHT</Title><Username>xtremeskier33</Username><Timestamp>955040744000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2000-04-06 13:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a stupid loser sick MF. Anyone that would constantly post #$%$ about someone he knows full well is dead will get his comeuppance. There is no difference in that and me telling you your #$%$ wife should and probably will die of cancer. Your mother also deserved to suffer when she died you effing POS.</Msg><Username>bob_dylan_64</Username><Timestamp>1351130204169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:56:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351131348679-204</Id><Topic><Title>junk is junk</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351087519276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no power to go up and hold the gains, I told you so! short short short short short!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1351131348679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:15:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351134178138-205</Id><Topic><Title>Options: SELLING JAN $21 CALLS</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351103682462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is EXACTLY what I think is going on. Since they own the PUT options, they can also exercise the puts early, "put" the shares, and not have to fund the $5 intrinsic value between the CALL and PUT for more than a couple days.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351134178138</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:02:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351135032999-206</Id><Topic><Title>Options: SELLING JAN $21 CALLS</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351103682462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you may be giving the option market maker more influence than he deserves. 30k contracts only equals 3 million shares on a stock that averages around 45 million shares traded daily. I doubt very seriously he'll be shorting INTC to the hilt anyway if the market jumps big and only if it tanks.</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351135032999</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:17:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351135471706-207</Id><Topic><Title>Options: SELLING JAN $21 CALLS</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1351103682462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep in mind I'm no options trader. Just a rational thinker.</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351135471706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:24:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351136303704-208</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is the next RIMM</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1350510973251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:56:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are living in 1990. --------------- 1990????? Is that your birthdate? I think maybe rom was the OS back then. LOL</Msg><Username>herbal_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351136303704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:38:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>