<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354942858489-1</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will rule the cloud</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354911571979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:19:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OpenStack is a project started by Rackspace and they shipped their first release in Oct 2012. The Platinium and Gold (Intel) members do most of the heavy lifting. I don't recognize any ARM representation in the group although there must be someone. All the work was done in Python with Linux defining the API. Getting OpenStack to run on some ARM CPU that runs Linux (Android) should be pretty easy. OpenStack is not "ARM compliant". OpenStack conforms to the OpenStack specification. OpenStack will run on an ARM chip if the that ARM chip and its version of OS provide the proper OpenStack API support. If the purchasing manager decides that the ARM based server offers the best solution to his problem, he will buy it. If the approving manager decides that there is a better solution, he will buy it. He will decide based on performance, power consumption, cost, how it will fit into his existing equipment and future plans. Will the ARM server be faster? No. It might be for FP workloads but nothing in the OpenStack. Will the ARM server be lower power? No. Intel power optimization, advanced process and code restructuring will easily match any ARM vendor offering. Will the ARM server be cheaper? No. Intel cost per transistor will make it easy to set their price right on top of ARM vendor products.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354942858489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 00:00:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354944626244-2</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will rule the cloud</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354911571979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:19:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Will the ARM server be cheaper? No. Intel cost per transistor will make it easy to set their price right on top of ARM vendor products." Intel currently charges way beyond cost per transistor for its server chips in the presence of little competition from AMD. With ARM based solutions entering the fray, since the ARM licensee is not developing the core IP and only the peripheral IP, their costs are much lower than Intel's which has to amortize its entire R&amp;D costs through its sales. This means the ARM licensees can operate at a much lower ASP than Intel which will drive down Intel ASP. This is the threat to Intel. They may not lose business but they will have to reduce their ASPs not to lose it because there will be a cheaper viable alternative than what they're current charging for their solution. So they may rule the cloud but the cloud will come down to Earth.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354944626244</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 00:30:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354949064979-3</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will rule the cloud</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354911571979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:19:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel currently charges way beyond cost per transistor for its server chips in the presence of little competition from AMD. " I agree with you. Today, Intel prefers "value prices" rather than "cost plus prices". "With ARM based solutions entering the fray, since the ARM licensee is not developing the core IP and only the peripheral IP, their costs are much lower than Intel's which has to amortize its entire R&amp;D costs through its sales. " This is where I disagree with your analysis. ARM licensees do not develop the core IP but they pay licenses and royalty fees for each part. They also have to negotiate wafer starts from foundries. The cost of that ARM + licensee + foundary food chain is higher than the cost (not price) that Intel charges. Does Intel charge a higher ASP today? Yes. Does that mean that Intel will NOT set "cost plus" price some products? Intel will "cost plus" price products in the future as they have in the past. "This is the threat to Intel. They may not lose business but they will have to reduce their ASPs not to lose it because there will be a cheaper viable alternative than what they're current charging for their solution. So they may rule the cloud but the cloud will come down to Earth." This is the key part of your argument. Intel ASP "will go lower" because of some ARM product offering. That might be true but Intel will have NO problems in being more than competitive. Intel cost per transistor is lower and it will always be lower than any ARM product chain. The key word you used is "viable". We will know how viable these ARM parts are when one is produced and its operation can be measured.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354949064979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 01:44:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354949953577-4</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will rule the cloud</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354911571979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:19:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel currently charges way beyond cost per transistor for its server chips in the presence of little competition from AMD." I agree but you should not confuse value pricing with cost plus pricing. Intel will not like it but they will not hesitate to cost plus price. The cost of the ARM IP, licensee development and foundry wafer charges for these chips will be higher than Intel's costs. You may think differently but we will just have to disagree. Intel will put 2x the transistors on their 14nm wafer than any process that will be used by any ARM microserver chip. Your key point is that ARM licensee products will pressure Intel ASP. True but Intel will have no problem competitively pricing products. The key word that you use is "viable". We will have to wait until there is a product and it can be measured.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354949953577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 01:59:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354956304001-5</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will rule the cloud</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354911571979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:19:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only point I'm making is there is an order of magnitude difference between the cost of manufacturing a chip and its selling price currently. If its costs $10 to produce it on average, it sells for $100. Going from this scenario to a cost plus pricing even with the advantage of process superiority and better integration lowering cost compared to ARM alternatives is a huge step backward for Intel. It's market cap may shrink.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354956304001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 03:45:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354965801512-6</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will rule the cloud</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354911571979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:19:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeh temporarily Intel may have some pressure so think what ARM will have: HELL. Them at some point ARM will be the next AMD. ouch.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1354965801512</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 06:23:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354976451101-7</Id><Title>There will always be competition. Intel needs to be cutting edge.</Title><Msg>If PaulO gets the Apple deal signed before he leaves Intel, he will go down in History at Intel as a superstar.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1354976451101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 09:20:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354977945886-8</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will rule the cloud</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354911571979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:19:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The key word that you use is "viable". We will have to wait until there is a product and it can be measured. ----- The first ARM servers have started to arrive. Do a google for Boston Viridis. A 96 core, 96GB RAM, 24x 256GB SSD drives 2U box burns 150 - 200 watts when running different benchmarks...</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1354977945886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 09:45:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354979254366-9</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will rule the cloud</Title><Username>ex.goldbug</Username><Timestamp>1354911571979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 15:19:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Boston Viridis appliance comes in a configuration that supports OpenStack. When its available, it will be a cloud player. I'm surprised these guys got to product this early. AFAIK, Calxeda, who supplies the SOC, has only been working on this for 3 years.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1354979254366</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 10:07:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354984468183-10</Id><Title>Intel in 2012: Singing the PC Blues at Motley Fool 11:01am EST</Title><Msg>see today's yahoo news</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354984468183</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 11:34:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354987840695-11</Id><Title>Boston Viridis Servers</Title><Msg>New thread .... thank you Yahoo for state of the art message board. 8-) You have to be very careful when comparing benchmark results. Comparing benchmark results is a game. The goal of the game is to figure out how the benchmark publisher has "tilted" the results. Intel has done it but the ARM newbies have much to learn about this art of benchmarking. The Boston Viridis ARM Apache benchmarks are among the first released. There are some more per CPU results on Phoronix that I will have some comments on. Boston Ltd is a UK company that currently builds and configures servers based on AMD, Intel and now ARM CPU. It will be nice to have a single point of reference when discussing what can be done with ARM. Boston Ltd has announced it will be releasing a line of green (Viridis) servers on the Calxeda ARM chips. If I read it correctly, they have released a 32-bit server version that contains up to a dozen of the 32-bit Calxeda cards and is currently priced at $50,000. This configuration contains up to 48 4-core, 32-bit ARM CPU, 192GB of memory on 12 of their 4-socket boards. The system contains 24 SSD drives of size ??? The server is a 192 32-bit core, 192GB system. The only benchmark that I can find is the Apache benchmark that they released on this new ARM system and compared it to a standard 80-watt Sandy Bridge system Xeon E3-1240 processor. Calxeda totaled the worst case power specs for the Intel CPU, memory and disk drives but not for their system. Calxeda matched the two configurations but the Intel CPU was IO constrained and the CPU was running at 14% load. They were comparing 14% of a Sandy Bridge to their solution. google for more detail on the first Intel reply to their Apache benchmarks. Xeon breaks Calxeda's ARM in Apache benchmark</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354987840695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 12:30:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354992932233-12</Id><Topic><Title>Intel in 2012: Singing the PC Blues at Motley Fool 11:01am EST</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354984468183</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 11:34:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>congratulations too funny, see you dug up some dirt to make your day. Don't pull on that thing too hard, you might do damage</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354992932233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 13:55:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354993069501-13</Id><Topic><Title>Boston Viridis Servers</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354987840695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 12:30:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Part of the AMD settlement was INtel compilers could no longer turn off the optimizations when it recognized an AMD CPU...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1354993069501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 13:57:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354993629514-14</Id><Title>BIG NEWS: Intel-based Android tablet coming!!!!</Title><Msg>Google 'Red Ridge' .. techradar is the most interesting article - Label filed with FCC - Label was on PRODUCTION DEVICE ...so commercial version right around the corner - techradar article says processor is Bay Trail!!!! Can it be true????</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354993629514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 14:07:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354993756249-15</Id><Topic><Title>BIG NEWS: Intel-based Android tablet coming!!!!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354993629514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 14:07:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sing it, sister! HI-HO WEAVERINO!!! TOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354993756249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 14:09:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354994932860-16</Id><Topic><Title>BIG NEWS: Intel-based Android tablet coming!!!!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354993629514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 14:07:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hate to say it but - TF/Lucy is demented</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354994932860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 14:28:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354995432510-17</Id><Topic><Title>BIG NEWS: Intel-based Android tablet coming!!!!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354993629514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 14:07:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for reading and responding to my messages, no-life buttplug. TOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354995432510</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 14:37:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354995494847-18</Id><Topic><Title>Boston Viridis Servers</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354987840695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 12:30:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. True. Now Intel HAS to make the assumption that the silicon supports a feature the way the Intel CPU does if the feature bit is on. It is not about the compiler but more about the hand optimized runtime libraries that are shipped with the compiler. The issue is more complex than the simple minded thinking "Intel cheated" and "AMD had to go to court for a fair deal". Now, the Intel runtime library code checks the FEATURE bits and if set, assumes that the feature is properly supported on the silicon. If the bit is set, is an AMD CPU and it has a bug, there is no way to turn off the feature and no way to avoid running the program on the AMD CPU. Example. There are some subtle differences in the way AMD handles the AVX instructions. The GIMP math library built with GCC runs fine on Intel Sandy Bridge but fails intermittantly on the AMD Bulldozer parts when using AVX instructions. AMD users cannot correctly run the program and if the program was compiled with the Intel compiler could not check to see if it was on an AMD part. For some fun reading, google amd avx problems</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1354995494847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 14:38:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354997304550-19</Id><Title>too funny, lucy nuff, coinmaker 77, wdgrowblow, etc</Title><Msg>thinking he is probably a paid basher and of course, an azzwipe. Sitting home in his soon to be foreclosed duplex.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354997304550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:08:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354999035674-20</Id><Topic><Title>too funny, lucy nuff, coinmaker 77, wdgrowblow, etc</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354997304550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:08:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imagine lying on your deathbed thinking you wasted your adult life bashing Intel and trying to run the US economy into the dirt. Such will be the end of the life of Lucy...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354999035674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:37:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354999036990-21</Id><Topic><Title>If you are long INTC and worried - Listen to Paul Otellini at the Bernstein Conference</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354783997804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 03:53:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It took Intel 10 years to figure it out. It will take them at least 5-7 years. It may be too late by then. Trigate is a HUGE breakthrough, should make Intel the Performance leader for the forseeable future. ARM cannot compete in Performance or Power.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354999036990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:37:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354999190123-22</Id><Topic><Title>Intel on Track for 5nm Process</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354919085227</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 17:24:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has 5nm in the near future. What does ARM have? Butkus...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354999190123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:39:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354999345477-23</Id><Title>The problem with TSMC's 20nm process is they have given up performance</Title><Msg>for low power. Intel now rules the Performance world, and will continue to do so for the forseeable future.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354999345477</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:42:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354999436847-24</Id><Topic><Title>too funny, lucy nuff, coinmaker 77, wdgrowblow, etc</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354997304550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:08:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Horrible thing to say but- hoping the end is near for him. When he gets to the judgement area upstairs, they won't be able to push the down button fast enough. His relatives will probably bury him in an asbestos suit.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354999436847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:43:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354999603930-25</Id><Title>Intel's Latest Low-Power Battle Plans</Title><Msg>Conclusion Intel's plans indicate that it plans to bring notebook battery life to all-new highs, as well as get their best and fastest chips into suitable power levels for high end tablets and even sleeker PCs. While the battle against the ARM camp is not quite won, it seems that Intel is very aggressively fighting to dominate the high performance, low power processor space. Now is the time to place your bets either way: does Intel extend its dominance into low power, or do the ARM vendors push Intel out of the notebook space? My bet's on Intel. Additional disclosure: Short ARMH From Ashraf Eassa</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354999603930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:46:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354999659135-26</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Latest Low-Power Battle Plans</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354999603930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seekingalphaDOTcom/article/1048411-intel-s-latest-low-power-battle-plans</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1354999659135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:47:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354999686316-27</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with TSMC's 20nm process is they have given up performance</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354999345477</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:42:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Heck yeah. Xeon is spelled M-O-N-O-P-O-L-Y.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1354999686316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:48:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355000122447-28</Id><Title>Intel Datacenter Press Briefing</Title><Msg>Tuesday, 12/11/12 at 8:30 AM PT Speaker: Diane Bryant, Vice President, General Manager, Datacenter and Connected Systems Group</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1355000122447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:55:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355000911873-29</Id><Title>CES 2013: January 8-11</Title><Msg>Intel outlines Ultrabook, tablet, smartphone plans for CES 2013 Intel has announced that Intel's vice president and general manager of the PC Client Group Kirk Skaugen and general manager of the Mobile and Communications Group Mike Bell will take to the CES stage to reveal the company's progress on its mobile products over the past twelve months. As well as an update on the new wave of convertible Ultrabooks, Windows 8-based devices that can transform from a tablet into a fully-powered PC, the company will be showcasing next-generation smartphone and tablet designs based on a next-generation revision of the Intel Atom low-power processor platform. From Expert Reviews Cars evolve at CES 2013 With several major automakers showing their latest electronics integration and suppliers displaying new products for manufacturers and the aftermarket, CES 2013 promises to host a significant car component. Intel is also pushing its Atom processors as an automotive solution for infotainment systems, and will likely have some sort of demonstration tucked away in its massive floor area. From C/Net</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1355000911873</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 16:08:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355001253050-30</Id><Title>Pre-CES 2013 Crystal Ball - Intel's Atom might win the ARMs race</Title><Msg>During our short time with the Atom Medfield powered Motorola RAZR i, which surprised us in many areas, we had an epiphany - What if Intel added moar cores and a better GPU engine into their upcoming torpedo (Clovertrail+) aimed at the ARM dominance in smartphones? From VR-Zone</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1355001253050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 16:14:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355009248449-31</Id><Topic><Title>If you are long INTC and worried - Listen to Paul Otellini at the Bernstein Conference</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354783997804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 03:53:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Going to take a crapp in a shoe box and mail it to you, C.O.D.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1355009248449</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 18:27:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355011871975-32</Id><Title>More about Red Ridge Android Tablet - Intel just got interesting</Title><Msg>Could CES hold a Medfield-powered Red Ridge tablet by Intel? FCC filing suggests the answer is 'yes' By Michelle Fitzsimmons 23 hrs ago Related stories Intel's next gen tablet chips leak with Bay Trail-T and Valleyview-T LG reportedly planning in-house chips for CES 2013 reveal Intel developing new tablet chip Intel is suddenly becoming very interesting. First, word got around that the chip maker might have two tablet processors to show off at CES 2013 - the Bay Trail-T and a SoC called the Valleyview-T. The chips are said to bring quad-core power, long battery lives and a whole lot of improvements that could give Qualcomm's S4 a taste of its dust. Now we're seeing a filing from the U.S. Federal Communications Commission (FCC) containing a tiny label with a load of info. The 20 millimeter by 35 millimeter tag is plastered (figuratively) on a device based on Intel's Red Ridge tablet platform. Red Ridge, you might remember, is based on the company's Medfield processor. Medfield minefield Relatively little has been spoken about Medfield in recent months, and what's been said isn't entirely positive. Intel successfully portedAndroid 4.1: Jelly Bean to Medfield in September, meaning devices like the Orange San Diego and ZTE Grand X IN could get a sugar bump up from Android 4.0: Ice Cream Sandwich, though that was an internal development with no commercial roll out. What also came to light back then was that the chip couldn't support LTE in phones, kind of a "wa-wa" in today's mobile world. However, Intel also said that it was planning to ship LTE products in late 2012, with deployment ramping up next year. Medfield might even push out a dual-core version to rival quad-core competitors. Could Medfield start the year off with a triumphant debut...possibly at a major event like, say, CES? The labeled device the FCC tested ran ICS and housed both Bluetooth and NFC capability. It also picked up 802.11a/b/g/n Wi-Fi. The filing also reveals something tantalizing: the device tested was apparently a production model, meaning a commercial unit could be ready in the next four weeks. That puts the timing squarely in CES territory. While we're not the gambling type, it sounds like a pretty sure bet Intel could have a Red Ridge-ready, Medfield-packing tablet to show off in Vegas next month.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1355011871975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 19:11:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355012469496-33</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with TSMC's 20nm process is they have given up performance</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1354999345477</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:42:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Makes sense to do since their customers aren't building PC type devices but mobile smartphones and tablets which need all day battery life and not lots of MIPS.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1355012469496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 19:21:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355012857258-34</Id><Topic><Title>More about Red Ridge Android Tablet - Intel just got interesting</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1355011871975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 19:11:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM has no response to Intel's Bay Trail technology. None whatsoever.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1355012857258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 19:27:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355014611674-35</Id><Topic><Title>More about Red Ridge Android Tablet - Intel just got interesting</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1355011871975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 19:11:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this guy wrong? He says Bay Trail for Tablets is coming in 2014. ))))))))))))))))))))))))) Intel roadmap leak outlines Bay Trail-based Atom for tablets in detail: 3D cameras, half the energy draw By Jon Fingas posted Nov 19th, 2012 at 3:39 PM 40 Intel roadmap leak outlines Bay Trailbased Atom for tablets in detail 3D cameras, half the energy draw Intel isn't having much success keeping its upcoming Bay Trail-era Atom platform under wraps. If the previous overview leak wasn't enough, a roadmap uncovered by Mobile Geeks has just explored the finer points of the tablet-oriented Bay View-T and its Valleyview-T processors. The most surprising leap may be in graphics: while we knew the GPU core would be much faster, we're now seeing that the new Intel hardware can output to as much as a 2,560 x 1,600 display and record stereoscopic, 1080p 3D video in the event that 3D-capable tablets come back into vogue. Likewise, battery life should be rosier than you'd expect; Bay Trail-T can reach the same performance at half the power, which should lead to about two extra hours of video playback for at least some of the 1.6GHz to 2.1GHz processors in the lineup. Don't get too excited by the potential, however. If the leak is accurate, Bay Trail for tablets isn't expected until early 2014, by which point 22-nanometer Atoms will be a step behind the cutting edge.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1355014611674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 19:56:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355016383084-36</Id><Topic><Title>More about Red Ridge Android Tablet - Intel just got interesting</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1355011871975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 19:11:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From my understand (someone correct if I am wrong), there was a leak earlier in the year that showed Intel had an excelerated roadmap and that Bay Trail would be available sometime in 2013. But last month there was another leak showing Bay Trail would not be available until 2014. So if latest leak is true then the techradar article is wrong and this Red Ridge tablet is probably a dual core medfield...the z2580....still should be the fastest SoC in market. If it is Bay Trail, then EVERYTHING changes!</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1355016383084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 20:26:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355018996883-37</Id><Topic><Title>If you are long INTC and worried - Listen to Paul Otellini at the Bernstein Conference</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354783997804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 03:53:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think they have APPLE!</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1355018996883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 21:09:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355023064842-38</Id><Topic><Title>too funny, lucy nuff, coinmaker 77, wdgrowblow, etc</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1354997304550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:08:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Waldo, an old man who still hasn't learned how the stock market game is correctly played. Unless of course, in bizarro world. 20 is far better than 24.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1355023064842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 22:17:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355023851000-39</Id><Topic><Title>If you are long INTC and worried - Listen to Paul Otellini at the Bernstein Conference</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354783997804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 03:53:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All 46 analysts that follow Intel will immediately downgrade Intel and lower the price target by $2 because the Apple foundry contract will lower the Intel gross margins. All 46 with then raise Samsung to a strong buy and raise targets because Samsung margins are going to increase without the Apple account.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1355023851000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 22:30:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355023916726-40</Id><Topic><Title>If you are long INTC and worried - Listen to Paul Otellini at the Bernstein Conference</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354783997804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 03:53:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All 46 analysts that follow Intel will immediately downgrade Intel and lower the price target by $2 because the Apple foundry contract will lower the Intel gross margins. All 46 with then raise Samsung to a strong buy and raise targets because Samsung margins are going to increase without the Apple account.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1355023916726</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 22:31:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355023959523-41</Id><Topic><Title>If you are long INTC and worried - Listen to Paul Otellini at the Bernstein Conference</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354783997804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 03:53:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All 46 analysts that follow Intel will immediately downgrade Intel and lower the price target by $2 because the Apple foundry contract will lower the Intel gross margins. All 46 with then raise Samsung to a strong buy and raise targets because Samsung margins are going to increase without the Apple account.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1355023959523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 22:32:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355023976023-42</Id><Topic><Title>More about Red Ridge Android Tablet - Intel just got interesting</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1355011871975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 19:11:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, let's keep in mind that the difference between sometime in 2013 and sometime in 2014 could be as little as a day...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1355023976023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 22:32:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355024150772-43</Id><Topic><Title>More about Red Ridge Android Tablet - Intel just got interesting</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1355011871975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 19:11:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We'll know more soon: "I expect that Intel -- along with its hardware partners -- will start talking about Bay Trail-T hardware at CES 2013 in January." From ZDNet</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1355024150772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 22:35:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355024638594-44</Id><Topic><Title>If you are long INTC and worried - Listen to Paul Otellini at the Bernstein Conference</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354783997804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 03:53:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All 46 analysts that follow Intel will downgrade Intel and reduce the price target because of the lowered gross margins.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1355024638594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 22:43:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355025391239-45</Id><Topic><Title>If you are long INTC and worried - Listen to Paul Otellini at the Bernstein Conference</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354783997804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 03:53:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As soon Apple is announced, all analysts will downgrade Intel because of lower Intel margins.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1355025391239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 22:56:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355027238302-46</Id><Topic><Title>If you are long INTC and worried - Listen to Paul Otellini at the Bernstein Conference</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1354783997804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 03:53:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel will be downgraded if it happens because their gross margin will drop. Samsung will be upgraded if they lose the Apple account since there margins will increase.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1355027238302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 23:27:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>