<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-24"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356325760129-1</Id><Title>Fiscal cliff looming but nothing inherently wrong with Intel if it pulls back from these levels</Title><Msg>If market corrects due to gov't inaction, all sectors will be down across the board. 97% of bashing on this board is due to the #$%$ Lucy and aliases. Don't listen to this #$%$/k and don't give him any attention. Maybe he'll go away.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356325760129</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 00:09:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356327466399-2</Id><Title>Thinking this keeper nut is another alias of coinmaker, etc</Title><Msg>So he bought AMD at $10 and shorted Intel at $19.23. What a freakin loser!</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356327466399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 00:37:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356329052818-3</Id><Topic><Title>A Red Ridge tablet from Intel</Title><Username>intel_xeon_processor</Username><Timestamp>1355290416385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 00:33:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah so brilliant they fired Steve Sinofsky the project lead. They know it is not doing well. I have it and it really ain't no big deal. Remember it came out at way lower price then the prior versions. The whole time you use it you will say wow ...why did they do this ? Eventually you learn the work arounds and 3rd party add ons, but it is not what it should have been. Don't believe me, go read the hundreds of Amazon reviews. Intel stated they thought it was not ready for release, but to no avail.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356329052818</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 01:04:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356330984559-4</Id><Topic><Title>INTC going lower and test 19.23, computers not selling, No chips in phones , no chips in tablets that are selling NOT GOOD, NOT GOOD</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356153383767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 00:16:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats what I have been wondering..why at near 52wk low???</Msg><Username>poppinmoremidols</Username><Timestamp>1356330984559</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 01:36:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356331110967-5</Id><Topic><Title>INTC going lower and test 19.23, computers not selling, No chips in phones , no chips in tablets that are selling NOT GOOD, NOT GOOD</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356153383767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 00:16:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe its the Obammur factor..too many uncertains..except Obama taking another Hawaii vacation..thats certain.</Msg><Username>poppinmoremidols</Username><Timestamp>1356331110967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 01:38:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356332188127-6</Id><Topic><Title>arm vs INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356303442982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone say DUMP.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356332188127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 01:56:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356332567493-7</Id><Title>Intel in 2013</Title><Msg>- Release of 7W Ivy Bridge chips making PC convertibles and PC detachables even more thinner and lighter. This will further allow the PC market to cannabalize the tablet market. - Release of mobile celeron chips adding to the breadth and variable of PC convertibles and detachables market. Soon the market will be bombarded by mobile PC devices that will blur the lines between tablets and PC - Release of Haswell the 4th generation Core will allow for average of 10+ hours of battery life for ultrabooks including convertibles and detachables. This will spur on a major refresh cycle, which many are predicting a 'pent-up' refresh. There will be a variety of Haswell including the ULV parts plus an ultra ULV parts which might come down to ~5W TDP! - Release of new Medfield SoC with integrated LTE 4G that will see Intel come into the US smartphone market for the first time. The single core Medfield has already proven to be superior to most current multi-core arm-based SoC in the market today both in terms of performance and battery life. Imagine the next version of the Medfield. There are reports that Intel will take a bigger step in 2013, by releasing the Bay Trail Medfield with quad-core developed on the most state of the art 22nm process! There are rumors flying around now that an Intel SoC will power the secret XPhone being developed by the Google's Motorola. The phone is said to have some innovations never before seen in a phone including flexible touch screens. - Intel will further maximize profits by doing foundry work on the side. Cisco and Apple are rumored to be future customers. In terms of Apple, the rumor is that Intel will not only be foundry for Apple but that future iPads will have Intel inside! Revenue are predicted to increase by $7 billion from these two foundry customers alone ($2 billion for Cisco and $5 billion for Apple)</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356332567493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 02:02:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356333534905-8</Id><Topic><Title>Intel in 2013</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356332567493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 02:02:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has competition like it has never seen before. As long as ARMH makes good products and makes money they can keep pressuring Intel. You ain't seen nothing yet, ARMH is very aggressive and getting into every flippin thing a chip can go in.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356333534905</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 02:18:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356334304066-9</Id><Topic><Title>Intel in 2013</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356332567493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 02:02:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>competition? the best arm chips doesn't have 64-bit yet and can't even compare with Intel's products from 6 years ago? you call that competition? Intel just took out AMD now they have their guns on arm...ya, you are right about one thing...you ain't seen nothing yet.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356334304066</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 02:31:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356338252766-10</Id><Topic><Title>100 PFLOPS of Ivy Bridge EP and Intel PHI supercomputer power.</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356201982667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:46:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Yes. My evidence is from Theo himself. He shows his calculations and assumptions in the article. He states his assumptions." Yeah... what makes his assumptions incorrect... "Did Intel sell below manufacturing cost?" Free is always below cost... "What is the die size on the Intel PHI?" You won't like this... for we have to use our assumptions... But INtel is using 30MB of cache, Thousands of floating point units, half that for DP And a 512-bit memory bus... Theo, you, me... will have to calculate &amp; assume some things here... "With the wafer cost, sort yield and die sizes you can estimate the final product manufacturing cost. " Add in the extra quals for the professional end... but with just the above, we can already 'assume' it's HUGE... "Theo is making assumptions on these." So... "What exact same thing are you referring to? Intel was sued for selling 100,000 Xeon E5-2567W v2 and Intel PHI?" YOu already knew that's not what I'm referring to... Just 3 yrs ago INtel lost to the EU... Settled with AMD before losing Settled with NVidia before losing... etc...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1356338252766</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 03:37:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356343680344-11</Id><Title>I just got a Samsung ATIV Smart PC!!!</Title><Msg>I went to the Microsoft store earlier today to check out some of the PC convertibles and PC detachables. The Samsung ATIV Smart PC caught my eye and I was playing with it and the girl there started showing me some of the tricks to use with Windows 8. She told me that, for the holiday season, I can buy and try it for 30 days and if I don't like I can return it. I said what the heck, sure! I've been playing with it for 3 hours now and I gotta tell you, it is pure joy. I don't know why there is such negativity regarding windows 8. To me it is amazing. The way you can flip thru the different apps you are using; the way you can have 2 windows on the same screen and still have backgroud apps like music playing in the background. Did you know there is a app called Music Tube that allows you to listen to your favorite songs and artist and watch their videos from youtube? You don't even need to buy any music! it is amazing. But the best feature with the Samsung ATIV Smart PC is it's a PC and tablet in one. I was playing with it on the couch and then I wanted to write an email and without missing a beat i went to my table which had the keyboard dock; i just placed the tablet half on it and started typing my email. Now that is cool! And then there is the Desktop ie. PC app that allows you to do everything you would normally do in windows 7. I don't have office installed on it yet, but I will just need to get a cheap USB portable CD/DVD drive to install all my software. I am tell you straight now. If you are long INTC...hold on to your shares. I am more convinced than ever that PCs will be making a come back in a big way. PC convertibles and PC detachables such as the Samsung ATIV Smart PC will eat away at the current tablets. They will dominant the tablet market in similar fashion as how Android took over the smartphone market. Intel is in the best position here because the only way to fully benefit from Windows 8 (with its touch capabilities) is to upgrade your hardware. And when people decide to upgrade their hardware, they are going to pick a Intel-based device because they want to be able use the same Windows program they have been using in Windows 7. The iPad can't give you this; android can't give you this; Windows RT can't give you this. Only a Windows 8 device running on Intel can!</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356343680344</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 05:08:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356345836038-12</Id><Topic><Title>arm vs INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356303442982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Medfield Atoms already blew away Tegra 3 and is competitive with Samsung's ARM. Next iteration would be even better.</Msg><Username>sharikou_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1356345836038</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 05:43:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356345960249-13</Id><Topic><Title>The Clover Trail (Atom Z2760) Review: Acer's W510 Tested</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356030773326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 14:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now ARM has a real competitor.</Msg><Username>sharikou_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1356345960249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 05:46:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356346547593-14</Id><Topic><Title>100 PFLOPS of Ivy Bridge EP and Intel PHI supercomputer power.</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356201982667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:46:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Yeah... what makes his assumptions incorrect..." I would like to read more from his source documents but I have not found much data available. One assumption that I know is wrong is his $2,500 E5, v2 estimated pricing. Anyone with a 100,000 part E5 v2 and 100,000 part Phi order will not pay anything near the 5,000 part tray price. Theo gave a pessimistic evaluation using 5,000 unit pricing and then made a guess at the manufacturing cost. Theo's assumptions was: "a Xeon E5-2567W v2should set you back (note: this is a future part, pricing was an estimate based on current line-up) for $2,500" How many cores, MB of cache, frequency do you think the E5-2567W, v2 will have? I think the computation model will be to operate primarily on the PHI and the E5, v2 will be needed to stream chunks of data to them. Streaming data to the Phi will not likely benefit from a large cache. The data will be read from a disk, transferred to the Phi and little E5 processing. They would use the streaming IO buffers to transfer data which bypass the cache. Adding capative loading to the bus quickly slows it down because the CPU memory buffers cannot drive the extra load at the same frequency. Your desktop machine will run faster if you have fewer DIMMs for the same reason. If you have 8GB of memory in a machine, it will run slower if you have 4 x 2GB DIMMs versus 2 x 4GB all operating at the same frequency. "Free is always below cost..." Even Theo estimates that $50,000,000 of the $100,000,000 contract will be going to Intel. That is not free. He also suggests that there is a service contract that goes along. Not free. Of course, you already knew that too. "YOu already knew that's not what I'm referring to..." YEs. I thought I knew BUt I WAs HOping I WAs WRong. You are quite rational when you are in discussion mode. I have read the first 100 pages of the 500 page EU report. I should go back and try to read it again. The first 100 pages were only about why the EU was justified in denying Intel a 6-month postponement and instead just issuing their findings without any Intel input. IMO, that was wrong and when results the July 8th EU appeals court are released, we will know a little more. I will discuss lawsuit with you if you really want but in a LAwsuit THread.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356346547593</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 05:55:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356346699026-15</Id><Topic><Title>arm vs INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356303442982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has been trying to get down to the power envelope of mobile for about 6 years now. Medfield is the first version of their chip that borderline fits. Their vantage point, therefore, continues to be the high power end. From there, its easy to speculate that getting your power consumption into a budget is simply a matter of optimizing from amongst a range of performance options that you've already developed. In other words a very tenable task. But if you look at their results from performing this very optimization over the last 6 years, they are depressing. It leads me to believe they don't know what they're talking about because they've never been there. ARM on the other hand has gone way lower than the mobile phone battery operating point. e.g. Their M0+ which is used in embedded. Secondly, if you look at design trends amongst computing gadget makers such as Apple, they are moving away from performance driven improvement to a more use-centric approach. This greatly favors the low end of the power spectrum because with advances in process technology, the low end is going to become more and more performant until it is good enough for most applications. No-one can tell the difference between a game running at 30 fps and 130 fps because after a certain speed, you can't tell the difference. The high end, Intel's vantage point, therefore gets relegated to niche uses such as super-computers.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1356346699026</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 05:58:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356347125627-16</Id><Topic><Title>I just got a Samsung ATIV Smart PC!!!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356343680344</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 05:08:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You got the one with the Intel Atom z2760 and not the i5 Pro version, correct? I was wondering if the z2760 was being shipped.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356347125627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 06:05:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356350625668-17</Id><Topic><Title>arm vs INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356303442982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should go write a puff piece about Arm on SA I'm sure they would let you, give all the reasons why 75x P/E is just peachy keen and investors should BUY BUY BUY... In th meantime I will short every bump like there's no tomorrow, CES is going to put a damper on your pipe dreams just like last year, ohhhhh this will be fun!</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1356350625668</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 07:03:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356353210272-18</Id><Title>No cliff deal, down another 6 cents in the pre-market</Title><Msg>I think we shoed if no deal by the end of the year (which their won't be I'm afraid)...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1356353210272</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 07:46:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356353820049-19</Id><Topic><Title>No cliff deal, down another 6 cents in the pre-market</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1356353210272</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 07:46:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they will kick the can down the road. Good enough for the markets I suppose.</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1356353820049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 07:57:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356357458060-20</Id><Topic><Title>Thinking this keeper nut is another alias of coinmaker, etc</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356327466399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 00:37:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yup this nut case is on ignore</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1356357458060</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:57:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356358431256-21</Id><Topic><Title>Intel in 2013</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356332567493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 02:02:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you might want to read up on what is coming very soon before you get too bullish.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1356358431256</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:13:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356358560824-22</Id><Topic><Title>Intel in 2013</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356332567493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 02:02:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>scream on but intel will be single digits late 2013 we go down to $19 again buy back scam with $6B+ in debt...........Fraud Management raping shareholders</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1356358560824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:16:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356358703442-23</Id><Topic><Title>Hope you sold Fri, Future all red</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1356321660226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 23:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The futures look weak, and it is not just because of the Cliff. Stocks are at fluffy price points.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356358703442</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:18:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356358877227-24</Id><Topic><Title>INTC may well skyrocket tomorrow! This is the key reasons why.</Title><Username>willian.attig</Username><Timestamp>1356353879245</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 07:57:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SCAM REPORTED !</Msg><Username>alphonite</Username><Timestamp>1356358877227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:21:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356359240881-25</Id><Topic><Title>WE HAVE A SIGNIFICANT LEAD</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1355190300684</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 20:45:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ignorance is bliss, to 12</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1356359240881</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:27:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356360352953-26</Id><Title>MSFT falling new computers and not selling. Thats not good for INTC , HPQ, DELL</Title><Msg>MSFT falling new computers and not selling. Thats not good for INTC , HPQ, DELL</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356360352953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:45:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356360657862-27</Id><Topic><Title>Intel in 2013</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356332567493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 02:02:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to be the one all excited. You know the 10% yield at single digits will attract some pension funds and other value investors. How can a transaction that puts $110mil on the bottom line be bad? Intel has to pay $110mil less to for the debt than the dividends. Why do you call it a scam ?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356360657862</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:50:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356361044459-28</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT falling new computers and not selling. Thats not good for INTC , HPQ, DELL</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356360352953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:45:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Microsoft discussion was relelated to Win8. It is probably a bad thing for HPQ and DELL because they are sold out. Intel also sells to Apple, Lenovo, Samsung, .... PC shipments have not changed for the last 2 months. You were saying earlier that Intel problems were because they had no smart phones or tablets. If Intel CPU occupied the sockets of 50% of all the smart phones and 50% of all tablets sold in 2012, what would you estimate the incremental impact of those market shares on Intel quarterly revenue and profit. How many dollars would it add to Intel revenue and profit. I estimate that a 50% smartphone &amp; tablet market share for Intel would increase their revenues by 13%. Is that what you compute?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356361044459</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:57:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356361461094-29</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT falling new computers and not selling. Thats not good for INTC , HPQ, DELL</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356360352953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:45:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trading High margin for lower margin is and will always be a bad thing. INTC going lower and it will retest 19.23 the only ? is will it hold and that is unknow for now</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356361461094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 10:04:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356361566474-30</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT falling new computers and not selling. Thats not good for INTC , HPQ, DELL</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356360352953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:45:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The bounce was not very high so my guess is that 19.23 will not hold, but I will have to wait and see</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356361566474</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 10:06:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356361884256-31</Id><Title>bodontknowsintel is a pumper and has lost a ton of money</Title><Msg>bo can not be trusted. He has a tiny thing and loses money every time he gets his welfare. Bo is a HO ho ho.</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1356361884256</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 10:11:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356363556016-32</Id><Topic><Title>We're Good for 30</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1327420596000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-01-24 10:56:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Almost one full year since you made your bogus "good for 30" call, Buttplug, and the stock is lower now than it was when you posted your fantasy prediction. TOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1356363556016</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 10:39:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356363879280-33</Id><Title>INTC ONE of the WORST STOCK of the YEAR.. INTC...</Title><Msg>LOADUP AMD BEST BUY</Msg><Username>buywhenallbazh</Username><Timestamp>1356363879280</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 10:44:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356364875691-34</Id><Title>Thank you Intel</Title><Msg>I am still 13 cents higher than last time I sold at $20.40. Can you please go lower to $20.00?</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356364875691</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:01:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356364934568-35</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT falling new computers and not selling. Thats not good for INTC , HPQ, DELL</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356360352953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:45:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I sold all my INTC shares at 29.25 and shorted at 29.25 that was the Day CNBC PETE the CON man told you to buy INTC. I covered my short at 19.41 I think, purchased shares at 19.36 and sold them at a little over $20, because nothing has changed for INTC and if it does they will be trading higher margin products for lower margin products. Thats not good for INTC or any company</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356364934568</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:02:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356365019026-36</Id><Topic><Title>100 PFLOPS of Ivy Bridge EP and Intel PHI supercomputer power.</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1356201982667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:46:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I would like to read more from his source documents" Wouldn't we all... :) "Theo estimates that $50,000,000 of the $100,000,000 contract will be going to Intel. That is not free." IF we stick to the E5 alone... 100K E5 units would be $1K each if INtel got 100% of the $1M... "Streaming data to the Phi will not likely benefit from a large cache." Would it benefit from a small cache... Besides, Xeon PHI cache is 512KB per core... The size of the cache has been a complaint of HPC GPGPU users... "You are quite rational when you are in discussion mode." Entirely dependent on the other poster... My id alone spawns new aliases everyday... And I admit, I do have far too much fun at times...:) If there's one common theme from the cheerleaders... It's been the same for years now.... "INtel is coming out with something next year, and the competition is thru" "I will discuss lawsuit with you if you really want " Hope Not !!!! INtel settled 3 yrs ago... The point was they were about dumping &amp; monopoly practices...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1356365019026</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:03:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356365209852-37</Id><Title>Happy New Year from the Semiconductor Wikipedia Project!</Title><Msg>It was an amazing year for SemiWiki and I would like to thank all who participated. SemiWiki traffic doubled again last year which is amazing in itself. SemiWiki membership more than tripled as we continue to add vertical markets (EDA, IP, Services, Foundry). More people are blogging on SemiWiki and the Forums and Wikis are coming to life. With millions of page views I can comfortably say that social media is now an integral part of the fabless semiconductor ecosystem. What’s in store for SemiWiki in the new year? We will continue to grow with more original content, another vertical market (FPGA), and increased exposure through a new partnership with Yahoo and other mainstream news sources. Today more than 450,000 people are reading SemiWiki. In 2013 that number will exceed 1,000,000, believe it. I hope to see you there!</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1356365209852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:06:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356365221575-38</Id><Title>I sold too early @ $20.40 last time</Title><Msg>then INTC traded as high as $21.30</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356365221575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:07:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356365467403-39</Id><Title>SELL now @ $20.52</Title><Msg>If it starts going UP, buy @ $21.35, that's a SMART move!</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356365467403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:11:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356365535832-40</Id><Topic><Title>I just got a Samsung ATIV Smart PC!!!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356343680344</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 05:08:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lingering on the desktop a moment, you can also forget gaming, too: though the Smart PC should technically run many legacy x86 games, its integrated Intel Graphics Media Accelerator yields a 3DMark06 score of just 374. In the disk benchmark ATTO, meanwhile, its read and write speeds topped out at just 82 MB/s and 36 MB/s, respectively. We'll venture to say we don't expect much better of other Atom-powered tablets; if anything, the buggy performance is the bigger crime here. Still, as we go through the list of possible use cases for this thing, it's worrisome that we have to cross mundane tablet tasks and desktop productivity off the list. If the Smart PC offers unreliable performance in tablet mode and is too sluggish to get much done in desktop mode, why might you spend $700 on a device like this?</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356365535832</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:12:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356365692603-41</Id><Topic><Title>arm vs INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356303442982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Medfield Atoms already blew away Tegra 3 and is competitive with Samsung's ARM. Next iteration would be even better." Tegra 3 is 40nm versus Medfield at 32nm? I wonder why Google chose Tegra 3 for their tablets instead of Medfield? Lets see how Medfield does against Tegra 4 on 28nm. My guess is that it won't even be close. Tegra 4 is a screamer.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1356365692603</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:14:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356366065915-42</Id><Title>SELL now @ $20.62</Title><Msg>before it's too late, you can always buy at higher, for example $21.35</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356366065915</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:21:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356366276161-43</Id><Topic><Title>arm vs INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356303442982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel has the advantage of being able to start from much higher-end architectures (xeon, sandybridge, ivy, etc) and simply reduce cache sizes and remove features until the desired power envelope is met." Those great speedups to the architecture are what eats up the power... INtel's dirty little secret is memory sizes matter.. If they bumped up the ATOM cache size, it would cut into other CPU SKUs... "This means that in the next year or two Intel will be completely outgunning ARM" Yawn... Textbook INtel cheerleader... "INtel will come out with something next year, and the competition is thru..." "ARM has a much more difficult task ahead of it. " YOu got me laughing... Thank You !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1356366276161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:24:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356366337544-44</Id><Title>Market tanking and Intel holding it's own. Can't be good for shorts.</Title><Msg>Shorts may get singed if fiscal cliff addressed. Recommend covering now at all costs.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356366337544</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:25:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356366341494-45</Id><Topic><Title>SELL now @ $20.62</Title><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356366065915</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:21:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why?,It's never to late to buy INTC in the long term.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1356366341494</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:25:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356366448430-46</Id><Topic><Title>Market tanking and Intel holding it's own. Can't be good for shorts.</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356366337544</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>meantime Qcom and AAPL green...can't be all that great for INTC longs, can it?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1356366448430</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:27:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356366473265-47</Id><Topic><Title>SELL now @ $20.62</Title><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356366065915</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:21:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am telling stupid people to SELL. Smart people do not have to be told.</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356366473265</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:27:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356366557182-48</Id><Title>my concern :</Title><Msg>Intc is so exposed to PC's and they have high margins there...could the pundits be right? Could these margins shrink significantly? Is their plan to Div'd 40% of bottom line earnings? If so, we could see a div'd cut this year couldn't we?</Msg><Username>previs_beameister</Username><Timestamp>1356366557182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:29:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356366868692-49</Id><Topic><Title>my concern :</Title><Username>previs_beameister</Username><Timestamp>1356366557182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:29:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>laptops replacing PCs to some extent and yet there will always be demand for PCs. Intel is providing Servers to the growing cloud computing. Buying back shares hence improving PE and growing div.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1356366868692</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:34:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356366922615-50</Id><Topic><Title>SELL now @ $20.62</Title><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356366065915</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:21:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are clearly quite an expert on stupid people. Must be surrounded by them in your family.</Msg><Username>previs_beameister</Username><Timestamp>1356366922615</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:35:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356366951697-51</Id><Title>Market closes in 1 hour 25 minutes</Title><Msg>hopefully ITC closes in GREEN today</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356366951697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:35:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356367592537-52</Id><Title>SELL now @ $20.72</Title><Msg>going down maybe?</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356367592537</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:46:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356367792830-53</Id><Topic><Title>SELL now @ $20.72</Title><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356367592537</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:46:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not as low as you.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1356367792830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:49:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356367955457-54</Id><Topic><Title>my concern :</Title><Username>previs_beameister</Username><Timestamp>1356366557182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:29:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cloud under attack too via ARMH and others. Margins are going down and sales are going down and competition from England is increasing daily.</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1356367955457</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:52:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356368010183-55</Id><Title>closing above $20.85</Title><Msg>or higher</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356368010183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:53:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356368044540-56</Id><Topic><Title>We're Good for 30</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1327420596000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-01-24 10:56:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>30 is a slam dunk --------- HI-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1356368044540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:54:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356368619273-57</Id><Title>Market closes in 1 hour</Title><Msg>58 minutes to go</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356368619273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:03:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356368671121-58</Id><Topic><Title>Market tanking and Intel holding it's own. Can't be good for shorts.</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356366337544</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dow down .35 percent, dimtel down .5 percent. Pass some of that stuff around man !!</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1356368671121</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:04:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356368910248-59</Id><Topic><Title>Market tanking and Intel holding it's own. Can't be good for shorts.</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356366337544</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slow bleed to $19 road map clowns Intel management $6B buy back scam with DEBT brought it back up</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1356368910248</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:08:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356369434668-60</Id><Topic><Title>my concern :</Title><Username>previs_beameister</Username><Timestamp>1356366557182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:29:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Engand shall never recover from it's 20th century implosion. It is now the Michigan of Europe, and London is Detroit...and there are parts of London that are worse than the worst parts of Detroit. ARMH is a sprinter. INTC is a marathon runner. ARMH will never pass the 100 yard marker.</Msg><Username>parched_remy_soot</Username><Timestamp>1356369434668</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:17:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356369510620-61</Id><Topic><Title>I just got a Samsung ATIV Smart PC!!!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356343680344</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 05:08:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes I got the one with the Clover Trail. The i5 Pro version was also available but I went with the Clover Trail. Writing this on it now and still playing with it</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356369510620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:18:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356369656081-62</Id><Topic><Title>We're Good for 30</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1327420596000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-01-24 10:56:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hahahahhahahaaa Good one! That's the problem with being a shameless shill, it will come back to haunt you.</Msg><Username>semiconductorguy</Username><Timestamp>1356369656081</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:20:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356370667566-63</Id><Title>Major hedge fund managers announce today across the board buy of Intel!</Title><Msg>Will be buying like there's no tomorrow. Unfortunate, but shorts and skeptics soon to be window jumpers.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356370667566</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:37:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356370801485-64</Id><Topic><Title>We're Good for 30</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1327420596000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-01-24 10:56:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"That's the problem with being a shameless shill, it will come back to haunt you." -DNenni- LMAO !!!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1356370801485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:40:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356370957550-65</Id><Title>mellanox stock long strong bullish start by friday</Title><Msg>buy buy</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1356370957550</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:42:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356371651865-66</Id><Title>LOL this POS down again today, merry Christmas...sell now.</Title><Msg>going lower</Msg><Username>vwtrikel_the_only_vw</Username><Timestamp>1356371651865</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:54:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356371686193-67</Id><Title>Just Recommened on CNBC</Title><Msg>Lots of cash and hefty dividend.</Msg><Username>dilo133</Username><Timestamp>1356371686193</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:54:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356372593322-68</Id><Topic><Title>Just Recommened on CNBC</Title><Username>dilo133</Username><Timestamp>1356371686193</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:54:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But is still defy's those facts and GOES DOWN!!!</Msg><Username>poppinmoremidols</Username><Timestamp>1356372593322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 13:09:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356376949986-69</Id><Title>TSMC Dashes Apple-Azalea Hopes</Title><Msg>“The US is one of the places under consideration,” Chang said. “But this has nothing to do with Apple.” Don't think TSMC Chief Executive can say this and then turnaround and sign a deal with Apple. Could it be that Apple has already selected Intel as its foundry partner?</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356376949986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:22:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356377060103-70</Id><Topic><Title>Just Recommened on CNBC</Title><Username>dilo133</Username><Timestamp>1356371686193</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:54:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But is still defy's those facts and GOES DOWN!!!" *** With the fiscal cliff looming and the DOW/Nasdaq down, the Chump Street #$%$ could only beat the stock down a lousy 12 cents. Chump Street is losing this battle as it becomes clear that ARMs fabrication roadmap is nothing but a set of missing bridges. And where's the huge honking miss that Chump Street promised last quarter. They promised an $8 billion revenue miss and there wasn't any. Intel is stupidly, insanely and most of all corruptly oversold. Watch "Inside Job" if you want to see what these skumbags are capable of in the pursuit of money. One of the funniest parts was when one of those interviewed said everyone wondered how the boys on Wall Street ever showed up for work given the immense amounts of cocaine they consumed. Drug use, criminal behavior, market manipulation, betting against their own customers, parties and prostitutes. Just another day on Wall Street. And in the midst of all of this they find time to mount attacks of one of America's best companies. What a wonderful group of people!</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356377060103</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:24:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356377530592-71</Id><Topic><Title>We're Good for 30</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1327420596000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-01-24 10:56:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah, fanboi, I see you no longer even attempt to defend ARMs pathetic fabrication and have curled up with one of the most shameless and inept character assassins. The infamous, discredited and now postless Nenni. Or maybe you are Nenni. But who really cares. You must still be smarting over the recent news that the new Atom SOC outperforms your precious Nvidia - even in power efficiency. There's going to be a lot of news like this in 2013. Intel is good for 30. And much more. And we will mock you and poke you with a stick the entire time, pinata boy...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1356377530592</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:32:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356378682837-72</Id><Topic><Title>arm vs INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356303442982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you arm fans are missing the point of what Matt is saying. Once the process gets to 14nm and below, arm will not be competing with Atom, it will be competing with Intel's Core processors because the power envelop will be equal at that point. I believe Intel's strategy has always been to move the core down into the Atom's power envelop...once we get to 14nm, Atom will be the low end SoC while the high-end SoCs will be running Broadwell. arm's job is alot tougher, they have to improve performance while still maintain the power envelop and they are 4 generations behind. In terms of the "good enough" argument, well 1) prices go up you build higher performing processors and processes 2) Given the choice, I would pick a faster processor over "good enough" anyday</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356378682837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:51:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356379413141-73</Id><Topic><Title>arm vs INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356303442982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just to clarify, Intel does not have to modify anything with the Core processors to get it to the same power envelop as the Atom's...Once it gets to 14nm, the PROCESS itself will take care of it. They are modifying Atom now as a Low-end architecture...onces the two meet, at 14nm...they will be basically the same....but Core will be high-end while Atom low-end. This is why are you hearing rumors that Broadwell might not have sockets and will be BGP only.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356379413141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 15:03:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356380054944-74</Id><Topic><Title>arm vs INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356303442982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh... "I believe Intel's strategy has always been to move the core down into the Atom's power envelop." ARM's success is partly due to that was exactly NOT INtel's strategy... "In terms of the "good enough" argument, well 1) prices go up you build higher performing processors and processes 2) Given the choice, I would pick a faster processor over "good enough" anyday" Do you use the i7 Extreme ?? Or is your CPU good enough...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1356380054944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 15:14:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356383447666-75</Id><Topic><Title>Thank you Intel</Title><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356364875691</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:01:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm confused by your posts, I suppose you might be regretting selling at 20.40 but now want it to go lower to get back in cheaper, but with a strong buy sentiment??.. Oh well, merry Christmas if we go over the cliff you might get your chance if not 2013 will be a wild ride and CES will be where it starts, just be sure to buy back before 1/7/2013!!</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1356383447666</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 16:10:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356383992165-76</Id><Topic><Title>Thank you Intel</Title><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356364875691</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:01:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>go away idiot</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1356383992165</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 16:19:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356384923153-77</Id><Topic><Title>arm vs INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356303442982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Tegra 3 is 40nm versus Medfield at 32nm? I wonder why Google chose Tegra 3 for their tablets instead of Medfield?" No/limited manufacturing availability at the the time they were needed?</Msg><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1356384923153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 16:35:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356385402436-78</Id><Topic><Title>arm vs INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356303442982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some very positive commentary here. I do think Intel will run into another unforeseen dilemma when its atom chips are second to none. Are you all sure that Intel won't be the recipient of a concerted backlash, with cries of trying to monopolize the whole chip industry, if they are successful in the handheld mobile device segment?</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1356385402436</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 16:43:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356388119306-79</Id><Topic><Title>Thank you Intel</Title><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356364875691</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:01:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suppose you might be regretting selling at 20.40 but now want it to go lower to get back in cheaper, but with a strong buy sentiment? OK. I did not say I sold all of my shares. I sold 50% of my holdings in INTC. Now you see why I have Strong Buy sentiment?</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356388119306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 17:28:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356390319939-80</Id><Topic><Title>We're Good for 30</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1327420596000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-01-24 10:56:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First of all, I'm not going to respond to any of the Lucy #$%$ aliases. As for the critisism you have been getting about being good for $30, you sure got pretty close. Only 2% away from the $30 mark. The dividend yield is higher than that. So good call during January, where in less than 4 months, your $30 mark was met if the dividend is counted. But Lucy forgets when Intel was at $19, the negative posts the #$%$ was posting and calling for a drop to $15. Didn't even move an inch towards $15. I"m sure Intel could make a run for $30 once again given its huge push lately for mobile products to more than fill any void that may be seen temporarily on the PC side. The latest argument regarding the "death of the PC" has diminished to "people are holding off longer to upgrade their PC". Hence my statement of void that may be seen temporarily. Because eventually, all these PC owners will fill more and more pressure to upgrade.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1356390319939</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 18:05:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356390664935-81</Id><Title>Last year Everyone said X86 was power hungry, couldn't fit smartphones</Title><Msg>This year, the topic is X86 Atoms have "no edge" over ARM in power and performance. What will it be next year? X86 can't get above 10% smartphone marketshare?</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1356390664935</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 18:11:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356391708187-82</Id><Topic><Title>arm vs INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356303442982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets us see how tegra 4 matches with the haswell architecture.</Msg><Username>clemsyn</Username><Timestamp>1356391708187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 18:28:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356392546500-83</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy capitulates, says buy INTEL</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1317740904000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-10-04 11:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Merry Christmas to Intel's most ticked off bagholder. LOL! Re: We're Good for 30 by lucy_nuff . Dec 18, 2012 3:08 PM . Permalink "We're good for 30" ----- Sing it, sister! HI-HO WEAVERINO!!!</Msg><Username>lucy_is_my_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1356392546500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 18:42:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356392625245-84</Id><Topic><Title>arm vs INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356303442982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Silvermont/baytrail will kick tegra4 butt.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1356392625245</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 18:43:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356394985875-85</Id><Topic><Title>arm vs INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356303442982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>arm's success does not translate into good earnings. not sure how investors can justify the high p/e</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1356394985875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:23:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356395180345-86</Id><Title>How big WAS AMD? How big is ARM?</Title><Msg>ARM will be a light snack for Intel now that they have both eyes on them. Demand for Mobile products will NEVER go away.............and neither will Intel. NEVER.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1356395180345</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:26:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356395656526-87</Id><Topic><Title>Fitch: Intel's Dominance in x86-Based Processors Will Give it Stable Market Opportunity for Foreseeable Future</Title><Username>hardballnick</Username><Timestamp>1354638926581</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 11:35:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dominance</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1356395656526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:34:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356395713083-88</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT comng out with 14.6 inch screen Surface Book based on Intel Haswell</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1354742216419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 16:16:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haswell</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1356395713083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:35:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356395795450-89</Id><Topic><Title>arm vs INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1356303442982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because the world is going ARM... And ARM64 hasn't even launched yet...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1356395795450</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:36:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356395814745-90</Id><Topic><Title>Intel won the war</Title><Username>semiwiz2002</Username><Timestamp>1334435741000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-04-14 16:35:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel won it.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1356395814745</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:36:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356395913806-91</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH gives up on advancing Technology, uses cheap cookie cutter Technology</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1348857887831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:44:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1356395913806</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:38:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356396020967-92</Id><Title>ACER laughs at ARMH</Title><Msg>(Reuters) - Taiwan's Acer Inc said on Monday it would remain closer to U.S. chipmaker Intel, even though Microsoft also embraces rival ARM for its new Windows 8 operating system.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1356396020967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:40:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356396071415-93</Id><Topic><Title>More pointing and laughing at ARMH Trash Tablets</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1354543565955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 09:06:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WoW</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1356396071415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:41:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356396431120-94</Id><Title>To use GETANID61's own words regarding his ARM 64 bit pumping</Title><Msg>When is ARM 64bit coming out? 2015?? Now WHO is deperate? Re: Haswell will in phone in 2014! by getanid61 . Nov 14, 2012 11:50 AM . Permalink You guys are now reaching out to 2014 to compete with ARM.... DESPERATE !!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1356396431120</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:47:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356398448500-95</Id><Title>intc, amat or glw long term buy</Title><Msg>seeking best tech stock for long term buy and hold. intel, applied materials or corning</Msg><Username>kleinmanstephen</Username><Timestamp>1356398448500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:20:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356399274248-96</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH gives up on advancing Technology, uses cheap cookie cutter Technology</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1348857887831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:44:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This reduces end costs without engaging large semiconductor companies like Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) in the wars for the development of larger and more sophisticated fabs, according to Hans Mosesmann, Managing Director, Equity Research, at Raymond James &amp; Associates, Inc. Majority of "chip" analysts don't comprehend the manufacturing aspect. Hans still lives in LaLa land of cheap ARM SoCs - these days ar over - fenito - basta.- Whens did Hans check TSMC capex the last time? The guy can't be more wrong! All the ARM chip analysts are clueless about increasing ARM manufacturing cost. 20nm litho cost = 1.7 x of 28nm Remember Getanid61 telling everybody TriGate was strictly optimized/useful for CPU architecture ....they all follow Intel don't they.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1356399274248</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:34:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356399360322-97</Id><Topic><Title>intc, amat or glw long term buy</Title><Username>kleinmanstephen</Username><Timestamp>1356398448500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:20:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same post in 2008 ?????? by kleinmanstephen . Dec 20, 2008 2:42 PM . Permalink Go to topic thanks for the response. im looking at a tech stock w/ dividend. glw,amat, intc. your oppinion would be appreciated</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1356399360322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:36:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356399980434-98</Id><Title>LOLoudest</Title><Msg>12/20/2012 9:42 PM EST Intel is becoming a joke. Intel Board needs to clean all senior management (more than CEO). Clover Trail should not be compared to a 2 year old shipping product (Tegra 3). No one is designing Tegra 3 into new hardware designs today. Correct comparison is Clover Trial with/versus A6, or current snapdragon Krait, or if you want to compare to Nvidia compare to Tegra 4 which many OEM have samples (being designed into tablets now) and we will see announced in January at CES. Arm A15 class products in 28nm make a joke out of Intel atom (32 or 22nm) and a joke out of Intel</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1356399980434</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:46:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356400545824-99</Id><Topic><Title>LOLoudest</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1356399980434</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:46:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surface RT just released and has Tegra 3. TSMC production problems at 28nm preventing high volume availability so MS went with it.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1356400545824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:55:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356400716207-100</Id><Topic><Title>To use GETANID61's own words regarding his ARM 64 bit pumping</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1356396431120</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:47:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haswell in a phone, you better be shaking in your custom baby deal leather boots son!</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1356400716207</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:58:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356400835478-101</Id><Title>An article on Google Finance for Intel, trashing Cramer's call.</Title><Msg>Here's a part of the article. I tend to believe that Cramer knows little about Mellanox, and as a television commentator, he creates unfound drama. Four years ago, I watched him "hang" then-SanDisk Corporation (Nasdaq:SNDK) CEO Dr. Eli Harari on the wall of shame in his weird studio, because Harari would not agree to sell SanDisk to Samsung at $26 per share, after which SanDisk crashed to $5 per share. But I did not see Cramer apologize when SanDisk's share recovered to $50 while Harari was still CEO.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1356400835478</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:00:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356400980573-102</Id><Topic><Title>LOLoudest</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1356399980434</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:46:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is plagued by over-commitment and under-delivery. They do need a management shake-up.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1356400980573</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:03:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356401149097-103</Id><Title>Acer to release $99 tablet in emerging markets.</Title><Msg>Now that just about everyone and their brother is selling tablets, the inevitable price wars will begin. Acer is off to an early start, according a report in the Wall Street Journal. The WSJ is reporting that Acer is planning to launch the Iconia B1 Android tablet for just $99, a major price cut compared to 7-inch tablets like the $159 Amazon Kindle Fire. Unfortunately for U.S. consumers, the company is currently planning on releasing the Iconia B1 in emerging markets, though it has submitted the tablet to the FCC. The launch is designed to combat Asus' rumored low-price Android slate, which is supposedly also due next year, though an Asus spokesperson denied such reports. The new budget tablet for developing economies marks a pivot for Acer in its tablet strategy. According to the Journal's unnamed source, the company is shifting from higher-profit devices as competitors like the Google Nexus 10 drag prices down. Acer's push for cheaper tablets isn't limited to the Iconia B1. Another source told the Journal that the company is developing a new Intel-based Windows 8 tablet as its current versions are "too pricey." These include the Iconia W510, which is selling for $549 and up, and the Iconia W700, which starts at $800. Even if the Iconia B1 never reaches American shores, the day when a major manufacturer releases a $99 tablet in the United States will soon be upon us. There are too many players in the market, and someone will be desparate enough to take the plunge in order to move units. Maybe it will be Acer after all, or another Android proponent like Lenovo. Or maybe Amazon will finally take the leap, and drop the Kindle Fire to an ad-supported $100.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1356401149097</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:05:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356401292000-104</Id><Topic><Title>Last year Everyone said X86 was power hungry, couldn't fit smartphones</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1356390664935</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 18:11:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder what Motorola's X phone will have inside. What on Earth could X stand for??</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1356401292000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:08:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356402075900-105</Id><Topic><Title>LOLoudest</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1356399980434</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:46:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is plagued by over-commitment and under-delivery ____________________________ Pretty hilarious to hear that coming from a guy who's favorite company depends on getting its chips made by the KING of over-promising and under- delivering. SMH</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1356402075900</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:21:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356402741491-106</Id><Title>Intel is gonna hurt Qualcom bad..........real bad</Title><Msg>Although the tweet didn’t mention specifically any launch delays, it said that Qualcomm is having problems meeting the demand for its highly sought-after Snapdragon S4 processor, which spells trouble for Asus, since it’s the same processor that powers the Asus Padfone. The Verge got in touch with an Asus spokesperson who confirmed the processor shortage that is “affecting all of Qualcomm’s customers”. Note, however, that a delay was not mentioned. So, how bad is this S4 chip shortage? Well, bad enough to warrant public declarations from Qualcomm’s top brass. CEO Paul Jacobs declared last week that the American chip-maker is facing problems with satisfying the big demand for the 28nm process chip. The shortage will supposedly not affect Qualcomm’s top-tier clients, such as Samsung, but is likely to perturb smaller clients, like Asus.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1356402741491</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:32:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356402992131-107</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is gonna hurt Qualcom bad..........real bad</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1356402741491</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:32:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many of Qualcom's customers will decide that working with Intel and a better or even equal chip makes much more sense than working with Qualcom at a later node that they can't even supply consistently? The tide is about to change in Mobile and WORST CASE, Intel will get a share of the pie that makes it's Mobile endeavors fruitful.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1356402992131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:36:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356408345186-108</Id><Title>Chart of the day: Apple shares are still up nearly 29% this year but not INTC</Title><Msg>LLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>intciscrud</Username><Timestamp>1356408345186</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:05:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356408463100-109</Id><Topic><Title>QCOM is the king!</Title><Username>yourdaddy830</Username><Timestamp>1334690604000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-04-17 15:23:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agree</Msg><Username>intciscrud</Username><Timestamp>1356408463100</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:07:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356408501466-110</Id><Topic><Title>Market tanking and Intel holding it's own. Can't be good for shorts.</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1356366337544</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>normal day</Msg><Username>intciscrud</Username><Timestamp>1356408501466</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:08:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356408709648-111</Id><Title>1 year, 2 year, 5 year, max chart...INTV vs QCOM......QCOM trounces INTC</Title><Msg>yet INTC bagholders continue to beat their hairy chests. Futilely might add. ahahhahhahahhahhaa</Msg><Username>intciscrud</Username><Timestamp>1356408709648</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:11:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356409902083-112</Id><Topic><Title>An article on Google Finance for Intel, trashing Cramer's call.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1356400835478</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:00:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cramer is a clown, The Street can't afford the proper attire, so just use your imagination.</Msg><Username>bankie3</Username><Timestamp>1356409902083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:31:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356410072743-113</Id><Topic><Title>QCOM is the king!</Title><Username>yourdaddy830</Username><Timestamp>1334690604000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-04-17 15:23:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How will Qualcomm compete with Intel once all baseband functions get integrated to the CPU? 4G and WiFi are big battery drains, rose point at 32nm halves the power and increases performance of WiFi, and will only get better at 22nm and 14nm. Digital radio freakazzoid it's coming and Qualcomm won't have it.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1356410072743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:34:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356410277703-114</Id><Topic><Title>1 year, 2 year, 5 year, max chart...INTV vs QCOM......QCOM trounces INTC</Title><Username>intciscrud</Username><Timestamp>1356408709648</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:11:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many times must I repeat this for the idiots?? Past performance doesn't indicate future performance, and PPS is a meaningless measure, Qualcomm trades at double the P/E of Intel which means they have a lot farther to fall.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1356410277703</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:37:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356410548219-115</Id><Topic><Title>Acer to release $99 tablet in emerging markets.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1356401149097</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:05:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A tablet for emerging markets should feature desktop applications and not assume a WiFi connection. So this is probably a tablet for people in emerging-market cities. But the idea of an affordable computer for third-world rural-areas is a computer that should have a keyboard. Then letters or documents can be typed and such. A tablet is best used as a coffee-shop browser.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1356410548219</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:42:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356411341825-116</Id><Topic><Title>1 year, 2 year, 5 year, max chart...INTV vs QCOM......QCOM trounces INTC</Title><Username>intciscrud</Username><Timestamp>1356408709648</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:11:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>QCOM UP today....INTC DOWN...AGAIN, it's started. Bye bye INTC bagholders.</Msg><Username>intciscrud</Username><Timestamp>1356411341825</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:55:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>