<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345954043000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Tick-Tock: The Intel Party Doesn't Stop</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345943992000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:19:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a queue of product families that are sequentially released on each new process. The Ivy Bridge desktop was the first product released on 22nm. Historically, the Atom was one of the last product families to migrate to the new process. Intel could change the order and move the Atom/SoC products up the process line. What effect would giving the low power smartphone/tablet products a pass to the front of the line have on the 2 year cycle? Cut it in half?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1345954043000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 00:07:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345954896000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Tick-Tock: The Intel Party Doesn't Stop</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345943992000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:19:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What effect would giving the low power smartphone/tablet products a pass to the front of the line have on the 2 year cycle? Cut it in half?" I don't think it's as simple as that. There's a reason why low power is at 32nm and the rest at 22nm -- Intel has not optimized the production of specific chips at low power below 32nm. It takes time to do this. Even if you prioritize low power first, you have to face the learning curve of going to a new process generation with a new chip architecture. The volumes involved are so high, there are so many possible variations in the process at fine resolutions that you have to optimize for everything. At low power, they would be doing that for the first time below 32nm. It not a simple mix and match exercise that would cut production time in half because you re-prioritized your targets.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1345954896000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 00:21:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345967281000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Tick-Tock: The Intel Party Doesn't Stop</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345943992000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:19:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Even if does give an advantage, Intel can't prevent someone else from following it." *** Yeah, all these things Intel does are easy. All the competitors have to do is follow. Gee, except it takes them three years on average to figure out how to do it and they still don't do it as well. It doesn't matter if what Intel does has a catchy name. It matters if it works and if it produces superior products. Yes to both. The process generation you refer to as long is the shortest in the industry. No one else can match Intel's every eight quarter fabrication cycle. No one even comes close. You continue to throw up criticism that only demonstrates your ignorance about fabrication. I don't know - maybe you're a Wall Street analyst...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345967281000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 03:48:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345968179000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Tick-Tock: The Intel Party Doesn't Stop</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345943992000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:19:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has said on a number of occasions that that is what they are doing and it will cut the time in half. Read up... "The move to Tri-Gate Transistors delivers roughly twice the improvement in transistor performance over conventional planar scaling when applied to low-power applications like smartphones and Ultrabooks. We combine our process technology, manufacturing and design to produce a highly leveraged business model that is becoming increasingly rare in our industry. That model allows us to do things others can't, like advancing our Atom roadmap at twice the rate of Moore's Law through 2014." http://seekingalpha.com/article/505221-intel-s-ceo-discusses-q1-2012-results-earnings-call-transcript</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345968179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 04:02:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345968481000-5</Id><Title>Intel's Next Major Catalyst: IDF</Title><Msg>"Technology Insight: Intel Next Generation Microarchitecture Code Name Haswell" According to the description, this session will give nitty-gritty details on how this next generation CPU will offer "significant improvements in performance and energy consumption, as well as supporting additional enhancements for graphics and support for powerful new instructions". This is particularly exciting, as this first that even on the same 22nm "tri-gate" manufacturing process, the company will manage to meaningfully improve performance and power efficiency. According to Anandtech: "Internally [to Intel] Haswell is viewed as the solution to the ARM (ARMH) problem. Build a chip that can deliver extremely low idle power, to the point where you can't tell the difference between an ARM tablet running in standby and one with a Haswell inside. At the same time give it the performance we've come to expect from Intel" The implications here are fairly dramatic: if Intel is successful, not only do traditional notebooks, as well as "ultrabooks", see significant performance and battery life improvements (spurring upgrades), but this could very well give Intel a huge competitive advantage in the high end tablet segment (for example, the Surface Pro from Microsoft (MSFT) ). That's not to mention that a high performance, even more power efficient CPU core will bring about dramatic performance and power efficiency improvements in higher performance desktops, workstations and servers. http://seekingalpha.com/article/828241-intel-s-next-major-catalyst-the-intel-developer-forum</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345968481000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 04:08:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345975468000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Next Major Catalyst: IDF</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345968481000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 04:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idle power is so yesterday. The future lies in dynamic power reduction. All day battery life on web browsing work-loads comes from this. That's also where your arhcitecture kicks in. When you have a lot of gates in your design, it becomes harder to bring this down.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1345975468000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 06:04:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345975805000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Tick-Tock: The Intel Party Doesn't Stop</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345943992000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:19:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously, we don't share the same level of optimism when it comes to Intel's performance as a technology company. I think their work is about par for the course and there are companies such as ARM that are superior in this area. I think Intel's suffers from an over-confidence in its process prowess when actually that's what's slowing them down.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1345975805000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 06:10:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345987412000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama documentary goes viral, tops box office</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1345942942000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:02:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think I forgot to spit on you today. Spitewee, take that you slimeball.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1345987412000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 09:23:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345988665000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Calls?</Title><Username>hortonhmej3545</Username><Timestamp>1345984537000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:35:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please always share this to us.</Msg><Username>minsterscgu75362</Username><Timestamp>1345988665000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 09:44:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345989077000-10</Id><Topic><Title>i don't care about the stock price</Title><Username>icantstanditnomore</Username><Timestamp>1345858186000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 21:29:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe you better care about the price, 6.3% loss in the last week or so. That's almost 2 yrs of dividends</Msg><Username>joleejones</Username><Timestamp>1345989077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 09:51:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345990306000-11</Id><Topic><Title>GETANID61 - One desperate hypocrite</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1345942597000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 20:56:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've read his posts from day one and he's deteriorated from a guy that said both Intel and ARM would succeed to..........and venomous snake dreaming of the death of Intel. Sick dude !</Msg><Username>getsome_nads</Username><Timestamp>1345990306000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345990654000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Calls?</Title><Username>hortonhmej3545</Username><Timestamp>1345984537000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:35:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing</Msg><Username>boydivs4164</Username><Timestamp>1345990654000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345990707000-13</Id><Topic><Title>i don't care about the stock price</Title><Username>icantstanditnomore</Username><Timestamp>1345858186000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 21:29:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not if you dont sell...it will be back up....</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1345990707000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:18:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345991796000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Calls?</Title><Username>hortonhmej3545</Username><Timestamp>1345984537000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:35:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clear videos</Msg><Username>cardozojlas8966</Username><Timestamp>1345991796000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:36:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345992121000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Obama documentary goes viral, tops box office</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1345942942000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:02:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep spitting. All you are doing is validating that Liberals are out-of-control losers. You're deep hatred for your own pathetic life makes me laugh.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1345992121000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:42:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345992357000-16</Id><Title>Is 21 a safe price longterm ?</Title><Msg>I'm in at 21 and want to turn the computer off, collect the Dividend for the next 20 years and move on to something else. Am I safe at a cost basis of 21 for the next 20 years or is this thing gonna end up being a 4 dollar stock like AMD as a result of ARM punking it?</Msg><Username>motorbike_trash</Username><Timestamp>1345992357000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:45:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345992493000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Tick-Tock: The Intel Party Doesn't Stop</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345943992000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:19:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TICK-TOCK, TICK-TOCK Intel is a DEAD STOCK! Has been for 10 years!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1345992493000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>30</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345992555000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Calls?</Title><Username>hortonhmej3545</Username><Timestamp>1345984537000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:35:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Expecting more news</Msg><Username>pingreeodia63605</Username><Timestamp>1345992555000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345992896000-19</Id><Title>TICK TOCK, TICK TOCK Wallis Weaver is a Stoopid SCHLOCK</Title><Msg>24 x 7 x 365 Wallwad. Like rust, he NEVER sleeps.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1345992896000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:54:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>37</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345992906000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Tick-Tock: The Intel Party Doesn't Stop</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345943992000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:19:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is a mature company and not a big growth stock. People buy intc mostly as a safe bet and to collect the dividends. You are a fool if you invest in intc and expect it to double or triple.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1345992906000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345994579000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 RT is simply another nearly non-existent ecosystem going up against two ecosystems each with hundreds of thousands of apps. The catch-22 is that nobody will buy it without apps,and developers won't build apps without customers. The big apps like Facebook, Angry Birds and IHeartRadio will come on fairly quickly for RT. The more obscure ones that have barely made it to Android such as banking and DVR management won't show up in RT. I know this sounds like it wouldn't be bad, but anybody who has ever used an Android tablet knows the feeling of seeing a much needed app that is only available for iPad. Multiply this times a thousand and that will be the experience. "I can't wait to get rid of my iPad for a Windows 8 RT tablet" said no high school student ever.</Msg><Username>lti.steve</Username><Timestamp>1345994579000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:22:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345995301000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Is 21 a safe price longterm ?</Title><Username>motorbike_trash</Username><Timestamp>1345992357000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no one knows for sure, diversification on that 20 years of dividends would be a good idea. Intel was king in the mid 90s and obviously missed opportunities but then hindsight is always 20/20</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1345995301000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:35:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345995365000-23</Id><Topic><Title>ARM World in Legal Bloodbath</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345908309000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 11:25:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The selling point and spirit of ARM is that small companies can build hardware and software and compete against the big boys. The reality is that the large corporations like Apple don't want competition. The lawsuits only retard growth and creativity in the market. Greed and the need to control markets is throwing a sword in the heart of the movement. We all benefit from competition, better products, more features, and lower prices. The problem with Apple is that walled garden is really a prison camp and the rulers aren't as benevolent as they claim to be.</Msg><Username>lti.steve</Username><Timestamp>1345995365000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:36:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345995529000-24</Id><Title>Apple patent victory is not good for consumers</Title><Msg>and aim at reducing competetion. http://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-patent-victory-boosts-microsoft-024338102.html common Apple didn't you steal deesign ideas ???</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345995529000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:38:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345996104000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Apple patent victory is not good for consumers</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345995529000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>someone should of patent the semiconductor and not anyone else use it unless they pay a fee.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1345996104000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:48:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345996692000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Apple patent victory is not good for consumers</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345995529000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All patents are stupid if you're not creating something entirely new. They seriously need a reform.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1345996692000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:58:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345997034000-27</Id><Title>Apple/Samsung/Intel</Title><Msg>Sure hope that Apple has another foundry source for those "A" chips that are essential to the iPhone, iPad, iPod and a few other products that make up about 80% of apple's revenue. If they are stuck with Samsung Austin, one could imagine that Samsung could mysteriously have a terrible yield problem and the "A" chip flow could turn into a trickle. Is Apple dumb enough to fire this commercial ICBM (lawsuit) at Samsung without having another supplier lined up? I don't think so. Think Intel. FYI, Paul Ottelini in NOT scheduled to speak at the Intel Developer Forum Sep 11-13. I can't find where that has ever happened before. Also remember that the rumored introduction date for the iPhone 5 is Sep 12. Just maybe an Ottelini appearance at the Apple announcement trumps his speech at the IDF. We've seen it before on the change from Power PC chip to x86 back in 2006. Ottelini was on-stage with Steve Jobs for that little announcement. Key question: If Intel is announced as the new Apple "A" chip supplier, does the Intel stock add $10 or $20 on the very next day of trading?</Msg><Username>semiwiz2002</Username><Timestamp>1345997034000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:03:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345997050000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Apple patent victory is not good for consumers</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345995529000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agree. some patents are so petty that shouldn't be accepted to begin with, like the rounded corners of the phone etc.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345997050000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:04:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345998274000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh My... nothing can possibly grow or change... give up now... new apps are non-existent... Yet here they come, and as always... you repeat game over before it's begun... btw, how much cheaper are they ?? 1/3 the price...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345998274000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:24:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345998460000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Apple patent victory is not good for consumers</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345995529000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It'l be good for Intel since people don't like being "stuck" with one company and Apple is looking more and more like a bully. I'm crossing my fingers that a United States launch date for this Motorolla phone is announced in September. This phone looks awesome, so what's the freaking hold-up? http://www.pcmag.com/article2/0,2817,2400278,00.asp</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1345998460000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:27:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345999095000-31</Id><Title>This Intel phone will be a winner, IMO</Title><Msg>I think they'll bring it out next year on 22nm. Intel is in it to win it, rolling out new phones around the world to see what's good and bad about them so when this one comes out, there will be no issues. Freakin sweet phone. pcmag.com/article2/0,2817,2400278,00.asp</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1345999095000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:38:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345999744000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Apple patent victory is not good for consumers</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345995529000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Motorolla ----------- must be one of them there Eyetalian phones! DUH! TOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1345999744000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:49:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345999815000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Apple/Samsung/Intel</Title><Username>semiwiz2002</Username><Timestamp>1345997034000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:03:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll go for $20.00. Were are already #10.00/share undervalued to fair market price and competitors. That would leave me to believe we get that back and another $10.00 too.</Msg><Username>StockJock44</Username><Timestamp>1345999815000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:50:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345999959000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Apple/Samsung/Intel</Title><Username>semiwiz2002</Username><Timestamp>1345997034000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:03:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whiner boy: Why doesn't management come forward and defend the shareholders? They could talk about the huge honking $5 miss that's already priced in. TOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1345999959000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:52:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>35</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346000115000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Windows 8 RT is simply another nearly non-existent ecosystem going up against two ecosystems each with hundreds of thousands of apps. The catch-22 is that nobody will buy it without apps,and developers won't build apps without customers" ditto</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1346000115000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:55:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346000217000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Apple/Samsung/Intel</Title><Username>semiwiz2002</Username><Timestamp>1345997034000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:03:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Just maybe an Ottelini appearance at the Apple announcement trumps his speech at the IDF. We've seen it before on the change from Power PC chip to x86 back in 2006. Ottelini was on-stage with Steve Jobs for that little announcement." could be, i like your thinking</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1346000217000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:56:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346000990000-37</Id><Topic><Title>Apple patent victory is not good for consumers</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345995529000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Motorolllllllllllllllllllllla! duhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh! toooooooooooooooooooooooooooo funnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnny!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346000990000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 13:09:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>34</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346001340000-38</Id><Title>My One-Star Puppy Dog</Title><Msg>I named him "Lemming." TOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346001340000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 13:15:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>35</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346005049000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Is INTC a Sure Shot? Im looking at INTC like a HAWK</Title><Username>mamiemamie27</Username><Timestamp>1345903677000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 10:07:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think people just pamper the Site.look So many people visit the site and gave lot of review.</Msg><Username>mcintoshmelanie</Username><Timestamp>1346005049000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 14:17:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346006848000-40</Id><Title>Back to $26 this week</Title><Msg>There is no other way around. INTC can't stay this low and the only way left for INTC to go is up and up.</Msg><Username>help4all1332</Username><Timestamp>1346006848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 14:47:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346008283000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Back to $26 this week</Title><Username>help4all1332</Username><Timestamp>1346006848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 14:47:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$26 can be accomplished just in one day but I think it is going back to $28 in September.</Msg><Username>cash_is_king_now</Username><Timestamp>1346008283000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 15:11:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346010134000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Next Major Catalyst: IDF</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345968481000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 04:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When you have a lot of gates in your design, it becomes harder to bring this down." *** Hahahahahahaha Your comments on fabrication are hilarious. I have three seconds - tell me everything you know about FinFET. Oh - you already did...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346010134000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 15:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346010743000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Tick-Tock: The Intel Party Doesn't Stop</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345943992000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:19:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obviously, we don't share the same level of optimism when it comes to Intel's performance as a technology company. I think their work is about par for the course and there are companies such as ARM that are superior in this area. I think Intel's suffers from an over-confidence in its process prowess when actually that's what's slowing them down." *** Call your physicist because your connection to the plane of reality has been broken. Intel has been three years ahead of the competition in fabrication for quite some time now. With FinFET that's moving up to four years. ARM isn't going to be capable of 14nm, FinFET, EUV or 450mm for years and years. They are struggling mightily with 28nm volume production and we won't see them do volume on 20nm for years. Do you have a single fact at your disposal? You are the typical lucy, fanboi type - making it up as you go...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346010743000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 15:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346010832000-44</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've been enjoying watching the RT get downgraded by Microsoft over the past couple of years. You were certain that it would be the death of Intel and ARM would be running native Windows programs. As one of your posts from Nvidia put it "Game over." But not only are there no legacy apps Microsoft seems to want this product all to itself. And you wonder why I am skeptical? Now you're saying that ARM64 is going to be the great savior of ARM. Next year Intel cranks up the 22nm production and will head directly to that wonderful ARM 95% market share in the smartphone world. You are the one who keeps coming on this board trying to paint the illusion that ARMH is in control of the future. Last year the "Whole world" invested in ARM and next year the "Whole World" will start to invest in Intel. Consumers buy products for what they can do oblivious to the electronics inside. If they transition from ARM to Intel most of the world won't know or care. If I were you I would be a bit more concerned than you claim to be. You are talking about one competitor who controls the entire design and manufacturing process, plus has money to spend on marketing it's products. Intel isn't a company that can often knock out the competition in the first round, but they have the stamina and tenacity to go round after round, each time getting smarter and fighting harder. Decentralized design, manufacturing and marketing among many companies means a diluted revenue stream to compete against Intel. You say it comes down to design, I say it comes down to money. We'll find out soon enough who is right.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1346010832000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 15:53:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346010977000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Obama documentary goes viral, tops box office</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1345942942000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:02:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. The loser to the loser of last election is going to defeat the winner of last election. Talk about people getting delusional. Obama is going to win it by a mile. The trailer trash can then decide to either move to Iraq or Afghanistan. Mexico won't take them.</Msg><Username>tsunamidec2004</Username><Timestamp>1346010977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 15:56:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346011127000-46</Id><Topic><Title>Obama documentary goes viral, tops box office</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1345942942000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:02:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. The loser to the loser of last election is going to defeat the winner of last election. Talk about people getting delusional. Obama is going to win it by a mile. The trailer trash can then decide to either move to Iraq or Afghanistan. Mexico won't take them. ___________________ "Real men don't use multiple aliases" - Wallisweaver</Msg><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1346011127000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 15:58:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346011307000-47</Id><Topic><Title>Obama documentary goes viral, tops box office</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1345942942000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:02:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are so smart. Must have the same genes as Sarah Palin. Can't even figure out the aliases.</Msg><Username>tsunamidec2004</Username><Timestamp>1346011307000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:01:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346012499000-48</Id><Title>TICK, TOCK, INTC IS A DEAD STOCK</Title><Msg>has been for years.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346012499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:21:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>31</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346012731000-49</Id><Topic><Title>Tick-Tock: The Intel Party Doesn't Stop</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1345943992000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:19:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dead money for 10 years</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346012731000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:25:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>32</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346014505000-50</Id><Topic><Title>Obama documentary goes viral, tops box office</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1345942942000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:02:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sarah Palin looks like a Brain Surgeon compared to John Edwards.....ouch.</Msg><Username>wallispumper</Username><Timestamp>1346014505000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:55:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346015812000-51</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Now you're saying that ARM64 is going to be the great savior of ARM." Open up all new markets for the ARM ISA... "Next year Intel cranks up the 22nm production and will head directly to that wonderful ARM 95% market share in the smartphone world." Next Year ARM64 cranks up production and will head directly to that wonderful x86 server market share in the server world... And with that 22nm, INtel still can't build an SOC... "You are the one who keeps coming on this board trying to paint the illusion that ARMH is in control of the future." ARMH is a rubber stamp... " Last year the "Whole world" invested in ARM and next year the "Whole World" will start to invest in Intel." Repeat: ARM64 " You are talking about one competitor who controls the entire design and manufacturing process, plus has money to spend on marketing it's products." With INtel controlling it all... Any chance Microsoft would port their OS to ARM... " Decentralized design, manufacturing and marketing among many companies means a diluted revenue stream to compete against Intel." wake up... ARM's numbers are growing !!!! "You say it comes down to design, I say it comes down to money." Who has more $$... INtel... or the world...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346015812000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:16:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346016572000-52</Id><Topic><Title>Obama documentary goes viral, tops box office</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1345942942000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:02:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gawwwd almighty are you delusional and dim. I know. You only look at Fuxed up news and listen to the Raspukin poll. Hey--the latest Rasmussen poll has Obummer pulling ahead. He was down 2 pts and he is now up 2 pts. Funny you teabagging imbreds telling women to have babys after being raped is not going so well. If it were you--most of you GOPtards--no baby anyway because the sperm count is too low. The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Sunday shows President Obama attracting support from 47% of voters nationwide, while Mitt Romney earns 45% of the vote. Three percent (3%) prefer some other candidate, and six percent (6%) are undecided. Eat it trash man.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1346016572000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:29:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346017066000-53</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But not only are there no legacy apps Microsoft seems to want this product all to itself. And you wonder why I am skeptical? Now you're saying that ARM64 is going to be the great savior of ARM." analyst saying the very same but getanid is well got a nid</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1346017066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346017144000-54</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But not only are there no legacy apps Microsoft seems to want this product all to itself. And you wonder why I am skeptical? Now you're saying that ARM64 is going to be the great savior of ARM." analyst saying the very same but getanid is well got a nid</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1346017144000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346017663000-55</Id><Topic><Title>Obama documentary goes viral, tops box office</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1345942942000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:02:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For Retards, sure Sarah Palin would look like what you said. For normal people, she is just a hooter's babe who is ripping of the tealiban for the money. Can you too see Russia from your porch? I can see it from my google map all the way from California.</Msg><Username>tsunamidec2004</Username><Timestamp>1346017663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:47:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346017704000-56</Id><Title>Wouldn't mind seeing $30</Title><Msg>Just bought on Thurs @25.13. Ask that all posters get friends and relatives to buy.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346017704000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:48:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346020071000-57</Id><Topic><Title>ThinkPad Tablet 2 boasts an Intel Atom processor</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1345925450000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 16:10:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a link to the Lenovo tablet: http://www.lenovo.com/products/us/tablet/thinkpad/thinkpad-tablet-2/ And I've been saying that the PC makers should be very clear that they have an Atom tablet for consumers and an Ivy Bridge tablet for business. Of course the screen size should be 10.1". But this Lenovo tablet has corners that are too square. I would go with oval shaped corners.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1346020071000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:27:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346020328000-58</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The catch-22 is that nobody will buy it without apps,and developers won't build apps without customers." How many legacy apps are there for touchscreen Win8 apps...?? Answer: NONE !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ""I can't wait to get rid of my iPad for a Windows 8 RT tablet" said no high school student ever." RT tablets still unavailable... but hey... when you got nothing, bring up the above...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346020328000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:32:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346020364000-59</Id><Title>DO YOU WANT MORE MISERY WITH OBAMA?</Title><Msg>I don't and my whole family feels the same. for us, obama is out, romney is in. p.s. We are independent voters.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1346020364000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:32:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346020567000-60</Id><Topic><Title>TA Travel Centers America</Title><Username>detroitredwings77554</Username><Timestamp>1345832998000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 14:29:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GET WITH TA Travel Centers America they...are ready for a big ride soon. Whats the secret, are you just pumping TA, do you actually know something? Why didn't you post the link about their 'big ride?' What does the Flying J think about this?</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1346020567000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:36:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346022930000-61</Id><Topic><Title>DO YOU WANT MORE MISERY WITH OBAMA?</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1346020364000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:32:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well we'll see about that. Our current misery is centered around the policies and actions taken by an imbecile Republitard president that we had for 8 years. Blaming Obama for this a joke.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1346022930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 19:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346025047000-62</Id><Title>Stripper recruitment for GOP convention...</Title><Msg>I guess Republiscum are not as 'pure' as they say they are. http://www.aol.com/video/tampa-strippers-gear-up-for-republican-convention/517455497/?icid=maing-grid10%7Chtmlws-main-bb%7Cdl3%7Csec3_lnk1%26pLid%3D196896</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1346025047000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 19:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346025204000-63</Id><Topic><Title>DO YOU WANT MORE MISERY WITH OBAMA?</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1346020364000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:32:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Americans love misery. They "elected" Bush and the sold out morons, money prostitutes. Then they elected him again to destroy everything that he didnt the first time. Then they tried to go democratic and elected Obama as a hope in the middle of Armageddon and it was averted for a while. Then they got miserable again and destroyed his capacity to legislate by taking congress again to republicans. That way the misery and the party of No continued the work of Bush to make America a third world country. Senate is non issue since filibuster methods by the party of No cant get anything done even if they do not have the majority. So you want to know what is misery??? Misery is being a republican and misery is being an idiot sub educated moron american that gives always a break to the real AIDS of this society that is the repugnant party of backwards marching to oblivion totalitarian plutocrat sucking losers. You want to recover America and restore its path to greatness, the solution is simple; Never ever again elect republicans in any facking position anywhere until first they prove they are no longer matherf@ckers that put the money of sobs above dignity, country and ETHICS. Burn the losers and bury them to the irrelevance of history they deserve. And then put a stick on them and nuke it to dust so that they never come back as vampires...like they love to do even as burned.</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1346025204000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 19:53:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346027667000-64</Id><Topic><Title>DO YOU WANT MORE MISERY WITH OBAMA?</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1346020364000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:32:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go romney.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1346027667000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:34:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346030401000-65</Id><Title>MR. BUFFETT = THE TECHNOLOGY LEADER (drops intc)</Title><Msg>Buffett drops ALL intc stock, but picks up more IBM shares ! What's the matter with holding intc stock ??</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1346030401000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:20:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346030557000-66</Id><Topic><Title>MR. BUFFETT = THE TECHNOLOGY LEADER (drops intc)</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1346030401000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spammer</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1346030557000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:22:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346030560000-67</Id><Title>Letter to Goldman Sachs</Title><Msg>Mr. Lloyd C. Blankfein, CEO The Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. 200 West Street 29th Floor New York, NY 10282 Dear Mr. Blankfein, It is with great dismay that I have watched Goldman Sachs engage in what appears to be a continuous campaign to negatively impact the stock price of one of America’s great businesses and success stories – Intel. Goldman Sachs, through its analyst James Covello, has expressed excessively negative opinions regarding Intel’s operations and results and enough downgrades to fill a bushel basket. This has occurred not just for a period of weeks or months but literally for a period of years. Mr. Covello appears not only to understand little about fabrication and the chip sector – he appears to have little or no learning curve. He not only has been wrong about Intel, he has been consistently wrong. When it becomes clear that he has been wrong, instead of correcting his views, he simply doubles down. This horrid record in regard to judging and predicting Intel’s performance leads one to question the internal machinations within Goldman Sachs. Are there no corrective actions within Goldman for an analyst with excessively bad judgment that continues for years? For if there are then there has to be another reason for Goldman’s constantly bearish opinions and reports to the press. There are only a couple of possibilities. My great fear is that Goldman’s opinions on Intel have nothing to do with Intel’s fundamentals or results – that Goldman’s opinions on Intel are related to some trading strategy. A phrase for this type of behavior would be "greed at the expense of ethics." Of course I have no way to know exactly why Goldman consistently bashes one of America’s great companies, one of America’s great success stories and a company that manufactures here at home. At a very difficult economic time it would seem that Goldman would attempt to assist in an economic recovery. It appears to me that Goldman is engaging in activities that are as a minimum ethically distasteful and that additionally work against US economic recovery. A review of Intel’s PE ratio clearly demonstrates that the company has been valued far below that of an average S&amp;P 500 while producing substantially better results. It appears to me that Goldman has had a significant role in this valuation with its constant negative views, downgrades and press releases. It also appears to me that Goldman’s efforts in regards to Intel are being mirrored by a number of other key Wall Street firms. I don’t know why anyone with access to information would attempt to present such a biased viewpoint for this extended period of time. I therefore request that you conduct a full investigation of Goldman’s trading, analyzing and reporting activities in regards to Intel. And that you report back to Intel shareholders exactly why Goldman has supported market views of Intel that are not substantiated by facts or actual performance. Until such time as you do, I will ask others to make this same request of you. And I will encourage everyone I know to stop doing business with Goldman until said report is issued. Intel shareholders and investors have had enough of this behavior. We want explanations. Sincerely,</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346030560000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346030866000-68</Id><Topic><Title>MR. BUFFETT = THE TECHNOLOGY LEADER (drops intc)</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1346030401000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr Buffett never invested in technology until recently. He did not make his money investing in tech stocks.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1346030866000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:27:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346030894000-69</Id><Topic><Title>MR. BUFFETT = THE TECHNOLOGY LEADER (drops intc)</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1346030401000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a tip: Don't pick old guys to give you advice on technology. Why do you think Wall Street is so clueless about Intel and yet gives ARM a huge, honking giant P/E ratio? Because they can barely get their minds around a cell phone - much less fabrication, servers and Big Data...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346030894000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346031714000-70</Id><Topic><Title>DO YOU WANT MORE MISERY WITH OBAMA?</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1346020364000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:32:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republiscum will burn in hell for what they have done to our great country.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1346031714000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346032481000-71</Id><Topic><Title>MR. BUFFETT = THE TECHNOLOGY LEADER (drops intc)</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1346030401000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel was the only 100% tech stock that he ever owned. He views IBM as a services and conculting company. Berkshire Hathaway Inc. Form 13F Information Table June 30, 2012 http://yahoo.brand.edgar-online.com/displayfilinginfo.aspx?FilingID=8772941-1188-20918&amp;type=sect&amp;TabIndex=2&amp;companyid=54239&amp;ppu=%252fdefault.aspx%253fcik%253d1067983</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346032481000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:54:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346035784000-72</Id><Topic><Title>Letter to Goldman Sachs</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346030560000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Scottsdale Scotty would be proud of you, pumpwad! LET'S CLEAN UP THIS FORUM NOW!!! TOOOO FUNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346035784000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 22:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>35</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346036914000-73</Id><Topic><Title>MR. BUFFETT = THE TECHNOLOGY LEADER (drops intc)</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1346030401000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a tip 4 U, blade. http://shine.yahoo.com/shine-food/only-way-cook-corn-cob-202600680.html</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346036914000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 23:08:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>37</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346037100000-74</Id><Topic><Title>MR. BUFFETT = THE TECHNOLOGY LEADER (drops intc)</Title><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1346030401000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is why lucy is in a bad mood today. http://news.ninemsn.com.au/world/8522236/man-in-malaysia-bitten-by-crocodile-during-toilet-break</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346037100000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 23:11:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346039128000-75</Id><Topic><Title>Letter to Goldman Sachs</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346030560000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for the articulate letter you sent GS clearly expressing the frustrations of many Intel investors. I agree with the suggestion you send a copy of that letter to the SEC. Thanks again.</Msg><Username>doo_the_baggar</Username><Timestamp>1346039128000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 23:45:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346039217000-76</Id><Title>Petascale Supercomputer Under Development in Russia</Title><Msg>Not much has been revealed regarding the specifics of the system, but Shabanov noted that energy efficiency is a key feature of the upcoming super and will employ a “unique cooling system” as well as and cutting-edge x86 coprocessors. The suggests the machine will rely on Xeon Phi (MIC) chips, Intel’s manycore acceleratore that is expected to debut before the end of the year. CPU and interconnect details weren’t revealed. http://www.hpcwire.com/hpcwire/2012-08-24/petascale_supercomputer_under_development_in_russia.html</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346039217000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 23:46:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346039626000-77</Id><Topic><Title>Letter to Goldman Sachs</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346030560000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, quit bashing GS, okay? I started buying INTC in da $18 thru $23. Without GS's downgrades, I probably wouldn't have got em so cheapie deepie. Iffin y'all like INTC you're probably are in buy mode. Iffin you're in buy mode, ya wanna buy cheap. If ya wanna buy cheap, ya need some great bashes. Now I axe ya, who better than GS to cook up a great bash, huh? C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( If you're a trader, just play da game. If you're trying to dump, ya shoulda dumped at da high. Look, just STFU and collect your GD dividends like da rest of us patient longs-who got in cheapie deepie and loving every minute of it. )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1346039626000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 23:53:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>