<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349507754423-1</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's A6 processor is good for Intel</Title><Username>stocktrade14</Username><Timestamp>1349481319567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:55:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A6 shrinks to 32nm from 45nm in A5. That makes A6 1.4X fastener. A6 possibly has 1.5X more transistors. Since I don’t know exactly, assume 1.3X. Another 1.3X speed. 32nm enables A6 to run at 1.6X clock speed. Another 1.6X bump Total speed bump =1.4*1.3*1.6 = 2.9 ------ Shrinks by themselves do not increase the speed of a processor. More transistors in the SoC do not increase the speed of the processor unless the transistors have been spent on the CPU. The A6 runs at 1Ghz while the A5 @ runs at 800 mhz. The A6 has around double the raw performance of the A5. This increase in performance is due to the new architecture, increased clock speed and a better memory interface. As for the rest of the ARM camp, the A15 can deliver this kind of performance (depending who/what you read, it will be faster) but the real question over the A15 is it's size (transistors) and power consumption. There is still a lot of leg room in the existing A9, with improved process tweaks (even at 40nm) meaning higher clocks for the same power envelopes, improvements to memory bandwidth etc</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1349507754423</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 03:15:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349512196663-2</Id><Topic><Title>TIRED OF OBAMA? I AM.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1349482647445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 20:17:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>me too</Msg><Username>gville632</Username><Timestamp>1349512196663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 04:29:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349528711991-3</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's A6 processor is good for Intel</Title><Username>stocktrade14</Username><Timestamp>1349481319567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:55:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even with their process lead, the A6 will be difficult to match for Intel, next year even, as long as they stay x86 based. The only way they can match is if they adopt ARM architecture, which I doubt they will do. My best case prediction for them is they come out slightly ahead of the A6 in 2013 with their 22nm OO chip and Apple will retake the lead 6 months later. Slightly ahead will not warrant a switch by either Apple or Samsung to IA. To stay in business, that's the kind of design win Intel needs. Otherwise, they're going to spend a lot of money and get very little market response. It's only now a matter of when they decide to can this whole low power IA effort.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1349528711991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:05:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349530667544-4</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's A6 processor is good for Intel</Title><Username>stocktrade14</Username><Timestamp>1349481319567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:55:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the umpteenth time............................Intel does NOT need Apple mobile business to succeed. It now has access to the Droid Market and Droids outsell Apple phones !!!!!!!!! Intel just needs to do what it does best and even if all it ever does is do "just as well" as Apple in chips, that will be fine because they'll be inside a zillion US-based Droids !</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1349530667544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:37:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349533350552-5</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's A6 processor is good for Intel</Title><Username>stocktrade14</Username><Timestamp>1349481319567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:55:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as long as the stock price dosnt shrink- 4%div with some upside. i will be a happy camper.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1349533350552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:22:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349533720353-6</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's A6 processor is good for Intel</Title><Username>stocktrade14</Username><Timestamp>1349481319567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:55:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read the comparisons between the razor i and razor m on the wedsites Engadget and The Verge. Both show an advantage for Intel in both performance and energy efficiency and thats with a 32mm single core medifield chip.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1349533720353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:28:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349533909493-7</Id><Topic><Title>TIRED OF OBAMA? I AM.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1349482647445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 20:17:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am voting romney in november</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1349533909493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:31:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349535170150-8</Id><Title>HAA HAA Like Romney cares about us? HAA HAA I heard his speak about the 47%</Title><Msg>He does noet give a rats about the midlle class in America. Yeah he is slick and great at debates, so what? he is still an ASH HOLE who outsourced jobs to other nations and moved his money off shore to avoid taxes. Do you pay 14% in taxes? Mitt does and he spits on the middle class. BUT Willard is going down and NO one day debate means sheeet. He loses by 6% or more. You rightwing teabagging trash can stick it and lick it. PUSSSSSSSSYS Unemployment down to 7,9% now so eat it crybaby teabagging KKK 1% #$%$.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1349535170150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:52:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349536739709-9</Id><Topic><Title>TIRED OF OBAMA? I AM.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1349482647445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 20:17:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I am voting romney in november" *** Guess you aren't a member of the 47 percent that Romney doesn't care about and thinks are deadbeats. Like seniors, students and members of the military...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349536739709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 11:18:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349536858379-10</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's A6 processor is good for Intel</Title><Username>stocktrade14</Username><Timestamp>1349481319567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:55:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Read the comparisons between the razor i and razor m on the wedsites Engadget and The Verge. Both show an advantage for Intel in both performance and energy efficiency and thats with a 32mm single core medifield chip." *** Shhhhhhhh. You'll upset Wall Street. They think Intel is going to have a $7 billion revenue miss come earnings...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349536858379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 11:20:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349537215487-11</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this Report on Intel Corporation? (INTC)</Title><Username>tamaton2495</Username><Timestamp>1349532926967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:15:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just subscribed. I am hoping for the best.</Msg><Username>myraxrur561500</Username><Timestamp>1349537215487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 11:26:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349537452526-12</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's A6 processor is good for Intel</Title><Username>stocktrade14</Username><Timestamp>1349481319567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:55:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right. Motorola has 12% of US market share which is big enough to make Intel's business viable.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1349537452526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 11:30:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349537519073-13</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's A6 processor is good for Intel</Title><Username>stocktrade14</Username><Timestamp>1349481319567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:55:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Even with their process lead, the A6 will be difficult to match for Intel, next year even, as long as they stay x86 based. The only way they can match is if they adopt ARM architecture, which I doubt they will do." [You must not have seen the Razor comparison showing that Intel already outperforms ARM, even using 32nm. You just keep spouting the same old stupidity...] "My best case prediction for them is they come out slightly ahead of the A6 in 2013 with their 22nm OO chip and Apple will retake the lead 6 months later." [Yeah the prediction from the guy who demonstrates daily that his knowledge of fabrication will fit on the head of a pin. Intel will easily be out in front with 22nm and hugely out in front with 14nm. It's all about the fabrication. Intel has it. ARM doesn't. Intel's fabrication is ramping up while ARM's coasts to a stop. ARM has nothing after 20nm - if they ever get there...] "To stay in business, that's the kind of design win Intel needs. Otherwise, they're going to spend a lot of money and get very little market response. It's only now a matter of when they decide to can this whole low power IA effort." [To stay in business. LOL. Intel is going to offer the best performance and the greatest power efficiency. And there is nothing ARM can do about it. After 2013 there will never be another reason to buy an ARM processor. ARM will be the next AMD - relegated to the low-end price value bargain basement section that Intel doesn't want. Intel has already won the low-power war. We're just waiting for it to play out. All about the fabrication, fanboi. All about the fabrication...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349537519073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 11:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349538441495-14</Id><Title>Downright Revolutionary</Title><Msg>This isn't rocket science, but it is enabled by Intel's clockwork fab execution. Designers can count on another 30% die area to work with every 2 years, so every 2 years they increase the size of these structures without worrying about ballooning the die. The beauty of evolutionary improvements like this is that when viewed over the long term they look downright revolutionary. Comparing Haswell to Conroe, the OoO scheduling window has grown by a factor of 2x, despite generation to generation gains of only 14 - 33%. [Where Intel goes, ARM can't follow. Why? ARM doesn't have the every 2 year fab cycle (not the money, not the technology and not the manufacturing prowess). And it never will...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349538441495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 11:47:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349538483328-15</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's A6 processor is good for Intel</Title><Username>stocktrade14</Username><Timestamp>1349481319567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:55:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel will be in Droids GLOBALLY and the DROIDS will NEED Inte's vast manufacturing to keep up with demand for its phones. Android races past Apple in smartphone market share By Julianne Pepitone @CNNMoneyTech August 9, 2012: 10:03 AM ET Android and iOS made up 85% of smartphone market share last quarter, according to an IDC report. NEW YORK (CNNMoney) -- The mobile space has quickly become a two-horse race between Google (GOOG, Fortune 500) and Apple -- and one of those giants significantly widened its lead last quarter. Google's Android surged to a whopping 68% share of the global smartphone market last quarter. That's four times the 17% market share held by Apple (AAPL, Fortune 500), according to a Wednesday report from research firm IDC. IDC, which tracks smartphone market share by operating system, said that nearly 105 million Android phones were shipped in the second quarter -- more than double the number shipped at the same time last year. Apple also showed strong growth, with an almost 28% gain over the previous year to 26 million phones shipped. "Android continues to fire on all cylinders," IDC senior research analyst Ramon Llamas said in the report, citing good prices and new phone models from Android's hardware partners as growth catalysts. More specifically, IDC pegged Android's gain "directly" to Samsung, which represented 44% of all Android phones shipped during the quarter. That's more than the next seven Android vendors combined, IDC said. Samsung's Galaxy S III debuted late in the quarter to favorable reviews. Apple and Samsung are currently locked in a heated court battle over Apple's allegations that Samsung illegally copied its iPhone design. Apple's iOS momentum was slowed this quarter by rumors that the iPhone 5 will be released in September. The iPhone 4S has been on the market since last October, so IDC said sales have "cooled." Meanwhile, Android and iOS's combined 85% market share didn't leave much room for competitors. Shipments of BlackBerry phones from Research in Motion (RIMM) fell a staggering 41% over the year to 7.4 million. That represented less than 5% of the market -- the lowest level since 2009, IDC said. It will be tough for RIM to improve its position this year, as the company said in June that its BlackBerry 10 operating system is delayed again until 2013. The once-popular Symbian operating system from Nokia (NOK) "sunk to a new nadir last quarter," IDC said, with shipments falling more than 60% over the year. Symbian now represents only 4.4% of the global market. Microsoft's Windows and the open-source Linux rounded out the last 6% of the market. To top of page</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1349538483328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 11:48:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349538577327-16</Id><Title>Android dominating Apple globally</Title><Msg>Intel will be a HUGE part of Android's GLOBAL future. It's a no-brainer. Droids will NEED Intel manufacturing to keep up with Demand and keep it's edge. Android races past Apple in smartphone market share By Julianne Pepitone @CNNMoneyTech August 9, 2012: 10:03 AM ET Android and iOS made up 85% of smartphone market share last quarter, according to an IDC report. NEW YORK (CNNMoney) -- The mobile space has quickly become a two-horse race between Google (GOOG, Fortune 500) and Apple -- and one of those giants significantly widened its lead last quarter. Google's Android surged to a whopping 68% share of the global smartphone market last quarter. That's four times the 17% market share held by Apple (AAPL, Fortune 500), according to a Wednesday report from research firm IDC. IDC, which tracks smartphone market share by operating system, said that nearly 105 million Android phones were shipped in the second quarter -- more than double the number shipped at the same time last year. Apple also showed strong growth, with an almost 28% gain over the previous year to 26 million phones shipped. "Android continues to fire on all cylinders," IDC senior research analyst Ramon Llamas said in the report, citing good prices and new phone models from Android's hardware partners as growth catalysts. More specifically, IDC pegged Android's gain "directly" to Samsung, which represented 44% of all Android phones shipped during the quarter. That's more than the next seven Android vendors combined, IDC said. Samsung's Galaxy S III debuted late in the quarter to favorable reviews. Apple and Samsung are currently locked in a heated court battle over Apple's allegations that Samsung illegally copied its iPhone design. Apple's iOS momentum was slowed this quarter by rumors that the iPhone 5 will be released in September. The iPhone 4S has been on the market since last October, so IDC said sales have "cooled." Meanwhile, Android and iOS's combined 85% market share didn't leave much room for competitors. Shipments of BlackBerry phones from Research in Motion (RIMM) fell a staggering 41% over the year to 7.4 million. That represented less than 5% of the market -- the lowest level since 2009, IDC said. It will be tough for RIM to improve its position this year, as the company said in June that its BlackBerry 10 operating system is delayed again until 2013. The once-popular Symbian operating system from Nokia (NOK) "sunk to a new nadir last quarter," IDC said, with shipments falling more than 60% over the year. Symbian now represents only 4.4% of the global market. Microsoft's Windows and the open-source Linux rounded out the last 6% of the market. To top of page</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1349538577327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349538647323-17</Id><Topic><Title>Downright Revolutionary</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349538441495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 11:47:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel focused a lot on adding more execution horsepower in Haswell without creating a power burden for legacy use cases. All of the new units can be shut off when not in use. Furthermore, Intel went in and ensured that this applied to the older execution units as well: in Haswell if you're not doing work, you're not consuming power.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349538647323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 11:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349539156082-18</Id><Title>IDF and Sharing: Intel Does and Apple/ARM Don't</Title><Msg>After the show many seemed to feel like Intel short changed us at this year's IDF when it came to architecture details and disclosures. The problem is perspective. Shortly after I returned home from the show I heard an interesting comparison: Intel detailed quite a bit about an architecture that wouldn't be shipping for another 9 months, while Apple wouldn't say a thing about an SoC that was shipping in a week. That's probably an extreme comparison given that Apple has no motivation to share details about A6 (yet), but even if you compare Intel's openness at IDF to the rest of the chip makers we cover - there's a striking contrast. We'll always want more from Intel at IDF, but I do hope that we won't see a retreat as the rest of the industry seems to be ok with non-disclosure as standard practice.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349539156082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 11:59:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349539460750-19</Id><Title>As a Platform, Haswell Looks Awesome</Title><Msg>As a platform, Haswell looks awesome. While the standard Haswell parts won't drive platform power down considerably, the new Haswell U/ULT parts will. Intel is promising a greater than 20x reduction in platform idle power and it's planning on delivering it by focusing its power reduction efforts beyond Intel manufactured components. Haswell Ultrabooks and tablets will have Intel's influence in many (most?) of the components placed on the motherboard. And honestly, this is something Intel (or one of its OEMs) should have done long ago. Driving down platform power is a problem that extends beyond the CPU or chipset, and it's one that requires a holistic solution. With Haswell, Intel appears committed to delivering that solution. It's not for purely altruistic reasons, but for the survival of the PC. I remember talking to Vivek about an iPad as a notebook replacement piece he was doing a while back. The biggest advantage the iPad offered over a notebook in his eyes? Battery life. Even for light workloads today's most power efficient ultraportable notebooks can't touch a good ARM based tablet. Haswell U/ULT's significant reduction in platform power is intended to fix that. I don't know that we'll get to 10+ hours of battery life on a single charge, but we should be much better off than we are today. Connected standby is coming to PCs and it's a truly necessary addition. Haswell's support of active idle states (S0ix) is a game changer for the way portable PCs work. The bigger concern is whether or not the OEMs and ISVs will do their best to really take advantage of what Haswell offers. I know one will, but will the rest? Intel's increasingly hands on approach to OEM relations seems to be its way of ensuring we'll see Haswell live up to its potential. Haswell, on paper, appears to do everything Intel needs to evolve the mobile PC platform. What's unclear is how far down the TDP stack Intel will be able to take the architecture. Intel seems to believe that TDPs below 8W are attainable, but it's too early to tell just how low Haswell can go. It's more than likely that Intel knows and just doesn't want to share at this point. I don't believe we'll see fanless Haswell designs, but Broadwell is another story entirely. There's no diagram for where we go from here. Intel originally claimed that Atom would service an expanded range of TDPs all the way up to 10W. With Core architectures dipping below 10W, I do wonder if that slide was a bit of misdirection. I wonder if, instead, the real goal is to drive Core well into Atom territory. If Intel wants to solve its ARM problem, that would appear to be a very good solution. From AnandTech</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349539460750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 12:04:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349541086281-20</Id><Title>PFE MESSAGE BOARD'S 'CHARTY' a Wallis Alias???</Title><Msg>There's a dude over on the PFE message board who is known as "Charty" and he reminds me of Wallis. He is a perennial pumper of PFE and, of course, he's been wrong for years. He also posts 24 x 7 x 365. He thinks he knows more than the man-who-wrote-the-book and is reminded of his stupidity on a daily basis by the other posters. Maybe he IS Wallis! No two people could be so DUHMBBBBBBB! TOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349541086281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 12:31:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349541369693-21</Id><Topic><Title>PFE MESSAGE BOARD'S 'CHARTY' a Wallis Alias???</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349541086281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 12:31:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He "works" various message boards 80 hours a week. So to himself, he's not lying when he says he works 80 hours a week. He's a complete chump, though.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349541369693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 12:36:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349541774958-22</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this Report on Intel Corporation? (INTC)</Title><Username>tamaton2495</Username><Timestamp>1349532926967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:15:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one. I will subscribe now.</Msg><Username>maidamttzo510706</Username><Timestamp>1349541774958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 12:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349542748765-23</Id><Title>Think Mitt Romney is a 1% #$%$ who is a liar too? I DO!</Title><Msg>He has off shore accounts all over to dodge taxes or at least reduce them. Companies do that--but a guy running for President sure should not. Do you pay less than 14% while making a hundred million in Dividends and other flim flam schemes? Well Mitt-full of shhhiiieet I never said that Romney does. Mitt is FOR and AGAINST everything. All Obummer has to do in the next debate is call him on all the lies and call him a liar on National TV. It is a fact and so there it goes. if Obummer takes the high ground and avoids ripping into Mitt, Obama wins by 6% in the election. However, if he rips into Willard real GOOOD. Calls him on all his lies and calls him a few names, Obummer can win by 10%. Kennedy Kennedy called Willard a liar in a debate and pointed out the facts and Willard went down hard in the election. Gawddammed is Welch an idiotl. He says Obummer forced the entire work force of the government who makes up the monthly unemployment numbers to LIE? Everyone of them? HAAA HAAAA Obummer must have them all under some trance with Obummer leftwing voodoo power because I am pretty sure that at least half of those rich college boys and girls who work for the government agency doping the monthly numbers are repubs. HAAA HAAA Jack--you are OLD dumb and a KKKK NUT! It is funny watching a man ruin his reputation.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1349542748765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 12:59:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349543875410-24</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this Report on Intel Corporation? (INTC)</Title><Username>tamaton2495</Username><Timestamp>1349532926967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:15:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok cool. Thank you for sharing this.</Msg><Username>heatherapdvc606015</Username><Timestamp>1349543875410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349543878109-25</Id><Topic><Title>PFE MESSAGE BOARD'S 'CHARTY' a Wallis Alias???</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349541086281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 12:31:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MOMMY, MOMMY, WALLIS TOUCHED ME ON MY PFE !!! Oh Dear!!! I think you are just as smart as Wallis. For sure. TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1349543878109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 13:17:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349545802127-26</Id><Topic><Title>Futures up HUGE! Business will hire again under Romney and............</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349321019758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:23:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are wrong about me being Wally. If you cannot detect the syntactic and semantic differences in the sentences, you are really not paying attention. Negotiating is "begging"? No wonder Romney is doing so well with followers who only hear what they want. I have complete confidence in him and his minions to return to his pattern. The Yahoo "default rating filter" is gone, not the 1-star (think about it). Thumbs up is 5-star. Thumbs down is 1-star. You just get to see all the 1-star (thumbs down) rated messages, including the commerical spam. The winners are the spammers that Yahoo wanted to "eliminate". There are some who do not want to be "real men". Like women. The "real men" you are describing are ... ugh ..... in the words of the board bully .... TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY! Cheers BTW, you do sound like a "real man".</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1349545802127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 13:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349547441371-27</Id><Topic><Title>Android dominating Apple globally</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1349538577327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you give me some kind of roadmap for how INTC will benefit from Android? What if Google goes ARM?</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349547441371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349547748849-28</Id><Topic><Title>Going Long On INTC Who Is With Me?</Title><Username>alvaelliott392</Username><Timestamp>1349524223378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 07:50:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm in with 48,000 shr</Msg><Username>doloresbranch943</Username><Timestamp>1349547748849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:22:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349548024213-29</Id><Topic><Title>Android dominating Apple globally</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1349538577327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Google goes ARM, then Intel is officially finished. But, to be fair, why would they go ARM when they just announced they are going Intel and are actually rolling Intel devices out ???????</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1349548024213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:27:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349548647453-30</Id><Topic><Title>Futures up HUGE! Business will hire again under Romney and............</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349321019758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:23:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i think that lucy and wallis are the same person</Msg><Username>ramalamalongdong</Username><Timestamp>1349548647453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:37:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349549100418-31</Id><Topic><Title>Android dominating Apple globally</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1349538577327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>depends upon what "going" means.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349549100418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:45:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349549455275-32</Id><Topic><Title>Futures up HUGE! Business will hire again under Romney and............</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349321019758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:23:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"i think that lucy and wallis are the same person" *** Then you don't have the brains God give a rubber duck...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349549455275</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:50:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349549709774-33</Id><Title>Can we have a discussion on Google + Intel</Title><Msg>There's a lot going on between Google and Intel. The first Googola phone has been released for European debugging and it sounds like a duzie...a very long battery life, fast as a banshie, and cool. This portends a lot of things for 2013 as LTE is solved and the first razr's buzz American shores...I would think. Second, there's direct purchase of server chips by Goog from INTC, cutting out middlemen such as HP and Dell...could it be there's a ginormous disconnect developing whereby the "PC is dead" chant misses the whole point? Could it be that HP and Dell are walking dead while INTC and Goog snuggle up cozy in bed and walk away with all the spoils, like Kathleen Turner in "body heat"??? Can anyone give more info than what we freely glean off Google on this? I think they are trying to fly below radar as long as possible..Are there hints that AAPL-ARM etal are soon to have their gooses cooked by the Google-INTC axis???? I know more than I can say, but suspect there are others out there who are free to comment....let's get it on the table. I want INTC to start the ascent to $100/shrs soon.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349549709774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349549771291-34</Id><Topic><Title>Don't buy INTC</Title><Username>vinhxle</Username><Timestamp>1349460746093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 14:12:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not going lower. lok at the technicals. This will run up to earnings.</Msg><Username>verioinc</Username><Timestamp>1349549771291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:56:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349549814324-35</Id><Topic><Title>Don't buy INTC</Title><Username>vinhxle</Username><Timestamp>1349460746093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 14:12:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bagofhorsepucky, get those toothpicks outa yo #$%$</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349549814324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:56:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349550040630-36</Id><Topic><Title>Going Long On INTC Who Is With Me?</Title><Username>alvaelliott392</Username><Timestamp>1349524223378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 07:50:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>20k shrs here, and short 4k equiv shrs worth of puts. Still have dry powder for another 20k shares. Heading to $100 in the next few years.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349550040630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:00:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349550644679-37</Id><Topic><Title>Can we have a discussion on Google + Intel</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349549709774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:55:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't know ANYTHING and it's despicable that you are trying to pump the stock by acting like you do. Bring out your gay cornhole and monkey aliases and try to pump it to 100, dirt-bag.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349550644679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:10:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349550817992-38</Id><Topic><Title>Can we have a discussion on Google + Intel</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349549709774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:55:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish they'd disallow access to computers in the reform school you're spending your miscreant youth in. Quit blaming your sad life and sorry #$%$ on Jerry Sandusky, do some reading and thinking, and maybe, just maybe you'll get a few years on the outside.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349550817992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349550955863-39</Id><Title>the outlook is more important that the earnings</Title><Msg>i'm long intel but i don't expect a very warm and fuzzy outlook, so i suspect the stock will trade lower after they report than where it is currently. i'll hold for the dividend which i believe will be raised in december. eventually the stock will rise to more acceptable levels</Msg><Username>ramalamalongdong</Username><Timestamp>1349550955863</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349550994466-40</Id><Title>att4gtle to be pitied</Title><Msg>It's probably Lucy with rabies, but I suspect it's more likely a Sandusky victim who's now broken real bad. Place on IGNORE in perpetuity. INTC will soon flatten all that is ARMH and AAPL. That's just the way it's gonna be.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349550994466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349551126432-41</Id><Topic><Title>att4gtle to be pitied</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349550994466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:16:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't have any info, like you say you do and your posts show it as one minute you are saying Intel is going to 40 overnight when Apple announces Intel in phones and the next minute you are crying about the stock performance and asking if it's even a Hold ! You and your Liberal scab aliases are a disgrace to society. Idiot.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349551126432</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:18:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349551127600-42</Id><Topic><Title>the outlook is more important that the earnings</Title><Username>ramalamalongdong</Username><Timestamp>1349550955863</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:15:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I disagree. INTC is just flying under radar with Goog...the handwriting is on the wall. Easy on the lama's kid.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349551127600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:18:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349551194291-43</Id><Topic><Title>att4gtle to be pitied</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349550994466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:16:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry..can't reply...you're on IGNORE where society has placed you, in perpetuity.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349551194291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:19:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349551245852-44</Id><Topic><Title>att4gtle to be pitied</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349550994466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:16:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He11, your posts today prove it! You say in one sentence that you have Info about great things coming from Intel that you can't discuss.......and in another sentence you ask what's going to happen if Google goes to ARM. LOL! You are a teriffied, very Liberal, VERY gay FREAK LONG !! No more, No Less !!!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349551245852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:20:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349551350772-45</Id><Topic><Title>att4gtle to be pitied</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349550994466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:16:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TEXTBOOK. Place those on Ignore that know EXACTLY who and what you are.........a scared, gay Liberal long. LMAO!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349551350772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:22:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349552309034-46</Id><Topic><Title>att4gtle to be pitied</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349550994466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:16:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A dishonest Liberal? A gay Liberal? Par for the course, eh ?</Msg><Username>backstreetboy_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1349552309034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:38:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349553130460-47</Id><Topic><Title>the outlook is more important that the earnings</Title><Username>ramalamalongdong</Username><Timestamp>1349550955863</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:15:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just raised div super yield 4%-give them time they will be in the hunt.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1349553130460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349553370944-48</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's A6 processor is good for Intel</Title><Username>stocktrade14</Username><Timestamp>1349481319567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:55:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[You must not have seen the Razor comparison showing that Intel already outperforms ARM, even using 32nm. You just keep spouting the same old stupidity...] ----- The benchmarks in question: Motorola RAZR i Motorola Droid RAZR M Quadrant 4,226 4,944 Vellamo 1,928 2,442 SunSpider 0.9.1 (ms) 1,077 1,951 AnTuTu 6,175 6,364 GLBenchmark Egypt Offscreen (fps) 41 56 CF-Bench 3,115 9,392 SunSpider: lower scores are better So, Intel beats in one benchmark (Javascript)....</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1349553370944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:56:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349554367093-49</Id><Topic><Title>TIRED OF OBAMA? I AM.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1349482647445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 20:17:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am a senior voting for Romney. I am tired of Obama's lies.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1349554367093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349554506685-50</Id><Topic><Title>att4gtle to be pitied</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349550994466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:16:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wouldn't expect anyone who even remotely considers Romney presidential to have the slightest decency, morality, maturity or intelligence. You posters (all in one att...) were Sandusky boys. Clear from your obsession with gay and other shower stall inuendo. In any case, that's what the IGNORE button is for. So phyuck Orff.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349554506685</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:15:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349554610399-51</Id><Topic><Title>TIRED OF OBAMA? I AM.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1349482647445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 20:17:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess you aren't a member of the 47 percent that Romney doesn't care about and thinks are deadbeats. Like seniors, students and members of the military... ___________________________ Keep spewing garbage. Romney was right, 47% are idiots just like you. 47% believe the LIberal LIES that Romney is a Felon and Romney contributed to the death of a lady with cancer. You freaks like to create chaos to get your way. Bunch of degenerates. Just absolute FILTH of the earth.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349554610399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:16:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349555953844-52</Id><Topic><Title>att4gtle to be pitied</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349550994466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:16:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The joke's on you. You don't even have a junior high education if you think anyone would believe "you have info you can't discuss". What a childish attempt to manipulate the price upwards. Unbelievable.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349555953844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:39:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349556307230-53</Id><Topic><Title>TIRED OF OBAMA? I AM.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1349482647445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 20:17:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Romney gets in, I'm investing in "CHEEK SPREADERS", and "KY JELLY". Might as well be making money while Romney screws the stupid. One cannot fix stupid.</Msg><Username>wolfgangjr1970</Username><Timestamp>1349556307230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:45:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349561546439-54</Id><Topic><Title>Don't buy INTC</Title><Username>vinhxle</Username><Timestamp>1349460746093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 14:12:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is this a buy? I'm thinking about putting some real money in this, I've got about 300k to invest. Or is there something better? I've looked at KO, COP, T, DUK.</Msg><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1349561546439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 18:12:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349563450352-55</Id><Title>If you knew what I know...</Title><Msg>you'd rather jump in an alligator pit than short INTC. But go ahead. Entertain us. Some real fun times are just around the corner.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349563450352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 18:44:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349566252273-56</Id><Topic><Title>If you knew what I know...</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349563450352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 18:44:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, this post from you the other day is evidence that you know something.....(as I roll my eyes at your ignorance). By flumoxed11 . Oct 3, 2012 3:56 PM . Permalink Go to topic But Wallis: I think they've also priced in the death of PC (which is #$%$, but not what it used to be) and the not-so-#$%$ underwhelming by ultrabooks, and the fact that INTC is yet to get a significant foothold in the smartphone space. I am a little worried. There's something very 1990's about INTC's style. They need to land some big ones. And soon.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349566252273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 19:30:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349567730482-57</Id><Topic><Title>TIRED OF OBAMA? I AM.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1349482647445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 20:17:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What country are you from? My business hasn't been better since Bushler left office.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1349567730482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 19:55:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349567850983-58</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's A6 processor is good for Intel</Title><Username>stocktrade14</Username><Timestamp>1349481319567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:55:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The benchmark scores you quote are true if you were comparing arm to arm chips. But your NOT. Look at the "real world" comparison and Intel is faster and more efficient. Arm has always thought that Intel maybe faster but Arm would always have the efficiency advantage and that was more important. THESE REVIEWS SHOW A SINGLE CORE 32MM MEDIFIELD IS AS POWERFULL AND MORE EFFICIENT THAN A DUAL CORE 28 MM SNAPDRAGON. If this holds true, what will Arm have to offer when Intel moves to 22mm next year and 14mm the next.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1349567850983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 19:57:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349568097571-59</Id><Title>Reminds Me of People on this Board</Title><Msg>Arkansas Republicans tried to distance themselves Saturday from a Republican state representative's assertion that slavery was a "blessing in disguise" and a Republican state House candidate who advocates deporting all Muslims. From ABC News</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349568097571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:01:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349568332735-60</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's A6 processor is good for Intel</Title><Username>stocktrade14</Username><Timestamp>1349481319567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:55:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple licenses the processor designs from ARM and then makes a system-on-chip. The processors are not pushing higher processor speeds but going to multiple cores so that the operating system runs faster from threading of the instructions to the multiple processors. But see, an ARM tablet is mostly for just connecting to websites. And an application on an ARM tablet is often just a connection to a website. But here are my questions. Will the consumer connect to their financial account websites while using their ARM tablet on a WiFi network ? And how does the consumer use their ARM tablet at home ?</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1349568332735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:05:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349568915645-61</Id><Topic><Title>Reminds Me of People on this Board</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349568097571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:01:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>John Edwards (Liberal degenerate) cheating on his wife that was dying of cancer......uhhhhh.........makes that look like childsplay. You are always trying to pass the buck instead of cleaning your own kitchen. Very pathetic character flaw.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349568915645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349569888139-62</Id><Topic><Title>Russian Chip Gurus ARM Intel Rivals With Secret Weapon</Title><Username>the_competitor</Username><Timestamp>1349485560095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 21:06:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Intel instruction set has already been emulated on the Sparc risc processor. They gave up when Intel caught up to their power consumption advantage. But the ARM risc processor is much simplier than the Sparc risc processor. The ARM processor has thousands of transistors while the Sparc processor has millions of transistors. The Intel Atom for computers is already at 3 watts power consumption. And it has millions of transistors.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1349569888139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:31:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349570027606-63</Id><Topic><Title>Reminds Me of People on this Board</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349568097571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:01:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, exactly. These people reminded me of you. Except they aren't as angry...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349570027606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349570218499-64</Id><Topic><Title>Reminds Me of People on this Board</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349568097571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:01:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell yourself I'm angry if it helps you sleep at night. Meanwhile I'll continue to grab the popcorn and enjoy the entertainment that is your arrogance and stupidity.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349570218499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:36:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349571584544-65</Id><Topic><Title>TIRED OF OBAMA? I AM.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1349482647445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 20:17:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's lies are far more subtle than Romney's. It takes Fox News reenactments and Fox News modifications to video/audio tapes to decern the Obama lies. Romney? His lies are so obvious that people walk right by them. When Romney attributed a McCain statement, quoted by Obama TO Obama and publicly said he knew of the lie, I understood at that moment, there is nothing you can believe that comes from Romney lips. You can predict the position he will take on any issue by the audience he is addressing. You are just not tired of the Romney lies yet. They are new and different lies. You are not going to benefit from a Romney election (unless you are a multimillionare posting on a message board). Your friends are not going to benefit because you have no multimillionare friends. Your family is not going to benefit because they are not multimillionares either. If you are from the South, your state will see a reduction in Federal spending that will be far greater than you state federal contribution. Fewer dollars in the south to support both large and small businesses. More poverty to put pressure on charitable NGO's. Of course businuesses will floursih there. Without a minimum wage, they can pay what ever they want. Without unions and all those bothersome regulations, they won't have to bother with benefit packages, safety, .... unless they decide to bother. I defend, your right to vote for Romney (and I have really done so). Please do what you believe is right. Romney has changed positions so many times on so many issues, that I don't know what his position is on anything. He is a MUPPET who wants to be president and noone really knows who has there hand up his back.</Msg><Username>dumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1349571584544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:59:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349572947404-66</Id><Topic><Title>Reminds Me of People on this Board</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349568097571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:01:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>John Edwards was a pathetic man who happened to be a liberal Democrat. If you piled up all the Demorats and Republicans exhibiting this behavior, the piles would be about equal. I thought that Republicans strongly supported the Constitution. They should distance themselves from this anti-Constitutional rhetoric if they support the Constitution more than the person saying these things. The House candidate Charlie Fuqua "deporting all Muslims" comment is a dagger at the heart of the 1st Amendment. The 1st Amendment does not say free speech is OK "as long as they agree with me". I am not sure what an unfaithful husband has to do with disparging the consititution. The Edwards act of adultry was denounced by everyone. The anti-Constitution quotes are just statements personal beliefs which should be criticized by those who belive and support the consitution. Amendment 1 - Freedom of Religion, Press, Expression Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof; or abridging the freedom of speech, or of the press; or the right of the people peaceably to assemble, and to petition the Government for a redress of grievances.</Msg><Username>dumpwad</Username><Timestamp>1349572947404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:22:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349577512662-67</Id><Title>I am Mitt and I approve this message</Title><Msg>My ?itch got a dancing horse</Msg><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349577512662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 22:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349577801306-68</Id><Topic><Title>I am Mitt and I approve this message</Title><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349577512662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 22:38:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How's this debate prediction work out for ya? Obama must have shot himself in the foot as much as he was looking down that night. Mitt armed with Quiver full of Zingers!! By gopsrsobs . Oct 3, 2012 10:01 AM . Permalink Watch this #$%$-bag shoot himself on to his foot tonight.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1349577801306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 22:43:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349579604846-69</Id><Topic><Title>Reminds Me of People on this Board</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349568097571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:01:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dunno, I just see your face on a lot of anger resolution treatment ads...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349579604846</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 23:13:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349579853873-70</Id><Topic><Title>Reminds Me of People on this Board</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349568097571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:01:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chump boy is just like those two Republicans. He despises groups of people. Anyone not in the same political party, anyone who doesn't think like him, anyone who doesn't look like him, anyone who is a different religion. And on and on...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349579853873</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 23:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349580206906-71</Id><Topic><Title>I am Mitt and I approve this message</Title><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349577512662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 22:38:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"shoot himself on to his foot tonight." *** Here's a prediction. Whoever wrote that will continue to need ESL lessons...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349580206906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 23:23:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349580377277-72</Id><Topic><Title>If you knew what I know...</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349563450352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 18:44:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, horsepuckey head, I've since talked to my bro who works in the industry. He's clued me in. Sorry, I can't discuss it further. But come Monday (if I can trade) I'm going to burn my powder on another 20k shares.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349580377277</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 23:26:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349580600339-73</Id><Title>Watch Google + INTC</Title><Msg>and if you want to play a more balanced hand, buy them both. But given how beaten up INTC is, the max gain is there. INTC $100 by 2014. Mark this post girls and boys. Mark this post.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349580600339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 23:30:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>