<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352783180462-1</Id><Topic><Title>MY PROPOSAL: CONCENTRATE ON MAKING A LOT OF MONEY TO BECOME RICH.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352779235133</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 23:00:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, what is american opportunity today? Get everything free from government.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352783180462</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:06:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352783305701-2</Id><Title>sinofsky out at Microsoft i bet we have another sell off.</Title><Msg>The recommended candidate for Balmers replacement is out. This probably doesn't bode well for Windows 8 and Surface. #$%$!</Msg><Username>balmer_tim</Username><Timestamp>1352783305701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:08:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352783498328-3</Id><Topic><Title>sinofsky out at Microsoft i bet we have another sell off.</Title><Username>balmer_tim</Username><Timestamp>1352783305701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:08:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The futures look ugly. My god when the hell this madness will end?</Msg><Username>moobyet</Username><Timestamp>1352783498328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:11:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352783509404-4</Id><Topic><Title>Crammer says don't buy Intc yet</Title><Username>suckerborneverysecond</Username><Timestamp>1352723131657</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 07:25:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After what Softie just did I would not be surprised.</Msg><Username>balmer_tim</Username><Timestamp>1352783509404</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:11:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352784794368-5</Id><Topic><Title>sinofsky out at Microsoft i bet we have another sell off.</Title><Username>balmer_tim</Username><Timestamp>1352783305701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:08:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not for a while. With sales of PC expected to decline the 19's look pretty obtainable unfortunately</Msg><Username>balmer_tim</Username><Timestamp>1352784794368</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:33:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352785208445-6</Id><Topic><Title>sinofsky out at Microsoft i bet we have another sell off.</Title><Username>balmer_tim</Username><Timestamp>1352783305701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:08:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We should have a bump up. He got fired for Surface RT...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352785208445</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:40:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352785300650-7</Id><Title>Faults found in Surface RT</Title><Msg>After years of having to avoid reporting about the faults in their favourite Apple toys, the Tame Apple press is jolly happy about a small number of cracks turning up in the touch cover of Microsoft’s Surface. Microsoft announced that a small number of covers for its Surface tablet are prone to splitting after two weeks or less in users' hands and that it's replacing the defective ones. The company is "aware of a small number of instances of material separation" of the cover accessory, Redmond, Washington-based Microsoft said in an emailed statement. The cover serves a protective jacket for the Surface, the tablet computer released last month. The defects with the Touch Cover, which users said had begun to split apart at the seams, were reported earlier on technology industry websites. Normally when stories like this appear about faults in Apple gear, the Tame Apple press rush to point out that they are small numbers of gear due to a production problem on one Chinese production line. Apple usually denies that there really is a problem and people soon forget about it. The Surface has had good reviews, but Microsoft CEO Steve Ballmer admits that sales have been “modest”. Given that Ballmer is not known for his modesty, it is probably fair to say that he probably means “not as good as I hoped.”</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352785300650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:41:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352785408800-8</Id><Title>Ballmer: Surface RT sales are modest</Title><Msg>Microsoft’s Surface RT tablet started shipping just a couple of weeks ago, but despite initial success, it seems it is off to a slow start. Speaking in an interview with a French daily, Microsoft CEO Steve Ballmer described the sales as “modest,” but argued that they are limited by channel constraints. He does have a point. The Surface is still plagued by limited availability in many markets. However, Ballmer stopped short of revealing any sales figures and Microsoft is not commenting.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352785408800</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:43:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352785714354-9</Id><Title>Europe Turns a Corner on Financial Crisis</Title><Msg>The worst of Europe's financial crisis appears to be over. European leaders have taken steps to ease the panic that has plagued the region for three turbulent years. Financial markets are no longer in a state of emergency over Europe's high government debts and weak banks. And this gives politicians from the 17 countries that use the euro breathing room to fix their remaining problems. Threats remain in Greece and Spain, and Europe's economy is forecast to get worse before it gets better. But an imminent breakup of the euro now seems unlikely, analysts say. "We are probably well beyond the worst," says Holger Schmieding, chief economist at Berenberg Bank in London. He says occasional flare-ups in financial markets are likely, but "coming waves of turmoil will be less severe." Evidence that Europe has turned a corner can be found in countries' falling borrowing costs, rising stock markets and a slow but steady stabilization of the region's banking system: — The interest rates investors are demanding to lend to struggling countries such as Spain and Italy have plunged — a sign that investors are less fearful of defaults. Spain's two-year bonds carry an interest rate, or yield, of just under 3% — down from a July 24 peak of 6.6%. Italy's bond yields have dropped just as sharply. — The Stoxx 50 index of leading European shares has surged 26% since June 1, while the euro has strengthened, from $1.26 to $1.29 over the same period. — After months of withdrawals, deposits are trickling back into Greek and Spanish banks, signaling that fears of their imminent financial collapse are abating. And U.S. money market mutual funds loaned 16% more to eurozone banks in September. That was the third straight monthly increase in short-term funding to European banks, and follows a 70% reduction since May 2011. More proof the crisis is easing: Gatherings of European financial ministers no longer cause global stock and bond markets to gyrate with every sign of progress or setback. As financial-market panic recedes, euro leaders have more time to try to fix the flaws in their currency union. Among the challenges are reducing regulations and other costs for businesses to stimulate economic growth, and imposing more centralized authority over budgets to prevent countries from ever again spending beyond their means. That's important because a major cause of the crisis was Greece's overspending during the calm years after the euro's introduction in 1999, and Italy's failure to cut the high levels of debt it joined with. Other governments — such as Spain and Ireland — were saddled with debt piled up by banks and real estate developers during boom years. Much of the credit for easing Europe's financial crisis goes to the European Central Bank, which has become more aggressive the past year under the leadership of Mario Draghi. The ECB said Sept. 6 that it was willing to buy unlimited amounts of government bonds issued by countries struggling to pay their debts. The ECB's pledge instantly lowered borrowing costs for Spain and Italy, which earlier in the year faced the same kinds of financial pressures that forced Ireland, Greece and Spain to seek bailouts. "Financial market confidence has visibly improved," Draghi said Thursday during a press conference. German Chancellor Angela Merkel has also helped ease financial tensions across the region by speaking more forcefully about the need to hold the euro together. Merkel's support is critical because Germany, the eurozone's largest economy, has the most at stake financially in any bailouts. Merkel has backed the ECB's bond-buying plan and has made conciliatory statements toward Greece. That has paved the way for the so-called troika of international lenders — the ECB, the European Union and the International Monetary Fund — to allow Greece more time to meet deficit-reduction targets. The Greek Parliament took a big step Wednesday toward securing its next batch of rescue loans from the troika by approving a new round of tax hikes and spending cuts. Another key breakthrough in the financial crisis came in late June, when leaders meeting in Brussels took new steps to steady banks and governments. They agreed to ease up somewhat on austerity demands; to use bailout funds to buy government bonds and help ailing banks; and to create a single supervisor for all of Europe's banks. From USA Today</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352785714354</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:48:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352785915615-10</Id><Title>China Exports Exceed Estimates in Sign of Global Pickup</Title><Msg>Overseas shipments increased 11.6 percent from a year earlier, the Beijing-based customs administration said in a statement yesterday. That compared with the 10 percent estimate in a Bloomberg News survey of economists and 9.9 percent in September. Imports rose 2.4 percent, the same pace as the previous month. The trade surplus widened to $32 billion, the biggest in almost four years. China’s transition to a new generation of Communist Party leaders, which began in Beijing last week, may be smoothed by the reversal of a slowdown that started in last year’s first quarter. The September-October pickup in export growth shows the economy is starting to stabilize, Commerce Minister Chen Deming said yesterday at a briefing in Beijing. “We are still cautious, but the robust export growth around 10 percent for two consecutive months might truly point to a real rebound,” said Lu Ting, chief Greater China economist at Bank of America Corp. in Hong Kong. The “elevated” trade surplus may mean the central bank will be reluctant to cut lenders’ reserve requirements, Lu said while maintaining his forecast for “at most” one 0.5 percentage-point reduction by year-end. From Bloomberg</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352785915615</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:51:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352786113804-11</Id><Title>U.S. oil output to overtake Saudi Arabia’s by 2020, IEA Says</Title><Msg>U.S. oil output is poised to surpass Saudi Arabia’s in the next decade, making the world’s biggest fuel consumer almost self-reliant and putting it on track to become a net exporter, the International Energy Agency said. Growing supplies of crude extracted through new technology including hydraulic fracturing of underground rock formations will transform the U.S. into the largest producer for about five years starting about 2020, the Paris-based adviser to 28 nations said today in its annual World Energy Outlook. The U.S. met 83 percent of its energy needs in the first six months of this year, according to the Energy Department in Washington. “The IEA outlook feeds into the idea of a shift in the center of influence in the world oil market,” said Gareth Lewis-Davies, an analyst at BNP Paribas SA in London. “Given Saudi Arabia is willing to shift production up and down it will retain a large degree of influence, and remain important as a price-influencer.” The U.S., whose crude imports have fallen 11 percent this year, is on track to produce the most oil since 1991, according to Energy Department data. In a year when Iran has threatened to halt Persian Gulf oil shipments, the growing output, coupled with a gas-production boom, may help insulate the nation from supply disruptions. President Barack Obama cited “freeing ourselves from foreign oil” as a policy goal in his election victory speech last week, echoing his predecessor, George W. Bush, who in 2006 urged the U.S. to break its “addiction” to imported crude. From Washington Post</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352786113804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:55:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352786444995-12</Id><Topic><Title>China Exports Exceed Estimates in Sign of Global Pickup</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352785915615</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:51:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finally a good news. I will take anything. It is just Gloom and Doom lately.</Msg><Username>moobyet</Username><Timestamp>1352786444995</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 01:00:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352786697267-13</Id><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Msg>1.) Chinese economy on the road to recovery. 2.) US economy improving. 3.) US on the way to becoming energy independent by 2020, providing a huge economic lift and improvements in employment. 4.) Europe has turned the corner on its economic crisis. 5.) Wall Street priced a ridiculous $8 billion revenue miss into the Intel stock price. The miss never happened yet the eight buck drop in the stock price hasn't been put back on. It should (and will). Instead Wall Street keeps attempting to bake the same thing in - again and again and again. 6.) Wall Street has grossly over-bet on doom and gloom and US and world economic collapse. It ain't gonna happen. Why exactly does Wall Street continuously attack American manufacturing and technology? 7.) Most economists see substantial economic recovery and improvements in the years ahead. 8.) After 2013, there will never again be a reason to buy an ARM processor.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352786697267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 01:04:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352787489687-14</Id><Title>INTC will hit 20.00 tuesday!</Title><Msg>Will it bounce off it or go under to 19's! We shall see--</Msg><Username>marrohead</Username><Timestamp>1352787489687</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 01:18:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352790022662-15</Id><Topic><Title>Let's hope for a really great jobs number tomorrow.</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1351826204707</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:16:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He lacks Clinton's balls that's for sure. Now that #$%$ caused the house bubble with his and greenspan's fog a mirror loan program, yet he is out there strutting his old butt for all to laugh at.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1352790022662</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 02:00:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352790083143-16</Id><Topic><Title>4 MORE YEARS OF MISERY AHEAD.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352272744072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 02:19:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romeny was dumb if he didn't know it was coming, I knew, I know bribes work.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1352790083143</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 02:01:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352813266786-17</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352786697267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 01:04:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm still stuck in a an average of $22.65 and the beat down on the stock price continues... how low it will go is anyone's guess... assuming the congress refuses to work with the president, the I see the whole market taking a HUGE hit of 2 or 3 thousand... Intel spiraling down to $14 or $15, making it a great buy then, but &amp;(Y%ing those of us that at stuck in at high prices now...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352813266786</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:27:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352813333876-18</Id><Topic><Title>China Exports Exceed Estimates in Sign of Global Pickup</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352785915615</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:51:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Market are down, prepare for a new 52 week low today... and to close lower again... should be fun... for the shorts anyway...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352813333876</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:28:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352813434516-19</Id><Title>Home Depot to Chump Street: Up Yours</Title><Msg>[Home Depot buying back an ADDITIONAL $700 million in stock in a nose-thumbing gesture to the #$%$ on Wall Street who continue to bet on doom and gloom and who continue to attempt to drive US manufacturing and the US economy into the dirt. Housing is healing. Employment is improving. And the US is on its way to energy independence. In the meantime the manipulators on Chump Street have beaten down Intel for a miss that never even happened. Europe has turned the corner, China is moving up and there's lot of good economic news in the US. I'm with Home Depot. Up yours, Chump Street...] Home Depot: Housing market is healing Home Depot (HD, Fortune 500) reported better-than-expected earnings and revenue Tuesday and raised its guidance for the current quarter, citing signs of a housing recovery. The news lifted shares of the Dow component 1.9% in premarket trading. The quarter only ran through Oct. 28, the day before Hurricane Sandy came ashore in New York and New Jersey. While some of the buying in preparation for the storm may have been included in the just completed quarter, other storm-related sales increases will be reported in the current period. The company did not quantify the impact the storm on sales. Instead it pointed to what it said is an important turnaround in housing, which lifted sales 4.6% to $18 billion, and operating earnings up 23% to $1.1 billion. Earnings per share topped forecasts by 4 cents. The strong results reflect "the start of the path toward the healing of the housing market," said CEO Frank Blake in a statement. From CNN</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352813434516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:30:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352813434612-20</Id><Topic><Title>sinofsky out at Microsoft i bet we have another sell off.</Title><Username>balmer_tim</Username><Timestamp>1352783305701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:08:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The madness will end in 4 years, but until then it will head towards the 6 to 7 thousands area...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352813434612</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:30:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352813500661-21</Id><Topic><Title>Home Depot to Chump Street: Up Yours</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352813434516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:30:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Note that the results had mostly to do with housing improvements and little to do with the storm which hadn't hit during the earnings period...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352813500661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:31:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352813553394-22</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352786697267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 01:04:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What we know now is that you are an idiot repeating his mantra no matter what is the share price and the revenues/earnings outlook. "strong buy" all the way from $20 to $29 to $21. Soon enough your "strong buy" will actually be the right call.</Msg><Username>c757172</Username><Timestamp>1352813553394</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:32:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352813657477-23</Id><Topic><Title>Crammer says don't buy Intc yet</Title><Username>suckerborneverysecond</Username><Timestamp>1352723131657</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 07:25:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cramer said that because his buddies haven't finished buying yet! When they're done he'll say buy and run it up.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1352813657477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:34:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352813734007-24</Id><Title>MSFT trading down over $1.14 in the early market...</Title><Msg>Should be a good buy right now. but I still wouldn't consider it till it reaches down to $25... It's downward spin may negativity affect INTC as a side effect...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352813734007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:35:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352813804131-25</Id><Title>Samsung reportedly jacks up Apple processor prices</Title><Msg>[More evidence of Apple's hugely troubled ARM foundry situation. What a mess having to choose between Samsung lawsuits and price increases and TSMC's inability to ramp up or stay on the cutting edge...] [Twenty percent!!! Ouch, there goes the profit...] A Korean daily is reporting that Samsung could be about to change its relationship with Apple, for the worse, of course. Chosun Biz reports that Samsung has increased manufacturing prices for Apple SoCs by almost 20 percent. Apple was apparently forced to accept the new prices, as it lacks viable alternatives. There are other foundries out there, but it seems they can’t meet Apple’s needs for one reason or the other. From Fudzilla</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352813804131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:36:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352813886608-26</Id><Topic><Title>sinofsky out at Microsoft i bet we have another sell off.</Title><Username>balmer_tim</Username><Timestamp>1352783305701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:08:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MSFT when lower by $1.23 at one point this morning, currently trading down $1.17... still not a good buy in my opinion...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352813886608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:38:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352814064112-27</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352786697267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 01:04:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't go up untill the big boys finish covering and buy in for the ride up. Paul is so nice to keep his mouth shut so they can manupulate the stock without interference. Some day Paul will realize that the 6 week quiet period is what allowes the big boys to get away with this. 6 weeks to bash INTC and no response is great for manupulation. Recently Paul has also taken to not saying anything during the other 6 weeks and this is why we have been and continue to stay on a straight down hill trajectory.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1352814064112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:41:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352814072816-28</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352786697267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 01:04:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I'm still stuck in a an average of $22.65 and the beat down on the stock price continues... how low it will go is anyone's guess... assuming the congress refuses to work with the president, the I see the whole market taking a HUGE hit of 2 or 3 thousand... Intel spiraling down to $14 or $15, making it a great buy then, but &amp;(Y%ing those of us that at stuck in at high prices now..." [If you are a long you're the dumbest on the planet. Is this what they teach you in shill school. Pretend to be a long-suffering long and then say every negative thing you can possibly think of? Give it up. No one believes you. A lucy by any other name is still a lucy...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352814072816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:41:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352814330159-29</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung reportedly jacks up Apple processor prices</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352813804131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:36:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[Twenty percent!!! Ouch, there goes the profit...] ---- The horror. How on earth are Apple going to cope with an extra $5 cost?</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1352814330159</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:45:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352814344706-30</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung reportedly jacks up Apple processor prices</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352813804131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:36:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yet their is no word from INTC that they will help AAPL out and help the stock holders out. If we made ARMH processors for AAPL with our excess capacity, our stock price would double(about the same PE as TCM) over night. Too bad that clueless clown and the BOD don't make this happen. Must be they want more cheap stock options before the think about doing this.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1352814344706</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:45:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352814757683-31</Id><Topic><Title>sinofsky out at Microsoft i bet we have another sell off.</Title><Username>balmer_tim</Username><Timestamp>1352783305701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:08:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We should have a bump up. He got fired for Surface RT..." Can I mark your post, Wallus?</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1352814757683</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:52:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352814763588-32</Id><Title>Let's See How Smart</Title><Msg>The Republicans in Congress are. After four years of doing everything they can to crash the economy, let's see if they are capable of putting the country first for a change. I bet no. I'm guessing we will see more of the denial of reality. No complaining from the fat cats on the board. You put these people in office. How do you like them when they are destroying your investments? Regardless, it's short-term. The economy is ready to be moving on up...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352814763588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:52:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352814914237-33</Id><Topic><Title>sinofsky out at Microsoft i bet we have another sell off.</Title><Username>balmer_tim</Username><Timestamp>1352783305701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 00:08:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure, Lucy. You're living large these days, right? Nobody enjoys human misery the way you do. But your good times are coming to an end. Skumbag</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352814914237</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:55:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352814969605-34</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung reportedly jacks up Apple processor prices</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352813804131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:36:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung is disgruntled partner who wants to get that $1B back (full refund) from Apple.before they leave. Probably, Samsung got some clear signs that they will be leaving sooner. So it would be a slap on Apple's face and show media that they won the battle before Apple gets out the door.</Msg><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1352814969605</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:56:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352815007969-35</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung reportedly jacks up Apple processor prices</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352813804131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:36:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't understand much about accounting, do you?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352815007969</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:56:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352815799909-36</Id><Topic><Title>Let's See How Smart</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352814763588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:52:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm guessing they'll say a big fat NO to raising taxes on the "rich".. but what would we expect... PS... INTC is trading down to $20.63 this morning... how low will it go...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352815799909</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:09:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352815914148-37</Id><Title>Any thoughts on Apple quitely working with Intel</Title><Msg>to shift from Samsung Foundry? Given the 20% increase pricing, TSMC not being ready even with 28nm, this scenario is quite a possibility.</Msg><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1352815914148</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:11:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352816069695-38</Id><Title>$20.58 in the pre-market... looks like we're going down again..</Title><Msg>Not good times...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352816069695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:14:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352816480535-39</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on Apple quitely working with Intel</Title><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1352815914148</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:11:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure hope so. If not, with all our excess capacity, Paul and the BOD should be looking at a class action lawsuit against them personally for gross incompetence.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1352816480535</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:21:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352816617677-40</Id><Topic><Title>$20.58 in the pre-market... looks like we're going down again..</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352816069695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:14:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Make that $20.55</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352816617677</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:23:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352816801955-41</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on Apple quitely working with Intel</Title><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1352815914148</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:11:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems highly unlikely given that they appear to be shifting away from intel in other areas...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352816801955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:26:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352816985553-42</Id><Topic><Title>Let's See How Smart</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352814763588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:52:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Wally, going to have to wait a long, long, long time for INTC to ever get back to 24.00. Obamination gets relected and the market crashes and burns.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1352816985553</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:29:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352817066401-43</Id><Topic><Title>$20.58 in the pre-market... looks like we're going down again..</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352816069695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:14:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kirk Skaugen is scheduled to talk to the UBS Global Tech Conference at market close today. I am not sure how much he will be able to disclose but it should be an interesting discussion. Some obvious PC Client questions should come up. INTC does many times track the market through ETF pressure and the markets are down too. 11/14/12 4:00 PM ET UBS Global Technology Conference Speaker: Kirk Skaugen, Vice President, General Manager, PC Client Group Listen to webcast</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1352817066401</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:31:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352817216928-44</Id><Title>Obamacare killing the economy as we predicted...</Title><Msg>...and to all those out there still long this market: my condolences. There is no help on the way. The clueless majority voted for this. Long way down...</Msg><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352817216928</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:33:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352817346176-45</Id><Title>No Help Coming - the Leftists have won</Title><Msg>What this means is, basically, our government is actively aligned against the private sector, and is looking for opportunities to nationalize more industries.</Msg><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352817346176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:35:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352817444270-46</Id><Topic><Title>4 MORE YEARS OF MISERY AHEAD.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352272744072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 02:19:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. When I see pictures of citizens in socialist countries, they look like zombies.</Msg><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352817444270</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:37:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352817473003-47</Id><Title>Poor misguided Wally</Title><Msg>Obama's done NOTHING for the middle class other than use them to get elected twice. He's laughing at how stupid you are and he knew printing free money would get you excited.........money we don't have.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1352817473003</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:37:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352817527576-48</Id><Topic><Title>$20.58 in the pre-market... looks like we're going down again..</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352816069695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:14:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I need some definite good news... if I did my math right, I can afford to hold on all the way down to $16 a share if I have to, but I hate the thought of it going that low...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352817527576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:38:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352817711452-49</Id><Topic><Title>$20.58 in the pre-market... looks like we're going down again..</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352816069695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:14:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why? what happens at $16? are you margined?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1352817711452</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:41:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352817786196-50</Id><Title>Same Thing</Title><Msg>Now priced in nine times. Where's the miss to back all this up, Chump Street??? You know - that great big huge honking miss you promised last earnings. The mysterious, missing miss. Another day of Intel longs being unable to find their backbones or their brains...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352817786196</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:43:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352817786627-51</Id><Topic><Title>$20.58 in the pre-market... looks like we're going down again..</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352816069695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:14:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at $16 the div yield is 5.63%, could that happen? Just think how much fun it will be going back to $29 from there.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1352817786627</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:43:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352818035546-52</Id><Topic><Title>Poor misguided Wally</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1352817473003</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:37:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>riots in Greece are because they want the handouts to continue. We have a Preesident here telling the people the rich made it off of them and the rich need to pay more so the handouts can continue. Is there really any surprise Jim Jones got his followers to drink poison? same mind bending #$%$.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1352818035546</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:47:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352818103489-53</Id><Topic><Title>No Help Coming - the Leftists have won</Title><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352817346176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:35:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you nailed it. Boeing plant? pipeline from Canada.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1352818103489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:48:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352818112874-54</Id><Topic><Title>$20.58 in the pre-market... looks like we're going down again..</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352816069695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:14:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I'm margin-ed... yes, I already know that was a stupid move...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352818112874</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:48:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352818210968-55</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung reportedly jacks up Apple processor prices</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352813804131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:36:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$3 eps, $30, what do you understand? marriage on the horizon?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1352818210968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:50:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352818229828-56</Id><Topic><Title>No Help Coming - the Leftists have won</Title><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352817346176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:35:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The majority voted for this mess... but look what the stupid REPUBs put in the arena to fight for them... just stupid...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352818229828</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:50:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352818294489-57</Id><Topic><Title>Let's See How Smart</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352814763588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:52:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more proof you're an idiot. More layoffs are not being done by the repubs of congress. obamacare is a burden that many businesses can't afford.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1352818294489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:51:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352818522955-58</Id><Topic><Title>Home Depot to Chump Street: Up Yours</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352813434516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:30:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>which had to do with lower interest rates and more lies that there is no inflation. JOBS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1352818522955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:55:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352818627993-59</Id><Topic><Title>Let's See How Smart</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352814763588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 08:52:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4 years of Obama spending, now it will be 4 years of increasing taxes Spend Obama Spend to Tax Obama Tax</Msg><Username>smkpit</Username><Timestamp>1352818627993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:57:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352818649174-60</Id><Topic><Title>Same Thing</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352817786196</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:43:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh contrare, I've still got my back bone and brain. It' s my wallet that they got and won't give back.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1352818649174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:57:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352818662698-61</Id><Topic><Title>$20.58 in the pre-market... looks like we're going down again..</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352816069695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:14:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh wow, sorry to hear that :(</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1352818662698</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:57:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352818674556-62</Id><Title>Obamaflation</Title><Msg>Forbes: Papa John Schnatter is no fan of Obamacare. The CEO of Papa John’s International has occasionally railed against the reform for months. Leading up to the election, he was a Mitt Romney supporter and fundraiser. Now that the election is over, he’s doubling down on his claim that the health care reform will force his company to increase pizza prices by 10-14 cents a pie. He estimates that Obamacare will end up costing his company $5-8 million annually.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1352818674556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:57:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352818790456-63</Id><Topic><Title>No Help Coming - the Leftists have won</Title><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352817346176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:35:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The leftist did not WIN!!! The IDIOT RIGHT spent election in their sister's crotch. The RIGHT has abdicated responsiblity to moderate a compromise agreements. INTSTEAD, they have veered more extreme and lost everyone except the wackos. There has been no nationalization. There has only been the abandonment of the center by the RIGHT. $400 million was not wasted on the election. The $400 million spent by superpacs keep the REPUBLICANS from TOTAL DISASTER. MITT got what he wanted. His $100mill superpac balance will be transferred to his Caymen shell corps and he will have pocketed a cool $100m from donors.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1352818790456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:59:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352818843529-64</Id><Topic><Title>No Help Coming - the Leftists have won</Title><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352817346176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:35:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THE BOEING PLANT WILL BE BUILT. The PIPELINE from CANADA to the HOUSTON OIL billionares will be built and Canadian will have a port to allow export to China and India. The Oil wil not go to Americans at $4 per gallon when Europeans will pay $10. Free markets ....</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1352818843529</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:00:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352819028948-65</Id><Title>Use this opportunity to BUY!</Title><Msg>I cannot believe that it went under pe of 9. I see it bounce over it now but was below it earlier. I guess the MS news scared off some weak hands. I am telling you, this is the best time to buy INTC. Don't be fooled by all these articles on weak PC numbers. The lines between what is a PC and what is a tablet are become blurry. It seems obvious to me that the PC is evolving with the touch capabilites that are demanded my consumers. In 2 years time, all PC will have touch capabilities. You won't find any labtops that you see now. Convertibles PCs will be the wave of the future. INTC will be a dominate player in this market. I would not be surprised to see a convertible PC coming from AAPL. I think come CES in January, you will see all new types of super thin powerful convertible PCs that will come pouring into the market with the new INTC Haswell chip. And at CES, you will also see smartphones with INTC's new z2580 chip inside. The media will have a different tune for INTC in 2013!</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352819028948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:03:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352819100009-66</Id><Topic><Title>Obamaflation</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1352818674556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:57:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>POCKETING $100m in superpac funds into his Caymen bank accounts. What a bunch of Maroons!!!! FREE MARKETS will fix the PIZZA price. PAPA JOHN is already starting to get DEAR JOHN orders. SURPRISE!!!! A REPUBLICAN ROMNEY SUPPORT does't like OBAMACARE. Maybe PAPA shouldn't give away 2 mill pizzas or spend the $5-$8 million annually on Peyton Manning's contract.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1352819100009</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:05:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352819898226-67</Id><Topic><Title>MY PROPOSAL: CONCENTRATE ON MAKING A LOT OF MONEY TO BECOME RICH.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352779235133</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 23:00:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The AMERICAN OPPORTUNITY is still there but the economy has to work through the REPUBLICAN dance BUSHCHENEY did on the head of the country. The only people who WANT FREE STUFF FROM THE GOVERNMENT are the RICH. The POOR don't want it but have no choice. The "JOB CREATORS" are the ones with their hands out.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1352819898226</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:18:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352820043521-68</Id><Topic><Title>4 MORE YEARS OF MISERY AHEAD.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352272744072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 02:19:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, at least ROMNEY has his $100mill Superpac balance that he can transfer to the Caymen Islands to salve his hurt. I am confident that you know how bribes work.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1352820043521</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:20:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352820138969-69</Id><Title>Windows RT Route</Title><Msg>Can't help but wonder if Mr. Steven Sinofsky, the well-regarded head of the software giant's Windows division, was leaving the company because of the Windows RT fiasco...He was the one who demonstrated the new Surface Tablet running Windows RT when it crashed and he was forced to grab another tablet from backstage to continue the demo. Windows RT looks and feels more like the old Windows CE, which had be the stripped down to run on devices with limited storage and computing needs...Wonder why they they just didn't call it CERT to FAIL? The bottom line at Micosoft is that Mr. Sinofsky is out the door. Meanwhile the "real" Windows 8 running Intel on the same Surface Tablets could be a winner. The newest convertables coming out with touch screens and Intel processors are close to being dream machines. They are fast, sleek, versatile and despite Apple's jab at trying to portray them as a combining a stove and a refrigerator together, these new laptop/tablets are the best of both computing worlds. And good luck to Apple when they try to run without Intel on their MacBooks! We may see some Apple's Execs likewise down the road.</Msg><Username>san_warzone</Username><Timestamp>1352820138969</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:22:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352820591539-70</Id><Title>Nice CDW commercial about Cisco Design with Intel Xeon inside</Title><Msg>Intel's gonna make a ton of money in the future and they know this. That's why they are building more Fab space. Can't wait for Fab 42 next year. Don't forget the talk about Cisco and Intel signing a Foundry Deal worth 1 Billion annualy to Intel.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1352820591539</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:29:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352821268963-71</Id><Topic><Title>Obamaflation</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1352818674556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:57:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he's correct, many firms are already cutting back on benefits, changing plans. never fear, higher and higher taxes will appear, and Obama will destroy the economy over the next 4 years</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1352821268963</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:41:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352821303624-72</Id><Title>Intel Phi Coprocessor released with broad industry support</Title><Msg>Intel Phi Coprocessor Released With Broad Industry Support By: John Rath November 13th, 2012 inShare Intel announced the commercial release of the Xeon Phi Coprocessor, that when combined with Xeon processors promise to drive innovation in high performance computing (HPC). The announcement was supported by many vendors, including SGI, Cirrascale and Appro. Intel (INTC) officially introduced the Intel Xeon Phi coprocessor at the Supercomputing Conference (SC12) in Salt Lake City Monday. Intel’s Xeon Phi was formerly known by the code name Knights Corner, featuring 3-D tri-gate transistors and 22-nanometer silicon. Most important in the new coprocessor is its familiarity in programmability, extending the Intel Xeon processor architecture. Specializing in efficient performance for highly parallel applications the Xeon Phi boasts up to 8GB of memory and 352 Gigabytes per second of peak memory bandwidth. “Intel Xeon Phi coprocessor represents an achievement in Intel innovation that will help propel us to new heights in research and discovery, and reaffirms our commitment to Exascale-level computing,” said Diane Bryant, vice president and general manager of the Datacenter and Connected Systems Group. “The combination of the Intel Xeon processor family and the Intel Xeon Phi coprocessor will change the scope and scale of what highly parallel applications can accomplish, by delivering unprecedented performance, efficiency and programmability. With this technology as a new foundation for HPC, solving real-world challenges from accurately predicting weather patterns 21 days in advance, to developing new cures for diseases will become increasingly possible.” Intel launched two Xeon Phi product families to provide optimal performance and performance-per-watt for highly parallel HPC workloads. The Xeon Phi coprocessor 3100 family will offer more than 1 Teraflop/s performance, up to 6GB memory at 240GB/second bandwidth, and will operate within a 300 watt thermal design point (TDP) envelope. The Xeon Phi 5110P will offer additional performance at a lower power envelope. Reaching 1.01 Teraflop/s and supporting 8GB of GDDR5 memory at 320GB/second bandwidth, it can achieve 225 watts TDP. It is a passively cooled chip, delivering power efficiency that is ideal for dense computing environments. With more than 75 percent of the November 2012 Top500 list choosing an Intel compute engine, the Xeon Phi coprocessor appeared in seven systems. These included the TACC Stampede effort with Dell, the Discover system at NASA Center for Climate Simulation and others. The Intel Xeon Phi coprocessor 5110P is shipping immediately with general availability on January 28, 2013. The Xeon Phi 3100 product family will be available in the first half of 2013. Vendor Support SGI announced support of the Intel Xeon Phi coprocessor in fully managed and integrated solutions across its entire server product line. SGI has been an Intel Xeon Phi Validation Partner with early adoption of the Xeon Phi coprocessor on SGI server platforms at NASA Ames, COSMOS Consortium and The Genome Analysis Centre (TGAC), who are driving important advancements in scientific simulations and genomics. The Intel Xeon Phi is offered on the SGI UV 2000, SGI UV 20, Rackable and SGI ICE X platforms. Professor Stephen Hawking said, “I am delighted that our new COSMOS supercomputer from SGI contains the latest many-core technology from Intel, the Xeon Phi coprocessors. With our powerful and flexible SGI UV2000 we can continue to focus on discovery, leading worldwide efforts to advance the understanding of our Universe.” Cirrascale announced the Cirrascale VB5400 blade server featuring support to handle up to eight of the newly released Intel Xeon Phi coprocessors. The company has developed a proprietary 80-lane PCIe switch, and integrates dual switches enabling it to support eight Intel Xeon Phi coprocessors in a single scalable system. “As a valued partner, Cirrascale is once again bringing to market a solution that helps to further extends Intel’s commitment for providing a revolutionary leap in discovery and innovation with the Intel Xeon Phi coprocessor,” said Dr. Stephen Wheat, General Manager of High-Performance Computing at Intel. “The Cirrascale VB5400 with 8 Intel Xeon Ph™ coprocessors is an example of how this massively parallel processing solution can scale to enable High Performance Computing breakthroughs unlike anything previously seen.” Appro announced the availability and support of the Appro Xtreme Line of Supercomputers based on the Intel Xeon processor E5 family combined with the new Intel Xeon Phi coprocessors to address high performance, energy efficiency, programmability and manageability for scientific technical discoveries. Both Xtreme-X and Xtreme-Cool systems support two socket based on the Xeon processor E5 family combined with the new Xeon Phi Coprocessors. Appro was recently acquired by Cray. “We are pleased to make available the next generation Appro Supercomputers based on Intel Xeon processors E5 family with a compatible option for Intel Xeon Phi coprocessors to be at the heart of our systems,” said Daniel Kim, CEO of Appro. “The combination of these processing technologies represents a leap forward in developing applications for parallel workloads while improving floating point performance, operational efficiency, and optimizations as new applications are introduced and updates to existing software packages are released.”</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1352821303624</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:41:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352821599331-73</Id><Topic><Title>Use this opportunity to BUY!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352819028948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We may have actually seen the bottom today at $20.50... it was certainly a prime buy at that price... but the future earnings reports will be the tell all to where the stock is headed... I only hope that we can maintain till then... there's not going to be any good upswing without some radically good news, and still everyday, more negative news about the PC industry doesn't bode well for intel as investors look at it as a PC company... the boys at intel need to get the news out, if there is any, that they are making great strides in the right direction... still 2 months till next earnings and we could plummet another $5 between now and then, but I sure hope we saw the bottom today...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352821599331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:46:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352822253978-74</Id><Topic><Title>Obamaflation</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1352818674556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:57:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NOT MANY!!! JUST THE LARGE REPUBLICAN DONORS, ANGRY REPUBLICAN POLLUTORS AND RELIGIOUS RIGHT WACKOS... like dirty coal producer MURRAY ENERGY. Has nothing to do with OBAMACARE costs. They are just angry that they could not buy the AMERICAN PRESIDENCY. TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYY Murray Energy Corp. CEO Enters 'Survival Mode' After Obama Reelection, Announces Layoffs With President Obama sticking around for another four years, Murray Energy Corp. CEO Robert Murray has entered “survival mode,” announcing Wednesday that more than 160 employees at various subsidiaries will be laid off, in part due to Obama-related regulations and taxes, WTOV reports. Murray outlined his views in a letter to employees, which included theories including that a new carbon tax will subsidize Obama supporters and lead to the "total destruction of the coal industry," perhaps by 2030. “Lord, please forgive me and anyone with me in Murray Energy Corp. for the decisions that we are now forced to make to preserve the very existence of any of the enterprises that you have helped us build,” Murray reported read aloud during a group prayer with staff members Wednesday, according to The Washington Post. “We ask for your guidance in this drastic time with the drastic decisions that will be made to have any hope of our survival as an American business enterprise.”</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1352822253978</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:57:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352822578983-75</Id><Topic><Title>Use this opportunity to BUY!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352819028948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At best INTC is a hold, and even that is a leap of faith. INTC is all about PCs, because that's the only market generating enough volume in discrete CPUs to keep the fabs busy, and fewer and fewer people see the need to upgrade their PCs every few years. People - and companies - are spending their money on phones and tablets, and INTC has the wrong business model for that. Phones and tablets are about differentiation, not similarity like the PC market. Servers and supercomputers are nice, but the volume is way too low to support INTC. Until INTC senior management buys themselves a clue about the right strategy these guys are more likely a short than a long. INTC is currently lost in the woods, blind and deaf.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1352822578983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:02:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352822683802-76</Id><Title>aholewad = alexander.dumba***</Title><Msg>Same pathetic liberal #$%$ Shame, because he's pretty good on Intel........yet as smart as he is, he's equally ignorant.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1352822683802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:04:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352823110852-77</Id><Topic><Title>Use this opportunity to BUY!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352819028948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have been reading your posts for the last few days. You keep telling that it will go down .....if I am correct you got in at $22.xx . why dont you sell and get in at a lower price? I see PC market evolving differently. Do you think tablets and regular laptops will be around in 2 years time? I dont think so. We are moving towards Convertible laptops ( with detachable screens = tablets). Intel is in that space. then why do you worry too much about this Price drop? a few things : 1. PPS is being manipulated. when Intel was at $22 - Bloomberg comes out saying apple doing to dump intel. Didnt we know that before? was it new info? that shaved a $1 off the stock price. Menas big boys are buying aggresively. 2. 2013 Intel will take off.......Windows Surface Pro will be the in thing. 3. Until then ignore the stock price worst come worst - it will drop to $18......4 yrs worth of dividends.......if you are not comfortable with that price drop please sell it today and get back in later. dont loose your sleep over this. 4. You keep telling it will drop $5...........please try to learn more on valuation. Have you read their balance sheet? it is rock solid and people invest in intel for: a) R&amp;D b) Best engineers in the world work there c) Cash flows d) best fabs around d) divy Dont freak out, hang on - this is a $28 stock IMO. Good Luck !!!!!</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1352823110852</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:11:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352823329310-78</Id><Topic><Title>Use this opportunity to BUY!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352819028948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really need to do a little research and look beyond the headlines. What you just described is classic mass media #$%$.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352823329310</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:15:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352823741374-79</Id><Topic><Title>Windows RT Route</Title><Username>san_warzone</Username><Timestamp>1352820138969</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:22:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So which is the greater fiasco? RT or forcing Windows 8 UI on desktop users. Both are huge mistakes.</Msg><Username>publicservice100</Username><Timestamp>1352823741374</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:22:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352823774301-80</Id><Topic><Title>Use this opportunity to BUY!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352819028948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Don't freak out, hang on - this is a $28 stock IMO." Right. And just this past May it was a $40 stock, maybe $50. Uh huh. Until INTC gets a better strategy than great fab process this is more likely a $15 stock than a $28 stock.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1352823774301</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:22:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352823872700-81</Id><Topic><Title>Nice CDW commercial about Cisco Design with Intel Xeon inside</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1352820591539</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:29:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Communication/Telecom is THE fastest growing chip segment - think FPGA! Tabula, Achronix ... and Netronome - a network processor company from Santa Clara, California – will all have access to 14nm .....Mar 28, 2011 – We've cast a skeptical eye on FPGA startups in the 21st century because of the tough task in breaking into the markets of the established Big ... Tabula Gets $108M – &amp; Cisco - Ethernet - Telecom News Analysis ... More cheers are pouring in today for AT&amp;T‘s (T) announcement Wednesday morning it will spend $14 billion over the next three years as part of a plan to upgrade its wireless and wireline plant.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1352823872700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:24:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352823967922-82</Id><Title>Here is the future..</Title><Msg>"We are extremely pleased with the grant of our first set of patents teaching context and interpersonal awareness systems," said Fred Falk, president and CEO of e.Digital Corporation. "These patents are foundational of the larger Nunchi™ patent portfolio that we expect to play an important role in the future of mobile communications. Additional Nunchi patent applications are in progress that we expect to add value to our portfolio."</Msg><Username>ocontow1</Username><Timestamp>1352823967922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:26:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352824890096-83</Id><Title>i told you so</Title><Msg>this junk just green at 3 seconds and no power to hold the gains. this is a garbage, every day makes a new low, they just like to make new low and doesn't like to make chips anymore. short short short! short it to become rich! I'm always 100+% right!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1352824890096</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:41:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352824954503-84</Id><Topic><Title>aholewad = alexander.dumba***</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1352822683802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:04:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're wrong, it isn't him.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1352824954503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:42:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352825563848-85</Id><Topic><Title>Use this opportunity to BUY!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352819028948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good Luck with that! It all depends on your time horizon. Hope you get it for $15 ( I bet you - you wont)</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1352825563848</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:52:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352825710237-86</Id><Topic><Title>Use this opportunity to BUY!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352819028948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'and fewer and fewer people see the need to upgrade their PCs every few years.' There is a certain amount of truth in that as probably Intel's biggest competitor is not AMD, not ARM but its older processors. In the old days, increasing clockspeed used to be the motivator, then more cores now it's probably less power. Haswell will provide a lot more performance and a lot less power sparking new upgrade cycles above the norm, that's what the raw specs are telling me. We don't have long to wait for this to be found out as benchmarks should start leaking out soon.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1352825710237</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:55:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352826186379-87</Id><Topic><Title>Use this opportunity to BUY!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352819028948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nonsense. I'm looking at what people around me are doing. All of the excitement and spending is in tablets and phones, and INTC isn't there. Absent. Yeah, I still do my work on INTC-powered desktop, and I use a notebook for business, but my notebook is three years old and I see no reason to replace it. Others I talk to feel the same way. PCs will grow in emerging markets, but existing markets are going to decline. Actually, INTC worst problem is MSFT. Windows 8 is not at all compelling. A big disappointment. I upgraded on that $40 Win 8 Pro deal, and I'm so sorry I did. Like I said INTC is lost, and it appears like they asked MSFT for directions, forgetting they were lost too. Both companies need some new blood at the top.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1352826186379</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:03:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352826409636-88</Id><Title>GOP meltdown-civil war coming</Title><Msg>Northern GOP vs southern GOP Rich GOP against Middle class GOP Religious GOP against non religious GOP Idiots who signed the no tax pledge against Wallstreet who wants a deal. Ladies in the GOP about to jump and leave the sinking GOP ship. We are talking a complete and utter meltdown of a party which will leave it either split into three or more pieces or completely dead. The idiots on the right wanted their country back? Not gonna happen. GOP just LIKE AMD, is ROADKILL!</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1352826409636</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:06:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352826615830-89</Id><Topic><Title>Use this opportunity to BUY!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352819028948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>' All of the excitement and spending is in tablets and phones, and INTC isn't there. Absent. ' That isn't true. Both Medfield (phones) and CloverTrail (tablets) are compelling competitive chips in those markets.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1352826615830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:10:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352826742565-90</Id><Topic><Title>Use this opportunity to BUY!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352819028948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you think Windows 8 and Haswell are for? INTC and MSFT are reacting to mobile craze! Convertible PCs is the means for INTC and MSFT going into the mobile world. PCs are merging into tablets and tablets into PCs. INTC is changing direction right before your eyes and you don't see it! As an investor, you should look beyond what is happening now (PC, non-touch, sales down) and look at the future .... thin convertible PCs selling crazy!</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352826742565</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:12:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352826754086-91</Id><Topic><Title>Use this opportunity to BUY!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352819028948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It keeps falling day by day and makes new 52 week new low every day, you''ll have at least more than a hundred times opportunities to buy.</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1352826754086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:12:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352827085210-92</Id><Topic><Title>Use this opportunity to BUY!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352819028948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It sure feels like end of the world by the way these technology stocks are falling so fast and so steep.</Msg><Username>moobyet</Username><Timestamp>1352827085210</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:18:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352827483388-93</Id><Title>General #$%$ gate.</Title><Msg>Some general sending 30,000 messages to a woman. No wonder we are losing the freaking war. Fire them all.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1352827483388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:24:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352828001211-94</Id><Title>I just feel this market will rocket up once rep/dem deal is made</Title><Msg>I like most others are ready to buy big, but waiting for this fiscal cliff thing to be resolved. The housing market where I live is recovering. All my friends have a lot of cash and little debt compared to 3 years ago. Watching, waiting, ready to pounce when the time is right.</Msg><Username>tfmvance</Username><Timestamp>1352828001211</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:33:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352828018991-95</Id><Topic><Title>General #$%$ gate.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1352827483388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:24:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that woman is from the middle east. maybe event planning is only her cover. something's fishy about all this.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1352828018991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:33:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352828101229-96</Id><Topic><Title>I just feel this market will rocket up once rep/dem deal is made</Title><Username>tfmvance</Username><Timestamp>1352828001211</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:33:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes--you are of course correct.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1352828101229</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:35:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352828302702-97</Id><Topic><Title>Use this opportunity to BUY!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352819028948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>P/E Below 9 again... 8.74.. WOW... how low can we go... sucks big time to be me... oh well.... just go with the flow and if I lose it all then I celebrate I guess...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352828302702</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:38:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352828341320-98</Id><Topic><Title>Exynos 5 Dual handily beats Apple’s A6 chip, Intel’s Atom Z2460</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1351590885743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'But the Geekbench scores will be meaningless for most people given the Nexus 10's trouble running various apps and games.' pcmagDOTcom/article2/0,2817,2411971,00.asp</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1352828341320</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:39:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352828437424-99</Id><Topic><Title>Windows RT Route</Title><Username>san_warzone</Username><Timestamp>1352820138969</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:22:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple's jab ... Also in that jab, Apple endorsed what MSFT was doing in that they said they wanted an OS that could be used across all platforms. However, AAPL went on to say that they might not get their phone/tablet OS extended to desktops until 2016/17. Not only will AAPL be pushing a phone OS "up" to desktops, they will be pushing a phone/tablet chip "up" to desktops. That chip is off into the future too ... remains to be seen. MSFT, and INTC for that matter, will be pushing a more robust OS and chips down to tablets and phones. And they now have a head start in pushing down, than AAPL pushing up. The use of RT only to intro Win8 wasn't very exciting, but the ramp was always expected to be slow. That being said, anyone have any new dates for INTC chip showing up in tablets, and INTC chips showing up in phones with LTE?</Msg><Username>wgrsh</Username><Timestamp>1352828437424</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:40:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352828439407-100</Id><Topic><Title>GOP meltdown-civil war coming</Title><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1352826409636</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:06:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LEFT, RIGHT, middle... we're all roadkill once they're done with us...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352828439407</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:40:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352828499351-101</Id><Topic><Title>i told you so</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1352824890096</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:41:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you've made MILLIONS off shorting INTC?</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352828499351</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:41:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352829199269-102</Id><Title>What will Intel Xeon Phi do to the GPGPU market? Analysis: Devastate it and leave no survivors</Title><Msg>From Charlie Demerjian, a guy who regularly informs NVDA shareholders about what's coming in terms of roadmap and yields and contract wins/losses much better than their management lol ! semiaccurateDOTcom/2012/11/13/what-will-intel-xeon-phi-do-to-the-gpgpu-market/ p.s. I have also been telling getanid61 the bad news about what Xeon Phi would do for over a year now while he was busy laughing at Larrabee so this will be no surprise to him.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1352829199269</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:53:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352829412630-103</Id><Topic><Title>What will Intel Xeon Phi do to the GPGPU market? Analysis: Devastate it and leave no survivors</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1352829199269</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:53:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>semiaccurateDOTcom/2012/11/12/what-does-it-take-to-code-for-a-xeon-phi/ semiaccurateDOTcom/2012/11/12/a-look-at-the-xeon-phi-cards-and-hardware/ semiaccurateDOTcom/2012/11/12/peeking-at-the-tacc-stampede-supercomputer/</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1352829412630</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:56:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352829569168-104</Id><Topic><Title>I just feel this market will rocket up once rep/dem deal is made</Title><Username>tfmvance</Username><Timestamp>1352828001211</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:33:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The world is cash-rich and demand-poor, odd ain't it? Some have cash, others have no jobs, and seemingly no way to connect the two. I don't see the Republicans and Democrats making any deals before we zoom over the cliff, the politics are way too poisoned now. Anyway it's the fundamentals of the economy that are broken, and that won't change even if they avert the immediate disaster. Going to be very very (very) tough over the next few years. Not sure what that means for Intel, but certainly it's not good news. Intel may even do relatively well, all things considered, but it's going to have to do well in a bad economy.</Msg><Username>whowants2be</Username><Timestamp>1352829569168</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:59:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352829663144-105</Id><Topic><Title>No Help Coming - the Leftists have won</Title><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352817346176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:35:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ha ha ha...your guy won, and somehow its my fault or the GOP's fault? I'm short the market and I am going to enjoy every Obama failure, every socialist-based screw-up. As our Idiot-in-Chief sets up Obamacare with a bankrupt treasury and an exploding deficit, and the Democrat Senate sits on their hands another year (no budget), I look forward to the disaster as clueless Democrat voters sniffle through the smoky haze. Four more years! Four more years! (of the same FAILURE)</Msg><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352829663144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:01:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352829707090-106</Id><Topic><Title>aholewad = alexander.dumba***</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1352822683802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:04:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i think lucy is wally. they seem to appear and dissappear at the same time</Msg><Username>ramalamalongdong</Username><Timestamp>1352829707090</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:01:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352829736695-107</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Phi Coprocessor released with broad industry support</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1352821303624</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:41:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Charlie Demerjian of Semiaccurate seems to really like the Intel PHI. That is so not like him. He seems to hate Intel. The software article from the 12th is pretty interesting and compares what has to be done for a PHI to run your code with what has to be done for a CUDA port. It seems like Intel did a pretty nice job building a seamless HPC engine. 4 articles on PHI in two days. Nov 13, 2012 analysis What will Intel Xeon Phi do to the GPGPU market? Analysis: Devastate it and leave no survivors Nov 12, 2012 Software What does it take to code for a Xeon Phi? Not much really, you have probably already done it Nov 12, 2012 Microprocessors Peeking at the TACC Stampede supercomputer 6400 Xeons, 6400 Phis, and one Linux instance Nov 12, 2012 Graphics A look at the Xeon Phi cards and hardware Intel releases a little bit more but not enough</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1352829736695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:02:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352829764945-108</Id><Topic><Title>GOP meltdown-civil war coming</Title><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1352826409636</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:06:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I get your point but we can party when we are still alive. Be flexable. Short the markets when it is profitable to do so. Go long the markets when the idiots bubble it back higher. Obummer and the Libs are benffiting from a rightwing swing in the Republican party that has spun far far to far rightl. Imagine when Reagon was the rightwing hero. We had a top end tax rate of 70%. Now Rombo super clown wanted to lower the Cap gains rate to 0. Now given that rich people make almost all their money with Cap gains, he was going to get rid of taxes for himself and his frineds who sip tea on yahts and have dancing horses. It will go like this and you can hold me to these predictions. Obummer will allow the tax rates to kick back to the Clinton era level by simply refusing the Republican offers for a deal. Then, after the taxes go up on everyone on the 1st of Jan, OB will put out the tax cuts for 250,000 dollars again and force the GOP to either take it or leave it. OB will #$%$ss into Cantor's little nazi face. Mitch maconnal has already offered a 1 dollar in new revenue for 1 dollar cut in spending. Funny how he said no to a much better deal last year. But OB has the power and the GOP is going to have to kiss his Illinois Rumppp and give him EVERYTHING. THE GOP bet everything on the election--all or nothing--they lost and now get nothing. How are those GOP polls showing how Romney was going to win a landslide? HAAAAA HAAAA GOP are ROADKILL--idiooots.</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1352829764945</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:02:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352829768131-109</Id><Title>anyone got stuck at 22.5</Title><Msg>when will we go back up to 22.5 , i just want my money back it never fails when i buy in :((</Msg><Username>lilies778</Username><Timestamp>1352829768131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:02:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352829878381-110</Id><Topic><Title>$20.58 in the pre-market... looks like we're going down again..</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352816069695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:14:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He talks tomorrow after the market close on the 14th. I was a day off.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1352829878381</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:04:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352830055460-111</Id><Topic><Title>anyone got stuck at 22.5</Title><Username>lilies778</Username><Timestamp>1352829768131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:02:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stock will go up when CEO says something good. Right now he has extende his quiet period from 6 weeks per qtr. to 12 weeks. It's like shooting fish in a barrel for hedge funds and shorters. We need an emergency meeting of the BOD to #$%$ Paul's competence and resolve. I personally would not be able to give him a vote of confidence.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1352830055460</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:07:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352830157277-112</Id><Topic><Title>anyone got stuck at 22.5</Title><Username>lilies778</Username><Timestamp>1352829768131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:02:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm stuck in at 22.60 average, but 1/2 of that is margin, so I'm in a little worse shape I think... don't think we are going to see 22 or 23 for a couple months...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352830157277</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:09:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352830186846-113</Id><Title>Support around 19 to 20 but mushy</Title><Msg>Lots of little support points, price/volume, long term moving averages, historic chart support, but none of them align very well. And next door, NTAP shot right down through a similar mushy support structure and still seems headed lower. I want to buy INTC around here, but the chart looks like a falling knife.</Msg><Username>whowants2be</Username><Timestamp>1352830186846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:09:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352830309215-114</Id><Topic><Title>anyone got stuck at 22.5</Title><Username>lilies778</Username><Timestamp>1352829768131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:02:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stuck at $22.75.</Msg><Username>moobyet</Username><Timestamp>1352830309215</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:11:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352830658291-115</Id><Topic><Title>Support around 19 to 20 but mushy</Title><Username>whowants2be</Username><Timestamp>1352830186846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:09:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There seems to be some support around 20.50, it's teettered there 2 times today and failed to fall below it... buy this is not looking good right now... it's falling fast today... a beat down is a beat down, but this is turning into a slaughter...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352830658291</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:17:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352830762190-116</Id><Title>Two ANALysts saying inventory building due to PC weakness.</Title><Msg>If that is truely the case and OEM are actually trying to clear inventory, then why did Intel just release its latest processor price list yesterday which showed absolutely none of its chips drop in prices. One of the analyst specifically stated that Intel is seriously cutting its chip prices. Yet the facts prove this analyst to be exagerrating or just plain lying to make her case. Anyone can go to INTC website under investor relations and see the facts for themselves. Analysts seem to have the green light by the SEC to say any lies they choose to.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1352830762190</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:19:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352830901677-117</Id><Topic><Title>Two ANALysts saying inventory building due to PC weakness.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1352830762190</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:19:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly... January will be the tell all though...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352830901677</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:21:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352830912592-118</Id><Title>45 Billion and counting</Title><Msg>INTC has lost 45 billion in the last 6 months and still no end in sight. Paul has extended the 6 week quiet period to complete silence. This has made shorting and bad mouthing this stock a turkey shoot. Never in my life have I seen a stock lose 30% of its value in 6 months and not heard from the CEO. Emails to investor relations go unanswered. I am requesting other share holders who have had enough to Email investor relations and request an emergency meeting of the BOD to render a vote of no confidence in the CEO and have him removed. They should then appoint a new CEO and address manufacturing ARM products for companies wanting 22nm and 14nm when available with excess capacity. INTC can continue with their 86 tech and if it proves better, they can phase out ARM as they won't have the capacity to manufacture it. This would immediately raise our stock price and make it compareable with TSM which has a PE of 16 vs out PE of 9. TSM also is runnung at 100% and they can't even make enouh 28nm for their customers.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1352830912592</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:21:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352831203656-119</Id><Topic><Title>45 Billion and counting</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1352830912592</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:21:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ousting the CEO would kill the stock price int he short term....</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352831203656</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:26:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352831206309-120</Id><Title>how fiscal cliff will effect INTC ?</Title><Msg>if they let the Bush tax cut expire, will this cause dividend tax to go back up , if yes do you think intc will be effected ?? opinion, they will most probably let Bush tax cut expire but maybe single out capital gain (since it's for the rich), and claim cap gain will not be change ? i wont put it pass them , anything to save this market from going down ....</Msg><Username>lilies778</Username><Timestamp>1352831206309</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:26:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352831687753-121</Id><Topic><Title>how fiscal cliff will effect INTC ?</Title><Username>lilies778</Username><Timestamp>1352831206309</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:26:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you know a CEO won't say anything to refute you, you can say anything you want with inpunity. This allowes you to make a fortune at the stockholders expense.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1352831687753</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:34:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352832070380-122</Id><Title>This dog aint huntin</Title><Msg>#$%$?????????</Msg><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1352832070380</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:41:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352832701858-123</Id><Title>I would really wait to buy INTC its going lower</Title><Msg>I would really wait to buy INTC its going lower</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1352832701858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:51:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352833460029-124</Id><Title>Mike Paulenoff's chart analysis on INC</Title><Msg>Mike tells MPTrader subscribers today: Intel Corporation (INTC) has pressed to a new 13-month low at 20.50 today, which amounts to a 30% decline since May. Yesterday, INTC closed beneath its 26-month support line and is vulnerable to downside continuation towards a test of its Sept 2011 low at 19.16 Although INTC is beginning to exhibit positive momentum divergences that often emerge prior to a counter-trend recovery rally, the price action remains weak and points to 20.20/00 next. Only a rally that hurdles and sustains above 21.10/20 will begin to neutralize the extreme near-term bearish outlook, but not the dominant medium-term bear trend. Chartwork on the MPTrader site under "Mid-Day Minute."</Msg><Username>jan5252</Username><Timestamp>1352833460029</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:04:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352833775521-125</Id><Title>levee about to break</Title><Msg>market whats to run will they let it?</Msg><Username>atrampminer</Username><Timestamp>1352833775521</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:09:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352833993276-126</Id><Title>support $19 $18 $12</Title><Msg>next stop $19</Msg><Username>febru3012</Username><Timestamp>1352833993276</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:13:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352834027670-127</Id><Title>Ready to Explode!</Title><Msg>Rumor on the street is that a Major Company Awareness Campaign is scheduled to kick off the next couple of days on PLSB</Msg><Username>tonilcvt974140</Username><Timestamp>1352834027670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:13:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352835247730-128</Id><Topic><Title>Support around 19 to 20 but mushy</Title><Username>whowants2be</Username><Timestamp>1352830186846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:09:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Had.. support at 20.50... not anymore... geesh.. is this dog dead or what?</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352835247730</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:34:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352835275449-129</Id><Topic><Title>Ready to Explode!</Title><Username>tonilcvt974140</Username><Timestamp>1352834027670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:13:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ will not explode!</Msg><Username>bridgecrew</Username><Timestamp>1352835275449</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:34:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352835283993-130</Id><Title>Fire paul O. He is a loser and OLD!</Title><Msg>Put someone with some balls in charge. paul O is THE Problem.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1352835283993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:34:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352835309857-131</Id><Topic><Title>support $19 $18 $12</Title><Username>febru3012</Username><Timestamp>1352833993276</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:13:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This stock is falling from a cliff.</Msg><Username>moobyet</Username><Timestamp>1352835309857</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:35:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352835584153-132</Id><Topic><Title>Fire paul O. He is a loser and OLD!</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1352835283993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:34:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's MAKING Millions. what does he care...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352835584153</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:39:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352835760265-133</Id><Topic><Title>Fire paul O. He is a loser and OLD!</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1352835283993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:34:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are falling almost everyday. What a disaster!!!!!</Msg><Username>moobyet</Username><Timestamp>1352835760265</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:42:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352835807017-134</Id><Topic><Title>$20.58 in the pre-market... looks like we're going down again..</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352816069695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:14:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guessed we were going down, didn't think it would get this bad... January can't come fast enough...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352835807017</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:43:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352836138720-135</Id><Title>Last 8 trading sessions...........</Title><Msg>including today - down 7 days &amp; one day no change..........interesting. P/e under 9. Cisco earnings today and Dell's earnings on Thursday will give us some clarity on the enterprise market. Hope the buy back is on in full swing. GL !!!</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1352836138720</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:48:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352836663000-136</Id><Title>Panic Selling</Title><Msg>Today we had couple of bad news - Microsoft's Steven Sinofsky leaving and also an exec from McAfee leaving as well. I think these are causing some panick selling at the moment. I don't think this price will last for very long. INTC is just too good a company with too good an outlook to have p/e less than 9. On Steven Sinofsky's leaving...i wonder if it has anything to do with Windows RT. MS really made a mess of things coming out with Windows RT. They caused confusion not only to cusomers but to hardware manufacturers. I think with Ballmer's admission that Surface RT is not selling well and HP, Acer and others not supporting Windows RT shows weakness with that windows version. I hope MS would ditch it. Most windows users are holding out for the Surface Pro and other PC convertibles.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352836663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:57:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352836811656-137</Id><Title>With Options expiring Friday, does that explain the fall today...</Title><Msg>If I'm guessing this right, with options expiring of this Friday, we are seeing the down flux related to that... My guess is that Friday or Monday we start a turn around and the smell of deep fried shorts fills the air...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352836811656</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:00:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352837122354-138</Id><Topic><Title>With Options expiring Friday, does that explain the fall today...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352836811656</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:00:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buffet buying? my gut feeling says he is. with 4.5% yield , R&amp;D, fabs, etc it is a value play. agreed demand is an issue now.....but PC being dead is exxagerated. Today Barcalays too added to the fall...."PC demand is down" - as though we never knew LOL.</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1352837122354</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:05:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352837809832-139</Id><Topic><Title>i told you so</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1352824890096</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:41:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I made a bundle on it. It is a garbage . If you listened to me you might have been made a bundle too. Short short short . No matter the market up or down, it just down down down and makes the new low.</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1352837809832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:16:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352837893703-140</Id><Topic><Title>Panic Selling</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352836663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:57:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Losing one person from a small division like Mcafee shouldn't cause any wave, but they will use any excuse to run INTC down. More likely, it is the MSFT news that did it. For all we know, he got canne for launching the ARMH version of Surface without the INTC version. That looks like a dumb move. So why is ARMH up and INTC down? Perception isn't reality, but it sure can move a stock price.</Msg><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1352837893703</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:18:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352838011607-141</Id><Topic><Title>Panic Selling</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352836663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:57:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forward p/e is 10.4 and that counts more than the trailing p/e of less than 9. There is no panic selling, just constant pressure on the downside. The stock follows most of the other tech stocks, down. It will very likely bottom at the high teens.</Msg><Username>c757172</Username><Timestamp>1352838011607</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:20:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352838069747-142</Id><Topic><Title>i told you so</Title><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1352824890096</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 11:41:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right, I would have... but I'm not that smart... anyway, I think we'll see down to $20 by this Friday, but I don't think there's much room for it to go lower than that... what do you think the low end will be?</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352838069747</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:21:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352838106101-143</Id><Title>Yesss!!! Thank you Obama!</Title><Msg>Anybody could've predicted this...am I the only one? There is no rescue coming. The Leftists bring only one thing to the table: ARBITRARY POWER. (And the private sector is a big juicy plum waiting to be picked by the power-mongers!)</Msg><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352838106101</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:21:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352838214628-144</Id><Topic><Title>Yesss!!! Thank you Obama!</Title><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352838106101</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:21:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hint of SARCASM in there somewhere, or did I miss it??? LOL</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352838214628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:23:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352838300535-145</Id><Topic><Title>No Help Coming - the Leftists have won</Title><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352817346176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:35:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now, because this country has a majority of uninformed people winning elections, it is a long way down...we're going to do things the Cuba or Kenya way instead of the "angry white man" way. Ha.</Msg><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352838300535</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:25:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352838409102-146</Id><Topic><Title>4 MORE YEARS OF MISERY AHEAD.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352272744072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 02:19:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama and the Leftists have been given free reign to raid the private sector. Short short short</Msg><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352838409102</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:26:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352838748005-147</Id><Topic><Title>anyone got stuck at 22.5</Title><Username>lilies778</Username><Timestamp>1352829768131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:02:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stuck at $23.00. Just have to sit back and collect the dividend. Better than a CD and have 20 years to retirement.</Msg><Username>fishfactory</Username><Timestamp>1352838748005</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:32:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352838749286-148</Id><Topic><Title>I would really wait to buy INTC its going lower</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1352832701858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:51:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only reason its going lower is because people like you warning that it will go lower. Business itself is pumping still.</Msg><Username>chcknlittle</Username><Timestamp>1352838749286</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:32:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352838892542-149</Id><Topic><Title>Panic Selling</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352836663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:57:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I don't think this price will last for very long. INTC is just too good a company with too good an outlook to have p/e less than 9." You know that. I know that. So what is wrong with 99.99% of the rest of them? To me this drip drip dripping away of INTC and the constant din of attacks by Motley Fools, Cramer Fools, and a hoarde of analysts has gone way way too far. I can't imagine what kind of nondiscrimnating born-yesterday imbeciles would buy into all that stuff, but it seems they do.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352838892542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:34:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352839076689-150</Id><Title>WE been selling all day and taking our profits</Title><Msg>You should be doing the same. The share price will not go any higher</Msg><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1352839076689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:37:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352839344487-151</Id><Title>Investors have declared war path rather than reading history....Since 1929 the stock markets</Title><Msg>has performed better under the dems that the pubs....There may be some hope for us in here somewhere....</Msg><Username>dc10050</Username><Timestamp>1352839344487</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:42:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352839350569-152</Id><Title>this garbage</Title><Msg>Will be under 20 very soon, short short short!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1352839350569</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:42:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352839378623-153</Id><Topic><Title>anyone got stuck at 22.5</Title><Username>lilies778</Username><Timestamp>1352829768131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:02:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Collect the dividend and sell covered calls... that's my strategy... unfortunately with the price being so dang low, I'm stuck too high to be able to sell covered calls right now...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352839378623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:42:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352839423113-154</Id><Topic><Title>anyone got stuck at 22.5</Title><Username>lilies778</Username><Timestamp>1352829768131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:02:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul needs to go. What a sucker.</Msg><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1352839423113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:43:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352839513558-155</Id><Title>Buy it while it's this cheap folks.</Title><Msg>Not gonna be this cheap that long.</Msg><Username>empire2008</Username><Timestamp>1352839513558</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:45:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352839585736-156</Id><Title>If there ever was a time!</Title><Msg>They say "Buy" when no one wants this stock! This seems like it might be the time. I think even the Board would agree to that since we don't hear anything from them.</Msg><Username>hweich</Username><Timestamp>1352839585736</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:46:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352839603245-157</Id><Topic><Title>Panic Selling</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352836663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:57:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD hiring JPM to investigate "options". AMD is looking to avoid bankruptcy. 15:38ET.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1352839603245</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:46:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352839666387-158</Id><Title>New puncture of Bollinger Band</Title><Msg>Not done going down.</Msg><Username>whowants2be</Username><Timestamp>1352839666387</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:47:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352839720518-159</Id><Topic><Title>GOP meltdown-civil war coming</Title><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1352826409636</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:06:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They voted for it...now we will sit back and watch the Idiot-in-Chief do what he does best: attack wealth and prosperity -</Msg><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352839720518</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:48:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352839828498-160</Id><Title>Company should start massive buyback</Title><Msg>At these prices, it is a good time to use cash to buyback shares.</Msg><Username>bobbleaque</Username><Timestamp>1352839828498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:50:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352839991945-161</Id><Title>AVXL MULTI DAY RUN ALERT</Title><Msg>AVXL has a history of being a "Former Runner" which means that any slight catalyst can send it soaring 10-25% EASILY. I have been scalping it over the past weeks and short swings have made me alot of money. AVXL has been uptrending the past 6 weeks and it is well off of its 52 week highs. Any positive news can make this an easy DOUBLE on a swing trade.</Msg><Username>larisajjbtu94423</Username><Timestamp>1352839991945</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:53:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352840131352-162</Id><Title>I now foresee the teens</Title><Msg>Never thought it would happen. Listened to Wallis and the other optimists. Still think this is way way overdone. But, nothing out there to prevent it. Sickening. Just sickening.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352840131352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:55:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352840196981-163</Id><Topic><Title>INTC SHORT INTEREST 178,239,189</Title><Username>dedrapop</Username><Timestamp>1352764882915</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:01:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...................</Msg><Username>dedrapop</Username><Timestamp>1352840196981</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:56:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352840387657-164</Id><Topic><Title>Company should start massive buyback</Title><Username>bobbleaque</Username><Timestamp>1352839828498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:50:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does not have sufficient net cash to spend on dividends and SIGNIFICANT stock buybacks.</Msg><Username>c757172</Username><Timestamp>1352840387657</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:59:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352840397987-165</Id><Topic><Title>Company should start massive buyback</Title><Username>bobbleaque</Username><Timestamp>1352839828498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:50:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They already have been buying back shares.</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352840397987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:59:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352840400784-166</Id><Title>No BUYBACK - need CASH for OBAMACARE</Title><Msg>There is no rescue coming. An Obama re-election was the nail in the private sector. Thank you, Obama voters, for giving us such an easy short situation. Third world economy on the way...</Msg><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352840400784</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:00:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352840427580-167</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>The bad news is that buyers appear to be sitting on their wallets. This makes a tedious market which tends to wear traders out. Wait for a better directional signal to step in. If you trade very short term, make sure to keep your downside limited by hedging or keeping stops tight. The way INTC is trading, we will see the teens again cause all of the high dividend stocks are being sold off on fear of fiscal cliff. have a nice day</Msg><Username>littlestew58</Username><Timestamp>1352840427580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:00:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352840596868-168</Id><Topic><Title>Panic Selling</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352836663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:57:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw that about AMD, but why did their stock price shoot up on the news... seems strange to me...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352840596868</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:03:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352840614415-169</Id><Topic><Title>I now foresee the teens</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352840131352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:55:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC is in a quiet period.</Msg><Username>patkc69</Username><Timestamp>1352840614415</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:03:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352840768737-170</Id><Topic><Title>Panic Selling</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352836663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:57:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those buying think that the AMD patents &amp; licenses will bring more than the market cap.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1352840768737</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:06:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352840775055-171</Id><Title>2.5 billion lost.</Title><Msg>INTC has managed to lose another 2.5 billion in stock holder equity today because Paul is once again silent. If you took the 55 million shares and added them up, you would find there was only 1 billion worth of shares traded that lost us 2.5 billion in equity. Way to go Paul! Most companies would fire someone for gross incompetence for a lot less than that. PS Don't forget the other 45 billion we lost since 5-12</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1352840775055</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:06:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352841009038-172</Id><Topic><Title>I now foresee the teens</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352840131352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:55:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Listened to Wallis ---------------- You should have listened to Lucy.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1352841009038</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:10:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352841063544-173</Id><Topic><Title>I now foresee the teens</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352840131352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:55:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Been there for the last 6 months. Paul should have his larynx checked to see it he really can talk or find out if he is a mute. At least we would know what the real problem is.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1352841063544</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:11:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352841299220-174</Id><Topic><Title>anyone got stuck at 22.5</Title><Username>lilies778</Username><Timestamp>1352829768131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:02:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seems to me Waldo, not happy to sell at the peak way up there at 29 is still holding his anyone who bought at 24.00's. the biggest chump of all</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1352841299220</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:14:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352841379666-175</Id><Title>Don't start buying until 19.50 and make sure it hold first, !9.50 might not hold this time</Title><Msg>Don't start buying until 19.50 and make sure it hold first, !9.50 might not hold this time</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1352841379666</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:16:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352841777272-176</Id><Title>...and make sure it hold first....</Title><Msg>Please get an education first, before you type.</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1352841777272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:22:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352841778988-177</Id><Title>maggot coinmaker over at CSCO trying to scare investors as usual</Title><Msg>LOL!!!! CSCO beat earnings!!! good for the whole tommorow.............................</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1352841778988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:22:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352841815199-178</Id><Title>Maybe CSCO can help rally the tech</Title><Msg>up 0.97 AH</Msg><Username>tlee22202</Username><Timestamp>1352841815199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:23:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352842055603-179</Id><Topic><Title>maggot coinmaker over at CSCO trying to scare investors as usual</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1352841778988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:22:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On September 20th Intel announced that it is working on a foundry partnership with Cisco System (CSCO). The partnership would call for Intel to manufacture Cisco's custom processors. Piper reports that the deal could "represent a $1B/year opportunity." Intel entered the foundry market earlier in the year. http://seekingalpha.com/article/882711-intel-sales-stagnant-hold-off-on-buying</Msg><Username>atrampminer</Username><Timestamp>1352842055603</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:27:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352842129235-180</Id><Title>juhnny chambers is here to help Wallus!</Title><Msg>Boooooooooooooooooooooo YAH!</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1352842129235</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:28:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352842317176-181</Id><Title>London Calling: Is Cisco Intel's $1 billion foundry deal?</Title><Msg>And who was it that mentioned the possibility of a billion-dollar Intel foundry deal to the assembled executives at the IEF? It was non-other than John Lofton Holt, chairman and founder of Intel foundry user Achronix.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1352842317176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:31:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352842447945-182</Id><Topic><Title>Panic Selling</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1352836663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:57:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the pe is meaningless as any reliable indicator of value. INTC is firmly entrenched in a bear market with a well established pattern of lower highs and lower lows. with each new low, lower points of resistance on any rally.. long gone, ancient history, 24</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1352842447945</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:34:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352842909264-183</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Phi Coprocessor released with broad industry support</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1352821303624</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:41:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good info, BUT supercomputers are not a significant piece of Intel's business. Nor will they ever be.</Msg><Username>trader_brad</Username><Timestamp>1352842909264</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:41:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352842942552-184</Id><Topic><Title>I now foresee the teens</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352840131352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:55:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh flumoxed flumoxed the ole INTC just got shoved up yer bummox!</Msg><Username>marrohead</Username><Timestamp>1352842942552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:42:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352843294070-185</Id><Title>AMD - CSCO</Title><Msg>With the news coming out of both of these companies, INTC should change their trajectory upward. However, never under estimate INTC to not say anything and the shorters and naysayers to go on an all out blitz to keep price down until they can cover.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1352843294070</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:48:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352843560498-186</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Phi Coprocessor released with broad industry support</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1352821303624</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 10:41:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are right....but this is about taking out one of their competitors in the mobile space, nVidia. If you read the articles, you will notice that nVidia is going to be impacted pretty badly with this Intel move. Between Xeon Phi and Haswell (with much better integrated graphics), nVidia is pretty much done for as an independent company. Next target: Qualcomm. Intel will train its cannons on Qualcomm with its Z2580 which will be a 2+GHz processor with integrated LTE for Smartphones. And lower-end Haswells for Tablets. Look forward to the Z2580 announcement. It is supposed to be sampling end of this year and ramping into 2013.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1352843560498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:52:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352844174442-187</Id><Title>LET'S ENJOY OUR MISERY WITH OBAMA.</Title><Msg>Americans are strange people. They like to punish themselves with misery.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352844174442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 17:02:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352845061626-188</Id><Title>Open at $21</Title><Msg>Selling way over done in Intel. Like to see the big boys force the short sellers to cover.</Msg><Username>spinergy888</Username><Timestamp>1352845061626</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 17:17:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352845391244-189</Id><Topic><Title>LET'S ENJOY OUR MISERY WITH OBAMA.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352844174442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 17:02:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on!!!! imagine how bad it coulda been!!!! better to listen to their whining than listening to their gloating.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1352845391244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 17:23:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352846596441-190</Id><Topic><Title>Out at $21.33 !!</Title><Username>jack_about_stocks</Username><Timestamp>1352325324214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 16:55:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This just keeps getting cheaper and cheaper!! As some in the south might say "This dog don't hunt. TIme to go out for one last trip." ... and come back alone!! Really, I feel bad for all the folks who own this stock. Intel should be bought when the stock hits about 17.50-18.00 and sold at anything above 22.00. Repeat that pattern and an investor can make money on this dog.</Msg><Username>jack_about_stocks</Username><Timestamp>1352846596441</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 17:43:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352846664497-191</Id><Topic><Title>LET'S ENJOY OUR MISERY WITH OBAMA.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352844174442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 17:02:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with that.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1352846664497</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 17:44:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352846706740-192</Id><Topic><Title>AMD - CSCO</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1352843294070</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:48:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes they have kept it down for 10+ years now</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1352846706740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 17:45:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352846810615-193</Id><Topic><Title>I now foresee the teens</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352840131352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:55:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100% of the time ?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1352846810615</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 17:46:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352846993330-194</Id><Topic><Title>No Help Coming - the Leftists have won</Title><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352817346176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:35:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you were fine until the last 5 words. which way do you prefer? you want a soweto? bell curve is real and the proof is at hand</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1352846993330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 17:49:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352847687384-195</Id><Title>Poll finds support for repealing Obama health law at record low</Title><Msg>House Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio) said last week that "ObamaCare is the law of the land" and the House therefore won't keep voting to repeal the entire law. Boehner's office quickly walked the statement back, but the Kaiser poll is further evidence that the public has little interest in continuing the fight over a law that passed more than two years ago.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1352847687384</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 18:01:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352849040768-196</Id><Topic><Title>No Help Coming - the Leftists have won</Title><Username>gouge_away</Username><Timestamp>1352817346176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 09:35:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Help? what kind of help? help from the government? What is this the corporate welfare state - Us corporations have never had so much cash - its never enough is it? Forget the weepy concern for the unemployed - corporations exist to make money not jobs.</Msg><Username>hulksweider2000</Username><Timestamp>1352849040768</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 18:24:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352849212009-197</Id><Topic><Title>Poll finds support for repealing Obama health law at record low</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1352847687384</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 18:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At this point it's just political theater. Obama would veto any legislation overturning it, and there would never be enough votes to override the veto. Besides which, since the law was a gigantic giveaway from the government to private insurance companies and, more importantly [and very incorrectly and sadly], established that obliging Americans to purchase a product from a private company is constitutional, the big businesses who run the US are ecstatic and just waiting for their respective turns to raid the already empty [and then some] public coffers. Pay close attention to what is happening in Greece; you are gazing upon the future of the US.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1352849212009</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 18:26:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352850700543-198</Id><Title>WHY AMERICANS WANT SOCIALISM?</Title><Msg>IT DOES NOT WORK IN EUROPE. EXPLAIN IT TO ME.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352850700543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 18:51:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352850870678-199</Id><Topic><Title>Poll finds support for repealing Obama health law at record low</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1352847687384</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 18:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take your political postings elsewhere.</Msg><Username>mark23503</Username><Timestamp>1352850870678</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 18:54:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352851344033-200</Id><Topic><Title>WHY AMERICANS WANT SOCIALISM?</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352850700543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 18:51:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree the American corporate welfare state must end.</Msg><Username>hulksweider2000</Username><Timestamp>1352851344033</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 19:02:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352852164556-201</Id><Topic><Title>WHY AMERICANS WANT SOCIALISM?</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352850700543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 18:51:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But how if people voted for obama. He is leading america into socialism.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352852164556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 19:16:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352852307856-202</Id><Topic><Title>Poll finds support for repealing Obama health law at record low</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1352847687384</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 18:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Take your political postings elsewhere." I would normally be voting with you on that, but healthcare is a big factor in the future of American business, so I'd have to say it's not wholly unrelated to INTC. (I actually think simgle payer would have been the way to go --- just get private financial companies out of the healthcare business altogether AND have universal coverage (not covering extravagant heroic measures or anything cosemetic, etc. (for which individuals could buy supplemental insurance if it existed)) so that health insurance would no longer be tied to one's job or place of employment at all --- THUS making the American workforce more flexible both for companies and workers. OK, back to GOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO INTC!</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1352852307856</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 19:18:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352853401954-203</Id><Topic><Title>Company should start massive buyback</Title><Username>bobbleaque</Username><Timestamp>1352839828498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:50:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC wasted far too much money with the last buybacks.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1352853401954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 19:36:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352853724405-204</Id><Topic><Title>Company should start massive buyback</Title><Username>bobbleaque</Username><Timestamp>1352839828498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:50:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wdblawgrow LOL how many silly monikers does one person need in your case freakshow?</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1352853724405</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 19:42:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352854094155-205</Id><Topic><Title>WHY AMERICANS WANT SOCIALISM?</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352850700543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 18:51:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHY AMERICANS WANT SOCIALISM? Don't understanD difference between social and socialistic The social market economy (German: Soziale Marktwirtschaft) is the main economic model used in West Germany after World War II. It is based on the political philosophy of Christian democracy Ordoliberalism from the Freiburg School. Ordoliberal ideas were most prominently developed in the academic journal ORDO and implemented in practice by Ludwig Erhard, Minister of Economics and Vice Chancellor under Konrad Adenauer's chancellorship (from 1949 to 1963) and afterwards Chancellor himself (1963 - 1966). Contents 1 Model 2 History 3 Main Elements 4 See also 5 References 6 External links Model The social market economy seeks a market economic system rejecting both socialism and laissez-faire capitalism, combining private enterprise with measures of government regulation in an attempt to establish fair competition, low inflation, low levels of unemployment, a standard of working conditions, and social welfare. The term "social" was chosen rather than "socialist" to distinguish the social market economy from a system in which the state.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1352854094155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 19:48:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352854183990-206</Id><Topic><Title>Open at $21</Title><Username>spinergy888</Username><Timestamp>1352845061626</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 17:17:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My guess is the friday or monday we start seeing the upswing and it continues through january... based on the options market, seems reasonable..</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352854183990</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 19:49:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352854472725-207</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe CSCO can help rally the tech</Title><Username>tlee22202</Username><Timestamp>1352841815199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 16:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm seeing it up over $1.21 now... good for CSCO, however their forward outlook isn't impressive, but not bad anyway... Maybe the techs will have a small rally tomorrow.. I think we'll have to wait till next week to see the start of a better upward movement.. also the congress needs to work with the pres and get the deal done on the economy and they need to do it now...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1352854472725</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 19:54:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352854689760-208</Id><Title>Intel + Qcom</Title><Msg>"Intel, Qualcomm in talks to invest about $378 million in Sharp: sources" see Reuters, not much more... You know what this means boys and girls..something like this: "Intel and Qualcomm in talks for Intel to fabricate Qcom chips designed by ARMH software"</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352854689760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 19:58:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352854819244-209</Id><Title>2 options for those holding Intel right now</Title><Msg>I hate it for you if you need the money right now that you have tied up in Intel, as this is an awful selling point. If your time horizon for selling is a year out, just stop looking at it to save some sanity. The stock absolutely will have accelerated earnings again and rise at least to the high 20's. Hard to watch right now so don't.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1352854819244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 20:00:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352855033205-210</Id><Topic><Title>2 options for those holding Intel right now</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1352854819244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 20:00:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or you could ask Mux if he used up all his dry powder on all those juicy call options he bought when the stock was 'a gift' at much higher prices.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1352855033205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 20:03:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352855516846-211</Id><Topic><Title>Intel + Qcom</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352854689760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 19:58:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lots of possible scenarios when Intel opens Fab 42 and hits 14nm.......I just can't see any of the possibilities being anything but good for Intel.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1352855516846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 20:11:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352856356099-212</Id><Topic><Title>2 options for those holding Intel right now</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1352854819244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 20:00:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In at 24 thought that was good buy guess I have to wait for a while</Msg><Username>funtoday89</Username><Timestamp>1352856356099</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 20:25:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352857251589-213</Id><Topic><Title>WE been selling all day and taking our profits</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1352839076689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:37:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raystock is broke and on welfare as he admits on the nuva message board. Never believe that lying money loser.</Msg><Username>rlmroller3</Username><Timestamp>1352857251589</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 20:40:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352857275090-214</Id><Topic><Title>LET'S ENJOY OUR MISERY WITH OBAMA.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352844174442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 17:02:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Election is over you lost,leave the country if you don't like it or go cry on a political forum.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1352857275090</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 20:41:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352858930640-215</Id><Title>Huge loss in PC Demand by 2015?</Title><Msg>This article will probably cost Intel another dollar per share tomorrow. : (. Is Intel a dead man walking? I thought Ultrabook convertibles were going to change things for the better. Pads, tablets eating into PC market: Barclays November 13, 2012, 12:04 PM Barclays Capital sees more tough times ahead for personal computers. And it’s not just about a weak economy and the reluctance of consumers to spend. In fact, consumers are willing to buy new computing devices, but they’re staying away from PCs, analyst Ben Reitzes said in a note. Barclays now expects PC sales to fall 3% this year, down from an earlier projection of flat growth. Next year, PC shipments are seen slipping 4% year-over-year, worse that an earlier projection for a 1% decline. “The consumer market remains weak and the tablet and smartphone markets continue to cannibalize the PC market; the iPad mini, new iPad and the iPhone 5 could continue to take wallet share,” Reitzes wrote. Reitzes argues that “a new generation of consumers and IT workers are figuring out how to compute differently than those that started using PC’s in the 90’s — relying more on mobile devices and the cloud — as PC’s see significant ‘task infringement’ by the day.” That means that it’s highly unlikely that the PC market “can remain in the range of 350 million units a year.” Instead, with consumers hanging onto their PCs longer, that could mean “the loss of 50-100 million units in annualized demand by 2015.” There’s another big problem: the industry isn’t preparing for this big change, Reitzes argued. “After years of denial, most PC industry players still don’t seem to realize what is happening – and don’t have contingency plans,” Reitzes said. “PC’s are not the only subsector impacted in tech — as printing also is caught in the wake of mobility. Given these factors we are significantly cutting estimates for the PC industry to reflect further deterioration in PC related revenues.” The big guns of the PC industry saw their shares in the red on Tuesday. Microsoft MSFT +0.63% shed 3% mainly on the departure of Steven Sinofsky, the head of its Windows division. Shares Hewlett-Packard HPQ +0.38% , Dell Inc. DELL +0.21% and Intel Corp. INTC +0.59% were also each down fractionally.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1352858930640</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 21:08:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352859449291-216</Id><Topic><Title>Huge loss in PC Demand by 2015?</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1352858930640</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 21:08:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hmmm..that's not a new article..I read that day before yesterday...guess you just like to stir a pot of s H % T</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352859449291</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 21:17:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352859632085-217</Id><Topic><Title>Intel + Qcom</Title><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352854689760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 19:58:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It takes so little effort to see the vast opportunities for INTC, I just can't understand how the bashers and Cramers are getting away with this. It speaks very ill of the average consumer investor. A little common sense and DD and this is an, if not the, obvious buy.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1352859632085</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 21:20:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352859703897-218</Id><Topic><Title>Huge loss in PC Demand by 2015?</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1352858930640</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 21:08:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The article is from today, jerk. Noon today, November 13th. Google it.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1352859703897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 21:21:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352860490362-219</Id><Title>Hey Joe, this is Fred over at Hawthorne Farms. Whaddya think about all that AAPL buzz and mobile stuff?</Title><Msg>Fred, this is Joe, don't worry. We have a Xeon Phi coming out with an optimized FORTRAN compiler. Hawkings loves it. We have already sold three of those creampuffs. AAPL is a bunch of long haired dreamers. That mobile stuff will blow over. FORTRAN compiler optimized for Xeon Phi? On the eve of IDF? That was AMAZING.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1352860490362</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 21:34:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352861172170-220</Id><Topic><Title>2 options for those holding Intel right now</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1352854819244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 20:00:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, I rather like it. Investor appreciate the opportunity to buy at a discount. INTC will prove to be one of, if not the, biggest winners over the next 2 years as global trade and currencies flows normalize to sustainable levels/rates. I've adjusted about 40% of my strikes into the money (held all LT OOM calls for the ride down from $23). I'll adjust the remainder after November options expiration.</Msg><Username>techstrategy</Username><Timestamp>1352861172170</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 21:46:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352864317376-221</Id><Topic><Title>Huge loss in PC Demand by 2015?</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1352858930640</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 21:08:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The two slowest sectors are the ones which have fallen the farthest from grace. Computer IC sales will drop to 34% of the total market in 2012 vs. nearly 42% in 2011. This year's -9% drop in computer IC sales is due to a -12% decline in memory sales. IC insight projected a 3.1% CAGR (2011-2016) for computer IC sales (see Solid State Technology 10/26/2012)</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1352864317376</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 22:38:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352864904341-222</Id><Topic><Title>45 Billion and counting</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1352830912592</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:21:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U have no freaking idea what u r talking about; I work in the fab i myself say do not foundary. For every processor design and FAB if u make 1$ u will make only 15 cents if u do foundry for somebody else. Every processor ARM sells is one less for intel. Its like giving u r axes and guns to u r opponent and hope he will not use them against u. Dude just be patient- haswell is going to send every ARM manufacturer to slaughterhouse one after another.. just a matter of time. 2013 is going to be a massive turn around.. intel is getting all the capacity and designs ready. Intel doesnt come wimpering to any table and when it shows up people will notice.</Msg><Username>kosu_99</Username><Timestamp>1352864904341</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 22:48:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352866837887-223</Id><Topic><Title>WE been selling all day and taking our profits</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1352839076689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:37:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course everyone knows that Raystock is a loser and a liar and doesn't even have a brokerage account but we love to laugh at how ignorant he is. Two of our favorite claims made by Raystock are when he posts that he bought "a lot of shares" and when he has been "selling all day" as if it was a marathon.</Msg><Username>rlmroller3</Username><Timestamp>1352866837887</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 23:20:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352868002308-224</Id><Title>Wall Street Punishes Me, I Punish Wall Street</Title><Msg>Here's the plan I'm supporting. Wall Street, as long as you continue to whine, cry, stamp your feet and hold your breath, then you need to be slapped. We'll ride your backs to fiscal sanity or until you shut up and stop with the doom and gloom. This should do it: I hope the president starts negotiations over a “grand bargain” for deficit reduction by aiming high. After all, he won the election. And if the past four years has proven anything it’s that the White House should not begin with a compromise. Assuming the goal is $4 trillion of deficit reduction over the next decade (that’s the consensus of the Simpson-Bowles commission, the Congressional Budget Office, and most independent analysts), here’s what the president should propose: First, raise taxes on the rich – and by more than the highest marginal rate under Bill Clinton or even a 30 percent (so-called Buffett Rule) minimum rate on millionaires. Remember: America’s top earners are now wealthier than they’ve ever been, and they’re taking home a larger share of total income and wealth than top earners have received in over 80 years. Why not go back 60 years when Americans earning over $1 million in today’s dollars paid 55.2 percent of it in income taxes, after taking all deductions and credits? If they were taxed at that rate now, they’d pay at least $80 billion more annually — which would reduce the budget deficit by about $1 trillion over the next decade. That’s a quarter of the $4 trillion in deficit reduction right there. A 2 percent surtax on the wealth of the richest one-half of 1 percent would bring in another $750 billion over the decade. A one-half of 1 percent tax on financial transactions would bring in an additional $250 billion. Add this up and we get $2 trillion over 10 years — half of the deficit-reduction goal. Raise the capital gains rate to match the rate on ordinary income and cap the mortgage interest deduction at $12,000 a year, and that’s another $1 trillion over 10 years. So now we’re up to $3 trillion in additional revenue. Eliminate special tax preferences for oil and gas, price supports for big agriculture, tax breaks and research subsidies for Big Pharma, unnecessary weapons systems for military contractors, and indirect subsidies to the biggest banks on Wall Street, and we’re nearly there. End the Bush tax cuts on incomes between $250,000 and $1 million, and — bingo — we made it: $4 trillion over 10 years. And we haven’t had to raise taxes on America’s beleaguered middle class, cut Social Security or Medicare and Medicaid, reduce spending on education or infrastructure, or cut programs for the poor. Mr. President, I’d recommend this as your opening bid. With enough luck and pluck, maybe even your closing bid. And if enough Americans are behind you, it could even be the final deal.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352868002308</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 23:40:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352868495218-225</Id><Topic><Title>Huge loss in PC Demand by 2015?</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1352858930640</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 21:08:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is the reason gor posting this if the news came out at 12the noon.</Msg><Username>funtoday89</Username><Timestamp>1352868495218</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 23:48:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352868714488-226</Id><Title>Cisco: Chump Street Gets It Wrong Again</Title><Msg>[Gee, now who else do we know that benefits from thriving data centers? Hmmmm. On the tip of my tongue. Somebody help me out. Obviously no one on Wall Street has a clue or they wouldn't have priced in the same miss on the same thing for the tenth time today. And after hours they get solid proof that they have quadrupled down on stupid...] Cisco Q1 Beats: Data Center Thriving "Cisco Systems reported quarterly earnings and revenue that topped analysts' expectations on Tuesday. I’d characterize the last quarter as a very solid quarter in what is clearly a tough market,” Chambers said on CNBC, noting that the company’s 6-percent revenue growth and earnings growing twice as fast as revenue..." Shares up 7.45 percent after hours.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352868714488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 23:51:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352869155016-227</Id><Topic><Title>Huge loss in PC Demand by 2015?</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1352858930640</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 21:08:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Priced in, priced in, priced in, priced in, priced in, priced in, priced in, priced in, priced in, and priced in. Priced in ten times and yet none of this has yet shown up as a reduction in revenues beyond what Intel initially indicated. Where's the miss from last quarter, Chump Street? It's an easy question. Where's the great big huge honking miss that you hyped like the second coming?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352869155016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 23:59:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>