<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348978981793-1</Id><Topic><Title>Intel gonna have HUGE Foundry business AND It's normal business over time</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1348966819142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The media is now telling us that GloFlo will produce 14nm production soon and draw even with Intel in fabrication. Really? Well, just a couple of comments after the belly-laughs: 1.) GloFlo isn't producing 28nm yet. So they would have us believe that they will do 28nm, 20nm and then 14nm - all in two years. That's three process levels in two years or triple the rate that Intel, which is the fastest in the world with its every eight quarter cycle, can do. If you believe this then I'll start gift-wrapping the watch, the bridge and the swampland because you are going to want all of them. 2.) The press says GloFlo will do this at the same time as Intel. Of course Intel actually is getting some 14nm off the line now but the roll-out date is the end of 2013. GloFlo's roll-out date is the end of 2014. The end of 2014 is NOT the same time as the end of 2013. 3.) In regards to GloFlo's new 14nm process: "Kengeri agreed that this probably won't result in as much of an improvement in density as you would normally expect moving from 20nm to 14nm using classical scaling." Just a minor detail right. It's not really equivalent to what Intel is doing. 4.) Posters on the Intel board may remember the many boasts of the ARM fanbois on how quickly 20nm production was going to be available. Of course, the ARM foundries then ran into huge problems ramping up 28nm and now you don't hear so much about the imminence of 20nm. In fact, no one is talking about ARM 20nm at all because it's way off in the future. 5.) To say that it's grossly dishonest to say you are going to jump three levels in fabrication in two years would be a vast understatement. But an ARM marketing department that would send shills to camp out on the Intel message board is apparently capable of the most egregious forms of bee ess. This is just one of them...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348978981793</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:23:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348979328324-2</Id><Topic><Title>Intel gonna have HUGE Foundry business AND It's normal business over time</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1348966819142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Singh, had to reach back to July 23 for that old piece of news. So, have we heard anything about any actual ARM or TSMC results relating to this two month old ARM marketing article? Nope, nothing. And Singh must have missed this statement in the article: This puts Intel "at least three years ahead of TSMC. Global Foundries will be even later."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348979328324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348980980212-3</Id><Title>Intel seeks tablet breakthrough with Clover Trail, Windows 8</Title><Msg>After months of heralding its Clover Trail processor for Windows 8 tablets, Intel on Thursday unveiled the chip that it believes is its ticket to success in the ARM-dominated market. Tablets with Clover Trail, aka the Atom Z2760 chip, will become available around the end of October when Microsoft ships Windows 8, Intel officials said. The chip will facilitate long battery life for Windows 8 tablets and full HD video. Intel has high hopes for Windows 8, and has worked with Microsoft to take advantage of OS features to provide fast performance and long battery life in tablets. Intel has said Windows 8 devices will have the advantage of supporting existing Windows applications and drivers, and users will be able to install existing Windows 7 programs and attach peripherals like printers and cameras. Intel has a better chance to succeed in the tablet market with the touch-based Windows 8, said Dean McCarron, principal analyst at Mercury Research. Clover Trail's predecessors were used in tablets running Windows 7, which was a desktop and not a mobile OS. Intel's primary goal with Clover Trail is to reduce power consumption in its tablet chips so it can catch up with ARM, whose processors were originally designed for smartphones and are considered more power efficient. Clover Trail is faster and more power efficient than the previous Atom tablet chip, code-named Oak Trail, which appeared in just a handful of Windows 7 tablets starting in 2011. Clover Trail is made using an advanced, 32-nanometer manufacturing process, which made the chip smaller in size while reducing power leakage. "With each generation the product becomes a better fit," McCarron said. Device makers have already shown off upcoming tablets with the Clover Trail chip. Lenovo announced the ThinkPad Tablet 2, while Hewlett-Packard announced the Envy X2, a PC with a detachable keyboard that turns into a tablet. Asus and Samsung have also announced Windows 8 tablets with Clover Trail. A prominent name missing is Microsoft, which has announced a Surface tablet model based on Intel's faster but more power hungry Core processors.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348980980212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:56:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348981111882-4</Id><Topic><Title>Intel seeks tablet breakthrough with Clover Trail, Windows 8</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348980980212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:56:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Atom Z2760 is a dual-core processor that runs at 1.8GHz and has 1MB of L2 cache. Depending on the configuration, tablets with the Z2760 can include NFC and LTE capabilities, Intel said. Some of the image processing features were drawn from the Atom chip for smartphones code-named Medfield, which is now in handsets from companies including Lenovo, Motorola, Orange, Megafon, ZTE and Lava International. Intel is open to making Clover Trail variants for device makers, said Steve Smith [CQ], director of tablets at Intel. The initial Clover Trail chips will be tuned to Windows 8, though the company wants to tune the Linux OS to take advantage of power-saving and graphics features on the chip. The company also offers Medfield for tablets, with those devices supporting Google's Android. Clover Trail will be succeeded next year by a tablet chip made using a 22-nanometer process, and by a 14-nanometer tablet chip in 2014. From ComputerWorld</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348981111882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:58:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348981256053-5</Id><Topic><Title>Intel gonna have HUGE Foundry business AND It's normal business over time</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1348966819142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think what you're missing here is the huge driving force behind GloFo which is the fabless customers clamoring to be competitive with Intel on process. As TSMC's chief said, the reason they are behind Intel on process is not technical but financial. In light of this, this force takes on added momentum. Going to 14nm in two years is very much achievable if you have the right amount of resources behind it (Moore's law is more of a guideline). There's no magic to fabrication as Intel would like you to believe. If there was, why are they so behind on architecture? Couldn't they use their super-intelligent engineers and their famed engineering process to good effect there?</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1348981256053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:00:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348981514756-6</Id><Title>Clover Trail Tablets: Workplace Friendly</Title><Msg>Some of the tablet makers at a launch event for Intel's "Clover Trail" processor emphasized the business smarts of their products as a way to distinguish them from Apple's market-leading iPad. Dell, Lenovo, Hewlett-Packard, Acer and other vendors are all banking on the new version of Intel's Atom chip, officially called the Z2760, coupled with Microsoft's Windows 8 OS, to give them a fighting chance in a market dominated by Apple. Intel invited PC makers to show off their Clover Trail Windows 8 tablets at a launch event Thursday in San Francisco. The new Atom is a dual-core processor that runs at up to 1.8GHz and offers a "full PC experience," according to Erik Reid, general manager of Intel's mobile client platforms group. Clover Trail tablets will play up to 10 hours of video on a single charge and last up to three weeks in standby mode, he said. Some models will be only 8.5 millimeters thick, he said, a hair's breadth thinner than the iPad. Taking on Apple will be tough, but emphasizing how Windows tablets fit well in an office environment is the best hope for PC makers, said Nathan Brookwood, principal analyst at Insight 64. Because the tablets run Windows on x86 processors they will be able to drop easily into a Windows 7 environment, working with PC technologies like Active Directory, Domain Join and Group Policy, Reid said. "This is very easy to manage and deploy, it goes right into a Windows 7 environment," said Lenovo's Tom Butler, describing the company's Thinkpad Tablet 2. They'll also run a broad range of productivity applications, such as Office and Quicken. Intel showed a sales application it developed with SAP that had a Metro-like interface, and a medical application doctors can use to look up patient records and view x-rays. Dell went furthest in positioning its tablets for business. It will offer its Latitude 10 with an optional finger-print scanner and smart card reader built into the back, for security authentication, and its tablets also have a removable battery, for "shift workers" who need to swap out a battery before they can get back to a power supply. The company will offer tablets for "multiple budgets and industries," and applications for vertical industries such as health care will be certified for its tablet at the outset, said Bill Gordon, Dell executive director for end user computing. "We also have a docking station that turns this product into a desktop," he said. Indeed, nearly all the devices shown Thursday could snap into a full-sized keyboard. Some had a separate battery in the keyboard. "Most of the time, when you unplug this tablet piece by itself it will be fully charged," because it's been in a dock all day, said Hewlett-Packard's Fredrik Hamberger, who showed HP's Envy X2. The X2 uses magnets to make snapping the screen back into the dock a one-handed operation. Bret Berg of Samsung's mobility group said he expects users to have its Series 5 tablet docked during the day when they're creating content, then undocked at home when they're watching video or listening to music. All the vendors played up the consumer appeal of their tablets as well, but there was an underlying theme that x86 and Windows are a better fit for the workplace than iOS. "It's about having a product that can transition seamlessly between the consumer and the enterprise," Reid said. From IDG</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348981514756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:05:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348981588253-7</Id><Title>Ann Romney: Biggest Fear Is For Mitt's 'Mental Well-Being'...</Title><Msg>Even Slick Willard's own wife recognizes that he is mentally weak and unfit to hold office as President of the United States. This week's debate will make her observation very clear to all Americans.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1348981588253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:06:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348992131403-8</Id><Topic><Title>Intel gonna have HUGE Foundry business AND It's normal business over time</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1348966819142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I think what you're missing here is the huge driving force behind GloFo which is the fabless customers clamoring to be competitive with Intel on process." [What you are missing is any connection to the planet Earth. Key word here is "fabless". It means the customers don't pay for supporting the fab. They may want to be competitive with Intel but they aren't putting up the money. No money, no state-of-the-art technology, The fabless model is broken. It's why ARM fabrication is coasting to a stop...] "As TSMC's chief said, the reason they are behind Intel on process is not technical but financial. In light of this, this force takes on added momentum." [He said they don't have the money. What part of that can't you comprehend?] "Going to 14nm in two years is very much achievable if you have the right amount of resources behind it (Moore's law is more of a guideline)." [LOL. Intel had time, money and technology. And it still took them ten years. ARM doesn't have money or technology. And you think they'll do it in two years. You're not a smart man....] "There's no magic to fabrication as Intel would like you to believe." [LOL again. Then why has it taken TSMC so long to ramp 28nm. Why did they have yield problems with 32 and 40nm?] "If there was, why are they so behind on architecture? Couldn't they use their super-intelligent engineers and their famed engineering process to good effect there?" [Your ignorance of architecture vs. fabrication is simply astounding....]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1348992131403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 04:02:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348992995308-9</Id><Topic><Title>Intel gonna have HUGE Foundry business AND It's normal business over time</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1348966819142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glo-Fo has virtually an unlimited amount of money supply via the Abu Dhabi Sovereign fund. It only lacks the technology not the money.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348992995308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 04:16:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348993871837-10</Id><Title>Cloverview - Max TDP of 1.7W</Title><Msg>arkDOTintelDOTcom/products/70105/Intel-Atom-Processor-Z2760-1MB-Cache-1_80-GHz</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348993871837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 04:31:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348995416101-11</Id><Topic><Title>Cloverview - Max TDP of 1.7W</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348993871837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 04:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only 1.7W for a quad-threaded 1.8 GHz dual-core when going flat out which is half what the previous 3W single-core 1.5 GHz Z670 did so Intel have improved their tablet performance/watt by a factor of 4 going from 45nm to 32nm. arkDOTintelDOTcom/products/70105/Intel-Atom-Processor-Z2760-1MB-Cache-1_80-GHz arkDOTintelDOTcom/products/55663/ Both the cpu and gpu performance of Cloverview will exceed the 2W Tegra 3 by 50% at lower power and only 15% greater die size and unlike Nvidia they don't have to pay a foundry to make them making true net margins greater. It will also have full PC business legacy compatibility. eetimesDOTcom/electronics-news/4397303/Slideshow--Intel-carves-new-path-to-x86-tablets pcworldDOTcom/article/2010798/clover-trail-tablets-pitched-as-workplacefriendly.html The gpu will be a bit faster per clock than Apple's one ... POWERVR SGX545 delivers real-world performance of 40 million polygons/sec and 1 Gpixels/sec fillrate at 200MHz imgtecDOTcom/news/Release/index.asp?NewsID=516 POWERVR SGX543 delivers real-world performance of 35 million polygons/sec and 1 Gpixels/sec fillrate at 200MHz imgtecDOTcom/News/Release/index.asp?NewsID=428</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348995416101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 04:56:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349001683527-12</Id><Topic><Title>Cloverview - Max TDP of 1.7W</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348993871837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 04:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your tablet options now are: 1. iPad 2. Android Tablet 3. Clover trail based Windows 8 Tablet that will also run all your legacy PC apps. Wait a minute, isn't that what a laptop is meant for?</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1349001683527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 06:41:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349005568829-13</Id><Topic><Title>Cloverview - Max TDP of 1.7W</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348993871837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 04:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the market for powerful laptops with screens larger than 10" is safe ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349005568829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 07:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349006901774-14</Id><Topic><Title>Cloverview - Max TDP of 1.7W</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348993871837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 04:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent info, Marsavian. Thanks! Summarizing your info: ================================================== nVidia Intel Tegra 3 Z2760 ================================================== Max TDP 2W 1.7W # of cores Quad-Core, Dual-Core with 5th battery-saver core 4 Threads Max Freq 1.4 GHz 1.8GHz CPU/GPU 50% more than Tegra 3 Performance ================================================== When the reviews start confirming this info, the tide would start turning in favor of Intel. More positive news should be coming in regarding: LTE-integrated Atoms, Quad-Core Atoms, New Atom (out-of-order) Architecture, Built-in Digital WiFi Radios, 22nm and 14nm Atoms, etc. More integration, higher BOM for Intel. Intel wouldn't need to compete on price because they will be providing more integrated features than the competition. TI already signed off of mobile. Intel will have to take out nVidia and Qualcom in that order.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1349006901774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 08:08:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349008203722-15</Id><Topic><Title>Cloverview - Max TDP of 1.7W</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348993871837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 04:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These numbers clearly indicate that Intel has scored one over Tegra 3 on TDP. I wonder why they're saying Clover Trail based tablets require huge batteries?</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1349008203722</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 08:30:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349008284729-16</Id><Topic><Title>Cloverview - Max TDP of 1.7W</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348993871837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 04:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"TI already signed off of mobile." Do you think TI got out of mobile due to INtel...?? "Intel will have to take out nVidia" Too bad NVidia isn't AMD... Been hearing for 15 yrs INtel is gonna commoditize NVidia...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349008284729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 08:31:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349012418410-17</Id><Topic><Title>Cloverview - Max TDP of 1.7W</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348993871837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 04:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>khitch - Your response indicates that you are open-minded to Intel's possible ascendancy in the mobile space. Unlike getanid61. Which is encouraging. Regarding huge batteries, it could very well be the Windows 8 drain. We have to see how Windows RT machines would perform, perhaps RT is highly-constricted version of Windows 8 - hence RT machines would work okay. We will have to wait and see. Though Intel hasn't pushed Clover Trail towards Android yet...I'm sure they will after giving Microsoft the initial attention. And that will see the introduction of x86 on Android tablets.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1349012418410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:40:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349013754362-18</Id><Topic><Title>Cloverview - Max TDP of 1.7W</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1348993871837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 04:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Unlike getanid61. Which is encouraging." ------------------------------------------------------------- "TI already signed off of mobile." Do you think TI got out of mobile due to INtel...??</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1349013754362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:02:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349014095343-19</Id><Topic><Title>Intel gonna have HUGE Foundry business AND It's normal business over time</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1348966819142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Back to the point of this thread: Lots of companies need chips made. Lots of companies will choose Intel to make such chips and Intel will thrive for a long, long time. Cisco using Intel as a foundry is HUGE HUGE news. Just HUGE.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349014095343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349015229838-20</Id><Topic><Title>Intel gonna have HUGE Foundry business AND It's normal business over time</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1348966819142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Globalfoundries to Take Over IBM's Manufacturing Capacity - Rumour Resurrects. New Challenges in Semiconductor World Can Lead to Transitions Across Manufacturing Industy [07/15/2012 01:12 PM] by Anton Shilov The rumors regarding possible acquisition of IBM'scontract semiconductor manufacturing divisions have just resurrected. This time it came out from an additional comment to a Future Horizons report. Perhaps, it makes a lot of sense. Or may not at all. "We assume GlobalFoundries will purchase IBM’s semiconductor division and that Hynix/Micron will buy up the remaining smaller memory firms," said an analysts from Future Horizons research company in an additional comment to the call for the European Union to fund transition to 450-mm wafer processing in Europe. 450mm fabs cost $10 billion to build. Meanwhile, many chips nowadays become commodity products. Moreover, the margins of the foundry businesses are shrinking, which is why the contract semiconductor business make a great sense for Abu Dhabi (the emirate that controls Globalfoundries), which is looking forward for long-term investments and has plenty of money. For Europe in general, with the exception of countries like the Russian Federation (which budget is plagued by Vladimir Putin's military ambitions amid necessity for high oil and gas prices, which is why no investments into leading-edge manufacturing will be made while this president keeps office) and Germany (which needs to keep high-tech manufacturing at home, but does not want to support companies, yet it has finances to do so) long term investments are unlikely to be made by the governments despite of obvious necessity. Given the situation, it hardly makes sense for European private groups to help to invest into semiconductor manufacturing facilities due to lack of spare cash and the current economic climate. In the long run, commoditization will happen to complex chips, such as Qualcomm Snapdragon or Nvidia Tegra; hence, the margins in the foundry business will eventually drop. Historically, IBM has got rid of all commodity/low-margin businesses. As a result, in 450mm world, IBM may not be interested in doing this business in the long-term, but may enter the market of very [relatively] high-scale 450mm manufacturing as one of a few 450mm contract makers, enjoy the situation for several years (so to get part of the investments back), and then sell the business off to its partner, Globalfoundries. GF will have two leading-edge fabs located in one region, which will make it relatively easy to transfer manufacturing technologies from one to another, in a manner similar to Intel's "copy exactly". Such an approach explains why IBM teamed up with Intel, Globalfoundries, TSMC and Samsung to research 450mm production. Nonetheless, in case IBM wants to get rid of foundry business at 300mm level, then the negotiations are underway and the deal may happen rather sooner than later. On the other hand, this does not explain, why IBM is researching 450mm manufacturing.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349015229838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:27:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349015405364-21</Id><Topic><Title>Intel gonna have HUGE Foundry business AND It's normal business over time</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1348966819142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Firms Rethink Fabless-Foundry Model By Mark LaPedus As chipmakers move toward 20nm designs, finFETs and 3D stacked devices, the industry is beginning to re-think the fabless-foundry model. Leading-edge foundries are finally getting serious about the “virtual IDM” model, in which vendors will act more like integrated device manufacturers (IDMs), as opposed to being mere production partners. In this model, the foundries are not only manufacturing partners, but there is a deeper collaboration within a customer’s design team. In fact, given the variability challenges with finFETs, there is a school of thought that chipmakers must reside at the same physical location as their foundry partners’ fabs to ensure that design and manufacturing are on the same page. Otherwise, according to some experts, the chances for first-silicon success are shaky. For this reason and others, Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. (TSMC) may take the “virtual IDM” model a step further. TSMC is considering a plan to build separate fabs for individual companies. And as part of its strategy, TSMC has accelerated its finFET roadmap. Rival GlobalFoundries is considering a plan to offer dedicated modules within a fab for customers. And taking another approach, United Microelectronics Corp. has floated an equity placement under which companies can buy a 10% stake in UMC. UMC also has licensed IBM’s 20nm and finFET technologies. Another foundry vendor, Samsung Electronics Co, has perhaps set the tone for the industry: It has already built a dedicated fab for Apple. And separately, in a surprise move, fabless chipmaker Qualcomm is considering the idea of building its own fab to gain better control of the manufacturing process. Qualcomm CEO “Paul Jacobs has discussed it openly of late,” said G. Dan Hutcheson, president of VLSI Research. “Qualcomm certainly has the revenues to build its own fab and start making its own wafers. The chance of success is still low. It would cost at least three times, and possibly as much as five times, to successfully get your first fab to viable production, or approximately $15 billion to $25 billion. In other words, it would be an out-of-body experience for the management team that tries it.” Sea of change In any case, there could be a sea of change taking place in the traditional fabless-foundry model. “The traditional foundry model, where you throw a GDS2 file over the wall, no longer works,” said Mojy Chian, senior vice president of design enablement at GlobalFoundries. “We have to work closer with the fabless guys. New challenges at 20nm and beyond will require deep, IDM-like collaboration to accelerate the time-to-market. In fact, the collaboration should start two to two-and-a-half years ahead of tape out.” In the late 1980s, the pure-play foundries emerged, which spawned a plethora of fabless companies. One of the drawbacks with the fabless-foundry model is that the design houses and foundries sometimes work in silos and do not cooperate. In some cases, fabless vendors will throw a clunky design “over the wall” to the foundries, which are still expected to make the chip on time. This brute-force methodology has experienced mixed success. The fabless and foundry firms began to change their ways at the 130nm node amid soaring IC design and manufacturing costs. “130nm is when process and design began to be recoupled. The result was the rise of DFM, which didn’t exist before then,” said VLSI’s Hutcheson. Then, starting in the early part of this decade, several foundries billed themselves as “virtual IDMs,” claiming they would work more closely with customers. But some of those efforts have fallen short of expectations. “The leading fabless suppliers got hurt badly when the leading foundries hadn’t dealt well with variability at 40nm, and more recently, with design-manufacturing interactive yield losses at 28nm,” Hutcheson said. Now, as the IC industry moves toward the 20nm node and beyond, the foundries have become more serious about embracing the “virtual IDM” model and for good reason: The stakes are higher. At 130nm, a fab was $1.45 billion, process R&amp;D costs were $250 million, and design costs were $15 million. But at 22nm, a fab runs $6.7 billion, process R&amp;D is $1.3 billion, and design costs are $150 million. Simply put, the traditional foundry model must evolve. “You can’t do it in silos,” said Subramani Kengeri, head of advanced technology architecture at GlobalFoundries. “The key is to have a tighter integration between product design and manufacturing.” This is especially true in the finFET era. Intel has moved finFETs into production at 22nm. Given the variability issues, the foundries face challenges to put finFETs into production at 14nm. Intel and the foundries are in the bulk finFET camp. But to make the finFET transition easier, the foundries should look at silicon-on-insulator (SOI) technology, said Chenming Calvin Hu, professor of electrical engineering at the University of California at Berkeley. “We are going to see (both bulk and SOI finFETs) in volume manufacturing,” Hu said. “[SOI] is easier. The supply chain is the one thing that manufacturers need to be assured of.” New business models On the business side, the industry could take one of two routes: Maintain the fabless-foundry status quo or move toward a “virtual IDM” model. Morris Chang, chairman and chief executive of TSMC, sees yet another model: Build dedicated fabs or joint-venture fabs for larger customers. “We made our mark serving many customers (in multiple fabs). We will retain that capability,” Chang said during a recent conference call. “There are going to be larger customers. So it makes complete sense to have one dedicated fab, or more than one fab, for one customer.” GlobalFoundries, meanwhile, is considering a slightly different model. “This is hypothetical,” said GlobalFoundries’ Kengeri. “Within a fab, we have modules. If one of our customers wants a dedicated module, it’s open for discussion.” In that arrangement, a chipmaker may have to share the risk and cost. And it must make economic sense. Clearly, though, Apple is one candidate for a dedicated fab. In fact, Samsung already has built a dedicated fab for Apple in Austin, Texas. Altera, Broadcom, Nvidia, Qualcomm and Xilinx are also possible candidates to occupy part or all of a fab. Qualcomm, for one, has the volumes and already is sourcing parts from all of the leading-edge foundries to keep up with 28nm demand. Qualcomm’s multi-foundry sourcing strategy “is a very expensive approach today, as designs don’t port to multiple foundries like they used to,” said VLSI’s Hutcheson. “Yields are far more difficult to obtain at these advanced nodes, and splitting production across multiple fabs means either less relevant data per learning cycle or longer learning cycle times. That results in longer time-to-money and higher costs, making going the IDM route seem more attractive.” It’s unlikely that Qualcomm will build its own fab, but it is possible it will end up with a joint venture fab with a foundry. In addition, Qualcomm and others would like the foundries to speed up their process roadmaps. The foundries are falling behind Intel, which also offers foundry services on a limited basis. TSMC, for one, plans to accelerate its finFET efforts. Originally, TSMC planned to introduce finFETs at 14nm by late 2014. Now, the company has no plans to brand its finFETs at 14nm, but rather it will introduce the technology at 16nm. TSMC’s finFET “risk production” is slated for the end of 2013 or early 2014, with production scheduled for the second half of 2015, Chang said. TSMC is not banking on extreme ultraviolet (EUV) lithography for 16nm. “We are very confident we can make 16nm finFETs without EUV,” he said. “I think EUV will come in at 10nm.” To accelerate 450mm fabs and EUV in the market, Intel recently inked a deal with ASML. ASML has also enabled customers to take a 25% stake in the company. Intel plans to acquire up to a 15% stake in ASML. TSMC and Samsung are also negotiating with ASML to take separate stakes in ASML. Taking a page from the ASML-Intel deal, UMC separately floated private equity shares under which strategic partners can take up to a 10% stake in UMC. This represents a change for UMC. The company has developed its own processes and has shied away from forming strategic alliances. UMC has controlled its own destiny, but it also has fallen behind its rivals. To jumpstart its process roadmap, UMC recently licensed 20nm and finFET technology from IBM. UMC’s finFET technology is reportedly a 14nm or 16nm front-end, with 20nm backend. “For UMC to do a finFET from scratch is very challenging,” said Shih-Wei Sun, chief executive of UMC, in a recent conference call. “This will kick start our finFET efforts.” GlobalFoundries and Samsung have yet to change their finFET strategies. GlobalFoundries still plans to roll out a finFET at the 14nm node in the fourth quarter of 2014 or first quarter of 2015, according to Kengeri.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349015405364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:30:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349015559208-22</Id><Topic><Title>Intel gonna have HUGE Foundry business AND It's normal business over time</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1348966819142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Singh, you can cut and paste all day long..............buy you can't change the FACTS that Intel has 3 solid Foundry cus tomers now and it looks like a GIGANTIC 4th in Cisco. You can't change it. You can't stop it. You're an idiot anyway. You say Intel is going to single digits........yet you'll cover at 19. What about Single digits and 19 not being on the same planet don't you understand? lol</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349015559208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:32:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349015926038-23</Id><Title>Bay Trail Tablets on 22nm next year will be the true ARM-killer.</Title><Msg>Huge year coming up for Intel.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349015926038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:38:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349016176929-24</Id><Topic><Title>Bay Trail Tablets on 22nm next year will be the true ARM-killer.</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349015926038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We saw a leaked hint of what was coming for Intel's Valleyview system-on-a-chip (SoC), but now the full plan appears to have been outed by Chinese blog Expreview. The lineup will feature four models of the 22nm chips, with the D- and M-series looking to replace the Cedar Trail 32nm SoC chips used in current netbook and low-end desktop devices. The I-series is for embedded and industrial use, while the T-series would appear in tablets and other small form-factor devices, according to the leaked slides. That model would supersede the Clover Trail SoCs, which are only just arriving themselves in upcoming Windows 8 slates like the Acer W510 or Asus Tablet 810. The chips should offer a burly horsepower bump over their predecessors, with up to four cores and clock speeds topping out at 2.4Ghz. The icing on the cake will be the integrated Gen 7 graphics engines of Ivy Bridge fame, featuring the same HD 4000 and HD 2500 GPU's as the grownup chips, but with only four "execution units" instead of the 16 you'd find there. That would offload functions like video decoding and 3D rendering from the CPU and allow simultaneous display to a TV or monitor. Bay Trail would also support 8GB of DDR3 RAM, double that of the "last" gen, as well as USB 3.0, SATA 2.0 and a host of other connection options. If the leak is accurate, the processors would arrive sometime next year, we'll just have to wait and see if that's soon enough for Intel to take a run at its formidable competition.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349016176929</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:42:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349016243883-25</Id><Topic><Title>Bay Trail Tablets on 22nm next year will be the true ARM-killer.</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349015926038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leaked Intel documents have revealed details of the company's next-generation Atom platform. Codenamed Bay Trail, various versions of the platform are slated to replace the Cedar Trail platform for desktops and netbooks, the Queensbay platform for embedded devices, and the Oak Trail platform for tablets when they launch at the end of 2013. According to the leaked documents, the heart of the platform is the Valleyview system-on-a-chip (SoC), a 22nm part that brings greatly increased performance and features on both the CPU and GPU sides of the fence. Valleyview will be available in four flavors: D- and M-series chips for desktops and netbooks, I-series chips for embedded and industrial devices, and T-series chips for tablets. We'll break down all of the improvements to make them easier to digest. The CPU: Silvermont brings big changes Enlarge / The Valleyview SoC brings big changes to Atom. Intel via Baidu The CPU side of Valleyview is codenamed Silvermont, and it represents the most substantial change to the Atom architecture since it was introduced in 2008. Silvermont brings out-of-order execution to Atom, which allows the CPU to process different instructions as soon as resources to execute them are available. The present Atom uses in-order execution, which executes instructions in the order in which they are received, leaving CPU resources potentially unused during a given CPU clock cycle. Out-of-order processor designs are much faster than in-order designs, but the feature requires a significant number of transistors to implement, which raises power usage and heat output. AMD's Bobcat architecture, for example, is faster than Atom, but can't reach the same low TDP values as the Atom processors can. Intel's 22nm manufacturing process is used in Ivy Bridge processors to lower power consumption while increasing performance, and it will finally allow Intel to implement out-of-order execution in Atom without sacrificing too much battery life in devices. Silvermont will also be available in quad-core flavors in addition to the single-core and dual-core designs, a first for Atom, and clock speeds will range from 1.2GHz to 2.4GHz. Hyperthreading, a feature available in past Atom processors, isn't mentioned in the leaked document, but it's possible we'll find out whether the feature is included as we get closer to Bay Trail's launch. The GPU: Atom meets Ivy Bridge Recent Atom processors have opted to use graphics processors licensed from PowerVR, the same company responsible for the GPUs in iOS devices and other smartphones and tablets. But Valleyview brings things back in-house: it will offer a seventh generation Intel-made GPU with four execution units. In plain English, this is the same graphics technology used in Ivy Bridge's HD 4000 and HD 2500 GPUs, though those parts have more execution units—16 in the HD 4000 and just six in the HD 2500. The GPU should support the same APIs as the Ivy Bridge graphics parts: that means DirectX 11, OpenGL 4.0, and OpenCL 1.1 should all be present. With Valleyview's GPU, you'll get all the media-related features of a modern GPU—Valleyview's GPU can decode H.264, MPEG1, MPEG2, MPEG 4, and VC1/WMV9 video and encode H.264 and MPEG2, and an included VXD392 coprocessor can also decode H.264, JPEG, and VP8, but the reduced number of execution units means you're not going to get staggering 3D performance in desktop games. What you do get is a GPU that can decode a 1080p stream at 60 frames per second while using just five percent of the CPU's power, which will be very useful for video playback—the GPU also supports Intel's Wireless Display technology to enable AirPlay or Miracast-like streaming to a TV from mobile devices. The GPU's two display pipes support up to two simultaneous displays at once over HDMI, DisplayPort, DSI (for the tablet versions), and VGA (for the desktop and mobile versions). Other platform features Since the Bay Trail platform is replacing so many of the older Atom platforms, it has to be versatile: to that end, it supports a plethora of interfaces, including SATA 2.0, USB 2.0, USB 3.0, Secure Digital Input Output (SDIO), the Serial Peripheral Interface (SPI) bus, I²C, I²S, and UART, which covers just about all of the major input and output interfaces across desktops, netbooks, and tablets. The non-tablet versions of the platform also sport gigabit Ethernet and four PCI Express 2.0 lanes for connecting other peripherals. Bay Trail also supports up to 8GB of 1066MHz or 1333MHz DDR3, an upgrade from Cedar Trail's maximum of 1066MHz, while the tablet versions support the lower-power 800MHz LPDDR2. Intel Virtualization Technology is also supported, which will be useful for low-power Atom servers—with 64-bit support and quad-core chips, the new Atom will give the server-oriented ARMv8 chips a run for their money. What it all means Enlarge / From many, one: Bay Trail replaces several older Atom platforms. Intel via Baidu Bay Trail is eventually going to replace the Cedar Trail Atoms common in today's netbooks and tiny desktops, but the platform is more important for its viability in the tablet space. The Medfield platform we've seen in the Xolo 900 smartphone and the upcoming ThinkPad Tablet 2 have served as the company's warning shots, but Bay Trail will be Intel's answer to the Cortex A15-based ARM processors that we're going to see on the market later this year and continuing into 2013. If OEMs can use Bay Trail to make true x86 Windows tablets that are comparable in cost, battery life, and performance to their ARM counterparts, Windows RT and the tablets that run it won't have a niche left to hide in. That said, Intel's competitors aren't standing still: to pick one recent example, the next iteration of Samsung's Exynos SoC is going to combine a higher-performing ARM CPU, a more powerful GPU, and support for many of the same APIs and interfaces as Bay Trail. Intel is also faced with the task of booting ARM SoCs from market segments that they dominate—iOS and Android and all of the apps that run on those platforms are all developed for ARM first, and while Intel's binary translator does a pretty good job of running Android applications on Intel's processors (see AnandTech's analysis here), there are still cases where things aren't working quite yet. Intel has three things in its corner: a lot of money, a lot of experience, and a clear manufacturing advantage. Intel already has a working 22nm manufacturing process while its competitors are still working predominantly with 45nm and 32nm chips, and the Silvermont CPU is already scheduled to be superseded in 2014 by the 14nm Airmont architecture. Intel faces an uphill battle for mobile devices, but Bay Trail and Valleyview may just help them to realize some of their mobile aspirations.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349016243883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:44:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349016361748-26</Id><Topic><Title>Bay Trail Tablets on 22nm next year will be the true ARM-killer.</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349015926038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel Virtualization Technology is also supported, which will be useful for low-power Atom servers—with 64-bit support and quad-core chips, the new Atom will give the server-oriented ARMv8 chips a run for their money.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349016361748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:46:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349016560205-27</Id><Title>Good move for Intel shorts from over 28 down to 22.</Title><Msg>BUT--you do not want to be sitting with your thumb up yours when Intel phone chips start shipping in volume in 2013. In fact, you do not want to be there when The boys at Apple have a glass of wine with Intel 12 miles away and come up with a long term deal which pleases both of them and which pusts Intel chips inside ALL of Apple's products including Iphones. That announcement will send Intel over 40. Good luck--but do you feel lucky shorty? Well do you punk?</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1349016560205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:49:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349017066163-28</Id><Topic><Title>Intel gonna have HUGE Foundry business AND It's normal business over time</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1348966819142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ZOMBIE $UCKS CAN PUMP BUT iNTEL IS HEADING TO $19 LOL bwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa THAT WHAT MATTERS........</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349017066163</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:57:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349018195247-29</Id><Topic><Title>Intel gonna have HUGE Foundry business AND It's normal business over time</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1348966819142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in this corner we have the champ conman and the challenger keep singing. intc going to 28-30 2013</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1349018195247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:16:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349021230001-30</Id><Title>SCREWY WALLY WAS UP ALL NIGHT POSTING MESSAGES</Title><Msg>"SCREWY" may be an understatement. TOOOOO FUNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349021230001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:07:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349021728711-31</Id><Topic><Title>SCREWY WALLY WAS UP ALL NIGHT POSTING MESSAGES</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349021230001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How's that Intel that you sold at 20 (like you said)......and then re-bought higher at 24 (like you said) and that you are holding the bag as a "cornerstone of your portfolio at 29 (like you said). How funny is that?</Msg><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1349021728711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:15:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349021794415-32</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy capitulates, says buy INTEL</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1317740904000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-10-04 11:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. Whiny little quitter. Lucy is a great name for him.</Msg><Username>lucy.vomit</Username><Timestamp>1349021794415</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349021850588-33</Id><Topic><Title>SCREWY WALLY WAS UP ALL NIGHT POSTING MESSAGES</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349021230001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another BIG SATURDAY NIGHT for Wallis!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1349021850588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>26</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349022971699-34</Id><Title>Dividend Arbitraging affects share price</Title><Msg>Arbitraging of dividend affects INTC share price in the week before and week after ex-dividend. Arbitraging offers a very low risk profit situation to large players. The process is to LOCK in a BUY before ex-dividend and a SELL after ex-dividend that is narrower than the dividend (including commissions and fees). It is not that hard. It just requires some capital. One example of DIVIDEND arbitraging would be executed a VERTICAL CALL SPREAD for NOV, DEC or JAN. Buy the lower strike CALL and sell the higher (more premium) strike CALL. QUOTE from option monster for vertical CALL spread from Friday close. BUY NOV $15 CALL, and SELL NOV $18 CALL; DEBIT BID $2.90 ASK $3.10 BUY NOV $16 CALL, and SELL NOV $19 CALL; DEBIT BID $2.90 ASK $3.05 BUY NOV $17 CALL, and SELL NOV $20 CALL; DEBIT BID $2.89 ASK $3.00 ----ASK of zero premium ------- If you take a position in the $17/$20 with an ASK DEBIT of $3.00, your premium over the $3 intrinsic value is $0.00. Your cost of transactions is about 3.5 cents per share to exercise CALLS and SHARE trades for largish volumes. If you can deal in the volumes where the 4 option trades and two share trades is less than the dividend, you can harvest the difference. For 10,000 contracts of the $17/$20 strike spread with a premium of zero: You exercise the NOV $17 CALL early before ex-dividend, capture 22.5 cent dividend, shares get assigned at $20. You share BUY, SELL and INTRINSIC value add up to zero. You get the dividend minus the transaction costs. The risk is that Intel finishes NOV below $20 and the call expires worthless and shares are not assigned. There are several other ways to reduce the risk. Smaller range .... $2 or $1 instead of $3. Use DEC or JAN month instead of NOV. Last NOV, there were 600,000 contracts at each of two different CALL strikes. Since it appears that a near zero premium position can be taken at market rates, someone locked 22.5 - 3.5 = 19 cents per share profit. 600,000 contracts would give $11,400,000 profit. Notice how the nake shorts data explodes to 11mil shares from 100k typical on the days that the option market maker is short these shares. When the option market maker supplies the shares for this arbitrage CALL EXERCISE, he is immediately short the shares to keep his position neutral. The option market maker shorts 11,400,000 shares for 2 days. Check out the Intel pricing before and after he does this. DATE COMPANY PRICE NAKED_SHORTS 20111026 INTC $24.63 494,407 20111027 INTC $24.70 11,606 20111028 INTC $25.13 4,898 20111031 INTC $24.98 38,499 20111101 INTC $24.54 10,596,564</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349022971699</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:36:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349023981461-35</Id><Topic><Title>SCREWY WALLY WAS UP ALL NIGHT POSTING MESSAGES</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349021230001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of Saturday nights, remember that time Lucy was all fired up to "go to the Saloon for the beer bladder bust". LOL! 65 year old man fired up to go to the bar and try to out-drink other idiots until the 1st guy has to pee. LMAO! He wastes the rest of his life right here accomplishing NOTHING.</Msg><Username>beer_bladder_lucy</Username><Timestamp>1349023981461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:53:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349025793031-36</Id><Topic><Title>Good move for Intel shorts from over 28 down to 22.</Title><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1349016560205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:49:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'In fact, you do not want to be there when The boys at Apple have a glass of wine with Intel 12 miles away and come up with a long term deal which pleases both of them and which pusts Intel chips inside ALL of Apple's products including Iphones. That announcement will send Intel over 40.' It's more likely that Apple designed chips will replace all of their Intel chips eventually. However I could see Intel eventually fabbing these ARM chips for Apple if none of the foundries are competitive then, maybe at 14nm or 10nm.. It would be a pure practical business decision and let's face it folks are more likely to buy or not buy Apple products due to design and o/s preference than any performance differential. Whatever happens, Intel will always have the Windows/Android market for its own chips.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349025793031</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:23:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349025925167-37</Id><Title>GOING TO THE DOGS</Title><Msg>"Coming in at No. 3, though, is a stock that has vaulted up the Dog list for all the wrong reasons. Intel (Nasdaq: INTC ) sports a yield of nearly 4%, in large part because it's the only 2012 Dog list member that has posted a negative return so far this year. Until the chipmaker manages to jockey for position and enter the mobile market more forcefully, Intel will face skeptical shareholders who remain unconvinced that the tech giant can evolve past its historical dominance of the PC market to broaden its reach."</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1349025925167</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:25:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>25</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349026632757-38</Id><Topic><Title>Bay Trail Tablets on 22nm next year will be the true ARM-killer.</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349015926038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Intel's 22nm manufacturing process is used in Ivy Bridge processors to lower power consumption while increasing performance, and it will finally allow Intel to implement out-of-order execution in Atom without sacrificing too much battery life in devices. ' Out of order execution can add 30-40% to performance, it's the basic difference between the ARM A8 and A9. Atom has been taking on ARM chips with one arm tied behind its back but it was important to get the initial legacy Atom architecture down to proper 1-2W mobile SoC levels first which they have finally done at 32nm. All these Medfield designs will still have a role to play even when Silvermont arrives as they can be made very cheaply on fully depreciated 32nm Fabs that Intel has already paid for by the Core chips and they can then fight for the cheap SoC marketshare at $5-$10. Denying oxygen to the smaller ARM players at the lowend means less future competition.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349026632757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:37:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349027787176-39</Id><Title>So much for singhlion2001's 30 dollar SOC argument, LOL. Illiterate clown</Title><Msg>All these Medfield designs will still have a role to play even when Silvermont arrives as they can be made very cheaply on fully depreciated 32nm Fabs that Intel has already paid for by the Core chips and they can then fight for the cheap SoC marketshare at $5-$10. Denying oxygen to the smaller ARM players at the lowend means less future competition.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349027787176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:56:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349028412085-40</Id><Topic><Title>Bay Trail Tablets on 22nm next year will be the true ARM-killer.</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349015926038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Huge year coming up for Intel." *** Indeed. After 2013 there will never be another reason to buy an ARM chip. Intel will be the performance and power efficiency leader. Intel's fabrication ramp and ARM's fabrication disaster insures that this trend will last for years and years. Of course, there will be some room for ARM as the low price contender, aka the AMD of 2013 and beyond. Shorts have to be and should be nervous. With a $7 billion revenue miss priced into the stock, only an idiot would conclude that this isn't going to adjust out in some hugely significant way in the very near future. And then climb and climb in 2013. Shorts should be covering like crazy but their greed and ego will keep them hanging on. Windows 8 in a week and earnings in another week. Absolutely nothing in the stock price for Motorola, ZTE, Lenovo, Lava, Orange, or MegaFon. Absolutely nothing in the stock price for the 2013 LTE smartphone roll-out in the US. Absolutely nothing in the stock price for the next two generations of smartphones already in planning. Absolutely nothing in the stock price for the new tablet reference design. Absolutely nothing in the stock price for 14nm production. Absolutely nothing in the stock price for Intel passing ARM in power efficiency. Absolutely nothing in the stock price for Intel's new WiFi chip development. Absolutely nothing in the stock price for Intel's leadership in the Internet of Things (IoT). In the meantime, shorts continue their preparation to enter the fetal position. It's what they do best....</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349028412085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349028463713-41</Id><Topic><Title>So much for singhlion2001's 30 dollar SOC argument, LOL. Illiterate clown</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349027787176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you $ucked brain that worried, you keep bashing?lol BWAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA Intel Pricing and ARM Intel claims that there's no reason that Atom based Windows 8 tablets, from a hardware bill of materials perspective, should be any more expensive than their ARM based counterparts. The important takeaway is that Intel is significantly reducing the price of the Atom Z2760 due to competitive pressure from ARM. Most ARM smartphone SoCs seem to be priced in the $15 - $30 range, and I'd expect the Z2760 to fall somewhere in that range. Intel has shipped cheap CPUs in the past, but I don't know that they've ever shipped something this cheap. ARM's impact on Intel is measurable, it is the new AMD. Welcome to Intel in the battle of $15 to $30 SoC's...A future at Intel..........and only Zombie $ucked brains can not figure out disaster at Intel next</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349028463713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:07:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349028826390-42</Id><Title>ANYONE REMEMBER...</Title><Msg>Remember that Wallis used to post under the aliases of texanjk99, viperjk99 and floridajk99. How he used to post about all the expensive cars, waterfront condos and other stuff he would buy with his "next dividend payment" and how, for years, he has called for "$34 by November." Wallis and his myriad aliases are absolutely and terminally delusional! He's a permanent resident of DREAMLAND!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1349028826390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>26</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349029029299-43</Id><Topic><Title>So much for singhlion2001's 30 dollar SOC argument, LOL. Illiterate clown</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349027787176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel really is fumbling with Atom, they need a real core refresh and they should have pushed to get the low power 22nm node ready. The gpu is way behind Apple's and I bet the display will not get more than 10 seconds of attention. And without DX11.1 there is no acceleration for the interface or the browser. I'm sure they will not use a high resolution display. And i bet one of the vendors will try and sell a tn based tablet I wonder if all the MS devs wear glasses or something. PowerVR 545 (single core at 200mhz) is capable of 7.2 GFLOPS in apposed to 6.4 for the SGX 543. On paper, the 545 is 12.5% faster than the SGX 543 (single core at 200mhz). If you calculate the number of cores vs clock speeds you'll get this out of the GPUs: - Apple A5X: 25.6 GFLOPS - Apple A6: 25.54 GFLOPS - Clover Trail: 19.2 GFLOPS Assuming that the Z2760 comes in single core configuration, it should be 25% slower on paper.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349029029299</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349029352896-44</Id><Topic><Title>So much for singhlion2001's 30 dollar SOC argument, LOL. Illiterate clown</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349027787176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clover Trail is still not competitive with ARM. It needs a 30 Whr battery, which is more than twice as large as most 10" tablets with a similar resolution (not counting iPad which has a much larger resolution. Clover Trail won't even support such resolutions, because they know battery will die too quickly). So even if they achieve the 10 hour mark, which I still doubt it. They're doing with a double battery. Doesn't exactly make for a "competitive" chip with ARM, does it? They're being misleading about a ton of other things, too</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349029352896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:22:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349029644437-45</Id><Topic><Title>So much for singhlion2001's 30 dollar SOC argument, LOL. Illiterate clown</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349027787176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clover Trail will already be replaced by Bay Trail next year, idiot. Keep copying and pasting your way to a hopeful 20 cent daytrader, small time #$%$clown.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349029644437</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:27:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349029737991-46</Id><Topic><Title>So much for singhlion2001's 30 dollar SOC argument, LOL. Illiterate clown</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349027787176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the ARM SoC business, the two biggest players are Apple with its AX and Samsung with Exynos. Its debatable whether Windows8 tablets will take away any market share from the iPad or from Samsung's Android tablets. Microsoft has tried several times before to enter the tablet space with little success. What makes this time different? Apple and Samsung already have touch enabled tablets that are light and have good battery life. Why would I buy the new Windows8 tablet instead?</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349029737991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:28:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349029818065-47</Id><Topic><Title>Bay Trail Tablets on 22nm next year will be the true ARM-killer.</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349015926038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely nothing in the stock price for Intel making A billion or so a year from fabbing high-end chips for Cisco.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349029818065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:30:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349029916965-48</Id><Topic><Title>So much for singhlion2001's 30 dollar SOC argument, LOL. Illiterate clown</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349027787176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is enough for you............Now you can scream your bashing:LOL You seem to have swallowed Intel's marketing FUD Some key points to understand about this [RT) version of Windows: 1) Does not include Windows Media Player 2) Includes Microsoft Office 2013 RT, a cut down version of Microsoft's "Office", for free 3) Only "Metro style" apps will run on Windows RT (so most Windows 7 applications will not run) Point 1) is irrelevant as Windows RT will include Metro applications for playing all contemporary media formats Point 2) the "cut down" features of Office on Windows RT is very small and the vast majority of users will not even be aware of the difference Point 3) actually most PCs users use a very limited set of applications, the majority of which will be support from and for those that are missing, well the ecosystem can move very quickly to support new platforms. Look at the success of iOS and Android in just 5 years. As for the differences between Windows RT and Windows 8, you need to think of this as Microsoft shedding the legacy of the PC platform. They are not trying to recreate the PC, but moving on....</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349029916965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:31:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349030300118-49</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy capitulates, says buy INTEL</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1317740904000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-10-04 11:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watching him get down and his knees, give up and pump Intel is WAYYYYYYYYY too funny. Jilted long- that's all he is.</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1349030300118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:38:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349030377368-50</Id><Title>Lucy sucks and pumps Intel at 24</Title><Msg>LMAO. ROFL!</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1349030377368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:39:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349030456327-51</Id><Title>Lucy bows down and pumps Intel at 24</Title><Msg>As of today, I officially capitulate and am encouraging the purchase of Intel shares. This company is hitting on all cylinders and the management team is doing everything right. The outlook for the shares is positive, imo. lucy_nuff aka tooofunnny aka lucifer_nuff</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1349030456327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:40:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349030706669-52</Id><Title>Lucy eats CROW and LOTS of it</Title><Msg>As of today, I officially capitulate and am encouraging the purchase of Intel shares. This company is hitting on all cylinders and the management team is doing everything right. The outlook for the shares is positive, imo.</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1349030706669</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:45:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349031301942-53</Id><Title>WALLIS EATS HIS OWN CRAP and PLENTY of IT!</Title><Msg>All the beee esss that he posted about huge earnings and revenues and that shorts would get punished and then INTEL WARNED and the stock collapsed! Enjoy a meal of your own crap, Pumpwad! TOOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349031301942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:55:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349032454079-54</Id><Title>this is why its going to 40 2013</Title><Msg>stay calm. 26-29 2013 w/4% div not bad.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1349032454079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:14:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349032989822-55</Id><Topic><Title>So much for singhlion2001's 30 dollar SOC argument, LOL. Illiterate clown</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349027787176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Atom can't compete with the ARM ecosystem (incl. under the radar companies like Mediatek (chips) and ZTE (finished product)). Intel ignored this market for too long (they actually acquired DEC's StrongARM back in 2001? and did nothing with it). Windows 8/Metro will have a very minor impact on the Consumer tablet market - they should have more luck in business and enterprise though. With so much competition in the PC and tablet space, something has to give ..........??? Windows 8 is the last nail in the coffin of WinTel. It may be creative and different, but its that difference that makes users learn something new. If everyone has to learn something new, why wouldn't they just switch to OSX for a intuitive experience, where everything just works, and syncs with the other Apple devices. Look at the numbers, AAPL has already sold more Ipads in a quarter then Wintel makers have made desktop and laptops.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349032989822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349033702784-56</Id><Topic><Title>WALLIS EATS HIS OWN CRAP and PLENTY of IT!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349031301942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:55:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's UTTERLY hilarious is that NONE of the aliases crushing you are Wally. He's a disgusting hypocrite Liberal. I'm the guy that bought all the shares you sold at 20 and have been enjoying the Dividend and gains while you have gotten NOTHING in 2 years from Cisco and you've GOTTEN NOWHERE here because Wally, the guy you are obsessed with..........has you on ignore. LOL! You are both old losers but my GOODNESS have you been chasing your smelly tail. LOLOL!</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1349033702784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:35:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349034148980-57</Id><Title>Thanks for all those shares you sold me at 20, Lucy_nuff aka Tooofunnny</Title><Msg>LOL! How's your Cisco, ya old loser?</Msg><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1349034148980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349034419067-58</Id><Topic><Title>Thanks for all those shares you sold me at 20, Lucy_nuff aka Tooofunnny</Title><Username>getmeoutuhhere</Username><Timestamp>1349034148980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, chasing his tail indeed. Can you IMAGINE chasing someone all your life on the internet when it's actually someone else laughing at you? TOOOOOOOOFUNNNNNNY !!!!!!!</Msg><Username>lucy_cisco</Username><Timestamp>1349034419067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:46:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349034452140-59</Id><Topic><Title>WALLIS EATS HIS OWN CRAP and PLENTY of IT!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349031301942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:55:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hahahahahahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>lucy_cisco</Username><Timestamp>1349034452140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:47:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349034760646-60</Id><Topic><Title>WALLIS EATS HIS OWN CRAP and PLENTY of IT!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349031301942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:55:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HEY!!!! I bought some of his $20 shares too!!!</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1349034760646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:52:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349034909876-61</Id><Topic><Title>WALLIS EATS HIS OWN CRAP and PLENTY of IT!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349031301942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:55:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, hey TOOOSTUUUUPID_nuff........your goal has been to drive Wally crazy, but he doesn't even read your 50 messages a day to him..........so where do you go now that you've completely failed (yet again)? LOL!</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1349034909876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349035059459-62</Id><Title>Hey Lucy !</Title><Msg>To prove you've been waiting your time, the responses to your messages and threads started to you will now dry up now that you've been made a complete fool of. Such threads/responses will dry up as..........of...........................................now. BYE dork !</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1349035059459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349035402034-63</Id><Topic><Title>Bay Trail Tablets on 22nm next year will be the true ARM-killer.</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349015926038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the mobile space, customers are not clamoring for performance. They are clamoring for lower power consumption which directly translates into longer battery life with lighter batteries and therefore lighter objects. Intel will have to compete on average dynamic power dissipation. Trigate is therefore out of the equation. Going from 32nm to 22nm will reduce power consumption by 2/3 appx. If CloverTrail is at 1.7W and assuming there is no growth in transistor count, Bay Trail will be at roughly 1.1W. This would put it at par with ARM 28nm offerings.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1349035402034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:03:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349035926411-64</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL WILL BE SINGLE DIGIT STOCK IN 2013:THIS IS THE REAL PROBLEM FOR INTEL NEXT $30 SoC or $250 CPU?</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1348796337780</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:38:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MORE HELL FOR INTEL Will the $49 aPC Android PC help bridge the digital divide?by J. Angelo Racoma on Sep 29, 2012 Mobile broadband is on the rise, and so is the world’s Internet user base. But that’s not the complete picture. A digital divide still exists, particularly in developing economies, where access to online resources is limited to an elite few. Sometimes, this is economically driven, although sometimes political — such as in North Korea, where statistically 0% of the population have Internet access. VIA Technologies plans to bridge the digital divide through a very cheap personal computer powered by Android. The aPC — or “Android PC” — costs just $49, but it provides a “complete PC experience at the fraction of the cost.” The aPC runs on a custom Android system, which is built for keyboard and mouse input. A full set of I/O ports is also included, which enables a user to connect the aPC to a monitor or TV. Some specs: VIA 800 MHz processor 512MB DDR3 memory 2GB NAND Flash Built-in 2D/3D Graphics, with resolution up to 720p HDMI, VGA, 4 USB 2.0 ports, audio out, mic in microSD slot 10/100 ethernet 170 x 85 mm size, neo-ITX standard The aPC is mostly a cloud-oriented computer. The creators say that the purpose of a PC has now evolved, in that computers now mainly connect to the Internet, and that “[i]t is the Internet that now defines computing.” As such, traditional computers are considered to be “expensive and overpowered,” and software is called “bloated.” But aside from cloud-based apps, the aPC also comes shipped with apps like a web browser, Angry Birds, and the like. Of course, the computer also has access to Google Play, which gives the user hundreds of thousands of apps for download. aPC has closed pre-orders, so that the creators can meet with demand in their first round of pre-orders. However, if this is a project that interests you, you can still sign up for the notification list. Check out the video below with VIA Technologies VP Richard Brown presenting the aPC concept and demonstrating the actual device at TEDx in Shanghai. The intro is a bit lengthy, but you can jump to the 6:30 mark, where the fun starts. Aside from smartphones and tablets, projects like the aPC are taking the post-PC concept to a whole new level. This does not just bring the computer (or mobile device) more accessible to the usual consumer set, but also to those unable to spend hundreds of dollars for a desktop or notebook computer. Will the aPC help bridge the digital divide? It certainly is an interesting idea, and if more manufacturers — aside from VIA — can focus on this market, then Android might just become a dominant OS in the desktop market, as well.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1349035926411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:12:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349036423200-65</Id><Title>More hell for singhlion2001</Title><Msg>Who seems to live on the INTC chatboard &amp; of course for investors that have to look at his endless demented selfserving tripe spewing posts.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1349036423200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349038775169-66</Id><Title>Intel will foundry chips for Toyota, too</Title><Msg>Toyota's been known to sell 8 or 10 cars a year, LOL. Krystal Temple Intel, Toyota Drive Joint Research on Next-Generation In-Vehicle Infotainment Systems NEWS HIGHLIGHTS Intel and Toyota engage in leading-edge research to enable new usage models for mobile device connectivity in the car. Joint research to focus on developing user interaction methodologies including touch, gesture and voice technologies as well as information management for the driver. The connected car is the third-fastest growing technological device, following smartphones and tablets. SANTA CLARA, Calif., Nov. 9, 2011 – Intel Corporation and Toyota Motor Corporation today announced that the companies are working together to define next-generation in-vehicle infotainment (IVI) systems that will enable new usage models for mobile device connectivity in the car. According to Mobile Future, the connected car is the third-fastest growing technological device, following smartphones and tablets. With the car becoming an extension of today’s digital lifestyle, Intel and Toyota are working together to adapt features that drivers and passengers use in the latest consumer electronic devices to an automotive environment. “Intel has been conducting research related to the connected car for years, and with the support of Toyota will extend that research to advanced services that will benefit the driver and passengers in many ways,” said Staci Palmer, general manager of Intel’s Automotive Solutions Division. “Through this joint effort, we hope to improve the driving experience by enabling a seamless connection between mobile devices and the vehicle so when brought together they naturally adapt and work in harmony.” As technology converges with the car, silicon solutions serving the infotainment and telematics market are expected to rise from $5.6 billion in 2010 to $8.7 billion in 2018.1 Intel and Toyota aim to integrate advanced technologies in the vehicle in a more intuitive manner that reduces driver distraction. To accomplish this, the companies will focus research on developing a user interaction methodology including touch, gesture and voice technologies as well as information management for the driver. Intel will also work to optimize these features and services using the performance of the Intel® Atom™ processor family. “Toyota aims to lead the future mobile world through integration of vehicle, home and information communication technologies as announced in the ‘Toyota Global Vision’ earlier this year,” said Kenichi Murata, project general manager, Electronics Development Div. 1, Toyota Motor Corporation. “Toyota, along with Intel, will use information technologies to drive innovations into the vehicle to make the vision a reality.” The companies will also explore emerging connectivity technologies and effective ways to integrate vehicles with the home to provide a seamless connection across all areas of people’s lives. For more information, visit the Intel Intelligent Systems press kit.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349038775169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:59:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349043618811-67</Id><Topic><Title>Good move for Intel shorts from over 28 down to 22.</Title><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1349016560205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:49:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Incorrect...Intel is in all of Apple's computers.</Msg><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1349043618811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:20:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349043939142-68</Id><Topic><Title>Bay Trail Tablets on 22nm next year will be the true ARM-killer.</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349015926038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dual-core 28nm Krait is 1.5W TDP.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349043939142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:25:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349044596409-69</Id><Topic><Title>Bay Trail Tablets on 22nm next year will be the true ARM-killer.</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349015926038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have not been able to find any public power specs for the ARM CPU. Where did you find it?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1349044596409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:36:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349045199618-70</Id><Title>FUTURES VERY REDDDDDDDDD!!!!</Title><Msg>LOOK OUT BELOW! Next stop $21. TOOOOO FUNNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349045199618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349045795185-71</Id><Topic><Title>FUTURES VERY REDDDDDDDDD!!!!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349045199618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What would it take to stop being such a matherf6cker? Would a -90% down week be enough for you to finally become happy and stop being such a pooper?</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1349045795185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349046298888-72</Id><Topic><Title>Bay Trail Tablets on 22nm next year will be the true ARM-killer.</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349015926038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"In the mobile space, customers are not clamoring for performance." []Yeah, KhitchD'uh - that's why AMD, Qualcomm and Nvidia were begging TSMC to get their 28nm yields up. Because their customers didn't care about performance. Hmmm, wonder why they didn't just settle for 90nm production. Since performance doesn't matter and customers don't care....] "They are clamoring for lower power consumption which directly translates into longer battery life with lighter batteries and therefore lighter objects. Intel will have to compete on average dynamic power dissipation. Trigate is therefore out of the equation. Going from 32nm to 22nm will reduce power consumption by 2/3 appx. If CloverTrail is at 1.7W and assuming there is no growth in transistor count, Bay Trail will be at roughly 1.1W. This would put it at par with ARM 28nm offerings." [We already know that Intel is competitive on power consumption, fanboi. And Intel has two more generations already in planning. And ARM's pathetic fabrication won't take them there. After 2013, there will never be another reason to buy an ARM processor. It is nice that you have finally given up on spouting falsehoods about ARM matching Intel on performance. Stick with the power efficiency argument for the short time before it fades...] "Bay Trail is eventually going to replace the Cedar Trail Atoms common in today's netbooks and tiny desktops, but the platform is more important for its viability in the tablet space. The Medfield platform we've seen in the Xolo 900 smartphone and the upcoming ThinkPad Tablet 2 have served as the company's warning shots, but Bay Trail will be Intel's answer to the Cortex A15-based ARM processors that we're going to see on the market later this year and continuing into 2013. If OEMs can use Bay Trail to make true x86 Windows tablets that are comparable in cost, battery life, and performance to their ARM counterparts, Windows RT and the tablets that run it won't have a niche left to hide in." [There you go, fanboi - ARM isn't going to have a niche to hide in. Game over for you, the shills, the analysts and the big Wall Street firm #$%$...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349046298888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:04:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349046867510-73</Id><Title>Intel Shorts - No Where to Run, No Where to Hide</Title><Msg>With a full $7 billion revenue miss now priced into the stock, what is the next move for Wall Street? The Q3 report certainly isn't going to show a $7 billion decline in revenues. So, what will shorts do when they have to deal with facts? Facts that clearly don't support a seven dollar decline in the stock price. Well, there's always the fetal position...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349046867510</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349047426366-74</Id><Title>IS $21 POSSIBLE TOMORROW?</Title><Msg>The Magic 8-Ball sez: "ABSOLUTELY!" TOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349047426366</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349047485345-75</Id><Topic><Title>FUTURES VERY REDDDDDDDDD!!!!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349045199618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't really think that anything will change the behavior of someone so psychologically damaged that they get out of bed every day, week after week and month after month, with the idea of destroying value that functional people have created. A person so full of bile, venom and self-loathing that no amount of therapy would fix them. A person like that craves attention. Even negative attention. If you want them to stop you simply have to stop feeding them. Just put the unfixable #$%$ on ignore...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349047485345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:24:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349047815008-76</Id><Topic><Title>FUTURES VERY REDDDDDDDDD!!!!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349045199618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>someone so psychologically damaged ----------- You want damaged? The guy who was screaming "BUY!" at $29 is DAMAGED!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349047815008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:30:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349048362412-77</Id><Topic><Title>Bay Trail Tablets on 22nm next year will be the true ARM-killer.</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349015926038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>alexander, it was actually measured anandtechDOTcom/show/5559/qualcomm-snapdragon-s4-krait-performance-preview-msm8960-adreno-225-benchmarks/4 'If you squint at the graph, you can see that one Krait core can use around 750 mW at maximum load. I didn't enable the CPU frequency graph (just to keep things simple above) but is 750 mW number happens right at 1.5 GHz.'</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349048362412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:39:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349048419200-78</Id><Title>TEENS or $30?</Title><Msg>Which is more likely? Better yet, which is closer.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1349048419200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:40:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>21</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349048780499-79</Id><Title>ARMH stock price will collapse in 2013 and Apple will dump the girlfriend that got fat and ugly</Title><Msg>check it</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1349048780499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:46:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349049391941-80</Id><Topic><Title>Bay Trail Tablets on 22nm next year will be the true ARM-killer.</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349015926038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'According to Deutsche Securities, TSMC has seen its 28-nm yield rate increase and has widened its 28-nm lead against second-tier contract manufacturers. As such the company is expected to benefit from 28-nm orders from major designers, Deutsche Securities said. As for UMC, its 28-nm yield rate is expected at 15 to 20 percent in the final quarter, trailing far behind TSMC's 75 to 85 percent, Deutsche said. Meanwhile, due to its weaker profitability and asset-liability structure, UMC is unlikely to be able to afford the high capital expenditure it needs to develop 20-nm and 16-nm technology. According to Deutsche, UMC's 28-nm will grow at a slower pace, with fourth-quarter 28-nm production at about 5 percent of the firm's total, or about 4 percent of TSMC's 28-nm proportion to the total.' chinapostDOTcomDOTtw/business/company-focus/2012/10/01/356130/TSMC-UMC.htm</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1349049391941</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:56:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349054580593-81</Id><Title>TSMC loses more business ?</Title><Msg>Samsung, ST reveal foundry deal Peter Clarke 9/28/2012 4:50 AM EDT LONDON – STMicroelectronics has selected Samsung's foundry business unit for the production of ICs using a 32/28-nm high-K metal gate manufacturing process. The deal provides ST with alternative supply of 28-nm silicon. In the past ST has worked with Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. Ltd. in the past as a supplier of leading-edge chips but during 2012 the Taiwanese foundry has been unable to meet the demand for 28-nm CMOS from its customers leading a number of them to announce plans to find other sources of silicon. ST is also a manufacturer of leading-edge chips itself. ST has opted to manufacture circuits using a fully-depleted silicon-on-insulator (FDSOI) process for leading-edge chips it makes at 28- and going on to 20-nm. It remains unclear is whether the deal with Samsung has any implications about ST's commitment to the FDSOI process it has chosen to pioneer itself. ST has been working with Samsung's foundry for some time and the relationship has already produced tape-outs of a dozen system-on-chip devices for mobile, consumer and networking applications. Tape-out represents the completion of the design phase although it can take several months for a chip to pass through manufacturing and be approved for sale. "We have successfully started production of STMicroelectronics' new-generation 32/28nm SoC products," said Kwang-Hyun Kim, executive vice president with Samsung's foundry business unit, in a statement. "A foundry relationship with ST demonstrates our commitment to advanced process technology and our 32/28nm HKMG process-technology leadership. We have aggressively ramped 32/28nm capacity and will continue to deliver the most advanced process solutions to our customers." "In addition to delivering waves of innovative new products, another key to ST's success in each of our target markets is working with industry leaders," said Jean-Marc Chery, chief-technology officer for STMicroelectronics, in the same statement. He added that ST and Samsung had worked together on process development in a body called the International Semiconductor Development Alliance.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1349054580593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:23:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349056143078-82</Id><Title>Going lower - glad I shorted all my stocks!</Title><Msg>INTC sucks and business is bad. going lower - short the hell out of INTC</Msg><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1349056143078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349056675270-83</Id><Topic><Title>Going lower - glad I shorted all my stocks!</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1349056143078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:49:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many shares are you short and at what price? Let's see how you fair. Thx.</Msg><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349056675270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349059439219-84</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH stock price will collapse in 2013 and Apple will dump the girlfriend that got fat and ugly</Title><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1349048780499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:46:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AAPL ain't so sleak anymore either..she'll be in the dumpster for long.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349059439219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 22:43:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349060797419-85</Id><Topic><Title>Going lower - glad I shorted all my stocks!</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1349056143078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:49:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5,000 at 26.62. ;) Going down to at least $18.00.</Msg><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1349060797419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349061919056-86</Id><Topic><Title>this is why its going to 40 2013</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1349032454079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:14:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yepp...that's the reason.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349061919056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:25:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349061955613-87</Id><Topic><Title>More hell for singhlion2001</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1349036423200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And...he's on everyone's IGNORE list!</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349061955613</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:25:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349061987273-88</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH stock price will collapse in 2013 and Apple will dump the girlfriend that got fat and ugly</Title><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1349048780499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:46:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you is da man!</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349061987273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349062060035-89</Id><Topic><Title>Bay Trail Tablets on 22nm next year will be the true ARM-killer.</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349015926038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fabbing for Cisco, and Toyota and Goggola and.....the list goes on and on ... with or without AAPL.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349062060035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:27:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349062142919-90</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Shorts - No Where to Run, No Where to Hide</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1349046867510</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:14:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Normally they hide rocks, but in the dry weather a large number of predators down there are picking them off .</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349062142919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:29:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349062192613-91</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will foundry chips for Toyota, too</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349038775169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a multibillion $$ channel. And it ISN't ONLY Toyota!!!</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1349062192613</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349063741042-92</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will foundry chips for Toyota, too</Title><Username>conmen_brokemen</Username><Timestamp>1349038775169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It realizes it needs to keep its fabs busy to recoup investment. Next big step which is a mental barrier for Intel is fabbing ARM based chips which would be win-win but it would require it to relinquish control over low power. It's high time they retired low power IA and concentrated instead on the dwindling market for high performance microprocessors. Servers are the spark of light in this darkness.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1349063741042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:55:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>