<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-31"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346386946432-1</Id><Topic><Title>Motorola and Intel send invites to Sept. 18 event in London</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346370960346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 19:56:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel's gorilla marketing blitz finally hits the US.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1346386946432</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 00:22:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346386987800-2</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News Shoots, They Score</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346385104176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:51:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"was an apparent attempt to set the world record for the greatest number of blatant lies and misrepresentations slipped into a single political speech." Ryan will only be in the top position for the GOLD until the next speaker. Ryan will then be relegated to SILVER for a solid 2nd place finish. The R-R team however, is an overwhelming favorite for the "pairs" GOLD. There work on the unparallel bars will not be touched for many years.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346386987800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 00:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346391649000-3</Id><Title>Dirty Harry should be renamed...</Title><Msg>'Filthy Harry'. A much better fit to the filthy GOP convention where black folks are considered animals.</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1346391649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 01:40:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346405801525-4</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News Shoots, They Score</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346385104176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:51:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did Ryan call Obama a Felon? Or did he say that Obama caused a woman to die of cancer or did he say Obama hated women? All things the Liberals have accused Mitt of. You guys wrote the book on lies. John Edwards has a book on how to tell the perfect lie coming out soon....</Msg><Username>wall.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346405801525</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 05:36:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346407400000-5</Id><Title>天殺龍神拳</Title><Msg>(EOM)</Msg><Username>hifs44</Username><Timestamp>1346407400000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 06:03:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346410609746-6</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood absolutely KILLED IT at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346381822113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wanna bet that Clint Eastwood actually cost the republicans and lost them votes in the undecided by presenting something without good taste and without good execution thanks to his old age. Its almost easy to imagine that he did it on purpose to hurt them without them knowing it. Now watch Obama lose a bit of %in polls for a couple days and gain it back 2fold after dem convention and taking both Ohio and Florida in November. Keep dreaming that Americans are so moronic to try again what took us here to begin with. The good news for the future is that republicans will soon be a minority in the population simply because of population growth of various groups that dont exactly like them a bit. Unfortunatelyt he party of No doesnt care if they win or lose. They will stall anyway everything. Either republicans change to represent consistently ethical yet conservative values without the hypocrisy and the sucking up to plutocracy (fat chance) or history will remember them as traitors of the American dream. This country has been under a hijack of its democracy from republicans for the past 12+ years (in fact 30+ because the financial house of cards that destroyed and sold out the real economy is a Ronald Reagan job). Either they steal elections and rule to disaster or they stall any progress as minority any way unethically possible by making Washington unable to legislate what is needed. They lie, cheat, distort the truth and are the ultimate hypocrites. The most unethical pseudo Christians ever. They mock Christ's teachings in the most profoundly insulting way. Worse than radical islamofascists. Seriously to all you republicans this is a warning. Either you reclaim your party back from the traitors you have or you will face a violent revolution that will eliminate the hypocrites the hardcore way because the party of NO is running US to the ground and the real patriots will reach their limit soon and get very angry with you and react in seriously violent ways. Watch it happen.</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1346410609746</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 06:56:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346411196273-7</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News Shoots, They Score</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346385104176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:51:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It doesn't really matter. This election should be a referendum on whether the current president has done a good job or not. To that end The current has failed. It doesn't really matter much who he runs against (assuming some minimal qualification standard has been met - and it has). This is the same situation as 2004. The president Bush should not have been reelected because he had failed. I consider myself a liberal person, but I do not change my standards based on the leaning of the individual. BO has failed and does not deserve my vote - and he won't get it. Luckily the republicans were smart enough not to nominate Cain, Bachmann, Trump, Perry, etc.</Msg><Username>cynicalanddisgusted</Username><Timestamp>1346411196273</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 07:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346412046285-8</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Present at Citi Tech Conference Tues 9am</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346261433506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Citi Forum comments from Intel will come before market opening Tuesday. Today is the last trading before the comments.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346412046285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 07:20:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346417611930-9</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News Shoots, They Score</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346385104176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:51:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I consider myself a liberal person" - means what ? in your opinion when someone says they are a liberal, what does that mean? I think it means you're for high taxes and gov't programs but I want to know what you mean.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1346417611930</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 08:53:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346417736876-10</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood absolutely KILLED IT at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346381822113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're a racist, a white hater, am i right? you need a helping hand, admit it, you can't do it on your own. that should be the left's motto. Left is pro union because they need to band together and extort higher wages. How else do dropouts make it?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1346417736876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 08:55:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346417790043-11</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News Shoots, They Score</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346385104176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:51:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#1 liar Teddy is gone, thankfully.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1346417790043</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 08:56:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346419006665-12</Id><Title>Next Support</Title><Msg>Next support down is $21.60 unless INTC can get the engine started.</Msg><Username>nj2h</Username><Timestamp>1346419006665</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:16:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346419743266-13</Id><Topic><Title>China fake GDP with empty cities about to crash with hard landing???</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1346414391672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 07:59:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shill boy, maybe if you got a job instead of working on world economic collapse every day you might see things differently. America's problem is that we have far too many non-contributors like you. You are a non-productive drag on the economy. Just like all the lucies. Intel actually produces products with real values, making the world a better place and providing a lot of people with meaningful work and professions. You and the big Wall Street firms spend every day trying to transfer the wealth created by hard working people into your pockets by manipulation, high-speed trading, distortion of information distributed to the media, and the like. What was the line in the old Wall Street trading commercial? "We make money the old-fashioned way - we earn it." You sure don't hear that any more. When was the last day you made an honest buck, shill boy? We won't hold our breath waiting for an answer...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346419743266</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:29:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346419973752-14</Id><Topic><Title>Next Support</Title><Username>nj2h</Username><Timestamp>1346419006665</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:16:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>better focus on resistance given the move up from 24.15.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1346419973752</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346420122041-15</Id><Topic><Title>Suggestions for a New Alias</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346354994425</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about "portaprincedollmaker2" ? You've always done well sticking it to the intellitubbies, hehehe. You can loom over the intellitubbie's likeness and your posts can be the virtual incantations delivering them to agony and penpricks at the same time, yes ?</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1346420122041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:35:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346420978026-16</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News Shoots, They Score</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346385104176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:51:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fox news did not say that Ryan told any lies. They printed a columnist who did- because they are fair and balanced. Ryan told nothing but the truth. Obumbler did steal billions from medicare with illusionary savings to replace the money. Doctors will not do more Medicare work for less money. They are already losing money and refusing patients. Ryan suggested saving that will stay within medicare and save medicare. The savings would come by using market forces, something the Democrats do not understand. All of Ryan's other "lies" are similar truths that are being spun by clueless Democrats both in the party and in the press. Just because you can't handle the truth, you don't get your own version of reality. I am sure that the left is going crazy spinning Clint Eastwood's little "conversation", but he had some great one liners. Biden is the "intellect" of the Democrat party and Obumbler is getting just like him. Just a couple smiles with bodies behind them. Why don't you get back to discussing INTC? I may have to put you on ignore and that would be a shame. I know your brain has been washed from living in CA, but you can get help.</Msg><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1346420978026</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:49:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346421274047-17</Id><Title>Coming Up</Title><Msg>IDF: A week from tomorrow Motorola Smartphone Announcement: September 18th Windows 8: October Looks like it's going to get a whole lot harder for the big firms on Wall Street to suppress the Intel stock price. Wireless charging is getting some nice press now. From EETimes: "But the leverage comes when Intel embeds the ability to charge nearby Intel-based smartphones from the ultrabook and denies access to the technology to other smartphone makers. In this way Intel could start to use the provision of mobile charging capability on Intel-based computers to enhance the desirability of mobile phones and tablet computers also based on its processors. Plonk your intel-phone down on the desk next to your ultrabook and it is fully charged and synched up when you are ready to go walkabout. Does that sound good? But if you put your iPhone or non-Intel Android smartphone down next to your ultrabook, or even next to your Mac notebook, it doesn't charge up. How uncool is that?"</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346421274047</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:54:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346421745388-18</Id><Topic><Title>We Must Have Bottomed</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346374845448</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:00:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cockroaches get it right again...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346421745388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:02:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346422102632-19</Id><Topic><Title>I Bought Intel at $28 When Wally Recommended It</Title><Username>bozoweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346349381635</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:56:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lucies head back to the woodshed. They all missed the bottom...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346422102632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:08:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346422249700-20</Id><Title>Close over $25 today</Title><Msg>Short covering due to announcement this weekend</Msg><Username>lkphomes</Username><Timestamp>1346422249700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:10:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346422340820-21</Id><Topic><Title>Close over $25 today</Title><Username>lkphomes</Username><Timestamp>1346422249700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:10:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>doubtful. nice bounce off rsi 30, INTC green, qqq red, a welcome change?</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1346422340820</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:12:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346422728972-22</Id><Title>Make 50 percent on your money in one day--seriously with INTC Sept 26 calls</Title><Msg>Buy INTC Sep 26 calls right now--- sell on Monday with 50 percent gain guaranteed</Msg><Username>fridaydogus</Username><Timestamp>1346422728972</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:18:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346422749856-23</Id><Topic><Title>We Must Have Bottomed</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346374845448</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:00:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wallis: You are soooooooo full of crap. You've been calling bottoms and predicting new highs for years here and for years the stock has been unchanged, Recently you claimed to be to busy to post because you were working 80 hours a week. Do you really have a job? You're posting frequency never slowed down. The only job that you may have is as a paid Intel pumper, If you insist on posting here 'round the clock, at least be sensible. Stocks go up AND DOWN but Intel shares have been rangebound for 10 years. Your non-stop chants of "Intel is good for 30" and "a huge honking $5 miss is already built in" are nothing more than your own wet dreams Give it a rest, pumpwad!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346422749856</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346423436359-24</Id><Topic><Title>We Must Have Bottomed</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346374845448</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:00:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But he is right. We have bottomed....good call W.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1346423436359</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:30:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346424135651-25</Id><Title>INTC is definitely not looking very good. Study why.</Title><Msg>Has any person taken a look at the articles being issued? Fascinating information that will assist any investor or trader. xtalstore.biz/INTC</Msg><Username>mcnairrobert339</Username><Timestamp>1346424135651</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:42:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346424336258-26</Id><Topic><Title>We Must Have Bottomed</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346374845448</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:00:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Do you really have a job? You're posting frequency never slowed down.....If you insist on posting here 'round the clock" I hope he's not an air traffic controller.</Msg><Username>son_of_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1346424336258</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:45:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346424343173-27</Id><Topic><Title>We Must Have Bottomed</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346374845448</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:00:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only person who posts more than Wallis is you. The difference between you two is that Wallis is overly positive ("pumps") Intel and posts clips from news articles. But you SPAM the board with personal taunts and insults. The pumpwad has more information in his worst posting than you do in your best.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346424343173</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:45:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346424710171-28</Id><Title>Why is Intel even up today?</Title><Msg>You mean the greedy mega rich are satisfied with their PUT gains? With Apple trading at $675, Intel should be trading at $250.</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1346424710171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346424754268-29</Id><Topic><Title>We Must Have Bottomed</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346374845448</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:00:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope he's not an air traffic controller. --------------------- He doesn't have the grit, the brains, the common sense or the emotional stability to be an air-traffic controller. He's a janitor.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346424754268</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346425120918-30</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood absolutely KILLED IT at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346381822113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even if you hate republicans, do you seriously want another 4 yrs of Obama? This guy is obviously incompetent. He plays golf mostly and divides the country with his class warfare. At least Romney has a good looking wife. Obama's wife looks like chewbacca, also known as "chewie".</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346425120918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:58:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346425614848-31</Id><Title>BARRONS- Intel: Argus Cuts Q3, Year View on Euro Weakness, Ultrabook Slowness</Title><Msg>August 31, 2012, 10:54 A.M. ET . Intel: Argus Cuts Q3, Year View on Euro Weakness, Ultrabook Slowness</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346425614848</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:06:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346425727998-32</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is definitely not looking very good. Study why.</Title><Username>mcnairrobert339</Username><Timestamp>1346424135651</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:42:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looking at it as we speak.</Msg><Username>matthewsthomas14</Username><Timestamp>1346425727998</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:08:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346425851757-33</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood absolutely KILLED IT at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346381822113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you have no idea how sick he is, yes he wants that turd for another 4</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1346425851757</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346425907729-34</Id><Topic><Title>BARRONS- Intel: Argus Cuts Q3, Year View on Euro Weakness, Ultrabook Slowness</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346425614848</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some are hoping they will meet the low end and avoid a preannouncement. Not sure if it makes any difference. Intel: Argus Cuts Q3, Year View on Euro Weakness, Ultrabook Slowness By Tiernan Ray Tags PC ultrabook Windows Argus Research’s Jim Kelleher this morning joins the discussion this week on whether Intel (INTC) will meet this quarter’s expectations on the Street. The current consensus is $14.25 billion and 60 cents per share in profit. Kelleher, who has a Buy rating on Intel and a $34 price target, thinks Intel will report just under the midpoint of its forecast range for $13.8 billion to $14.8 billion, or slightly less than $14.2 billion. Kelleher has reduced his estimates after concluding that the company is contending with economic pressures, as well as the slow ramp of “ultrabook” computers it has been endorsing, and the slow development of tablets based on Microsoft‘s (MSFT) Windows: Intel may deliver calendar 3Q12 revenue toward the low end of guidance, in our view, based on Persistent macro-economic headwinds buffeting the global economy and particularly Europe. In addition to weaker revenue, Intel could see a less-favorable CPU mix, based on signs that the Ultrabook – which uses some of Intel’s highest-end PC processors – has not really caught on yet. We expect Intel’s overall volumes to remain reasonably good, based on emerging economy demand; but we expect the Ultrabook ramp to be slower in emerging economies compared with mature nations. Thus, Intel’s emerging economy mix is likely to remain below company margins. In addition to economic headwinds and competitive pressures from tablets, Ultrabook is being impacted by its lack of alignment with the Windows 8 launch, which will not take place until October 2012. Based on past precedent, Windows 8 will likely ramp slowly, with slightly better early uptake by consumers; enterprise buying of PCs with Windows 8 will likely be pushed into 2013.</Msg><Username>romekay</Username><Timestamp>1346425907729</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:11:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346426208294-35</Id><Topic><Title>BARRONS- Intel: Argus Cuts Q3, Year View on Euro Weakness, Ultrabook Slowness</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346425614848</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two weeks ago, my one-star puppy would have already given my message about 100 one-star ratings in an effort to make the message unreadable to many people . Oh well, one-star puppy, you and your myriad aliases can always give my messages about 100 "thumbs down" ratings.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346426208294</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:16:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346426269397-36</Id><Topic><Title>We Must Have Bottomed</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346374845448</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:00:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could well be that a short term bottom was put in yesterday. Wally's problem is that is that he has never been able to pick and sell a top. he just rides the merry go round</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1346426269397</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346426437906-37</Id><Title>CNBC PETE THE CON MAN BUY INTC AT $29.25, LOOK WERE INTC IS TODAY UNDER $25</Title><Msg>Cnbc pete the con man buy intc at $29.25, look were intc is today under $25</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346426437906</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:20:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346426603743-38</Id><Topic><Title>We Must Have Bottomed</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346374845448</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:00:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could well be -------------- The above words never came into play in any of wallwad's messages. I'd cut him some slack if he wasn't so cocksure and so cockwrong all the time</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346426603743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:23:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346426632165-39</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC PETE THE CON MAN BUY INTC AT $29.25, LOOK WERE INTC IS TODAY UNDER $25</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346426437906</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:20:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>POOOOOOR Baby!!!! Did you listen to Pete, buy at $29.25 and not make your own decisions? You shouldn't blame your failure on Pete.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346426632165</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:23:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346426700826-40</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC PETE THE CON MAN BUY INTC AT $29.25, LOOK WERE INTC IS TODAY UNDER $25</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346426437906</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:20:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wiil see if INTC goes under $23, Going to miss big time, Look at HPQ,DELL</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346426700826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:25:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346427082178-41</Id><Title>Romney chooses Eastwood to open up prime time on the big night.</Title><Msg>Could have chosen anyone. Could have had a war hero. Could have had a famous woman. Could have had a great Republican. Could have had so so many but the Romney team and Rombo chose Clint Eastwood who is a Hollywood leftwing nutcase. HAAAA HAAAAA Did Clint Sneak in to wreck the night? HAAA HAAAA He was the manchurian speaker on the night making Romney un noticed by most. Not only that--he said nothing that made sense and was talking dirty to an empty chair. HAAAA HAAA Way to go Mitt. You are incompetent.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1346427082178</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:31:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346427109277-42</Id><Title>Lets see if INTC can go under $23 insiders know and are selling big time, Look at HPQ and DELL earnings miss</Title><Msg>Lets see if INTC can go under $23 insiders know and are selling big time, Look at HPQ and DELL earnings miss</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346427109277</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:31:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427260426-43</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC PETE THE CON MAN BUY INTC AT $29.25, LOOK WERE INTC IS TODAY UNDER $25</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346426437906</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:20:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YEPPER! We will see. i think that intel is set to talk on Tuesday. you only have a couple hours left to bash Intel before market closes. HPQ and DELL did not miss. they got pessamistic about Q3 when they reported their Q2. When Intel talks on Tuesday, they will have a better view of the future than either HPQ or DELL had. intel also knows what the HPQ/DELL competitors are building and ording.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346427260426</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:34:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427410622-44</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood absolutely KILLED IT at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346381822113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes we need Obama for Romney is all lies. He is just their to let the rich pay no taxes and turn the US into a 3rd world country with no more middleclass. Just all poor and a few filthy rich! US will be just like South Africia countries with Romney.</Msg><Username>sirtom99</Username><Timestamp>1346427410622</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:36:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427432728-45</Id><Topic><Title>Romney chooses Eastwood to open up prime time on the big night.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1346427082178</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:31:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm pretty much apolitical, waldung, but I will say this... At least Romney looks like a president.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346427432728</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:37:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346427645373-46</Id><Title>Better cover shortie Sept 26 calls will soon be in the money</Title><Msg>$27 by next Thursday</Msg><Username>fridaydogus</Username><Timestamp>1346427645373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427647564-47</Id><Topic><Title>Romney chooses Eastwood to open up prime time on the big night.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1346427082178</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:31:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And acts like one. More important he has experience and success....Only one running that has.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1346427647564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427681871-48</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC PETE THE CON MAN BUY INTC AT $29.25, LOOK WERE INTC IS TODAY UNDER $25</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346426437906</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:20:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Insiders are sell big time, Get out while you still can, but you won't and you will cry later</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346427681871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:41:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346427802661-49</Id><Title>Intel ---- $22</Title><Msg>next week. DELL, HPQ and Marvell gave you a preview last week. When they officially lower estimates, don't act surprised. $22</Msg><Username>whynot327</Username><Timestamp>1346427802661</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427819537-50</Id><Topic><Title>Lets see if INTC can go under $23 insiders know and are selling big time, Look at HPQ and DELL earnings miss</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346427109277</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TIC TOC get ready for the drop</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346427819537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346427907693-51</Id><Title>Told you to buy $26 Sept INTC calls made mucho dinero already</Title><Msg>Don't wait--maybe earn another 50 on your money in 2 days</Msg><Username>fridaydogus</Username><Timestamp>1346427907693</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:45:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346428208298-52</Id><Title>THE FED IS THE SAME AS THE BOY WHO CRIED WOLF I AM GOING TO DO SOMETHING I AM, I REALLY AM</Title><Msg>The fed is the same as the boy who cried wolf i am going to do something i am, i really am</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346428208298</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:50:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346428216263-53</Id><Title>I made 40 percent rate of return on INTC Sept 26 calls in 2 hours more to come</Title><Msg>cashed in $4000 gain on $10,000 investment in 2 hours</Msg><Username>fridaydogus</Username><Timestamp>1346428216263</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:50:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346428451428-54</Id><Topic><Title>THE FED IS THE SAME AS THE BOY WHO CRIED WOLF I AM GOING TO DO SOMETHING I AM, I REALLY AM</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346428208298</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the fed every does anything. Which they can't until the bombs start dropping on iran</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346428451428</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:54:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346428554149-55</Id><Title>Bernanke Gives Market QE3 Reasons to Rally</Title><Msg>August 31, 2012, 11:28 AM . Bernanke Gives Market QE3 Reasons to Rally . MarketBeat HOME PAGE By Steven Russolillo FactSet The Dow’s intraday chart (click for bigger image). This is just about everything the bulls could have wanted. After some choppy trading immediately following the release of Bernanke’s speech, stocks are trading around session highs. Investors are finding comfort in the Fed Chairman’s comments that more stimulus could be coming sooner than later. “Bernanke left the door wide open to more QE,” says Alan Ruskin, a strategist at Deutsche Bank DBK.XE +5.06%. “I think the US equity market has either the benefit of stronger US data coming down the pike, or QE3, and is relatively well protected, so this is good for macro risk.” The Dow recently rose 137 points, or 1.1%, to 13138, with Friday’s gains pushing the blue-chip index back into positive territory for the month of August. All 30 Dow components are trading higher, led higher by Intel INTC +2.68%, Hewlett-Packard HPQ +1.55% and Microsoft MSFT +1.68%. But Friday’s action has been choppier than usual, at least compared to the market action throughout the summer. The Dow was up more than 100 points before Bernanke’s speech was released, then pared gains and was up only 20 points minutes after the release and now has reverted back toward the day’s highs. Perhaps no explicit mention of QE3 prompted the initial downdraft. But now, the consensus seems to think Bernanke’s speech did nothing to change the view that more unconventional accommodation is coming soon. The euro is also jumping, pushing back above $1.26, while the dollar continues to fall. “The U.S. dollar will remain marginally vulnerable to an ongoing euro short squeeze,” Ruskin says. Furthermore, Dan Greenhaus, chief global strategist at BTIG, said Bernanke’s speech didn’t dissuade his view that the Fed is likely to extend its rate-guidance adjustments. Greenhaus also thinks there’s a greater than 50% chance of another bond-buying program, or QE3, to be announced at the September meeting. “The speech doesn’t necessarily add anything new to the current debate about what the Fed may or may not do in September,” Greenhaus says. “It colors in slightly the Chairman’s thinking, but after the last FOMC minutes, it would have been hard, short of outright saying ‘QE3 is coming’ for the Chairman to boost expectations much further. In that regard, we are unsurprised.” For more MarketBeat and other streaming markets coverage from The Wall Street Journal.....</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346428554149</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346428942712-56</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is definitely not looking very good. Study why.</Title><Username>mcnairrobert339</Username><Timestamp>1346424135651</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:42:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Regular spam. not as good as LUCY SPAM.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346428942712</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:02:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346429011213-57</Id><Title>Hay Look PETE THE CON MAN IS ON CNBC TOLD YOU TO BUY INTC AT $29.25 while he sold and his GS buddies</Title><Msg>Hay Look PETE THE CON MAN IS ON CNBC TOLD YOU TO BUY INTC AT $29.25 while he sold and his GS buddies</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346429011213</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:03:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346429054351-58</Id><Topic><Title>Close over $25 today</Title><Username>lkphomes</Username><Timestamp>1346422249700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:10:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doubtful??? Nice call. Over 26 by Tuesday</Msg><Username>fridaydogus</Username><Timestamp>1346429054351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:04:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346429292195-59</Id><Title>PETE TOLD YOU TO BUY WFC , LOOK OUT HE IS SELLING SHORT WFC</Title><Msg>Pete told you to buy wfc , look out he is selling short wfc</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346429292195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:08:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346429298415-60</Id><Title>PETE TOLD YOU TO BUY WFC , LOOK OUT HE IS SELLING SHORT WFC</Title><Msg>Pete told you to buy wfc , look out he is selling short wfc</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346429298415</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346429967933-61</Id><Title>Yay! light at the end of the Tunnel</Title><Msg>AAPL $750 MSFT $35 INTC $29. Why would stocks go down in the face of Windows 8, iPhone5 and an improving world economy? And don't give me that #$%$ the worlds going to end economically. You starting to look silly as Europe fades from the picture and was not as bad as every doom and gloom sayer said it was. (iPhone, 5 iPad 7", Windows phone 8, Windows 8, Office 13 Surface tablet, many more tablets, phones, Apps, and other technologies coming down the pike real fast.)</Msg><Username>barrylam2000</Username><Timestamp>1346429967933</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:19:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346430588717-62</Id><Title>$34 by November</Title><Msg>slam dunk!</Msg><Username>texasjk99</Username><Timestamp>1346430588717</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:29:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346430827147-63</Id><Topic><Title>THE FED IS THE SAME AS THE BOY WHO CRIED WOLF I AM GOING TO DO SOMETHING I AM, I REALLY AM</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346428208298</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TIC TOC WAITING FOR THE BOMBS TO DROP ON IRAN</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346430827147</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346430914561-64</Id><Topic><Title>Close over $25 today</Title><Username>lkphomes</Username><Timestamp>1346422249700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:10:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>H'mm, did the markets close already?</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1346430914561</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:35:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346431505018-65</Id><Topic><Title>THE FED IS THE SAME AS THE BOY WHO CRIED WOLF I AM GOING TO DO SOMETHING I AM, I REALLY AM</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346428208298</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>make em good!!!</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346431505018</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346431627555-66</Id><Topic><Title>PETE TOLD YOU TO BUY WFC , LOOK OUT HE IS SELLING SHORT WFC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346429298415</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:08:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be very afraid!!!! of his recommendations.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346431627555</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:47:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346432283649-67</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood absolutely KILLED IT at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346381822113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you took all the wealth from the rich people and re-distributed it to everyone in the U.S, it would hardly make a dent. The poor people would waste it on cigarettes, alcohol, drugs and prostitutes. After that, the country would just be all poor. Obama will eventually turn our country into another Greece, all lazy people, retiring in their 40's, wanting a gov't handout. Obama sees votes when he talks about the middle class. Obama is rich, he is playing you.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346432283649</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:58:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346432431860-68</Id><Title>Poor Old Clint Eastwood and Romney.</Title><Msg>What a sad epitaph for a moderate republican celebrity. Sometimes a man's got to know his limitations.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1346432431860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346432909498-69</Id><Title>Wallis Aliases</Title><Msg>Any alias that includes any of the following words is a wallis alias. he has hundreds of aliases. "monkey" "roadkill" "cornholed" Please add your favorite wallis aliases to this list</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346432909498</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:08:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346433268082-70</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Old Clint Eastwood and Romney.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1346432431860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They did just fine and their limitations pale compared to the chosen one.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1346433268082</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:14:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346433743727-71</Id><Topic><Title>Lets see if INTC can go under $23 insiders know and are selling big time, Look at HPQ and DELL earnings miss</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346427109277</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good old cnbc pump and dump told you to buy at the high of the day</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346433743727</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346434084859-72</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Old Clint Eastwood and Romney.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1346432431860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next good laugh will be the VP debates. We'll see how out of touch the GOP really is.</Msg><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1346434084859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:28:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346434619782-73</Id><Topic><Title>Intel/McAfee building quite the porfolio</Title><Username>herbal_dud</Username><Timestamp>1346157182694</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:33:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet you've forgotten a lot about computers and other parts of your life. All kinda hazy now? No, all that pot you smoked never caught up to you, did it? So, what you are telling us that not even Symantec and McAfee want to look at you? What do you do with all your time. Oh, silly me, I know, you spend it on here insulting people who disagree with you. No, you're not bitter. But thanks for responding so harshly to the unemployed comment. Hit a nerve, huh? What do wives think about husbands who are unemployed for long periods of time? I mean, honestly, makes you look like less of a man in their eyes, don't you agree?</Msg><Username>intel_4ever</Username><Timestamp>1346434619782</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:36:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346434950083-74</Id><Title>Watch the close TSP money moving b ack to G fund or cash, cash , cash, cash</Title><Msg>Watch the close TSP money moving b ack to G fund or cash, cash , cash, cash</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346434950083</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346435579194-75</Id><Topic><Title>Hay Look PETE THE CON MAN IS ON CNBC TOLD YOU TO BUY INTC AT $29.25 while he sold and his GS buddies</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346429011213</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:03:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can thank Pete the con man for the drop from 29.25 and going to $22.50 very soon</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346435579194</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:52:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346435957320-76</Id><Topic><Title>Hay Look PETE THE CON MAN IS ON CNBC TOLD YOU TO BUY INTC AT $29.25 while he sold and his GS buddies</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1346429011213</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:03:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>conmaker77 is a PETE</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346435957320</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346436398587-77</Id><Title>A Wall Street Shill by any other Name is still a Wall Street Shill</Title><Msg>flashcrashcoming = coinmaker77</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346436398587</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346437486857-78</Id><Title>Intel to $30 by year-end</Title><Msg>Booooooooooooooooooooyyyyyyyyyyyyaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhh</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1346437486857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:24:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346438451006-79</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to $30 by year-end</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1346437486857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:24:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"sujit_98" is one of pumpwad weaver's aliases.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346438451006</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346438980217-80</Id><Title>Just in!</Title><Msg>Goldman upgrades to buy with price target of 35 by end of year.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346438980217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:49:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346438990459-81</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Old Clint Eastwood and Romney.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1346432431860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I heard the surprise speaker for the DNC was Eva Longoria. LOL! You guys have ruined America.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346438990459</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:49:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346439015897-82</Id><Title>Intel to $45 by 2014</Title><Msg>boooooooooooooooooyyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1346439015897</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:50:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346439060053-83</Id><Title>Maybe you don't know this</Title><Msg>but Wall Street has easy access to all stop orders placed so it can figure the best time to collectively take them out and buy at the low for big profits. Wall Street sees all and knows all you do.You think your account info is private? Hahahahahahaha. Guess again. Retails are dog meat to WS.</Msg><Username>bobbobwhite</Username><Timestamp>1346439060053</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:51:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346439063156-84</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood absolutely KILLED IT at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346381822113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What we don't want is four years of people who pander to the rich. Four years of a focus on tax cuts. Four years of excessive defense spending. Four years of punishing the middle class to make the rich richer. Four years of re-trying the useless strategy of cutting taxes and regulations to create jobs. The Republican Party is in the total control of the lunatic fringe. Michael Steele was excluded from the convention. Jon Huntsman was excluded from the convention. Ron Paul wasn't allowed to speak and his signs were removed. Herman Cain was excluded from the convention. And none of those in control thought using Clint Eastwood as the poster boy was anything but wonderful. An old, angry, rich white man. In a recent poll Romney got zero percent of the black vote. Zero. Now Republicans are working the same magic on Hispanics and women. Huntsman and Jeb Bush have both warned recently that the Republican Party will self-destruct unless it becomes less exclusionary. The rich are wreaking the country. By representing only them, Republicans are insuring they will never win another election. Nor should they...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346439063156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:51:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346439188084-85</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood absolutely KILLED IT at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346381822113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally, you are a complete idiot that has made it clear that you are broke, and hate other because they aren't. You're a sad little man.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346439188084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:53:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346439519495-86</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood absolutely KILLED IT at the DNC</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346381822113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>best description of wallis follows: Envy: "Envy is best defined as a resentful emotion that "occurs when a person lacks another's (perceived) superior quality, achievement or possession and wishes that the other lacked it."[</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346439519495</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:58:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346439681014-87</Id><Topic><Title>Just in!</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346438980217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:49:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oops, sorry, price target should be $38,</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346439681014</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:01:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346440034441-88</Id><Topic><Title>Just in!</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346438980217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:49:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Link please?</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1346440034441</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:07:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346440154049-89</Id><Topic><Title>Just in!</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346438980217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:49:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't remember where I read it. Recommend, though, that you "bet the ranch" on this.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346440154049</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:09:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346440228600-90</Id><Title>Look at Wallisweaver show how pathetic a human being he is</Title><Msg>He HATES rich people......Uncountable millions of dollars are donated by rich people to search for cures for childrens diseases, cancer, world hunger, etc...those people don't spend their time on a yahoo board. Then there's Wally, spends all his time here and helps nobody. What a guy! What a COMPLETE and UTTER DISGRACE of a man. But hey, if he wants to hang out here and beg for QE3, that's his gig !!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346440228600</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346440393833-91</Id><Topic><Title>Look at Wallisweaver show how pathetic a human being he is</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346440228600</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So...., do you like Mr. Weaver then?</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346440393833</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:13:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346440455165-92</Id><Title>FINAL HOUR FADE(FHF) IN PROGRESS!</Title><Msg>please stand by.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346440455165</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:14:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346440505011-93</Id><Topic><Title>Look at Wallisweaver show how pathetic a human being he is</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346440228600</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>then it makes more sense.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346440505011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:15:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346440790151-94</Id><Topic><Title>Look at Wallisweaver show how pathetic a human being he is</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346440228600</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis is a small-minded, green-with-envy, middle/lower-middle class twit.</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346440790151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346441210693-95</Id><Title>Lucy Needs to Begin his Final Hour Fade to Black</Title><Msg>Lucy posted how many hundreds of messages about me saying people who bought at $24 would be fine. And then Intel went to $29+. And he shut up for a while. But then he got his little, tiny ego all brushed off, took it to the tire store and re-inflated it, got up every morning and told himself that he really wasn't an idiot and hadn't totally humiliated himself again and again and again with his posting stupidity. I put him and all his many alias on ignore a long time ago. Unfortunately I still see replies and topics. I can tell without even reading his garbage that he is posting the same things yet again. Like the 10-year statistic he trots out every time he can't find anything in the last nine years to bash Intel with. Now he is re-cycling the same old "24" garbage but has replaced $24 with $30. And he doesn't think anyone has or will notice. I suppose we will get to do this again at $36 and again at $42 and so on. Lucy is not a smart man. And he doesn't write well which is why he has to re-cycle his material and has to stick to things he can handle like saying "Reeeeeeeeeeeeeeedddddd." He bashed Intel constantly from 17.67 to almost 30. Years ago I told him it was all about the fabrication. He didn't listen. He's not a smart man. There's only a couple of possibilities as to why he is here daily embarrassing himself: 1.) He's getting paid. 2.) Intel fired him or ran over his dog or put his start-up out of business. 3.) He's psychologically damaged. 4.) He's not a smart man. 5.) Some combination of one through four. Frankly I could care less. I have him and his aliases on ignore. My world view is not something that Lucy will every affect. But I have to say that those of you who don't yet have Lucy on ignore I have to classify as equally lame. When you lie down with dogs you are bound to get fleas. I wish you the same financial success as anyone would enjoy who had listened to Lucy. None. He's not a smart man. And those who take him seriously aren't either...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346441210693</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:26:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346441221863-96</Id><Topic><Title>Just in!</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346438980217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:49:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No linkeee #$%$eeee</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1346441221863</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346441455827-97</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Old Clint Eastwood and Romney.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1346432431860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>biden gonna look like a real dunce after ryan gets to him at the debates... common, stand up chuck...</Msg><Username>snickbobby</Username><Timestamp>1346441455827</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346441741626-98</Id><Topic><Title>Look at Wallisweaver show how pathetic a human being he is</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346440228600</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's really sad. I've tried to give him the benefit of the doubt, but he constantly posts his hatred for rich people. He's the worst kind of man - one that loaths seeing others happy instead of being happy for them. Total dweeb. No surprise he is a democrat.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346441741626</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:35:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346441774448-99</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Old Clint Eastwood and Romney.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1346432431860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, may not be ruined but they are sure working on it...Hey, intc is up nicely. What a day. And Romney will be ahead in polls tomorrow.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1346441774448</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:36:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346441775996-100</Id><Topic><Title>Just in!</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346438980217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:49:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Am rewarded by Intel for pumping their stock. Get sent a prostitute once weekly. So, please buy so I can continue getting serviced.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346441775996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:36:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346442090640-101</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy Needs to Begin his Final Hour Fade to Black</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346441210693</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:26:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have him and his aliases on ignore ------------ In addition to all your other issues, you are a LIAR,</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346442090640</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346442543218-102</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy Needs to Begin his Final Hour Fade to Black</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1346441210693</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:26:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the best thing about the final hour fade is that there is only one more hour of high frequency lucy.spam!!! then he kicks into low frequency mode.</Msg><Username>lucy.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346442543218</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346442692324-103</Id><Topic><Title>Just in!</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346438980217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:49:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet they send you the $50 special...</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1346442692324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346442706466-104</Id><Title>More good news Tuesday.</Title><Msg>Stay tuned, INTC might go higher.</Msg><Username>hedgecutter10</Username><Timestamp>1346442706466</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346442838128-105</Id><Title>To the moon on Tuesday</Title><Msg>Better cover AH</Msg><Username>fridaydogus</Username><Timestamp>1346442838128</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346443141364-106</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Old Clint Eastwood and Romney.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1346432431860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You lose on both points made. One day does not dispel weakness, as INTC is still way down from recent prcie dump, And Romney will fall further behind as America better sees the doddery old people who support him, like Clint(is that still my name?)Eastwood....... "Hey, did I ever tell you about when I was a boy?" Yawn, yes you did, and did you know Jesus?</Msg><Username>bobbobwhite</Username><Timestamp>1346443141364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:59:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346443578126-107</Id><Topic><Title>Just in!</Title><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346438980217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:49:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, I get the high class call girl. So please, buy, don't want to get downgraded to the $20 crack head.</Msg><Username>kblank657</Username><Timestamp>1346443578126</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:06:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346443924714-108</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Old Clint Eastwood and Romney.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1346432431860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>intel and romney will be just fine. Makes it easy to go against such a poor record.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1346443924714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:12:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346444760197-109</Id><Title>I Added 10K Shares Today</Title><Msg>Were you a buyer today?</Msg><Username>crazy.wally</Username><Timestamp>1346444760197</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:26:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346447628304-110</Id><Title>bullish kicker pattern</Title><Msg>bounced off of 24.15 strongly tells me it made an important bottom.</Msg><Username>greghassen</Username><Timestamp>1346447628304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346450663812-111</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Lucy are the same guy</Title><Username>wally.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346448724124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:32:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'm thinking they may be one person but if their not which one is worst?</Msg><Username>ramalamalongdong</Username><Timestamp>1346450663812</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346450725393-112</Id><Topic><Title>Look at Wallisweaver show how pathetic a human being he is</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346440228600</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell me how much of that 85% of the wealth of US owned by the top 20% or the 40% owned by the top 1% is given to charities per year or per decade. Because if its like some 0.1% then all i have to say is that the biggest charity of them all is the middle class and poor that work in order to sustain that collapsing plutocracy which is easily worthy of 7 tril $ per year in hard work none of which ends back to the wealth of that 80% because it all goes out to life expenses (ie private companies that see it as income lots of which ends up to rich guys that own them) unlike the rich (not the self made ones first generation wealth that are creating it now, those are celebrated and respected if they do not cheat to win) that accumulate often without working (or working from a position of power and total control and no hard conditions) and who rarely end up spending more than 25-30%of their income in anything that goes back to society. You tell me how much of the real value of a society that 7 tril per year is due to the hard work of the bottom 80% that own only 15% of total wealth. You wanna talk about resentment of the rich. #$%$ Lets talk about something else. Lets talk about resentment of what they do with their money instead. Which unlike say companies like intel that put a ton of it to research and top quality efforts and even shareholders they simply accumulate that money to feed hedge funds to attack the markets to manipulate the system to send it overseas and fund other countries and all kinds of things that are self serving and unpatriotic and have nothing to do with local JOB CREATION. And you punks have the audacity to want to attack Obama for a socialist or whatever #$%$ crap. Talk about the punk losers calling the top kid a failure. How about the ignorant imbecile traitors calling those that love their country welfare nation and other insults. How about you morons show exactly how the rich in this country actually help society and deliver true work back to the system (taxed so little) instead of simply spending time to figure out how to party, consume drugs and prostitutes, corrupt others, spend money overseas and send jo#$%$ there, close businesses , short the market and all kinds of unpatriotic money making ideas. Charity??? 7 tril per year work of the 80% is the real charity. Its the true wealth transfer that has nothing to do with the transfer of land or cash but its the transfer of human life, pure human life (the value of your time of living in this planet, the value of your dreams and promises) transferred away to those that do the least for their country and only for a bit of an effect to keep face have the charities and the well timed behavior to cover the real self not for true ethical su#$%$tance. There are rich that do indeed help this country and generate jo#$%$ and then promote research and good charities and are an example for us all. Republicans, Democrats whatever they are, they do something and have worked for it. But tell me how much of the top20% are these really and what quality will their kids deliver??? And there are also poor that are lazy and uneducated and not working. But really who actually tried to force them to work and gave them an opportunity to work on something that will make them feel good about themselves and have an effect of contribution to themselves and society through honest work. You wan to really help a society, illuminate its poor and give them some chance to prove themselves and make the middle class feel secure and capable to start up small businesses. Create jo#$%$ and opportunity for them and educate their kids properly. Assist them only when they truly need it and mostly in the form of true opportunity to do something to fill their time with real creative employment. Its ok, lose a little bit of profit that goes to Asia and employ people here instead. You will not have huge profits but will have a stable society that after all is the reason you are rich. How many of the rich are the type instead that fund political campaigns that promote lies, manipulate the truth and have assisted in hijacking our democracy by stalling any progress and rejecting any creative idea, simply proving daily they are the bankrollers of the party of NO. NO to America party. Are these the rich and their lackeys you are proud of?</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1346450725393</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:05:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346451352545-113</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Old Clint Eastwood and Romney.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1346432431860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fact that people are talking today about how Clint hammered Obama equals Mission Accomplished. Expect a 5-point pop from RNC.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1346451352545</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:15:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346451450863-114</Id><Title>I bought another 10K shares at $24.20 yesterday</Title><Msg>The smart move is to average down in this area. Will buy a NYC apt. with my dividend check next week. Life is good.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1346451450863</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346451518714-115</Id><Topic><Title>Look at Wallisweaver show how pathetic a human being he is</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346440228600</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'm reading this thread with interest and i'm wondering what your guidelines are for rich. what do you guys consider rich? just curious. thanks</Msg><Username>ramalamalongdong</Username><Timestamp>1346451518714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:18:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346452388384-116</Id><Topic><Title>I bought another 10K shares at $24.20 yesterday</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1346451450863</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOU ARE SO SMART. CONGRATULATIONS.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1346452388384</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:33:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346452534696-117</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Old Clint Eastwood and Romney.</Title><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1346432431860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:00:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It just amazes me that it is even close. Been a bad bad bad four years. How could anyone want more?</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1346452534696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:35:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346452803763-118</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis Aliases</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346432909498</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:08:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've lost count, but my ignore list is over a page long with just one posters mutliple ids... just follow the responses to my id... they are usually wallis</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1346452803763</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:40:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346454904492-119</Id><Topic><Title>Look at Wallisweaver show how pathetic a human being he is</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346440228600</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fire Obama, get rid of social idealoques who have no business running the country. and someone who got rich from his job as a politician; he sure didn't earn it the old fashioned way via a real job.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1346454904492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:15:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346456529694-120</Id><Title>MR.BUFFETT = THE TECHNOLOGY LEADER (dumps intc)</Title><Msg>Adds IBM.</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1346456529694</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:42:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346456862868-121</Id><Topic><Title>Suggestions for a New Alias</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346354994425</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, what's your new handle ?</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1346456862868</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346458645000-122</Id><Title>This board still functional...</Title><Msg>Why have the Republiscum fled to the new one?</Msg><Username>jerry_cornholed_you</Username><Timestamp>1346458645000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:17:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346459341674-123</Id><Topic><Title>Suggestions for a New Alias</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346354994425</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Porta Prince, Haiti practices a lot of VooDoo.</Msg><Username>kit3taylor</Username><Timestamp>1346459341674</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:29:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346460773995-124</Id><Title>INTC a $30 stock if they meet estimates</Title><Msg>Market is factoring in a big miss with their PC is Dead mantra. No warning means $30.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1346460773995</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:52:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346460988638-125</Id><Topic><Title>INTC a $30 stock if they meet estimates</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1346460773995</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:52:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A huge honking $5 miss is already priced in.</Msg><Username>wallisweiner</Username><Timestamp>1346460988638</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:56:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346461136366-126</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Lucy are the same guy</Title><Username>wally.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346448724124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:32:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wally is paul ottellini too</Msg><Username>starbauch</Username><Timestamp>1346461136366</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:58:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346462926767-127</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Lucy are the same guy</Title><Username>wally.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346448724124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:32:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lucy once said "you all talk to me all the time, you just don't know it." He's a freak and I agree that they are the same delusional, VERY SICK guy. Sad story.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1346462926767</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 21:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346463686213-128</Id><Topic><Title>Suggestions for a New Alias</Title><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346354994425</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't have new handle yet but I'm leaning toward "Star comedy by Democrats." I'm big on palindromes..... but I'm not big on Sarah. Thanks to all who responded.</Msg><Username>lucifer_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1346463686213</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 21:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>27</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346464089898-129</Id><Topic><Title>Look at Wallisweaver show how pathetic a human being he is</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346440228600</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"he sure didn't earn it the old fashioned way via a real job" you mean he did not have a real job like Mitt Romney, the humanitarian that preserved the so many jobs overseas??????????????</Msg><Username>gerdfricke</Username><Timestamp>1346464089898</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 21:48:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346464453707-130</Id><Title>Told you Intel and VMware make Intel worth 50</Title><Msg>In company news, Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) was up 2.35% to $24.84 per share. The company has recently announced a new collaboration with VMware in which they will protect data and decrease threats to cloud data centers. The stock has traded 60.46 million shares in the last trading session, far beyond the normal average of 33.12 million shares.</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1346464453707</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 21:54:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346464541964-131</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Lucy are the same guy</Title><Username>wally.spam</Username><Timestamp>1346448724124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:32:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VERY SICK guy. Sad story ------------------------ and then there's herbal doooooooooooooosh! TOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1346464541964</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 21:55:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346464634867-132</Id><Title>Intel revolutionizing the data center while ARM scrambling for 64 bit, LOL</Title><Msg>Aug 31, 2012 - 10:01AM PT Intel immerses its servers in oil — and they like it! By Derrick Harris</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1346464634867</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 21:57:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346466766005-133</Id><Title>VMware boss says ARM servers not happening anytime soon</Title><Msg>VMware Boss Puts Brakes on ARM Server Revolution Wired‎ - by Cade Metz‎ - 1 day ago</Msg><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1346466766005</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 22:32:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346467368857-134</Id><Topic><Title>I bought another 10K shares at $24.20 yesterday</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1346451450863</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>idiot</Msg><Username>robinenu</Username><Timestamp>1346467368857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 22:42:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346467422064-135</Id><Topic><Title>VMware boss says ARM servers not happening anytime soon</Title><Username>duhboysarebackintown</Username><Timestamp>1346466766005</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 22:32:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is huge. The Server market alone makes INTC a $40-$50 stock.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1346467422064</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 22:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346469789575-136</Id><Title>John Kerry still cutting in lines using Senator celebrity status</Title><Msg>LOL! Bunch of fools with false-pride. Total misfits: The Liberal way.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1346469789575</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 23:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346471925212-137</Id><Title>Nailed it. Bought 50k shares yesterday, $ 23.30 - 23.50</Title><Msg>This will make me a very very rich man in a few years. Eat that Lucy #$%$ 4 lunch.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1346471925212</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 23:58:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>