<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-09"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362805394698-1</Id><Topic><Title>James Cavello for next Intel CEO. That dude knows what he is</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362796527666</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 21:35:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't sneak anything past you. Think about it.</Msg><Username>getanad61</Username><Timestamp>1362805394698</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:03:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362806680063-2</Id><Topic><Title>James Cavello for next Intel CEO. That dude knows what he is</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362796527666</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 21:35:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Can't sneak anything past you. Think about it." [I do think about it. Poor ARM's lack of any server business. As well as: The ARM RT disaster Apples woes and stock dropping by almost 40 percent Nvidia is falling apart and no Tegra 4 products until the end of the year. One design win TSMC reporting lower revenues in February ARM insiders selling at a significant level ARM's stock price dropping for 4 days in a row ARM's fabrication stuck at 28nm for years ARM's 20nm planar declared a poor step forward with bad economics and performance ARM's FinFET years and years away and only a half-step at that The number of ARM foundries dropping and dropping No major ARM smartphones announced at MWC 2013 Shrinking ARM ASP's, margins and profits Yep, it's enough to tear up an ARM investor. Sniff, sniff. Well, unless you're buying puts....] ...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362806680063</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:24:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362806991974-3</Id><Title>Intel Seeks Additional Professionals for Custom Foundry Division</Title><Msg>Intel Confirms: Contract Manufacturing Business Needs New Employees Intel Corp. rarely makes big announcements regarding its contract manufacturing business division that was quietly formed in 2010, but there are things that cannot be hidden. Apparently, the world’s No. 1 maker of chips is currently hiring – and hiring massively – to add professionals to Intel’s custom manufacturing division. According to jobsDOTintelDOTcom, an Intel’s hiring web-site, the company is looking for as much as hundreds of new employees to fill various positions across different Intel manufacturing sites in the U.S. to serve the needs of the contract manufacturing division called Intel Custom Foundry. The positions that Intel wants to fill vary from design automation engineer to physical verification engineer and span across different manufacturing sites in the U.S., including those in Arizona and Oregon.. From xbitlabs</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362806991974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:29:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362807043824-4</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Seeks Additional Professionals for Custom Foundry Division</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362806991974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:29:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...the world’s No. 1 maker of chips is currently hiring – and hiring massively – to add professionals to Intel’s custom manufacturing division..." [Take that, James Covello...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362807043824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:30:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362807898784-5</Id><Title>Surface Pro To Hit UK In Coming Months</Title><Msg>Microsoft Germany announced at CeBIT in Hannover that the Surface Pro will begin rolling out in the UK, France and Germany as early as late March. CEO Christian Illek didn't say what the exact price in pounds would be, but that in euros it would be similar to the US dollar price, $899. According to mobile PC analyst, Salman Chaudhry, "The 128GB version is $999 in the US without a keyboard so it is safe to say it will be £800 in the UK and somewhere between £900 to £1,100 for the full package (including keyboard)." Both the 64 GB and 128 GB versions are expected to make it to Europe. Europeans aren't the only ones who will be getting the Surface Pro; on the Surface Blog Microsoft says it plans to make the tablet available in Australia, China, Hong Kong, New Zealand, Japan, Mexico, Russia, Singapore and Taiwan. Microsoft first made the announcement three weeks after its North American launch on 9 February 2013. Intended to compete with the HP ElitePad 900 on the business user market, the Surface Pro runs on Windows 8 and has an 11.6-inch Full HD 1080p LCD display, a 1.7 GHz Intel Ivy Bridge Core i5 dual-core processor, 4 GB of RAM, two 720p cameras and a USB 3.0 port. Beyond the business world, Microsoft is also hoping to draw in other consumers let down by what some perceived as the Surface RT's 'lack of meat'. Hopefully the Pro will be Microsoft's chance at a reboot... From digitalversus</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362807898784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:44:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362808024165-6</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro To Hit UK In Coming Months</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362807898784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:44:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Beyond the business world, Microsoft is also hoping to draw in other consumers let down by what some perceived as the Surface RT's 'lack of meat'." [That's a pretty good way to define ARM's PC and server products: The lack of meat. Where's the beef, fanbois? Where's the beef?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362808024165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:47:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362808410755-7</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro To Hit UK In Coming Months</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362807898784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:44:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The meat that users get to taste on the Surface Pro is all the left overs that are the legacy WIndows apps that run on it. For fresh newly designed apps optimized for the platform, there's no other optoon but iPad and Android. That's why WIndows 8 will be an abject failure. No new apps are being made for it.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1362808410755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:53:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362809023783-8</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro To Hit UK In Coming Months</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362807898784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:44:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The meat that users get to taste on the Surface Pro is all the left overs that are the legacy WIndows apps that run on it..." [That meat is the performance and full functionality that girlyboy computer users like you said the world doesn't want. You were clearly wrong in all of your assessments about RT and Pro. What good is an iPad app when you want real computing? The results speak for themselves. All the words in the world won't dress up ARM's RT failure...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362809023783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 01:03:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362809443058-9</Id><Title>XOLO to launch phone with Intel 'Clover Trail+' Atom processor on March 14</Title><Msg>XOLO has recently started teasing a new smartphone on its official Facebook page and website. While not much is known about the phone, it will be officially announced on March 14 The company is calling it “Mission X” in its teaser, suggesting the phone will be part of its X-series. We did a little more digging and turns out, the phone will indeed be a part of company’s X-series and come with Intel’s Clover Trail+ platform based dual-core Atom processor. We could not get any other concrete details right now. Speculation Whatever I am writing now is pure speculation based on XOLO’s previous Intel launches. XOLO has introduced two Intel-powered smartphones so-far in the Indian market and both the phones were based on Intel’s reference designs with little or no tweaking on the software part. I believe that company is going to do the same with this upcoming device. Intel showcased a new reference design along with its Clover Trail+ platform at the Mobile World Congress and it is very much likely the upcoming XOLO phone will be based on this reference design. Now, if we take a look at the reference phone, it packs some massive specs, so unless XOLO and Intel step down some of the internals in this reference phone, it will be a phone in the category of Optimus G, S III or HTC Butterfly.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362809443058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 01:10:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362809539114-10</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Seeks Additional Professionals for Custom Foundry Division</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362806991974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:29:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very interesting.... Dec 21, 2012 – Cisco Presents TSMC with Silicon EcoSystem Excellence Award. ... "Creating a great ecosystem for customers throughout the supply chain is ... Feb 25, 2013 – 26, 2013 /PRNewswire/ -- TSMC (TWSE: 2330, NYSE: TSM) and Altera ... ALTR) today reaffirmed their commitment to a long-term partnership to set ... .. the times they are a changing....very rapidly</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1362809539114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 01:12:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362810181945-11</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro To Hit UK In Coming Months</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362807898784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:44:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Performance is secondary. The presence of applications that provide useful functionality is the first thing users look for and that's missing with Windows 8</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1362810181945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 01:23:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362810294829-12</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Seeks Additional Professionals for Custom Foundry Division</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362806991974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:29:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suppose SoC would be part of custom silicon operations</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1362810294829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 01:24:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362810731534-13</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro To Hit UK In Coming Months</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362807898784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:44:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Performance is secondary." [You keep saying this and the market keeps handing you your head in a basket. Below Tom Warren at the Verge suggests that Microsoft never should have gone with ARM at all on the Surface RT. In other words, no one agrees with you...] "A Clover Trail tablet or laptop would make a lot of sense for a future Surface product. I have personally been testing Samsung’s Ativ Smart PC recently, and aside from the performance limitations in gaming it's surprising Microsoft didn't opt for this Intel chip over ARM and Windows RT for its original Surface tablet. Intel's Clover Trail offers great battery life in a slim profile, with the addition of full legacy app support. For most people that would be enough for this type of device, and having 10 hours of battery life and a full desktop OS would make Surface a killer offering."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362810731534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 01:32:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362811736576-14</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro To Hit UK In Coming Months</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362807898784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:44:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your vision is a little myopic, like a horse with blinders on.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1362811736576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 01:48:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362811876074-15</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro To Hit UK In Coming Months</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362807898784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:44:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Your vision is a little myopic, like a horse with blinders on." [Sez the guy who can't see RT's failure right in front of his face...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362811876074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 01:51:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362824501917-16</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Insider Trading Reported.</Title><Username>ray.mary</Username><Timestamp>1362317312220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:28:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>badrian639</Username><Timestamp>1362824501917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 05:21:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362824714552-17</Id><Topic><Title>INTC to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>almeda.mosley</Username><Timestamp>1362591601010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:40:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>badrian639</Username><Timestamp>1362824714552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 05:25:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362827397227-18</Id><Topic><Title>How does INTC keep good talent any more?</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1362802575548</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 23:16:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This company has gone nowhere since "Magic Paul" took over. Some say he has been one heavily-misguided, swanking tinkerer who thought it a good idea to "forget the Windows machines" and apply all effort to take the "Server Space" .... but I couldn't possibly comment. Regardless that the w/w TAM for servers at that time was 500K units, and the w/w TAM for Windows machines was 1 BILLION units! Lots of good people left in disgust (me included) and some say that lots of dopes (yes-men pandering to the super-dope) got promoted via glib, snazzy Powerpoint presentations in support of the Big Chief. Again, I couldn't possibly comment. Magic Paul made the Intel bed, and now the shareholders (who sat back and did nothing for over a decade) must pay the price. AND SERVE THEM RIGHT! For those who think that things are turned-around by now...... are you aware that a VERY senior sales person in Intel Europe remains at the reins. Some say he's a FAILED SHOE SALESMAN! They might say that, but I couldn't possibly comment....... Chap</Msg><Username>sterlingchap</Username><Timestamp>1362827397227</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 06:09:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362828138394-19</Id><Topic><Title>The TRUTH about Intel Corporation...</Title><Username>wayne.garza</Username><Timestamp>1361975360186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful report</Msg><Username>duenas.helen</Username><Timestamp>1362828138394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 06:22:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362828258309-20</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Insider Trading Reported.</Title><Username>ray.mary</Username><Timestamp>1362317312220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:28:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful report</Msg><Username>duenas.helen</Username><Timestamp>1362828258309</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 06:24:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362828492556-21</Id><Topic><Title>INTC to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>almeda.mosley</Username><Timestamp>1362591601010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:40:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful report</Msg><Username>duenas.helen</Username><Timestamp>1362828492556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 06:28:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362829693339-22</Id><Topic><Title>XOLO to launch phone with Intel 'Clover Trail+' Atom processor on March 14</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362809443058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 01:10:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On XOLO's home page is a clock with the bottom half of a phone that is above a launch pad. On the phone is the "Intel Inside" logo. If you click on the clock, the next page will ask you for information to get email alerts. On this page is the statement; "The speed barrier is all set to be shattered. Fasten your seatbelts and get ready for Mission X. 5 days to take off." The bottom of both web pages states; Intel Inside® and the Intel Inside® logo are trademarks of Intel Corporation in the U.S. and/or other countries. xoloDOTin/</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1362829693339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 06:48:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362834940032-23</Id><Topic><Title>Our team projects $20.50 near term</Title><Username>thomasflurkey</Username><Timestamp>1362775529282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 15:45:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please let me introduce you to Backbay_Bstn. You should sync your model with his. Between the two of you, you might be just shy of a clue.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1362834940032</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 08:15:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362835351198-24</Id><Topic><Title>So, Who Is It Then?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362790535973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 19:55:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The best thing that ever happened with respect to Intel's mobile aspirations was when Nokia screwed them by walking away from their strategic partnership over same. Intel would have to be stupid to ever trust Nokia again,... they should be left to rot.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1362835351198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 08:22:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362835538595-25</Id><Topic><Title>How does INTC keep good talent any more?</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1362802575548</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 23:16:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Short answer,.... they don't.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1362835538595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 08:25:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362835647800-26</Id><Topic><Title>INTC to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>almeda.mosley</Username><Timestamp>1362591601010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:40:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing !!</Msg><Username>rolanda.huff</Username><Timestamp>1362835647800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 08:27:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362835848348-27</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Insider Trading Reported.</Title><Username>ray.mary</Username><Timestamp>1362317312220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:28:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing !!</Msg><Username>rolanda.huff</Username><Timestamp>1362835848348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 08:30:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362835916985-28</Id><Topic><Title>The TRUTH about Intel Corporation...</Title><Username>wayne.garza</Username><Timestamp>1361975360186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing !!</Msg><Username>rolanda.huff</Username><Timestamp>1362835916985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 08:31:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362836975340-29</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>carl.hand</Username><Timestamp>1362392578308</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:22:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>rideout.fred</Username><Timestamp>1362836975340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 08:49:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362839590771-30</Id><Topic><Title>So, Who Is It Then?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362790535973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 19:55:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is Nokia still "large"? Even Ikea is going to H.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362839590771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 09:33:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362840442356-31</Id><Topic><Title>INTC to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>almeda.mosley</Username><Timestamp>1362591601010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:40:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome report !</Msg><Username>tricia.daniel</Username><Timestamp>1362840442356</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 09:47:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362840490823-32</Id><Topic><Title>So, Who Is It Then?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362790535973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 19:55:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We will just have to wait for an official news but IMO, it could be Apple with their Ipads and Iwatch.</Msg><Username>clemsyn</Username><Timestamp>1362840490823</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 09:48:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362840502014-33</Id><Topic><Title>So, Who Is It Then?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362790535973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 19:55:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>appleinsiderDOTcom/articles/13/02/13/nokia-rumored-to-join-apple-in-dumping-samsung-as-a-supplier Wednesday, February 13, 2013, 06:21 pm Nokia rumored to join Apple in dumping Samsung as a supplier By Daniel Eran Dilger With Apple known to be working overtime in its efforts to reduce its dependance on Samsung as a component supplier, word comes that other companies, including Nokia, are also considering plans to do the same thing, for similar reasons. Apple's tight business partnership with Samsung became severely strained after the Korean electronics conglomerate initiated efforts to closely duplicate the success of the iPhone 3GS in 2010, followed by Samsung's subsequent cloning of the iPad and iPod touch under its "Galaxy" brand. While Apple remains Samsung's largest customer (and Samsung a critical source of Apple's components), there are clear indications that the iPhone maker is seeking to shift its business to other component manufacturers and chip fabs, the same way that Apple has worked to divorce itself from dependance on Google for maps and other online services. And just as Apple isn't the only company that has left behind Google Maps, "Apple isn't the only one moving away from Samsung," a well connected hardware industry source tells AppleInsider. Supplier turned competitor Among the companies evaluating their alternatives is Nokia, the world's second largest phone maker after Samsung. Gartner credits Nokia with selling 85 million phones in Q4 2012, nearly twice the number of iPhones Apple sold (43.5 million) and about 80 percent of the almost 107 million phones Samsung sold.</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1362840502014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 09:48:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362840569457-34</Id><Topic><Title>How does INTC keep good talent any more?</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1362802575548</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 23:16:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, basically they reprice the older vested options with new ones having a lower price. There was a board vote on compensation a year or two ago that was passed to do this. The purpose of stock option compensation is to reward employees for their effort in raising the value of the stock to shareholders. Repricing options to make employee's stock in-the-money while the stock is flat for shareholders is in my opinion a violation of shareholder trust. Repricing options also undermines the notion of everyone working hard for shared benefit to an atmosphere of entitlement.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1362840569457</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 09:49:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362840661825-35</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Insider Trading Reported.</Title><Username>ray.mary</Username><Timestamp>1362317312220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:28:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome report !</Msg><Username>tricia.daniel</Username><Timestamp>1362840661825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 09:51:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362840726674-36</Id><Topic><Title>The TRUTH about Intel Corporation...</Title><Username>wayne.garza</Username><Timestamp>1361975360186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome report !</Msg><Username>tricia.daniel</Username><Timestamp>1362840726674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 09:52:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362843702952-37</Id><Title>INTC to be featured and they said RUN and SELL, SELL, SELL Lots and lots of problems to over come</Title><Msg>INTC to be featured and they said RUN and SELL, SELL, SELL Lots and lots of problems to over come</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1362843702952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 10:41:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362844994001-38</Id><Topic><Title>So, Who Is It Then?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362790535973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 19:55:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As many have predicted, we are getting to the "War of the Eco-systems". Eco-systems is a nice word - one with nature, etc etc. The "war" part is accurate. I think the word "balkanization" of the industry is a more apt word/description. Android, Apple, Windows. One could make the case that Intel is caught in the middle. Will Apple go x86? Will Samsung try to remain a player, producer, supplier in Android and Windows and Tizen, and continue to make chips in competition with Intel? Nokia is going with Microsoft, so that part is clear. Nokia is not a large presence in the US (they're working on it), but Nokia makes and sells a lot of phones, at every price point, globally. Nokia's technical capabilities in wireless is unsurpassed. Nokia/Microsoft has to be a tempting partner for Intel Will any of the Balkan states develop a "special" relationship with Intel, or will Intel try to remain a neutral supplier, if in fact that's an option as Apple may go it's own way, and Samsung, too. Are the advantages offered by Intel (cost, production technology and capacity) too compelling for Apple and/or Samsung to pass up? Lots of questions, and while I work to read and understand industry dynamics, I do not have the background in the industry to have any special insight as to the answers. I yield the floor to those who perhaps know things I don't.</Msg><Username>clcellve</Username><Timestamp>1362844994001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 11:03:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362845460786-39</Id><Topic><Title>INTC to be featured and they said RUN and SELL, SELL, SELL Lots and lots of problems to over come</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1362843702952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 10:41:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may say that you are not long or short. Then what is your motive for all the "advice"? I expect a reply but I don't expect an answer. Intel is a slow moving large cap that pays a well covered, increasing dividend yield. Intel will track the general markets. For those interested in investing and income, your advice has little or no value. They will enter a position slowly with a 4+% yield and their cost basis will be about $20 per share. Value funds are accumulating Intel. If you worry about next week, don't invest in the stock market. Find a better place for your money. Barrons The Patient Investor By RESHMA KAPADIA Kathleen Gaffney spent nearly 30 years working with one of the bond world's biggest luminaries. A few months ago, she brought her shrewd analysis and value orientation to Eaton Vance, co-managing its fixed-income allocation fund and heading up a new launch of her own. .... ----- She's also finding good opportunities for income among dividend-paying stocks. Particularly appealing areas include technology and energy, which have been beaten-down, and materials, which offers a less frothy way to play the housing recovery. "There are creative ways of getting access to continued growth in the recovery—you just have to focus on individual companies and the best valuations." For example, she owns bonds of privately held Irish packaging company Ardagh Group. .....---- In the investment-grade corporate sector, Gaffney says, cyclical companies in the U.S. and banks, telecom, and utilities in peripheral Europe are attractive. Shares of Occidental Petroleum (OXY) and Intel (INTC), plus bonds of Western Union (WU), Ciena (CIEN), and Jefferies Group (JEF) are among the new fund's top holdings.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1362845460786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 11:11:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362846811852-40</Id><Topic><Title>INTC to be featured and they said RUN and SELL, SELL, SELL Lots and lots of problems to over come</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1362843702952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 10:41:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The real ? why are you always PUMPING INTC all the way down from $29.25 to 19 never a sell, Just BUY and you know that all the insiders are selling all they can WHY OH WHY do you want people to buy INTC</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1362846811852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 11:33:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362848639030-41</Id><Topic><Title>INTC to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>almeda.mosley</Username><Timestamp>1362591601010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:40:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you !</Msg><Username>steven.williams74</Username><Timestamp>1362848639030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 12:03:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362849377399-42</Id><Topic><Title>INTC to be featured and they said RUN and SELL, SELL, SELL Lots and lots of problems to over come</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1362843702952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 10:41:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You may say that you are not long or short. Then what is your motive for all the "advice"? I expect a reply but I don't expect an answer. " BTW, you supplied a REPLY to my message but NOT an answer to my question. Your reply was not an ANSWER to my question "why are you here if you hold no interest ?" Pretty good prediction.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1362849377399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 12:16:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362849954400-43</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>carl.hand</Username><Timestamp>1362392578308</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:22:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great job</Msg><Username>jeromewenner</Username><Timestamp>1362849954400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 12:25:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362849979514-44</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Seeks Additional Professionals for Custom Foundry Division</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362806991974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:29:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot NM. We are also hiring</Msg><Username>typea1948</Username><Timestamp>1362849979514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 12:26:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362852650657-45</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro To Hit UK In Coming Months</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362807898784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:44:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The market predicts Surface Pro huge success, that why Apple is being crashed with no relief in sight</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1362852650657</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 13:10:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362853614381-46</Id><Topic><Title>INTC to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>almeda.mosley</Username><Timestamp>1362591601010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:40:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report !!</Msg><Username>sinclair.james</Username><Timestamp>1362853614381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 13:26:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362857533344-47</Id><Title>INTC to be featured in MAD MAGAZINE this month!</Title><Msg>WHAT, ME WORRY??? HI-HO ALFRED E. WEAVERINO! TOOOOO FUNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1362857533344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 14:32:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362858089497-48</Id><Title>DanaLucy Fired by Intel</Title><Msg>Now being fired by the Yahoo Message Boards. Yahoo management concludes getting rid of DL is worth chunking the whole operation down the drain...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362858089497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 14:41:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362859778091-49</Id><Title>Another Day</Title><Msg>Another day closer to Haswell Another day closer to Intel 14nm FinFET production Another day closer to announcement of the next big Intel deal Who is the major mobility player signing on with Intel's state-of-the-art manufacturing???</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362859778091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:09:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362860044931-50</Id><Topic><Title>Another Day</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362859778091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:09:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another day closer to the teens. TOOOO FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1362860044931</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:14:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362860136128-51</Id><Title>Rumor: Apple to purportedly use Qualcomm's Snapdragon SoC in low-cost iPhone</Title><Msg>Reason: Reduction of the amount of those nasty royalties to ARM ARM continues its descent into the land of sharp objects...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362860136128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:15:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362860171053-52</Id><Topic><Title>Another Day</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362859778091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:09:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so, when do you become a teenager toostupid? Have your testacles descended yet? Probably never will.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362860171053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:16:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362860334604-53</Id><Topic><Title>Rumor: Apple to purportedly use Qualcomm's Snapdragon SoC in low-cost iPhone</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362860136128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:15:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One comment to the article: "Rumor: Apple to purportedly use Qualcomm's Snapdragon SoC in low-cost iPhone" That, and a sh!tload of duct-tape. [LOL...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362860334604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:18:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362861073384-54</Id><Topic><Title>Rumor: Apple to purportedly use Qualcomm's Snapdragon SoC in low-cost iPhone</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362860136128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:15:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another comment to the article: Quote: Originally Posted by saarek I don't see why Apple wouldn't simply reuse the A4. They could modify it if needed. The A4 is a joke, even by low-end standards.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362861073384</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:31:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362861261177-55</Id><Topic><Title>Another Day</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362859778091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:09:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't imagine what DuhLucy will do when he can no longer use the boards to run out from under his porch like a little dog to bite people on the ankles...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362861261177</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:34:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362862019856-56</Id><Topic><Title>Another Day</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362859778091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:09:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He'll sit in his lonely room cutting himself and watching kids walk by from behind the blinds, like he usually does. Eat the occasional c-roach.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362862019856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:46:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362862572348-57</Id><Topic><Title>Another Day</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362859778091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:09:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have your old lady's boobs descended yet, gramps? Do they look like two fried eggs hanging on naiis? TOOO FUNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1362862572348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:56:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362869083986-58</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Seeks Additional Professionals for Custom Foundry Division</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362806991974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:29:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't understand what you are saying here........Are you saying Cisco is using TSMC instead of Intel ?</Msg><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1362869083986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 17:44:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362869188302-59</Id><Topic><Title>Another Day</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362859778091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:09:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought the Finance boards were staying open? Is this board being shut down?</Msg><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1362869188302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 17:46:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362869393897-60</Id><Title>Intel will foundry speciality chips like Altera's, Xilinix and Cisco's. Margins are very high for</Title><Msg>these chips. The $20 ARM chip market will be left to TSMC.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362869393897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 17:49:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362870200429-61</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will foundry speciality chips like Altera's, Xilinix and Cisco's. Margins are very high for</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362869393897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 17:49:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't Intel agree with Altera that they wouldn't do business with Xilinix?</Msg><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1362870200429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 18:03:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362870404445-62</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will foundry speciality chips like Altera's, Xilinix and Cisco's. Margins are very high for</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362869393897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 17:49:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't see EXCLUSIVITY anywhere in their Press Release.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362870404445</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 18:06:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362870706516-63</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will foundry speciality chips like Altera's, Xilinix and Cisco's. Margins are very high for</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362869393897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 17:49:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw this in a Seeking Alpha article by Mr. A Eassa: Unfortunately for Xilinx, it will not be able to also sign on to Intel's foundry services as the agreement between Altera and Intel stipulates that Altera be the only major FPGA vendor to be allowed access to Intel's 14nm node technology. However, this makes perfect sense for what Intel is aiming for: strategic customers.</Msg><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1362870706516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 18:11:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362871209466-64</Id><Topic><Title>XOLO to launch phone with Intel 'Clover Trail+' Atom processor on March 14</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362809443058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 01:10:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's pretty awesome. It would be nice to start seeing some commercials emphasizing phones with Intel chips inside. Let people know it's a big deal and just happening for the 1st time.</Msg><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1362871209466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 18:20:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362871967823-65</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will foundry speciality chips like Altera's, Xilinix and Cisco's. Margins are very high for</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362869393897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 17:49:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Altera PR says its the only major FPGA vendor with access to Intel's 14nm. This is true, since others haven't signed up yet (1 at a time). It does not say it has EXCLUSIVE access to 14nm. Mr Essa is a novice at this, he needs to listen and learn first, before shooting his mouth off.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362871967823</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 18:32:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362873208683-66</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will foundry speciality chips like Altera's, Xilinix and Cisco's. Margins are very high for</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362869393897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 17:49:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This was in an article at the register: Either you or Mr. Eassa is a novice, flip a coin. Wrong. The terms of the deal cut between Intel and Altera were not disclosed, but apparently Intel did not keep its options open with the deal it cut with Altera. According to a report in the Wall Street Journal, Intel agreed to a twelve-year deal with Altera and said that the other major suppliers of FPGAs – that is mainly Xilinx – would not be given access to Chipzilla's fabs.</Msg><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1362873208683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 18:53:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362874752377-67</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will foundry speciality chips like Altera's, Xilinix and Cisco's. Margins are very high for</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362869393897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 17:49:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You hear all sorts of things on the internet. Very often they are wrong. Anyway enough of this.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362874752377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 19:19:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362878405090-68</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will foundry speciality chips like Altera's, Xilinix and Cisco's. Margins are very high for</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362869393897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 17:49:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will_amd_yu, Perhaps you should follow your own advice.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1362878405090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 20:20:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362879041269-69</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will foundry speciality chips like Altera's, Xilinix and Cisco's. Margins are very high for</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362869393897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 17:49:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will, You're the only here shooting your mouth off..........with absolutely ZERO factual evidence to back up your claims. No wonder you've had enough, YOU turned out to be the novice.</Msg><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1362879041269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 20:30:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362879851893-70</Id><Title>Gelsinger as Intel next CEO would be GREAT</Title><Msg>VMware's Gelsinger May Replace Intel's Otellini: Report By Joseph F. Kovar March 08, 2013 7:56 PM ET Big changes could be in store for VMware as the company's CEO may be in the running to take the reins at his former employer, Intel according to a report. Online news site Quartz, owned by the parent company of The Atlantic, on Friday said that VMware CEO Pat Gelsinger and former Motorola CEO Sanjay Jha are among the names being considered to take over as CEO at Intel when current CEO Paul Otellini steps down this year. Gelsinger would feel right at home at Intel. [Related: Gelsinger Taking Over VMware As Storage, Virtualization Come To A Crossroads] Prior to joining EMC in late 2009, Gelsinger was senior vice president and co-general manager of Intel's Digital Enterprise Group, a group that accounted for more than half of Intel's annual revenue and was responsible for Intel's enterprise products including products for PCs, servers, embedded systems, communications, visualization and storage. Gelsinger at the time had been widely expected to be in line to succeed Otellini as president and CEO of Intel. Gelsinger was on the short list of candidates to take over as EMC CEO when current top exec Joe Tucci retires. Tucci has said he will remain at his post through early 2015. Gelsinger in July took over as VMware CEO after then-CEO Paul Maritz moved to EMC to manage the two companies' joint Pivotal Initiative cloud computing project. Joining Gelsinger on the list of Otellini successors is Sanjay Jha, who last year left Motorola Mobility after its acquisition by Google. A VMware spokesperson said VMware does not comment on rumor or speculation. Meanwhile, VMware on Friday confirmed a Tech Crunch report that Rick Jackson, the company's CMO, is stepping down from that role to a new position as senior vice president of global enablement. Jackson will help with the search for a new CMO. VMware, in a statement sent t</Msg><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1362879851893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 20:44:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362881406131-71</Id><Topic><Title>So, Who Is It Then?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362790535973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 19:55:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember last year when INTC opened an office down the street from QCOM in SanDiego? Wonder if it was for competition or collaberation of cell phones?</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1362881406131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 21:10:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362886308217-72</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>carl.hand</Username><Timestamp>1362392578308</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:22:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAMMER !!</Msg><Username>daxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362886308217</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 22:31:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>