<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371009628329-1</Id><Topic><Title>Intel could win the smartphone race</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371009543405</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 23:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The new Lenovo K900 is the company’s flagship product and it uses the latest Atom as well. The 6.9mm thick stainless steel body has a 5.5” HD 400ppi screen and 13MP camera make this a desirable phone as well – alas Lenovo has no intention to bring it to Australia either. ZTE (a Chinese OEM that makes some of Telstra’s wireless modems) has announced that its Grand X2 (pictured) will be powered by the Intel Atom running at 2GHz. We may see this very powerful smartphone as a Telstra own brand later this year. The Atom was chosen as it was the fastest currently available system on a chip and its low battery drain. Intel’s new Clover Trail+ 32 bit Atom CPU’s for Android are gaining popularity with the ASUS FonePad Note 6, Samsung Galaxy Tab 3 10.1” and Asus Transformer Book Trio taking the Intel route. But the new Atom Bay Trail (22 nm Silvermont) due out very soon may seal the deal for Intel over ARM. This is a 2.1GHz quad core, 64 bit processor with Intel’s Ivy Bridge GPU that is reputed to be 3x faster than the Z2580 and will be optimised for Android Key Lime Pie. Not satisfied Intel has also announced a 14nm Airmont quad core for 2014. These specifications are well ahead of anything ARM has announced. From ITWire</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371009628329</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 00:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371010469429-2</Id><Title>Beware of ghostupinhere</Title><Msg>yet another alias</Msg><Username>iknow.whoyouare</Username><Timestamp>1371010469429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 00:14:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371010525177-3</Id><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Msg>What we know now is that Intel is getting traction across the board. The Apple show at WWDC was proof of this where Intel technology was the only hardware excitement present. Sure there were some nice new software features but the real computing power coming to the Mac Pro was the best example of what Apple is capable of - with Intel's help. The Mac upgrades were a very nice extension of the traction from the Haswell announcement, Computex and the huge number of new product releases. And all of this leads nicely into Intel's roadmap for the rest of the year with back-to-school traction and holiday sales traction and then what will be monumental excitement over the arrival of Intel's volume production of 14nm at the beginning of 2014. We know now that the big Wall Street firms are going to do everything in their power to try to #$%$ the Intel ramp. We've seen this repeatedly lately and we've seen it substantially fail. Intel has huge positive press now and it seems clear that there is real excitement over the new performance coupled with new form factors. We know now that ARM investors have recognized the Intel threat and know that it is real to the extent of a 20 percent drop in the ARM stock price. We know now that we have the Samsung deal to add to the Altera deal and the Mac upgrades. More information on that at the June 20th Samsung event. Across the entire computing spectrum, Intel is on the move and gaining ground consistently. The tipping point has been reached and the ARM era is coming to a close. 2013: Year of the Intel Tablet 2014: Year of the Intel Smartphone</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371010525177</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 00:15:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371010676614-4</Id><Title>Beware of this sick individual</Title><Msg>Here uses the following aliases and will often use one or more of these alias to respond to same bashing post which he started with another alias. ghostupinhere backpain_bstn boiled_n_oil chump.weaver will_amd_yu backbay_bstn att4glte aintezbeingreen wdblawgrow wallisdreamweaver fourteennanometer itakebackmyapology dominateamerika singhlion2001 coinmaker77 jimbohomegameedyall aulus_vitellius_germanicus geraldmcginty walrusweener</Msg><Username>iknow.whoyouare</Username><Timestamp>1371010676614</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 00:17:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371011534475-5</Id><Topic><Title>Apple will announce Intel on its Ipads this year, with Baytrail.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370994627423</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 19:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel and Apple have a close working relationship. Apple got the low power Haswell before anyone else Nevertheless Apple will go (at least to some degree) with TSMC @ 20nm. I think Apple is not the only one who underestimated Intel's SoC capabilities - and TSMC probably gave Apple a great deal. Apple is stuck with TSMC whether they like it or not. Intel 22 nm SoC has at least 6 to 9 months lead compared to TSMC - Samsung jumped on it and Apple is stuck with TSMC . Since TSMC 20nm won't be ready for fall there is good chance we'll see Intel SoC in Ipads</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1371011534475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 00:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371011743484-6</Id><Title>HP DISCOVER: HP UNVEILS WHISPER-QUIET HASWELL-POWERED MICROSERVER</Title><Msg>HP launched three servers for small and medium businesses at its Discover conference in Las Vegas Tuesday. All three are single-processor servers powered by the latest Haswell chips Intel announced one week ago. HP designed the eighth-generation ProLiant MicroServer for use in an office with 10 or fewer employees. The ProLiant M310e Gen8 v2 is a tower server geared mainly for remote and branch offices, and the ProLiant DL320e Gen8 v2 is a rack server designed with smaller-than-usual depth to fit in as many kinds of spaces as possible. The ProLiant DL320e Gen8 v2 rack server is about 15 inches deep, which means it can be installed in small spaces, running applications for small businesses, chain stores, factory automation, medical, transportation, telecom and military. This is the first time HP has built a server of this size. “That's actually a new form factor for us,” Glass said. The new ML310e server is basically a version of its predecessor upgraded with one of the new Intel Xeon E3-1200 v3 chips. The new MicroServer's starting price is about US$500, and the ML310e (the tower) and the DL320e start at $870 and $900, respectively. From datacenterdynamics</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371011743484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 00:35:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371012103776-7</Id><Title>The new MacBook Air with Haswell on the way</Title><Msg>My laptop collection is about to get larger as I couldn't pass on the new MacBook Air with the Haswell processor from Intel. The new processor is powerful and almost doubles the battery life of the new MacBook Air compared to the last generation model. That combination was too good for me to pass up, so an 11-inch MacBook Air will soon be arriving at my door. The biggest update to the new MacBook Air comes with the latest processor from Intel, the Haswell. I have been anxious to get my hands on a Haswell-equipped laptop and I am excited the MacBook Air will be that device. The Core i5 Haswell processor in the MacBook Air comes standard with a 1.3 GHz processor but a 1.7 GHz option is available. The Haswell processor upgrades the graphics to the Intel HD 5000. This is reported to be 40 percent faster than the HD 4000 used in most laptops today. The most significant improvement in the new MacBook Air is the extended battery life due to the Haswell processor. Apple is quoting 9 hours for the 11.6-inch model compared to 5 hours in the previous model. My experience with Apple products is the quoted battery life is very close to what you actually get, unlike the case with some other vendors. This battery life should get me through an entire day away from an outlet, even with heavy usage. Summary: Apple announced the next generation MacBook Air with the new Intel Haswell processor that almost doubles battery life. By James Kendrick for Mobile News</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371012103776</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 00:41:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371012132378-8</Id><Topic><Title>The new MacBook Air with Haswell on the way</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371012103776</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 00:41:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"My laptop collection is about to get larger as I couldn't pass on the new MacBook Air with the Haswell processor from Intel."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371012132378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 00:42:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371012230341-9</Id><Topic><Title>The new MacBook Air with Haswell on the way</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371012103776</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 00:41:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The new MacBook Air will be here in just a few days as Apple is already shipping them. That's a lesson that other companies should learn from Apple. It's always better to ship right after the product announcement than give prospective customers time to think about it. It worked on me."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371012230341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 00:43:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371013199715-10</Id><Topic><Title>Beware of this sick individual</Title><Username>iknow.whoyouare</Username><Timestamp>1371010676614</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 00:17:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong, wrong wrong. I have one alias, the same one I have used for years. You need to go see your PCP immediately as you have been diagnosed with paranoid delusional schizophrenia. You will need a permanent prescription of Navane otherwise you will start killing people I'm sure. Remember boiled_n_oil... one alias. Remember iknow.whoyouare... delusional.</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1371013199715</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 00:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371013419960-11</Id><Title>"That is about to change, and this time it's for real..."</Title><Msg>The ARM Singularity Intel (INTC) has been trying to break into the mobile markets for quite some time. It even got close with a few design wins from friendly OEMs like Motorola or Lenovo (LNVGY.PK). But in reality it never really broke through. ARM (ARMH) designs always kept a strong hold on 90%+ of the market, no matter what. That is about to change, and this time it's for real I'm not even talking about the present Clover Trail+ design wins, namely with the new Samsung Galaxy Tab 3. This is already significant because Samsung is a first tier OEM and is certainly not giving Intel this win because of its friendly nature. Samsung is doing something predictable taking into account the latest benchmarks (on a Lenovo K900), which show Clover Trail+ to be competitive with the present smartphones at the highest end. But as I said, Clover Trail+ is not the reason why I'm penning this article. Intel's Silvermont architecture, which will be on products before 2013 is out, is the real singularity about to hit ARM. This architecture is entirely new, and showcases Intel's superiority both in product and process technology. The same superiority which relegated AMD to "also-ran" status. From Paulo Santos</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371013419960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 01:03:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371013466539-12</Id><Topic><Title>"That is about to change, and this time it's for real..."</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371013419960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 01:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The possible catalyst which might open the floodgates While the performance and power consumption specs, by themselves, are probably enough to extend Intel's penetration into the market well beyond what Clover Trail+ will manage, the really large impact will probably come all at once. This impact will come from the likely adoption by Intel either during the iPhone 6 cycle in 2014, or most likely during the 2015 cycle. The reason is simple. Apple (Apple) greatly values power consumption, as seen from the way it kept the iPhone's ARM-based CPU at 800Mhz long beyond necessary. Apple is thus highly likely to spring for the state-of-the-art if it guarantees it outstanding power consumption, which Silvermont seems likely to. Also, Apple is already using Intel in its OSX products, and would probably gain efficiencies internally from concentrating on a single architecture. The wildcard would obviously be backward compatibility, though re-compiling apps would probably enable it. Thus, on the day Apple decides to go with Intel on mobile, ARM will instantly lose around 25% of the smartphone market in one single blow. While the market could conceivably accept slow erosion, such hit would be impossible to ignore.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371013466539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 01:04:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371013592760-13</Id><Topic><Title>"That is about to change, and this time it's for real..."</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371013419960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 01:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel's further wildcard Another wildcard is the fact that Intel will bring down its Haswell architecture to fanless tablets. A fanless tablet with the kind of power Haswell provides will blow everything else out of the water. The main problem with Microsoft's Surface Pro could be said to be the fact that it still has a fan, which makes it much thicker and heavier, as well as less reliable. At the class of power Haswell provides we already know no other company is able to field a competitive product, so this also effectively cuts ARM's wings above Silvermont (if it were able to field anything there). Further implications ARM is just the IP vendor for ARM CPUs, but these are then produced by a multitude of OEMs. Of these, several trade in the stock market, including Qualcomm (QCOM) and Nvidia (NVDA). Intel's forceful entry into the mobile market isn't just negative for ARM, it's also deeply negative for these vendors. From Paulo Santos</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371013592760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 01:06:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371013733175-14</Id><Topic><Title>"That is about to change, and this time it's for real..."</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371013419960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 01:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Conclusion Intel has reached parity with Clover Trail+, and is now getting ready to launch Silvermont before the year is out. Silvermont seems likely to finally be wildly superior to anything that ARM is fielding this year or next, so Silvermont is likely to give Intel its much-coveted beachhead into the mobile market. Not only that, but Silvermont's superiority seems so large, and its upgrade schedule is so aggressive, that most probably Intel will switch towards it either during 2014, or most likely in 2015. When this happens, ARM will lose 25% of the worldwide smartphone market in a single hit. These developments are positive for Intel and deeply negative for ARM, which to make matters worse trades at a huge valuation premium - its EV/EBITDA stands at 45.3 times. But it doesn't stop there. These developments are also significantly negative for OEMs producing ARM on a license, like Qualcomm and Nvidia. The current design wins by Intel mean the dam has been breached, when Silvermont arrives the floodgates will surely open. From Paulo Santos</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371013733175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 01:08:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371014992020-15</Id><Topic><Title>Short Interest as of 5/31</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370998478013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 20:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think we will see a significant drop in the period ending 6/14. These numbers will be available at 4pm EST on the 25th. Hopefully it will give some momentum after the Samsung event (June 20th) and before earnings July 17th.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1371014992020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 01:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371015554226-16</Id><Topic><Title>Apple:Writing on the wall for ARM</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1370894779478</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 16:06:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The day that Apple goes full Intel is the day that they are never coming back to ARM. I know what you are saying about not wanting to have a touch screen on a home based PC. Still being a one OS company is the holy grail of all ideas for Microsoft and Apple, even Linux based companies like Google and Ubuntu. There are a few reasons why. #1. Developers would only have to develop on one platform per company. Microsoft's metro apps have to be designed differently for RT versus x86. If you want it to work on Windows Phone that's a yet another app. Developing for one platform per company will make attracting developers an easier task. #2. One user experience across the board. If someone was comfortable working an iPhone and they really liked it then the Mac sale would be much easier. If they can freely navigate their phone then the same would be true of their laptop computer. #3. Apple could focus on one and only one operating system at a time. Having two major OS's at the same time is like managing different companies. The issue for Microsoft has become Windows 8 is wonderful if you have a touch device, but is horrible if you don't. The problem has been that for phones and tablets we want simplicity, and for desktops we demand more complexity. I believe that nobody really wants to touch their desktop monitors. We are used to mice and we're never giving it up. I believe Apple is starting to move in the direction it needs to go by offering shared look and feel between iOS 7 and OS/X Maverics. Where I see thing going is that your phone will put out more complex menus when hooked up to an external keyboard and mouse. Your phone will be more like OS/X when plugged in, and will simplify down the iOS look and feel for the touch screen experience when it's being used in the smartphone mode. Doing this in a manner that is intuitive is something I believe Apple can do very well.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1371015554226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 01:39:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371024006473-17</Id><Topic><Title>Apple:Writing on the wall for ARM</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1370894779478</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 16:06:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#1. Developers would only have to develop on one platform per company. Microsoft's metro apps have to be designed differently for RT versus x86. ---- If you build a metro app, it'll work on ARM and x86 - as a developer you don't care. It's the store that distributes the app, so it handles the ISA issue. If Apple goes x86, it'll use the same approach. Microsoft has shown that a touch UI doesn't work well in a WIMP environment, so you need to have a different UI for touch. The kernel of iOS/OSx is effectively the same, just different API's/UI's.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1371024006473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 04:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371024921789-18</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst: Intel Atom chip outperforms Nvidia, Qualcomm and Samsung</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370619798024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:43:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know as well as I, some benchmarks favor different CPUs. The Antutu results (for clovertrail+) are interesting as they are much better than Medfield+ even taking into account the two extra threads. This performance scaling improvement doesn't show in other benchmarks (javascript, geekbench etc) so the real question is why such an improvement in Antutu and not in others?</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1371024921789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 04:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371027204457-19</Id><Topic><Title>Derivatives Shifting</Title><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1370237011973</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 01:23:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure will!</Msg><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1371027204457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 04:53:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371030036681-20</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst: Intel Atom chip outperforms Nvidia, Qualcomm and Samsung</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370619798024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:43:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Pentup, do you have a life? I'll take Ashraf's facts, opinion and commentary any day over your inane babbling about boring days. ;-/</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1371030036681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 05:40:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371037316855-21</Id><Topic><Title>"That is about to change, and this time it's for real..."</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371013419960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 01:03:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From your lips to God's ears, IMHO INTC going back to 75, been long time investor, this is good news !!!</Msg><Username>stcdegree2003</Username><Timestamp>1371037316855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 07:41:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371037985102-22</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>With VIX remaining relatively high, expect more choppiness in the near term. The bears have the momentum and downside risk has increased. However, the uptrend started in November is still intact. Technical conditions show a mixed picture. On one hand, relatively weak volume today suggests that selling pressure was contained. On the other hand, new 52-week lows on the NYSE were at the highest level since November 15 indicating the uptrend started in November is in trouble. In addition, today's global selloff suggests that although the U.S. economic picture may look better than those in the European countries or Japan, our stock market isn't immune from what happens overseas. For the S&amp;P 500, watch for support near 1610 followed by 1600.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1371037985102</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 07:53:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371040247599-23</Id><Title>Large movements in options. Bulls picking up steam.</Title><Msg>"OptionMonster's tracking programs show that traders sold the June 26 calls yesterday and bought the July 27s. Blocks of 40,000 contracts in each traded for a net cost of $0.11." "Yesterday's roll accounted for the bulk of the option paper in Intel yesterday. Calls outpaced puts by 128,000 to 19,000."</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1371040247599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 08:30:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371040812311-24</Id><Topic><Title>Apple will announce Intel on its Ipads this year, with Baytrail.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370994627423</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 19:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is definitely something they would keep a secret until the iPad is announced. It would be one of those "one more thing" moments when, after showing the iPad and how it looks, etc. they add, "by the way, it is running on an Intel processor." The apps will run "as is" so there was no need to announce in advance at WWDC in order to give developers advanced notice (as has been the case i 2005 when they announced the switch from PowerPC to Intel x86). We saw the same thing with the Galaxy Tab 3 10.1-inch. Although there were rumors a few weeks before, Samsung did not need to (and did not) announce in advance that they were switching the device to Intel's Atom processor. I would not expect Apple to behave any differently.</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1371040812311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 08:40:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371041354079-25</Id><Topic><Title>How many millions did Intel waste on intel TV?</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1371005787361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 22:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has a long history of this. They are always looking elsewhere for sources of new growth, but nothing ever works and the end up making all their money o he processor business. Many may not recall, but for a while in the 1990s and into the earlier 2000s they sold an Intel branded MP3 player and and Intel branded digital camera (intended to take advantage of their flash memory production) and for a while they sold a whole line of Intel branded home and small business networking equipment. You could go to the store and buy an "Intel" router. They need to still with their core competency of manufacturing microprocessors which, fortunately, they do for the most part and they do that very well. But it seem to be human nature (not just at Intel) to be looking at what the other guy is doing. "The grass is always greener on the other side of the fence." So some genius at Intel looks around and sees Google, Netflix, Apple, Amazon, Hulu, Microsoft, etc. all getting into the delivery of video content to televisions and the Intel guys say, "we should get in on that too." Who cares that it is a completely different type of business than what Intel has always done? These things come and go and I doubt the money they spent makes even a tiny dent in their financials.</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1371041354079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 08:49:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371043150695-26</Id><Title>Intel Has A Secret Version Of Haswell</Title><Msg>I would like to thank InvestorsHub long-timer wbmw for bringing the following to my attention. Intel (INTC) recently released the data sheets for its ultra low power editions of its "Haswell" processor aimed for Ultrabooks and even high end tablets. While Intel has been bragging that its latest "Haswell" designs can be configured to have a 6W "SDP" (which basically means "when the chip is behind the glass, throttle/manage the frequencies so that the chip does not consume more than 6W on average"), it seems that the company has actually been a little shy in its PR statements. Intel's own data sheet acknowledges the existence of yet another "Haswell" - a 4.5W SDP part. The 4.5W Part For Fanless Tablets Straight from the data sheet, here is the evidence for the existence of this other "Haswell" part: (click to enlarge) The implications of this part are enormous. While it seemed likely that a 6W SDP part would be enough for 13" fanless tablets/detachables and even fanless clamshells, the 4.5W SDP part would likely be capable of driving a fanless 11.6" tablets and convertibles with good battery life. While the performance against, say, a 15W or 11.5W unrestricted TDP "Haswell," will likely be appreciably lower, such devices would still very likely be significantly faster than the best ARM (ARMH) based devices in competing form factors due to the sophistication of the design/process technology superiority. From Ashraf Eassa</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371043150695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:19:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371043246556-27</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Has A Secret Version Of Haswell</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371043150695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:19:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Pincer Attack On ARM &amp; Its Partners It seems that Intel is, in the words of a good friend of mine, executing a classic "pincer" attack on the ARM world. Attack from below with "Silvermont," which should be faster and lower power than ARM's finest, and then attack from above with the "Core" micro-architecture with even higher performance levels at similar power consumption levels. The interesting thing about "Haswell" is the dramatic idle power consumption improvements that it brought to bear on the same process generation as "Ivy Bridge," implying a Herculean effort on the micro-architecture and physical design side of things, to substantially widen the dynamic range. In particular, while "Ivy Bridge" CPU + PCH consumed 3.2W - 3.4W (again, thank you, wbmw) in their deepest idle states, "Haswell" reduces this down to mere milliwatts: (click to enlarge) So, what we have here is a family of high performance processors that can idle nearly as low as the very best smartphone processors. This dynamic range in a high performance processor is unheard of and is a very dramatic advancement in the state of micro-processors. Keep in mind that these idle numbers don't just include the processor, but the on-package 32nm PCH - so there's still some room to drive things down further. From Ashraf Eassa</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371043246556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:20:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371043335612-28</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Has A Secret Version Of Haswell</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371043150695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:19:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Conclusion This is why I have been so bullish on Intel, and this is why it is ever-frustrating when the press and sell-side don't "get it." While some outfits, particularly PC enthusiast sites, are off making claims about Haswell running too hot when overclocked (this is preposterous as overclocking is running the chip way out of specification), the fact is that "Haswell" redefines the dynamic range of what a high performance, high end processor can do. The highest end fanless tablets will feature "Core" processors, as well as the sleekest, thinnest Ultrabooks and notebooks. Sure, the overclockers on the (dying) desktop platforms will see their overclocking headrooms contract, but Intel is moving to where the market is going - mobile - and doing so in a wildly ambitious fashion. From Ashraf Eassa</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371043335612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:22:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371043388519-29</Id><Topic><Title>Apple will announce Intel on its Ipads this year, with Baytrail.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370994627423</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 19:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ios is a native environment (unlike android) and as such there are a lot of ARM binary specific code floating around (even in assembly) so Apple would need to prep developers otherwise a lot of apps wont work.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1371043388519</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:23:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371043685061-30</Id><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Msg>What we know now is that Intel is getting traction across the board. The Apple show at WWDC was proof of this where Intel technology was the only hardware excitement present. Sure there were some nice new software features but the real computing power coming to the Mac Pro was the best example of what Apple is capable of - with Intel's help - innovative design with state-of-the-art performance. The Mac upgrades were a very nice extension of the traction from the Haswell announcement, Computex and the huge number of new product releases. And all of this leads nicely into Intel's roadmap for the rest of the year with back-to-school traction and holiday sales traction and then what will be monumental excitement over the arrival of Intel's volume production of 14nm at the beginning of 2014. We know now that the big Wall Street firms are going to do everything in their power to try to #$%$ the Intel ramp. We've seen this repeatedly lately and we've seen it substantially fail. Intel has huge positive press now and it seems clear that there is real excitement over the new performance coupled with new form factors. We know now that ARM investors have recognized the Intel threat and know that it is real to the extent of a 20 percent drop in the ARM stock price. We know now that we have the Samsung deal to add to the Altera deal and the Mac upgrades. More information on that at the June 20th Samsung event. Across the entire computing spectrum, Intel is on the move and gaining ground consistently. The tipping point has been reached and the ARM era is coming to a close. 2013: Year of the Intel Tablet 2014: Year of the Intel Smartphone</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371043685061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371044844509-31</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371043685061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:28:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trading poorly this morning thus far. Hopefully it will Improve.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1371044844509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371044963735-32</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371043685061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:28:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorts in the morning assault. They like to start early and fade early...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371044963735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:49:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371045141628-33</Id><Title>You got trapped buying in the upper 25s</Title><Msg>Again. You won't see it again this summer.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1371045141628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:52:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371045336612-34</Id><Title>Wait and see</Title><Msg>Famous last words of INTC pumpers. For over a decade now it is the same mantra. A new product release will result in millions of revenues which should mean increased profits driving up the stock prices. The highest this stock has hit in a decade is 30+. There are better places to put your money for the next decade.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1371045336612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:55:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371045838003-35</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371043685061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:28:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you shouldn't be so sure of yourself. Even when INTC seems the strongest it gets creamed. Don't forget that.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1371045838003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 10:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371046779538-36</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371043685061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:28:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"you shouldn't be so sure of yourself. Even when INTC seems the strongest it gets creamed. Don't forget that." [It doesn't have anything to do with being sure of myself. It has to do with due diligence and the Intel technology, manufacturing, fabrication, roadmap and product pipeline. And of course I have no faith whatsoever in the morons on Wall Street to see any of it. But sooner or later fundamentals will rule the day. It looks like that day is on the way. What the cretins on Wall Street do in the meantime is a lessor concern...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371046779538</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 10:19:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371047632078-37</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371043685061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:28:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same exact lines you babbled when Intel topped 29. You have no shame to you WW?</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1371047632078</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 10:33:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371047970950-38</Id><Topic><Title>How many millions did Intel waste on intel TV?</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1371005787361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 22:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't fault Intel for being entrepreneurial, innovative companies should be willing to take risk. However, Intel's Web TV plan as announced demonstrates a serious lack of understanding of the entertainment industry and the critical factors necessary to compete in this market. The Web TV project has the look of a project hatched by tech geeks with technology looking for a problem to solve, yet completely devoid of any meaningful industry experience. It should be no surprise that Comcast is launching its own competitor to Apple TV and hence pre-empt Intel's Web TV. And it should be no surprise that Intel is finding it difficult to negotiate content deals that make good business sense. As I said before on this topic, the incumbent cable companies enjoy too many regulatory and market advantages in the U.S. for any hardware vendor (Intel or Apple) to use the cable's own infrastructure to successfully compete against them for delivery of live TV. It's not going to happen, at least not this decade. Intel should just shutdown the Web TV streaming plan and try to find a more realistic way to get their silicon inside TV's and entertainment products. I'm not concerned about the money spent on the project, it's likely too small to matter, but I would rather see them focused on opportunities they have a reasonable chance of succeeding.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1371047970950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 10:39:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371049354768-39</Id><Topic><Title>How many millions did Intel waste on intel TV?</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1371005787361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 22:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The U.S. Federal Trade Commission should investigate whether such arrangements violate antitrust laws, Rich Greenfield, an analyst at BTIG LLC, said in a report yesterday. You can be sure they will soon. Google, Apple and Intel are pushing in to the game and exclusive deals locking out others from enterance done by a group is illegel. Funny how Anti Intel nuts loves the FTC before when it was attacking Intel and now they will hate it for helping Intel.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1371049354768</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 11:02:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371049594747-40</Id><Topic><Title>How many millions did Intel waste on intel TV?</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1371005787361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 22:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.Time Warner Cable Content Incentives Thwart New Web TV By Andy Fixmer &amp; Alex Sherman - Jun 11, 2013 11:01 PM CT ..Facebook Share Tweet LinkedIn Google +1 2 Comments Print QUEUEQ..Time Warner Cable Inc. (TWC) and other pay-TV operators are offering incentives to media companies that agree to withhold content from Web-based entertainment services such as those pursued by Intel Corp. (INTC) and Apple Inc. (AAPL), people with knowledge of the matter said. Google, Intel, and Apple will rip the big cable TV providers some new holes in courts soon. The desperation from TV providers shows that the Intel TV thing will work.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1371049594747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 11:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371050479117-41</Id><Topic><Title>How many millions did Intel waste on intel TV?</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1371005787361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 22:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets all bad mouth a company that makes billions every stinking year. No, not me. They do just fine.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1371050479117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 11:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371051169419-42</Id><Topic><Title>How many millions did Intel waste on intel TV?</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1371005787361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 22:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The control cable companies have been given over cable infrastructure (which use public right-of-way) and the video and data services delivered is unquestionably anti-competitive. The problem for Intel, Apple or Google is that the status quo, however anti-competitive, is supported by the FCC, Congress, State regulatory bodies and the courts - essentially everyone that matters. These projects cannot survive without cable cooperation but there's no reason for cable companies to partner with them. The cable companies can acquire all the technology they need. I'm not saying this is the way it should be - it's simply the reality today and no full-service live streaming project that exists today can survive long enough to see the policies change.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1371051169419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 11:32:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371052085261-43</Id><Topic><Title>Apple will announce Intel on its Ipads this year, with Baytrail.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370994627423</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 19:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just a bunch of guesses but I would be interested in your take on them. One of the first things that I would do if I were Apple would be to define a new iOS API and new Xcode tool chain kit to clean up the Apps space. I would try to make it attractive for the Apps developers to migrate to. For those misbehaving Apps, I would probably just use the Intel binary translator to convert the ARM RISC code into those complex CISCy x86_64 instructions. Apple most likely has a Bay Trail prototype up and running today. They also have pretty good control over the Apps space. They have know for years what the problem Apps are and likely have converted them and tested them too.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1371052085261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 11:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371053083117-44</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Has A Secret Version Of Haswell</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371043150695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:19:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, I thought the secret version of Haswell has the NSA Seal of Approval stamped Inside. ;-\ My bad.</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1371053083117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:04:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371053754879-45</Id><Topic><Title>46k in 2 months? net PROFIT</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1366433177700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DFOM</Msg><Username>johnwillous</Username><Timestamp>1371053754879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:15:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371053757885-46</Id><Title>Ready one , two, three SELL , There goes the good old boy insider system selling there INTC stock again, Pound it down</Title><Msg>Ready one , two, three SELL , There goes the good old boy insider system selling there INTC stock again, Pound it down</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053757885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371053820811-47</Id><Topic><Title>Ready one , two, three SELL , There goes the good old boy insider system selling there INTC stock again, Pound it down</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053757885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ready one , two ,three SELL AGAIN</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053820811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:17:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371053867640-48</Id><Topic><Title>Apple will announce Intel on its Ipads this year, with Baytrail.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370994627423</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 19:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know little of the Apple code- app store- device process, but after a quick google, it looks like as a developer you compile to specific revision of the ISA (ie, ARMv7 for the later stuff), so as long as Apple added an option to compile for x86 then that would solve a bulk of problems. You would expect this to happen before a device is launched, otherwise no apps. The low level stuff (assembly code) is typically for the SIMD instructions (NEON), so image manipulation, graphics libraries, game engines that kind of stuff. This would be hard to emulate/translate and maintain any level of performance. Stackoverflow has some interesting questions/answers regarding assembly code usage under ios.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1371053867640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371053929812-49</Id><Topic><Title>Ready one , two, three SELL , There goes the good old boy insider system selling there INTC stock again, Pound it down</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053757885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ready one two three SELL AGAIN and POUND it DOWN</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053929812</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:18:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371054389965-50</Id><Title>much better now that the zero-content bs posters , aka coinmaker, lucys on ignore.</Title><Msg>life is grand</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1371054389965</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:26:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371054610365-51</Id><Topic><Title>Apple will announce Intel on its Ipads this year, with Baytrail.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370994627423</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 19:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for these good points. I still don't see Apple announcing something like that in advance of the hardware demo. More likely they will work with some developers in advance and keep things secret and, assuming they are able to provide tools to allow quick and easy recompilation of ARM code to x86, it probably would not take long to get a critical mass of ready-to-go apps available for when the device (new iPad) actually goes on sale. They usually have the demo about two weeks before the product goes on sale. They could stretch that to three or four weeks by doing the demo earlier (using the apps from their "partners" who will have had advanced access) so that they will have apps to show at the product announcement event. Then, the device goes on sale two to four weeks later during which other developers can recompile code. Of course, I could be completely wrong about this. Also, I still think it is likely that they will stick with ARM for the next generation of iPads using A7 processors and make the switch to Intel in the Fall of 2014 after the next generation of Intel processors are available which will be even more energy efficient than the just reased ones. Basically, the newly announced Intel processors are roughly on par with ARM so whether Apple uses ARM or Intel this year is not of much consequence, but by Fall of 2014, Intel's processors will be clearly superior to ARM-based processors and Apple will have to adopt Intel's processors to remain competitive. I figure there is a chance we might see Intel in, at least, full-sized iPads this Fall, but it seems more likely that will happen in the Fall of 2014. Disclosure: I am long INTC and AAPL.</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1371054610365</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:30:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371055365991-52</Id><Title>WOW there the CNBC pump again get ready for the dump, Wall Street must want out very bad</Title><Msg>WOW there the CNBC pump again get ready for the dump, Wall Street must want out very bad</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371055365991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:42:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371055472119-53</Id><Topic><Title>Ready one , two, three SELL , There goes the good old boy insider system selling there INTC stock again, Pound it down</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053757885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1.2.3 SELL again</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371055472119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371056591822-54</Id><Title>Awesome Service</Title><Msg>Can't beat getting free picks. Every single pick I've gotten has made me look like a genius. Definitely recommend to all traders. Text the word "stocks" without quotes now to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT</Msg><Username>samuellarson435</Username><Timestamp>1371056591822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371056995556-55</Id><Topic><Title>Wanna make 300% on your next stock trade??</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1366937596462</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:53:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>QVYH</Msg><Username>johnwillous</Username><Timestamp>1371056995556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:09:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371057119538-56</Id><Topic><Title>Awesome service</Title><Username>knowleslucas319</Username><Timestamp>1371053102635</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Major Information Happening</Msg><Username>wyattmack173</Username><Timestamp>1371057119538</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:11:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371057336808-57</Id><Topic><Title>Ready one , two, three SELL , There goes the good old boy insider system selling there INTC stock again, Pound it down</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053757885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are extremely short sighted aren't you? I respect you going down with your ship, all good captains do.</Msg><Username>inteldominance</Username><Timestamp>1371057336808</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:15:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371058125063-58</Id><Topic><Title>Ready one , two, three SELL , There goes the good old boy insider system selling there INTC stock again, Pound it down</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053757885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No I have watch INTC for over 20 years, Not short sighted, INTC is lower than 14 years ago, 7 years ago and 2 years ago, Not a good investment if you are hoping to make money on the stock price, Insiders are the ones making all the money. They Get free stock and then sell it, There making millions, If your lucky you might make a few dollars</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371058125063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:28:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371058366361-59</Id><Topic><Title>Ready one , two, three SELL , There goes the good old boy insider system selling there INTC stock again, Pound it down</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053757885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for 20 years its be the same old CNBC pump INTC and Then Wall Street dump INTC and the insider make all the money with there FREE STOCK over and over again</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371058366361</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:32:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371058757371-60</Id><Topic><Title>Ready one , two, three SELL , There goes the good old boy insider system selling there INTC stock again, Pound it down</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053757885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am just tired of watching people getting burned over and over again in INTC, By the CNBC PUMP and the WALL STREET dump and the INSIDERS getting there free stock and then sell it over and over again</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371058757371</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:39:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371058826850-61</Id><Topic><Title>Awesome service</Title><Username>knowleslucas319</Username><Timestamp>1371053102635</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks man, greatly appreciated</Msg><Username>acallahan950</Username><Timestamp>1371058826850</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:40:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371058862619-62</Id><Topic><Title>Ready one , two, three SELL , There goes the good old boy insider system selling there INTC stock again, Pound it down</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053757885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC ends up lower every time they burn more and more investors</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371058862619</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:41:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371059041913-63</Id><Topic><Title>Ready one , two, three SELL , There goes the good old boy insider system selling there INTC stock again, Pound it down</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053757885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CNBC keeps wondering why Investor are not coming back, All they have to do is look in the mirror and the CNBC pump and dump</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371059041913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:44:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371059934449-64</Id><Topic><Title>Awesome Service</Title><Username>samuellarson435</Username><Timestamp>1371056591822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:03:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do I sign up?</Msg><Username>walrusweener</Username><Timestamp>1371059934449</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:58:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371060278553-65</Id><Title>Nice to be in a Solid stock</Title><Msg>Feels good to be in a stock that there is no worry about day to day up and downs. When you know where a stock is going these days don't both you. Bring on $30. Thanks coinmaker though for all your silly amusement and worries about us, I promise we will be ok :)</Msg><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371060278553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371060959061-66</Id><Topic><Title>Nice to be in a Solid stock</Title><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371060278553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:04:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's sad when the board is finally quiet and then people like you try to get the bad posters back on here by instigating them. You guys can't get through a single day without some sort of chaos, which is pitiful.</Msg><Username>mark.steffenhagen</Username><Timestamp>1371060959061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:15:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371061003670-67</Id><Topic><Title>Apple will announce Intel on its Ipads this year, with Baytrail.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370994627423</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 19:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Android is bytecode - no need to re-compile except for a few exceptions. IOS apps are compiled in native ARM instructions.</Msg><Username>mrpoorguy</Username><Timestamp>1371061003670</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:16:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371061392982-68</Id><Topic><Title>Ready one , two, three SELL , There goes the good old boy insider system selling there INTC stock again, Pound it down</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053757885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like the 2 insiders don't like the truth</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371061392982</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:23:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371061831201-69</Id><Title>Can't miss this - intc</Title><Msg>If or when you are looking for information on the stock market, then you might as well see this. Link:- ln-sDOTnet/-G0m</Msg><Username>downeycharles73</Username><Timestamp>1371061831201</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:30:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371061947934-70</Id><Topic><Title>Can't miss this - intc</Title><Username>downeycharles73</Username><Timestamp>1371061831201</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:30:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>confusing indicators</Msg><Username>downeycharles73</Username><Timestamp>1371061947934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:32:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371062114639-71</Id><Topic><Title>Awesome Service</Title><Username>samuellarson435</Username><Timestamp>1371056591822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:03:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>scammer.. you'll be disputing charges on your phone if you text</Msg><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1371062114639</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:35:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371062148818-72</Id><Title>If INTC breaks $24.50 watch the really selling begin, Already lower than the CNBC pump and the Wall street dump</Title><Msg>If INTC breaks $24.50 watch the really selling begin, Already lower than the CNBC pump and the Wall street dump</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371062148818</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:35:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371062245248-73</Id><Topic><Title>If INTC breaks $24.50 watch the really selling begin, Already lower than the CNBC pump and the Wall street dump</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371062148818</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:35:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CNBC PETE the con man did a great job for Wall Street again</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371062245248</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:37:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371062330136-74</Id><Topic><Title>Nice to be in a Solid stock</Title><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371060278553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:04:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This board isn't quiet and never will be, if it does we are in trouble . Good luck in your lala land being on a board without both sides spewing nonsense.I'm sorry but your pathetic response is worse than coinmakers because yours is negative and unrealistic .</Msg><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371062330136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:38:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371062394184-75</Id><Topic><Title>Ready one , two, three SELL , There goes the good old boy insider system selling there INTC stock again, Pound it down</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053757885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One two three all the insiders SELL again</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371062394184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:39:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371062420309-76</Id><Title>Welcome to the Coinmaker77 Intel Bashing Message Board!!!</Title><Msg>Intel bashing, 24 hours a day, 7 days a week!!! No lines, no waiting!!! No content to wade through!!! Just machine gun, streamlined, content-free bashing!!!</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371062420309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:40:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371062554889-77</Id><Topic><Title>Welcome to the Coinmaker77 Intel Bashing Message Board!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371062420309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:40:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There the # one pumper wait for you to show up</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371062554889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:42:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371062688550-78</Id><Topic><Title>Ready one , two, three SELL , There goes the good old boy insider system selling there INTC stock again, Pound it down</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053757885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>one two three watch all the insiders SELL the FREE STOCK</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371062688550</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371062798749-79</Id><Topic><Title>If INTC breaks $24.50 watch the really selling begin, Already lower than the CNBC pump and the Wall street dump</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371062148818</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:35:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Come on PUMP and DUMP wallisweaver</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371062798749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:46:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371062937183-80</Id><Title>Come on no stop PUMP and DUMP wallisweaver Watched you pumpinig INTC for years</Title><Msg>Come on no stop PUMP and DUMP wallisweaver Watched you pumpinig INTC for years</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371062937183</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371063048404-81</Id><Topic><Title>Come on no stop PUMP and DUMP wallisweaver Watched you pumpinig INTC for years</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371062937183</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:48:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be one of the insiders that get all the FREE SHARES to SELL all the time with your none stop pumping</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371063048404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:50:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371063210118-82</Id><Topic><Title>Ready one , two, three SELL , There goes the good old boy insider system selling there INTC stock again, Pound it down</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371053757885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I am just tired of watching people getting burned over and over again in INTC" [The only people getting burned are those that are listening to your non-stop bashing, CoinBoy. Intel is up $5.30 since November and you have bashed the entire time - meaning, of course, that listening to you would have lost investors $5.30. You and the truth shall never meet. But, hey don't let me stop you from throwing up another 40-50 bashes today. It's what you do best...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371063210118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:53:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371063614977-83</Id><Topic><Title>Welcome to the Coinmaker77 Intel Bashing Message Board!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371062420309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:40:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This lunatic must be delusional. One thing is for sure, there has not been any dumping of INTC stock going on this year. YTD the stock is up nearly 20%. Doesn't sound like dumping to me. Keep up the good work Wallis. Good to have an intelligent follower of Intel in Ashraf through S.A.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1371063614977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:00:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371064066520-84</Id><Topic><Title>Welcome to the Coinmaker77 Intel Bashing Message Board!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371062420309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:40:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Come on, CoinBoy - you need at least a small crowd and some torches to continue with your attempt to incite the investing public. Otherwise you are just never going to get the kind of frenzy you so desperately seek. More enthusiasm, more energy, more people, more tar, more feathers, more mindless slogans!!! You can do it!!! Post, post, post!!! Go, Go, Go!!!</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371064066520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371064088665-85</Id><Topic><Title>Come on no stop PUMP and DUMP wallisweaver Watched you pumpinig INTC for years</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371062937183</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:48:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no pump and dump outside your imagination. Your activity, however, exceeds WW by 10x and you spam the same message over and over. So ... Intel is on the WSJ BUY ON WEAKNESS list today. PUMP and DUMP puts the stock on the SELL ON STRENGTH list. Intel is behaving quite normally. Intel is trading with the market with a slightly stronger RSI. There is probably some short term hedging disruption from the $41m Wells Fargo paper they sold yesterday.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1371064088665</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:08:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371064105789-86</Id><Title>Insider dumping list. Looks to me like all the insiders are dumping all they can</Title><Msg>Insider Transactions Reported - Last Two Years Date Insider Shares Type Transaction Value* Jun 3, 2013 HOLT WILLIAM MOfficer 65,494 Direct Option Exercise at $19.04 per share. 1,247,00 Jun 3, 2013 KILROY THOMAS MOfficer 41,250 Direct Option Exercise at $19.51 per share. 804,787 Jun 3, 2013 HOLT WILLIAM MOfficer 65,494 Direct Automatic Sale at $25.70 per share. 1,683,195 Jun 3, 2013 KILROY THOMAS MOfficer 41,250 Direct Automatic Sale at $25.55 per share. 1,053,937 Jun 2, 2013 KILROY THOMAS MOfficer 7,970 Direct Option Exercise at $19.04 per share. 151,748 Jun 2, 2013 JAMES RENEE #$%$fficer 41,250 Direct Automatic Sale at $25 per share. 1,031,250 Jun 2, 2013 PERLMUTTER DAVIDOfficer 535,000 Direct Option Exercise at $21.52 - $22.11 per share. 11,671,0002 Jun 2, 2013 HOLT WILLIAM MOfficer 7,919 Direct Option Exercise at $21.09 per share. 167,011 Jun 2, 2013 KILROY THOMAS MOfficer 7,970 Direct Automatic Sale at $24.99 per share. 199,170 Jun 2, 2013 HOLT WILLIAM MOfficer 7,919 Direct Automatic Sale at $25.30 per share. 200,350 Jun 2, 2013 PERLMUTTER DAVIDOfficer 535,000 Direct Automatic Sale at $25.10 per share. 13,428,500 Jun 2, 2013 JAMES RENEE #$%$fficer 41,250 Direct Option Exercise at $19.63 per share. 809,737 May 30, 2013 BRYANT ANDY DOfficer 10,960 Indirect Disposition (Non Open Market) at $0 per share. N/A May 27, 2013 HOLT WILLIAM MOfficer 83,147 Direct Option Exercise at $15.67 - $20.3 per share. N/A May 27, 2013 HOLT WILLIAM MOfficer 102,138 Direct Automatic Sale at $24.19 per share. 2,470,718 May 8, 2013 KILROY THOMAS MOfficer 57,191 Direct Automatic Sale at $24.49 per share. 1,400,607 May 8, 2013 KILROY THOMAS MOfficer 57,191 Direct Option Exercise at $19.04 per share. 1,088,916</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371064105789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:08:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371064283268-87</Id><Title>HOLY #$%$ WHAT A DEAL!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>UNXL... AMAZING LONG FOR HUGEEE GAINS INCOMING</Msg><Username>ilovetechnology66</Username><Timestamp>1371064283268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:11:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371064305139-88</Id><Topic><Title>Welcome to the Coinmaker77 Intel Bashing Message Board!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371062420309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:40:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now that's the pot calling the kettle black. Nonstop INTC pumping from Waldo going on for years and years and years. Never fear, during the next recession only INTC will thrive.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1371064305139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:11:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371064397097-89</Id><Topic><Title>Insider dumping list. Looks to me like all the insiders are dumping all they can</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371064105789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:08:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC buy back program is to buy back shares then give them to insiders for FREE so they can sell them. Its a great program for insiders</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371064397097</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:13:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371064458161-90</Id><Topic><Title>Insider dumping list. Looks to me like all the insiders are dumping all they can</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371064105789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:08:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like 4 people. Holt, Kilroy, Perlmutter and James. James .... planned sale set up in January. Perlmutter .... lost in last Intel reorg. Holt ... looks like real sales although a couple were triggered by expirations. Kilroy ... looks like real sales too. Perlmutter..... Intel CEO shakes up units, creates 'new devices' group The chipmaker's main product groups - including the PC client group, mobile communications and data center unit that previously reported to Intel Architecture group chief Dadi Perlmutter - now report directly to Krzanich. After Perlmutter transfers his business groups, he and Krzanich will "define his next significant contribution at Intel," according to the email described by the source. Renee James ... from SEC Form 4 ... was planed in January. Transactions reported on this Form 4 were made pursuant to trading instructions adopted by the undersigned on January 30, 2013 that are intended to comply with Rule 10b5-1(c).</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1371064458161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:14:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371064512921-91</Id><Title>Watch Out For These Numbers</Title><Msg>The last 5 percent correction we had the DOW jumped up from 14884 to 15200, this time around watch for: Significant Numbers To Watch . DJIA. 14444 - Support - the 04/19/2013 low 15542 - Resistance - the 5/22/2013 high 14923 - 50-day simple moving average 13854 - 200-day moving average . S&amp;P 500. 1536 - Support - the 04/18/2013 low 1687 - Resistance - the 05/22/2013 high 1605 - 50-day simple moving average 1494 - 200-day moving average . NASDAQ. 3154 - Support - the 04/18/2013 low 3532 - Resistance - the 05/22/2013 high 3349 - 50-day simple moving average 3155 - 200-day moving average If the DOW hits 14K that means a good 10 percent correction has occurred and you can tip toe back in diversifying your portfolio once again. goodluck.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1371064512921</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:15:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371064706034-92</Id><Topic><Title>Insider dumping list. Looks to me like all the insiders are dumping all they can</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371064105789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:08:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is part of the Intel compensation system. Can you show me a technology company that Intel competes with that does not have a stock based compensation system? I think they all do. If you discontinue this practice, then compensation will need to be adjusted elsewhere for Intel to be able to hire. If this is a problem for you, why complain here? Why not contact investor relations to file your complaint?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1371064706034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:18:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371064817191-93</Id><Title>Don't you just love the INTC good old boy system INTC buys back shares to give them to insiders for FREE to SELL great for insiders</Title><Msg>Not so great for investors</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371064817191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:20:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371064894112-94</Id><Topic><Title>Watch Out For These Numbers</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1371064512921</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:15:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so far, very nice symmetry on the SQQQ, ran from an intrday low of 26.40 to 29.00 at spy 1600, pulled back to 26.40 and a rally ever since approaching 29.00. If spy 500 doesn't hold, oh woe a terrible time to be long and wrong. Meanwhile, Wally, you keep pumping and sitting on your hands</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1371064894112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:21:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371064908719-95</Id><Title>Jeffries &amp; Co. raises INTC price target to $27.</Title><Msg>This was at Google Finance section on Intel.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1371064908719</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371064921940-96</Id><Topic><Title>Welcome to the Coinmaker77 Intel Bashing Message Board!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371062420309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:40:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your bashing is far worse than any PUMPING done by CNBC. Dylan Ratigan, is that you? It seems like you have an ax to grind with CNBC even more than Intel.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1371064921940</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:22:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371064961563-97</Id><Title>Market Chatter - IBM LayOffs</Title><Msg>These bas!ards layoff American workers and then they bring contract workers from overseas. I wish there was something we as US Citizens could do to punish these corporations for their behaviors. How can these #$%$ layoff workers and yet lobby for HB1 visas saying they don't have enough skilled workers. These corporations should be crucified.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1371064961563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:22:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371065076992-98</Id><Topic><Title>Don't you just love the INTC good old boy system INTC buys back shares to give them to insiders for FREE to SELL great for insiders</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371064817191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:20:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Insiders ready 1,2 ,3 SELL</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371065076992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:24:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371065087358-99</Id><Topic><Title>Don't you just love the INTC good old boy system INTC buys back shares to give them to insiders for FREE to SELL great for insiders</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371064817191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:20:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Investor do not have a problem with it. No problem for Investors. The vote for the employee compensation plan had no opposition when the shareholders voted for it. Do you know of another tech company that does not have a similar program? 3rd request.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1371065087358</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371065239972-100</Id><Title>Todays Action has caused me Vertigo Effect</Title><Msg>what a roller coaster day.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1371065239972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:27:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371065249687-101</Id><Title>Question on Dividend</Title><Msg>I HAVE 1050 SHARES OF intc. if THE PAID A 22 CENT DIVIDEND, WHY DID MY ACCOUNT ON GET CREDITED $112.50? tia</Msg><Username>richie22a</Username><Timestamp>1371065249687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:27:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371065288401-102</Id><Topic><Title>Don't you just love the INTC good old boy system INTC buys back shares to give them to insiders for FREE to SELL great for insiders</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371064817191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:20:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is tracking the market and will follow it closely because of the ETF index pressure. Intel will be a little stronger than the market until the short interest is reduced. Intel is going to track the market. Insider activity makes no difference. Intel down 1.07% NDX down 1.17%</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1371065288401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371065315708-103</Id><Topic><Title>Insider dumping list. Looks to me like all the insiders are dumping all they can</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371064105789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:08:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All selling on the same days is planed by insiders for sure, Pound it down to get more FREE SHARES at a lower price , Pump it up , SELL Pound it down 15 years of insiders control</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371065315708</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:28:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371065577985-104</Id><Topic><Title>Don't you just love the INTC good old boy system INTC buys back shares to give them to insiders for FREE to SELL great for insiders</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371064817191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:20:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC is not tracking the market Nut case. INTC is lower than 14 years ago, lower than 7 years ago and 2 years ago. Market is a lot higher than 2 years age INTC is not get your head out of your DASS</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371065577985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:32:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371065614992-105</Id><Topic><Title>Todays Action has caused me Vertigo Effect</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1371065239972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:27:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who engulfed my candle?</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1371065614992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:33:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371065708593-106</Id><Topic><Title>Don't you just love the INTC good old boy system INTC buys back shares to give them to insiders for FREE to SELL great for insiders</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371064817191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:20:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only one making any real money is the good old boy insiders</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371065708593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371065838569-107</Id><Title>INTC buy back some more shares and give them to the insiders for FREE so they can sell them all at the same time like always</Title><Msg>INTC buy back some more shares and give them to the insiders for FREE so they can sell them all at the same time like always</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371065838569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:37:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371065909679-108</Id><Topic><Title>INTC buy back some more shares and give them to the insiders for FREE so they can sell them all at the same time like always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371065838569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pound it down some more insiders</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371065909679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:38:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371065936342-109</Id><Topic><Title>Todays Action has caused me Vertigo Effect</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1371065239972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:27:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe Tiger Woods and his Ol Lady Lindsey Von..........LOL</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1371065936342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:38:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371066045866-110</Id><Title>If Most Of D Mkt Gurus Want</Title><Msg>the S&amp;P to end the year around 1575 then S&amp;P has to pullback significantly to around 1500 before resuming the ascend back to 1575 by year end.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1371066045866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:40:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371066120266-111</Id><Topic><Title>How many millions did Intel waste on intel TV?</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1371005787361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 22:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Merlot, I know you have been lukewarm on this idea since this was announced by Erik Huggers (spelling?) at Intel Media due to the privacy issue (embedded camera) as well as other competitive challenges. I am aware of the huge challenges Intel faces in all areas of providing this service: Content, Delivery, Billing, Customer Service, etc. It would be highly remiss of Intel to have not thought through the various issues in transmission of video over cable/dsl/wireless -- and developed solutions (in-house or licensed) to address these issues. Intel has said that they want to make video delivery ubiquitous - over cable lines, DSL, and wireless mobile. Though I don't claim to know the details, public carriers are required to provide access to third-parties who wish to use the carrier infrastructure. That's why we have so many mobile providers (Walmart, Cricket, Virgin, etc.) who use AT&amp;T, Verizon, and Sprint infrastructure to deliver their services. I suspect Intel may be able to work some deals with AT&amp;T, Verizon, and Sprint/Clearwire based on this. Further, I wouldn't be surprised if Intel has develop or licensed any special compression algorithms which would allow better streaming of video data to its set-top box. Also, if Intel manages to come out with a decent offering, it may well be able to acquire some companies in this area to round out its service and develop some management capabilities in parallel. Just some thoughts on how Intel may be able to pull this off. We'll see what happens.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1371066120266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371066199941-112</Id><Title>Welcome to the Coinmaker77 Intel Bashing Message Board!!!</Title><Msg>Tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat Just like a machine gun. You go, boy. Tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat, tat</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371066199941</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:43:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371066223378-113</Id><Topic><Title>INTC buy back some more shares and give them to the insiders for FREE so they can sell them all at the same time like always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371065838569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All of the tech company do this because it is part of compensation. Shareholders approved it without controversy. Can you point me to one that does not? I have not been able to find one. 4th request.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1371066223378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:43:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371066226349-114</Id><Title>From 14.844K to 15.2K Was</Title><Msg>dead cat bounce. We will have another leg down tomorrow and then a bounce on Friday. Life is great in wallst.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1371066226349</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371066313281-115</Id><Title>The real ? is why should any insider be getting Free shares with the stock lower , Revenue lower , earnings lower and margins lower</Title><Msg>The real ? is why should any insider be getting Free shares with the stock lower , Revenue lower , earnings lower and margins lower</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371066313281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:45:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371066405765-116</Id><Topic><Title>The real ? is why should any insider be getting Free shares with the stock lower , Revenue lower , earnings lower and margins lower</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371066313281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:45:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All of the tech company do this because it is part of compensation. Shareholders approved it without controversy. Can you point me to one that does not? I have not been able to find one. 5th request.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1371066405765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371066431548-117</Id><Topic><Title>From 14.844K to 15.2K Was</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1371066226349</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:43:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've called the next leg down since DOW 11k. What a boob....</Msg><Username>herbal_dud</Username><Timestamp>1371066431548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:47:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371066501003-118</Id><Topic><Title>The real ? is why should any insider be getting Free shares with the stock lower , Revenue lower , earnings lower and margins lower</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371066313281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:45:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Come on, CoinBoy - answer Alexander's question!!! Put up or put a sock in the volume bashing...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371066501003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:48:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371066543126-119</Id><Topic><Title>INTC buy back some more shares and give them to the insiders for FREE so they can sell them all at the same time like always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371065838569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If everyone is standing in front of a on coming train doesn't make it right, That is why the big TECH stocks have done nothing for years and will do nothing for years to come until the good old boy system is changed</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371066543126</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371066723076-120</Id><Topic><Title>INTC buy back some more shares and give them to the insiders for FREE so they can sell them all at the same time like always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371065838569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may make 5-10 a share if you every sell if not you will never make anything , But the insiders make $20-30 a share everytime on the FREE SHARES what a good deal for them</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371066723076</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371066766301-121</Id><Topic><Title>INTC buy back some more shares and give them to the insiders for FREE so they can sell them all at the same time like always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371065838569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coinmaker is a big baby.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1371066766301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:52:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371066814953-122</Id><Title>Low volume today</Title><Msg>nice to see</Msg><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371066814953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:53:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371067004795-123</Id><Topic><Title>The real ? is why should any insider be getting Free shares with the stock lower , Revenue lower , earnings lower and margins lower</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371066313281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:45:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you real want INTC stock to really do something the good old boy system has to go away</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371067004795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:56:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371067107823-124</Id><Topic><Title>The real ? is why should any insider be getting Free shares with the stock lower , Revenue lower , earnings lower and margins lower</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371066313281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:45:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may make $5-10 dollars if you trade INTC, but the insiders make 20-30 dollars on there FREE stock every time.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371067107823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:58:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371067143907-125</Id><Topic><Title>INTC buy back some more shares and give them to the insiders for FREE so they can sell them all at the same time like always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371065838569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If everyone is standing in front of a on coming train doesn't make it right, That is why the big TECH stocks have done nothing for years and will do nothing for years to come until the good old boy system is changed" [I've heard used car salesmen and other snake-oil salesmen with better lines than you, ConBoy. You not only a pathological liar, you are a lousy pathological liar. Fortunately you have no effect on the stock price. But it was fun poking you with a stick today. Go ahead and post up another 100 content-free distortions tomorrow. I'll keep my stick handy...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371067143907</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371067161333-126</Id><Topic><Title>The real ? is why should any insider be getting Free shares with the stock lower , Revenue lower , earnings lower and margins lower</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371066313281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:45:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you get the answer?</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371067161333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:59:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371067240316-127</Id><Title>ARM Barely Holds Off $40</Title><Msg>That must have cost some people to support...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371067240316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:00:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371067347679-128</Id><Topic><Title>The real ? is why should any insider be getting Free shares with the stock lower , Revenue lower , earnings lower and margins lower</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371066313281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:45:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you get you answer INSIDER pump and dump</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371067347679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:02:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371067504772-129</Id><Topic><Title>The real ? is why should any insider be getting Free shares with the stock lower , Revenue lower , earnings lower and margins lower</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371066313281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:45:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No but I did mark all your posts today as Abuse...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371067504772</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:05:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371067845847-130</Id><Title>Another 70 hour work week for Wallisweaver</Title><Msg>He "did his part" in society today............by his own words, .he spent all day marking Coinmakers post as abuse. Wow, what a productive day. Wallisweaver's time is very valuable, as you can see.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1371067845847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:10:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371067959301-131</Id><Topic><Title>Another 70 hour work week for Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1371067845847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh, and he hates rich people that don't do their fair share. They should follow his lead and instead of creating jobs, working hard, feeding families, donating to charities, etc...........they should be like him and mark posts as abuse on a 4th rate message board all day. You can't make this stuff up.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1371067959301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:12:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371069322422-132</Id><Topic><Title>INTC buy back some more shares and give them to the insiders for FREE so they can sell them all at the same time like always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371065838569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How you as an AMD investor has the nerve to come here and complain about excessive stock compensation is beyond me. Hypocrite is the word that comes to mind. Unlike Intel AMD does not buy back the shares it gives to its employees, they come out of existing shareholder capital and continually dilute the common stockholder. The way Intel does it is fine as the shares number is still going down and the shares the employees get provides a bit more motivation to meet deadlines than just cash would. You are a Grade 1 Idiot and you are not shy about telling the whole world about it. Go away fool and stop trolling and cluttering this board with your nonsense. If you had a few more brain cells you would realize how stupid your emotional illogical rants are.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1371069322422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:35:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371070429564-133</Id><Title>Samsung pays Apple $1 Billion sending 30 trucks full of 5 cent coins</Title><Msg>Samsung pays Apple $1 Billion sending 30 trucks full of 5 cent coins, google it. kind of funny</Msg><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1371070429564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:53:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371070535837-134</Id><Title>Off topic umc</Title><Msg>I know this is intl which I own a nice amount I also own UMC Does any one know there thoughts because the message board or umc is dead I hope umc is t dead</Msg><Username>ilcsm718</Username><Timestamp>1371070535837</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:55:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371070759822-135</Id><Title>This filthy stock will hit 23 tomorrow before it continues its fall to 19</Title><Msg>nm</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1371070759822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:59:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371070774060-136</Id><Topic><Title>How many millions did Intel waste on intel TV?</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1371005787361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 22:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have no doubt Intel is capable of doing billing, streaming content and optimizing codec technologies to reduce some of the bandwidth needed to deliver live content. I don't underestimate what Intel is good at doing. But the plan to stream live TV requires access to infrastructure and content they have to get from the very same regulated monopolies they would be competing with and those assets will not be made available to Intel, or any outside competitor on a competitive basis. See the previous posts regarding the un-level playing field regarding use of cable Internet bandwidth. Intel has access to a new codec which can help reduce bandwidth requirements around the margins but it doesn't change the overall outcome, not for cable Internet and it sure doesn't solve the issue for slower forms of transport such as DSL or anything mobile wireless where bandwidth is far more limited and controlled by the carriers. And no, I don't assume that because Intel has spent considerable money chasing this that they have some secret solution to this problem. Nothing has changed to eliminate the market advantage cable companies enjoy and there's nothing on the horizon to believe that this will change in time to save Intel's live TV streaming aspirations. And if one looks at Intel's history it is clear they invested considerable cash and energy into other misguided and mismanaged projects that had no more chance of success than this. And I say this with great fondness for the company. Note, I didn't even mention Intel's camera and facial recognition plans to monitor family members in the privacy of their homes. Given the present circumstances I think it is safe to say that the American public will think very hard before introducing another more intrusive surveillance device in their homes.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1371070774060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371071415262-137</Id><Topic><Title>INTC buy back some more shares and give them to the insiders for FREE so they can sell them all at the same time like always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371065838569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Over the past 15 years, the fully diluted share count per Intel's 10Ks: 2012 --- 5.16 2011 --- 5.41 2010 --- 5.70 2009 --- 5.66 2008 --- 5.75 2007 --- 5.94 2006 --- 5.90 2005 --- 6.18 2004 --- 6.49 2003 --- 6.62 2002 --- 6.76 2001 --- 6.88 2000 --- 6.99 1999 --- 6.94 1998 --- 7.04 1997 --- 7.10 Nearly 2 billion shares eliminated --- wait a second, what about 1st quarter, 2013? --- strike that "nearly", share count per recent quarter is 5.08 billion fully diluted shares, a full+ reduction of shares. And the beat goes on....</Msg><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1371071415262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371072851773-138</Id><Topic><Title>See you at 23 today</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1370956800051</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:20:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep. you did predict $23 YESTERDAY.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1371072851773</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:34:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371072902004-139</Id><Topic><Title>Another 70 hour work week for Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1371067845847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO 70 year old man marking posts for abuse on a dumb message board. What an utter goober.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371072902004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:35:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371073694614-140</Id><Title>New Comcas Modems with Intel inside</Title><Msg>Just more $$$$$$ for Intel. Are These the Comcast Routers You're Looking for? By Anders Bylund | More Articles June 12, 2013 | Comments (0) Comcast just introduced a far more powerful cable modem, boasting gigabit download speeds and digital video decoding right in the box. With this tool in your wiring closet, you can match the bandwidth of Verizon FiOS customers, thus joining the next generation of high-speed networking without abandoning your trusty coaxial cable fee. It's so powerful, Intel wanted to brag on providing the Atom-style chips that power this new beast. Oh, and Comcast diverted some of that extra processing and networking horsepower to provide a secondary Wi-Fi network for other Comcast customers in or near your home. That move is a tantalizing blend of convenient network access for your guests and potential liability for the host. In the video below, Fool contributor Anders Bylund discusses what the new Comcast Xfinity gateway might mean for the future of high-speed consumer-grade networking. Let's just say that Google is licking its chops as Comcast gives its users more ways to find Big G's online ads.</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1371073694614</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:48:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371074132590-141</Id><Topic><Title>Insider dumping list. Looks to me like all the insiders are dumping all they can</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371064105789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:08:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like 4 people. Holt, Kilroy, Perlmutter and James. James .... planned sale set up in January. Perlmutter .... lost in last Intel reorg. Holt ... looks like real sales although a couple were triggered by expirations. Kilroy ... looks like real sales too. Perlmutter..... Intel CEO shakes up units, creates 'new devices' group The chipmaker's main product groups - including the PC client group, mobile communications and data center unit that previously reported to Intel Architecture group chief Dadi Perlmutter - now report directly to Krzanich. After Perlmutter transfers his business groups, he and Krzanich will "define his next significant contribution at Intel," according to the email described by the source. Renee James ... from SEC Form 4 ... was planed in January. Transactions reported on this Form 4 were made pursuant to trading instructions adopted by the undersigned on January 30, 2013 that are intended to comply with Rule 10b5-1(c).</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1371074132590</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:55:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371075800876-142</Id><Topic><Title>New Comcas Modems with Intel inside</Title><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1371073694614</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:48:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it's true that the Comcast modem features an Intel Atom that is a big win for Intel. Convincing vendors and cable companies to use Intel chips in the cable company-supplied gear is the strategy Intel can win and should pursue. The same goes for getting Intel chips inside TV's and other consumer electronic devices. But to be clear, this is not the Intel branded live TV streaming service Intel's Media Group and Eric Huggers is championing.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1371075800876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 18:23:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371076069003-143</Id><Topic><Title>Another 70 hour work week for Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1371067845847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Wally, 80 hour work weeks and he's made absolutely nothing just holding INTC for an entire year, pumping endlessly all along the way. Never fear, worldwide recession coming your way, Wally will still be pumping INTC night and day.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1371076069003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 18:27:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371076692410-144</Id><Topic><Title>New Comcas Modems with Intel inside</Title><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1371073694614</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:48:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more at Intel newsroom Intel Puma 6 Powers Comcast’s New XFINITY Wireless Gateway Posted by IntelPR in Intel Newsroom on Jun 10, 2013 9:47:04 AM</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1371076692410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 18:38:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371082212134-145</Id><Topic><Title>Another 70 hour work week for Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1371067845847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Telling his flock the truth only upsets them :) Let them learn the hard way. $24 in 2011 was all he's got. No $30 in the bag and no where near his $3 eps boast. Hot air.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1371082212134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:10:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371082287600-146</Id><Topic><Title>See you at 23 today</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1370956800051</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:20:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WW predicted $3 eps 2 years ago.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1371082287600</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:11:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371082362165-147</Id><Topic><Title>Another 70 hour work week for Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1371067845847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>22-Feb-12 05:04 pm Two out of every three people receiving stock dividend payments are rich, many totally, incredibly rich and should be paying more taxes instead of us soaking the middle class. I'm sick of the deadbeat rich who are unwilling to carry their fair share of the load... wallisweaver</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1371082362165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371082412024-148</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Barely Holds Off $40</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371067240316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:00:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC has held off $30 for over a decade.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1371082412024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371082482444-149</Id><Topic><Title>The real ? is why should any insider be getting Free shares with the stock lower , Revenue lower , earnings lower and margins lower</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371066313281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:45:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul went away. Do you really think Paul would leave if greatness were right around the corner?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1371082482444</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:14:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371082995305-150</Id><Topic><Title>Question on Dividend</Title><Username>richie22a</Username><Timestamp>1371065249687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:27:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.225 div = $236.25</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1371082995305</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:23:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371083034286-151</Id><Title>They Must Be Getting Paid</Title><Msg>I have concluded that the shills on this board must be getting paid. I can't believe any real investor would post messages as consistently stupid, mindless and repetitive as we see daily from the shills. In the future I will therefore mark their posts as Abuse (which they clearly are to anyone trying to get use out of the boards). Under the caption I will put: "Volume negative but content-free posting using multiple IDs with the purpose of preventing reasonable discourse in an attempt to influence the stock price and disrupt the integrity of the message boards". I would encourage others to do the same and to not respond to the shills. While it has been fun poking the shills with a stick, it's time to get rid of these cretins. Any reasonable investigation by Yahoo will disclose their multiple ID use and the spamming quality of their posts. It's a good chance for us to see if Yahoo really does care about the quality and integrity of the message boards.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371083034286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:23:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371083129605-152</Id><Topic><Title>Market Chatter - IBM LayOffs</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1371064961563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:22:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>littledipshit, why don't YOU start a business and show all us business owners how to run it and pay big bucks and pay big taxes, and stay in business? don't forget tp pay social security taxes ans workers comp too.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1371083129605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:25:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371083579963-153</Id><Topic><Title>Don't you just love the INTC good old boy system INTC buys back shares to give them to insiders for FREE to SELL great for insiders</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371064817191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:20:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you look back 14 years or 7 years or 2 years ago, you are right. If you look at my post, I said "is" and I also put the qualifier about reduced short interested. It was clear that I was talking about the day to day trading and not some long term historical range. Intel is part of every significant INDEX and its day to day trading is highly influenced by ETF (market) trading. Intel's day to day trading will track the market and as long as their is 200mil shares of extra short interest hanging over the shares, Intel will likely trade stronger than the market as the short interest evaporates.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1371083579963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:32:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084241558-154</Id><Topic><Title>INTC buy back some more shares and give them to the insiders for FREE so they can sell them all at the same time like always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1371065838569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Insiders are making $20 to $30 per share? The very DAY that the options vest, they are required to pay the tax on that "$20-30 a share" profit on those FREE SHARES. You should know all about paying taxes if you are giving TPS guidance to all those VETS. I think that these Intel execs will be paying top tax bracket on the vesting. I can understand why Perlmutter is cashing out. BK just took his job away and left him standing after the music stopped. Some of the others passed over for CEO may not be with Intel in a few months as they go to other companies. It will give you plenty of "insider selling" info for your spams.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1371084241558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:44:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084765815-155</Id><Topic><Title>the Exynos 5 Octa, the chip may not be all it’s cracked up to be.</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1370188588800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:56:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>another bandaid from arm</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371084765815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:52:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084791734-156</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung, Intel team up to stream media from PCs to TVs</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370358133984</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:02:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung and Intel teaming up for TVs as well</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371084791734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:53:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084812383-157</Id><Topic><Title>Intel reveals Merrifield processor in new smartphone reference design, promises 'integrated sensor hub'</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370357536910</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2014: Year of the Smartphone</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371084812383</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:53:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084827252-158</Id><Topic><Title>ASUS FONEPAD 6" SMARTPHONE WITH CLOVERTRAIL (NOTE THIS IS DIFFERENT FROM THE 7" FONEPAD RUNNING Z2460)</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370249057463</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 04:44:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another design win for Intel</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371084827252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:53:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084837954-159</Id><Topic><Title>ACER ANNOUNCES ICONIA W3: WORLD'S FIRST WINDOWS 8" TABLET</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370235416603</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 00:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great device!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371084837954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:53:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084858396-160</Id><Topic><Title>Sony’s Second-Generation Duo Is a Windows 8 Slider That Makes Sense</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1370410779718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 01:39:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10 hours battery life...nice!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371084858396</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084885668-161</Id><Topic><Title>Intel shows reference design for smartphones with “Merrifield” chips</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370408353846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 00:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Merrifield SoCs will dominate smartphones in 2014!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371084885668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:54:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084890501-162</Id><Topic><Title>They Must Be Getting Paid</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371083034286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:23:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WW - the shills only come out when there is money to be made... I take their slow but steadily increasing volume of posting as a sign that the market makers, hedge funds, and/or large brokerages wish to dimimish the possibility that common folk will be able to catch educational posts from the likes of you, aa, semi-junkie, etc... If you want to see how #$%$ up a board can get from the shills and (most likely) robo-posters, look at BAC. Don't waste your time with the shills... That's what the ignore button is for. And when they come out in mass the day before action like today, I can't help but think that they are part of an organized effort to shake shares and options from "weak" hands. The stock price went down today. And it went down enough to trigger many stops... Tomorrow it, most likely, will go up again, and those who want to buy their shares back will do so at a higher price. It happens all the time. So much so that I can't accept that the market functions freely. It seems that the path is pre-determined by some manager who tells some button pusher to make the machines bring the stock price to X by this time... I'm sure there is some programmer who knows exactly how it works but signed gag order on his work... But as you have said before, at some point fundementals will eventually have to rule. It may not be until later in 2014 (3rd or 4th qtr) when the competition has been proven out researched and manufactured, AND the market data shows INTC owning the market. Despite what you post, I believe the next big event is the July earnnigs report. Everything else has been leaked, or is baked into the price. Shares won't pop before then, and depending on how the market gods decide to spin the report, in context of the reports of ARMH, and others, may not pop then. But the 4th quarter, IMHO, holds promise... Hold your shares, or position accordingly.</Msg><Username>jeffreyklotzlongmeadow</Username><Timestamp>1371084890501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:54:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084897995-163</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Global 4G LTE modem will ship in the Samsung GALAXY Tab 3 10.1 within weeks</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1370392554081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:35:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has LTE!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371084897995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:54:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084925723-164</Id><Topic><Title>Is the Samsung Galaxy S 4 coming with an Intel mobile chip? (update)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370438010507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>June 20 Samsung Event should be exciting!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371084925723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084942961-165</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Cortex 12: Too Little, Too Late</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370410288409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 01:31:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>something wrong with A15 for arm to do this!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371084942961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:55:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084954914-166</Id><Topic><Title>June 20: Samsung announces new Windows and Android products in London</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370448077728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>June 20, I have it marked !</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371084954914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084964093-167</Id><Topic><Title>Sony VAIO Duo 13"</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1370458635321</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:57:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome device!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371084964093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:56:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084982760-168</Id><Topic><Title>Y Haswells</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370457012085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:30:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These will provide fanless tablets!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371084982760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:56:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371084993069-169</Id><Topic><Title>Fujitsu Lifebook UH90/L is Purportedly the World's Thinnest Ultrabook</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370487611085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:00:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice find!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371084993069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:56:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371085005521-170</Id><Topic><Title>GALAXY TAB 3 10" WITH LTE 4G SUPPORT WORLDWIDE</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370526078670</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:41:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This just the tip of the iceberg!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371085005521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371085023524-171</Id><Topic><Title>Rumor – Samsung to Release Intel-Powered Version of Galaxy S4</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370526284139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:44:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hope so!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371085023524</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371085049126-172</Id><Topic><Title>Dell XPS 11 combines the best of Lenovo's Yoga and Microsoft's Surface</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370531664364</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:14:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Dell XPS 11 will sell better than the Yoga!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371085049126</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:57:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371085062220-173</Id><Topic><Title>Another Intel slide showing Samsung Galaxy S4 phone</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1370539621062</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:27:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good find</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371085062220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:57:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371085093493-174</Id><Topic><Title>HP to launch fanless Haswell-powered tablet later this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1370546281005</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:18:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can wait to see these Haswell fanless tablets!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371085093493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:58:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371085106373-175</Id><Topic><Title>June Calendar: Still More to Come!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370575277369</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:21:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good summary Wallis!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371085106373</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371085134253-176</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Apps Processor Outperforms NVIDIA, Qualcomm, Samsung, According to ABI Research</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1370619665023</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This report is really amazing. Everyone should read this!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371085134253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:58:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371085229295-177</Id><Topic><Title>New Comcas Modems with Intel inside</Title><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1371073694614</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:48:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great find!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371085229295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:00:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371085394974-178</Id><Topic><Title>The new MacBook Air with Haswell on the way</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371012103776</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 00:41:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With 80% more battery life, these should sell very well!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371085394974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371085901060-179</Id><Topic><Title>June Calendar: Still More to Come!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370575277369</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:21:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vinnie - due to your lack of original content, and incessant regurjatory posting, welcome to ignore...</Msg><Username>jeffreyklotzlongmeadow</Username><Timestamp>1371085901060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:11:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371086119802-180</Id><Topic><Title>They Must Be Getting Paid</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371083034286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:23:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>p.s. I think you too are "getting paid"...</Msg><Username>jeffreyklotzlongmeadow</Username><Timestamp>1371086119802</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:15:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371086230484-181</Id><Title>SETTING UP FOR BIG BOUNCE TOMORROW!</Title><Msg>- Haswell, with tremendous battery life improvement will start the PC refresh. Every company will start upgrading their workers with hybrids machines with Haswell inside - Consumers too will look to upgrade to a hybrid machine. Hybrids offer the best of both worlds in one device (2 for 1) and most consumers will elect to buy a hybrid. Some will decide on a tablet. For that, Intel will be rolling out Bay Trail tablets that run full Windows 8 with legacy software support making the device much better BYOD. Bay Trail tablets can also be configured with dual boot so that consumers can run both Windows 8 and Android in one device. The Intel advantage is clear - By end of this year, Intel will begin shipping Merrifield SoCs and begin their assault on the smartphone market. With the XMM 7160 modem, Intel now have the support for LTE 4G and will begin making their mark on the US smartphone market. - With PE less than 12 and Intel expecting record revenues this year, its clear Intel there is only one direction INTC stock is going...UP</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371086230484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:17:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371086383227-182</Id><Topic><Title>Textbook Case: Low Volume Pullback</Title><Username>booman587</Username><Timestamp>1370983454825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 16:44:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today followed the same low volume pullback motif as yesterday. Volume today was about 24.5million.</Msg><Username>booman587</Username><Timestamp>1371086383227</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:19:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371086763765-183</Id><Topic><Title>the Exynos 5 Octa, the chip may not be all it’s cracked up to be.</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1370188588800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:56:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm surprised this piece is news is not getting any press. This is serious design flaw!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371086763765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:26:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371086936628-184</Id><Topic><Title>Another 70 hour work week for Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1371067845847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pathetic, entitled Liberal.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1371086936628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371086983963-185</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst: Intel Atom chip outperforms Nvidia, Qualcomm and Samsung</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370619798024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:43:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again, I'm surprise there not more press around this piece of news! Intel is 5-year-old architecture on old 32nm technology is already beating the #$%$ out of the best of arm. Bay Trail/Merrifield will destroy the competition. Its very clear how this is going to play out.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1371086983963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:29:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371088208151-186</Id><Topic><Title>They Must Be Getting Paid</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371083034286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:23:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The shills must be using PC or such, it's hard to be productive using ARM tablet . With they pennies they accumulate it will take them a year buy a Haswell machine.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1371088208151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:50:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371088618231-187</Id><Title>500 Million PCs Forecasted To Ship In 2013 On Surging Tablet Sales</Title><Msg>HotHardware 500 Million PCs Forecasted To Ship In 2013 On Surging Tablet Sales Wednesday, June 12, 2013 - by Seth Colaner What was that we were saying about the “PC market” needing to be redefined to include tablets? More market predictions are out, and this one from Canalys includes tablets in the mix, which paints a different picture of the PC market from one that’s experiencing lagging sales to one that is simply evolving to include a wider breadth of form factors in its sales numbers. When including tablets, Canalys predicts that the PC market will see 7% year-over-year growth, from 459.6 million in 2012 to 493.1 million--nearly half a billion--in 2013. In 2017, the firm forecasts shipments of PCs to reach 713.8 million. Driving this bus will be tablets. Last year, Canalys lists desktops with 111 million units shipped, notebooks at 234 million, and tablets at 114.6 million. In 2013, both desktop and notebook shipments will dip to 105 million and 205.6 million, respectively, while tablets will jump to 182.5 million. If Canalys’ predictions for 2017 hold true, the PC landscape will be totally different; tablet shipments will explode to 456.1 million, while desktops and notebooks will drop down to 85.8 million and 171.9 million, respectively.</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1371088618231</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:56:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371088632460-188</Id><Topic><Title>They Must Be Getting Paid</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371083034286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:23:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a crybaby and a pumping shill with no morals, values or conscience. Dweeb.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1371088632460</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371090209696-189</Id><Title>Asian markets are crashing tonite...</Title><Msg>WTH is going on in Japan &amp; China?!?</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1371090209696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 22:23:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371090403628-190</Id><Topic><Title>Another 70 hour work week for Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1371067845847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BEWARE: This whole thread was started and replied by the same individual</Msg><Username>iknow.whoyouare</Username><Timestamp>1371090403628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 22:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371090448128-191</Id><Title>chump.weaver = backbay_bstn</Title><Msg>Beware of this sick individual and his B S</Msg><Username>iknow.whoyouare</Username><Timestamp>1371090448128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 22:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371090757990-192</Id><Title>Beware of this sick individual</Title><Msg>He uses the following aliases and will often use one or more of these aliases to respond to the same bashing/disruptive post which he started with another alias. His intent is to disrupt this message board and confused current/would-be INTC investors. tiglet2l ghostupinhere backpain_bstn boiled_n_oil chump.weaver will_amd_yu backbay_bstn att4glte aintezbeingreen wdblawgrow wallisdreamweaver fourteennanometer itakebackmyapology dominateamerika singhlion2001 coinmaker77 jimbohomegameedyall aulus_vitellius_germanicus geraldmcginty walrusweener</Msg><Username>iknow.whoyouare</Username><Timestamp>1371090757990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 22:32:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371093713537-193</Id><Topic><Title>500 Million PCs Forecasted To Ship In 2013 On Surging Tablet Sales</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1371088618231</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:56:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This underscores the point that the "PC" has been on a long and predictable path of introducing new form factors since the development of the desktop, which then added the tower, notebooks, netbooks, ultrabooks, mini's, NUCs and now tablets. The trajectory of the past 30 years has been toward smaller more mobile form factors that offer the PC experience. The tablet as a PC, the smartphone as a PC and even wearable computers are merely next steps in the PC evolution. It is difficult to see any productive discourse from the "PC is dead" crowd other than to promote the ARM dream, but now with Haswell and Silvermont that argument doesn't even work.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1371093713537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 23:21:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371094099049-194</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Global 4G LTE modem will ship in the Samsung GALAXY Tab 3 10.1 within weeks</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1370392554081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:35:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My understand is it's date LTE, not voice - voice LTE late '13, early '14. Per reports, and Intel CEO comments in a recent conference call. (Someone correct me if that's not accurate)!</Msg><Username>clcellve</Username><Timestamp>1371094099049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 23:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371094238421-195</Id><Topic><Title>Another 70 hour work week for Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1371067845847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama ?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1371094238421</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 23:30:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>