<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-17"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363493027213-1</Id><Topic><Title>Intel/Apple Alternatives and the Intelligence of Mr. Market</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363466781864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 16:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gregory.lynn, Intel's 32nm SoCs are already as good as the best ARM stuff. The lead will come at 22nm ;)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363493027213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 00:03:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363493729275-2</Id><Topic><Title>Dual booth Android and Window devices will be the Ace</Title><Username>only_paper_money</Username><Timestamp>1363488113514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 22:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From an Engineering standpoint its not that complex and typically this is the only standpoint Intel takes. From an end use standpoint, dual-boot is adding unnecessary complexity to a single OS. It's much like Windows 8 which has a metro mode and a classic mode.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1363493729275</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 00:15:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363494461407-3</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 Sucks!</Title><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1363490678531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 23:24:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"INTC hit a 52 week low after MSFT released Windows 8. Looks like the so called 'Ultrabooks' aren't so Ultra running MSFT's latest crapware. Ultrabooks might sell better if they ran a different OS that had a Start Menu." [Well, you're a little clueless about the dynamics. Windows 8 was released but there was a lag with the hardware to support it, particularly with tablets. There is huge pent up demand for a good tablet running Windows 8 from IT professionals and other business people. Windows 8 is going to be a product much more on mobility than on desktops. So, a lot of the new form factors are just now coming to market. It will therefore be 6 or even 12 months before it makes much sense to judge the success. The real power as already stated by a number of people on this board is that Windows is one of the few operating systems that can cover a complete ecosystem from desktops to laptops to to Ultrabooks to tablets and to phones. This may be a slow developing factor but it is an extremely important factor. As usual, critics like you are incapable of more than a two sentence analysis with any of your criticisms, and most of that is used to call people, companies or products names. The Windows deployment is likely to get stronger and stronger but Intel is also wise in addressing the Android market. Dual boot is a great competitive advantage...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363494461407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 00:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363494802056-4</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 Sucks!</Title><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1363490678531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 23:24:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BS. Windows 8 was released with a $40 upgrade for Windows 7 users. Obviously there was tons of hardware out there on which it could run.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1363494802056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 00:33:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363494876714-5</Id><Topic><Title>Dual booth Android and Window devices will be the Ace</Title><Username>only_paper_money</Username><Timestamp>1363488113514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 22:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Windows 8 is complicated so is dual boot. People will stick with straight Android tablets, mostly ARM based and the richer ones may get iPad. In the tablet space, the tone has been set by the iPad which is a very easy to use product. A novice user can start using one in minutes. Microsoft seems to overlook this fact with their design of their new OS." [Yet more of the lame analysis that you used to predict that RT would be a success. And instead we found out that people wanted exactly what you said they wouldn't. No matter how many times you say it, it won't be true. People want more capability than they can get out of an iPad or an ARM Android tablet. And even kids as opposed to you have no problems with a Windows-based system. I don't know why you consider everyone's computer needs as under-developed as yours...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363494876714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 00:34:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363495380202-6</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 Sucks!</Title><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1363490678531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 23:24:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't take advice from Troll penguins</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1363495380202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 00:43:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363495876684-7</Id><Topic><Title>Dual booth Android and Window devices will be the Ace</Title><Username>only_paper_money</Username><Timestamp>1363488113514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 22:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Dual boot in the past has been just rewriting the master boot record and then installing the new OS on a section of the disk. The articles I found with a quick search don't indicate any complexity." [khitchdee says you need to keep a master boot record only if you have bought more than three pairs...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363495876684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 00:51:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363496034701-8</Id><Topic><Title>Dual booth Android and Window devices will be the Ace</Title><Username>only_paper_money</Username><Timestamp>1363488113514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 22:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're obviously obsessed with RT.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1363496034701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 00:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363496065974-9</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 Sucks!</Title><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1363490678531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 23:24:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"BS. Windows 8 was released with a $40 upgrade for Windows 7 users. Obviously there was tons of hardware out there on which it could run." [It's designed to run with touch screens, butkus...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363496065974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 00:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363496229967-10</Id><Topic><Title>Dual booth Android and Window devices will be the Ace</Title><Username>only_paper_money</Username><Timestamp>1363488113514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 22:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You're obviously obsessed with RT." [Just with seeing Microsoft end this failed ARM experiment that may cause some people to think Intel based systems are this lame...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363496229967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 00:57:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363496663219-11</Id><Title>This is what khitchdee wrote on Dec. 28, 2012 regarding Windows 8</Title><Msg>"What this author doesn't account for is the way Windows 8 convolutes the mix. With Windows 8, the line between tablet and laptop/desktop completely blurs since the OS fully supports both platforms. Secondly, as you can see, Intel is bringing down the power consumption of its elite core series chips down to tablet levels. What we are going to see is desktop and laptops being replaced by a slew of touch enabled form factors all combining the features of laptops with tablets with touch. From the consumer's perspective, they are buying devices that have all the power and functionality of a desktop/laptop with the added convenience of a tablet. Its a win-win for the consumer and Intel. Since we're starting from the laptop/desktop end, you can expect them to pay the same price that they were used to before. Since we're also supporting the tablet form factor with a hybrid design, the total size of the market grows to include the tablet market." [khitchdee, you are one sick cookie]</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363496663219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 01:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363497134758-12</Id><Title>Intel is Well-Positioned on Three Operating Systems</Title><Msg>[Android, Windows, or Tizen. Intel is prepared to do them all. And has a chance at an expanded relationship iwth Samsung on Tizen...] "The truth is that Samsung needs Google more that Google needs Samsung, because the company's smartphones and tablets run on Android. In fact, the Android OS is the reason Samsung has become the biggest smartphone manufacturer in the world. For now, Samsung is stuck with the Android operating system and Google, even if it would prefer to get a divorce. Ever since Google bought Motorola, Samsung has seen the writing on the wall. That writing says that the two companies are officially competitors and have different interests. While Google is not making any money from Motorola yet, the fact is that it sees very big potential based on the amount of money Samsung is making. Sooner or later, Google will want to copy Samsung's model and also cash in on hardware sales, in addition to the ad revenue from mobile devices. Samsung has probably known this for some time now, and is making preparations for parting from Google and the Android OS altogether. Samsung has confirmed that it will roll out a new smartphone that will run on the Tizen OS that is fully supported by Intel (INTC). In fact, Japan's NTT DoCoMo (DCM) has agreed to carry the phone. But Google also has a problem. If Samsung stops supporting the Android OS and rolls out a Galaxy phone running the Tizen OS, that might shrink Android's market share. And Samsung might just become successful at it, knowing how it makes such high quality phones. And if Samsung is successful, what's to stop Tizen from becoming an Android competitor?" From George Kesarios</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363497134758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 01:12:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363497389556-13</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is Well-Positioned on Three Operating Systems</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363497134758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 01:12:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Tizen project resides within the Linux Foundation and is governed by a Technical Steering Group (TSG) composed of Intel and Samsung. From Wikepedia</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363497389556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 01:16:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363497573240-14</Id><Topic><Title>Intel/Apple Alternatives and the Intelligence of Mr. Market</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363466781864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 16:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another new addition to the list... So how smart is Mr. Market: Nothing in the stock price for an Apple deal that could eventually result in Intel doing all of Apple's fabrication. Nothing in the stock price for Intel's highly profitable, cash cow deal with Altera, and the deal with Acronix. Nothing in the stock price for Haswell which will be arriving sooner than expected. Nothing in the stock price for Intel 14nm FinFET arriving at the end of the year. Nothing in the stock price for Clover Trail or Bay Trail. Nothing in the stock price for the new deal with ZTE. Nothing in the stock price for the new smartphones by Lenovo and Xolo. Nothing in the stock price for the FonePad by Asus. Nothing in the stock price for the success of the Surface Pro. Nothing in the stock price for the Cisco deal. Nothing in the stock price for ARM's delays at 20nm. Nothing in the stock price for ARM not having FinFET for years and years and years. Nothing in the stock price for Intel's web TV project. Nothing in the stock price for a potential iWatch deal. Nothing in the stock price for more big foundry deals. We know one big one is in the works. Nothing in the stock price for dual booting of both Windows 8 and Android. Nothing in the stock price for Intel's partnership with Samsung on Tizen.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363497573240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 01:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363498352430-15</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is Well-Positioned on Three Operating Systems</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363497134758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 01:12:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel and Samsung were chosen to keep each other honest. Intel is around to ensure that Samsung doesn't attempt to embed all of its technology and dominate the operating system at the expense of other handset vendors, while Samsung is there to ensure the OS will work with any mobile chip.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363498352430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 01:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363498534030-16</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is Well-Positioned on Three Operating Systems</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363497134758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 01:12:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel and Samsung, as well as numerous partners, believe that HTML5-based applications will eventually be more widespread and competitive that programs designed for particular eco-systems, such as Apple iOS or Google Android.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363498534030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 01:35:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363499148759-17</Id><Title>Roku will be adding Miracast to it's device</Title><Msg>Looks like Roku is preparing for competition from Intel's upcoming set-top box, which will have a WiDi receiver. BTW, WiDi also supports Miracast. I really hope that Intel will market its upcoming set-top box as a stand-alone box and not just for use with it's Web TV service. This way, they will be generating revenue from 2 markets - Web TV service and the Streaming/DVR player market. Roku and Tivo generate roughly $500 million/ year in revenue. If Intel can capture some of that market, it will be like icing on the cake. BTW, there's been some negative views on the camera on this set-top (which has a shutter to disable it), but on the positive side, it allows for video-conferencing. Intel can also market this set-top to businesses that might want a way to video-conference or use it as a projector with it's WiDi feature. You know, the more I think about Intel's Web TV project, the more I like it. Intel's Web TV is like how Netflix began streaming movies over the Web. But Intel is taking it to the next level by streaming live TV. This has a lot of potential. Just like Netflix can market itself to have it's service added to devices like Roku, MS Xbox, and Apple TV, Intel can do the same with it's Web TV service. By having control over this service, Intel is in a much better position to bargain for having its chip inside these devices. Also, Intel can work with Smart TV manufacturers like Samsung to allow it's Web TV services added on the condition that the Smart TV have Intel inside.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363499148759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 01:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363503575577-18</Id><Topic><Title>Dual booth Android and Window devices will be the Ace</Title><Username>only_paper_money</Username><Timestamp>1363488113514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 22:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For those who want access to dual environments, dual boot is one way. The VM environments are very nice too. Neither is very complex from a user view today. They are quite robust. The increased flexibility will be very useful in a number of usage models. There will be those who will not need nor want a more "complex" configuration. You sound like a simpler configuration works for you. That is great. I will be building more robust configurations for my needs.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363503575577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 02:59:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363503814514-19</Id><Topic><Title>Dual booth Android and Window devices will be the Ace</Title><Username>only_paper_money</Username><Timestamp>1363488113514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 22:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Users who want access to two operating systems are power users since they know about the boot process of an OS. Average users don't know. You could argue that the number of power users is growing, but absolutely, its very small and will likely remain so.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1363503814514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 03:03:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363505022364-20</Id><Topic><Title>Dual booth Android and Window devices will be the Ace</Title><Username>only_paper_money</Username><Timestamp>1363488113514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 22:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is good. That means the "complexity" issue is one that will be confined to power users who know how to handle it. All the others won't have any problem. That is great!</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363505022364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 03:23:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363506510935-21</Id><Topic><Title>Intel/Apple Alternatives and the Intelligence of Mr. Market</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363466781864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 16:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel's 32nm SoCs are already as good as the best ARM stuff. The lead will come at 22nm ;) ---- Yeah right, on both points *cough*:) gregory.lynne is right, it's the 14nm node that the ARM guys fear. Intel still has to get the CPU and GPU design right and get it to market at the right time...</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1363506510935</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 03:48:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363527043725-22</Id><Topic><Title>A post from Khitchdees other personality regarding Surface Pro</Title><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1363349088151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 08:04:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hilariious. I bet KHITCHDEE's hands tremble like he's had twelve cups of coffee spiked with Red Bull when he types. He doesn't know if he's coming or going.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363527043725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:30:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363528080868-23</Id><Title>ARMH assualt on Intel next Bread and butter product XEON ak Server Chips:UNIVA AUTOMATES ARM INFRASTRUCTURE FOR HADOOP</Title><Msg>UNIVA AUTOMATES ARM INFRASTRUCTURE FOR HADOOP Beta version of Grid Engine for ARM available for HPC, analytics and cloud deployments 14 February 2013 by Yevgeniy Sverdlik - DatacenterDynamics Univa, provider of workload-management software for data centers, has rolled out a version of its platform that supports IT infrastructure built on ARM processors. Gary Tyreman, Univa CEO, said the company viewed ARM chips as the next “Lego block” in the building of next-generation data centers, similar to the addition of accelerators and graphics processing units (GPUs) to make modern applications perform better. There will be a mix of processor architectures in data centers in the near future, which will include ARM servers running some applications and x86 servers running others. Univa released the beta version of its Grid Engine software for ARM early on so customers can start testing it, Tyreman said. There are multiple applications that are core for Univa’s technology, including serial and parallel ones, such as Hadoop. Grid Engine can schedule serial jobs and complex parallel ones on a single shared infrastructure. Hadoop and high-performance-computing applications are Univa’s primary targets. Automation of data center resources for cloud infrastructure is another obvious use. Adoption of ARM chips for servers is going to accelerate because of the typical modern data center concerns: space, power and cooling resources. So-called “wimpy-core” chips address all three, Tyreman says. ARM Holdings is a UK company that licenses its processor designs to chip makers. Its processors are currently dominating the mobile-device market, while also picking up momentum in the server space. Univa started support for wimpy-core processors with ARM, as opposed to Intel’s rival product Atom, because, in Tyreman’s view, the former has greater momentum in the server space than the latter does. Grid Engine does not support Atom at this time, but “we will,” he said. ARM’s momentum is about to increase further because first server chips using the 64-bit version of the architecture are already on the market, and more are expected to become available next year. Applied MIcro announced availability of its 64-bit ARM server processor called X-Gene in January and said it expected multiple vendors to ship servers with the chips inside by the end of the year. Calxeda, Applied Micro’s rival in the ARMs race, plans to release its 64-bit product in 2014. Univa uses servers based on Calxeda’s 32-bit ARM chips to develop Grid Engine.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1363528080868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:48:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363528089539-24</Id><Topic><Title>Dual booth Android and Window devices will be the Ace</Title><Username>only_paper_money</Username><Timestamp>1363488113514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 22:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You will see it even if Windows sales increase.. It will happen because a system that dual boots or multi-boots is more useful, more functional and worth more than a system that has access to only one software ecosystem. In addition to multi-boot, devices that use Core x86 can run nearly every operating system in existence using virtual machine software. So if an Intel tablet user wants to access the applications of a different software ecosystem they will a couple ways to do this, 1). Multi-boot for best performance or 2). Run a virtual machine under Windows for best convenience and still very good performance. The point is that if you've paid for good hardware there's no reason one should be limited to just one OS alone. The added flexibility also increases the resale value when one is ready to upgrade. ARM promoters hate the Windows multi-OS feature because they know they can't offer this no matter what they do their chip.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1363528089539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:48:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363528308203-25</Id><Topic><Title>Dual booth Android and Window devices will be the Ace</Title><Username>only_paper_money</Username><Timestamp>1363488113514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 22:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Windows 8 is complicated so is dual boot. People will stick with straight Android tablets, mostly ARM based and the richer ones may get iPad" Yet just 3 days ago you posted that the sales numbers have spoken and Microsoft had "a verifiable hit on their hands" with the Surface Pro. You are just lonely and like to have someone to talk to. Not even you believe 103% of the BS you post up.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363528308203</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:51:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363528342871-26</Id><Topic><Title>A post from Khitchdees other personality regarding Surface Pro</Title><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1363349088151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 08:04:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump. Khitchdee the hypocrite exposed.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363528342871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:52:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363528396589-27</Id><Title>CONCLUSION:::LONG TERM ARMH Keeps the lead over Intel 2013 and beyond.................</Title><Msg>Regardless of Intel's progress in developing power-saving semiconductor hardware, ARM will retain a fundamental advantage over Intel x86-based processors through ARM's simpler and more power-efficient instruction-set and design philosophy. Intel is working hard to erode ARM's power-efficiency advantage through industrial leadership in the development of many new semiconductor manufacturing technologies; however, ARM's strategic partnership with IBM, another industrial giant in semiconductor fabrication (as part of a broad industrial alliance) for the development of a standardised 14nm semiconductor manufacturing process for the fabrication of ARM processors and SoCs will help to ensure that ARM will not fall far behind Intel in this important field. Intel will continue expending significant amounts of money on research and development to retain their lead in process technology so as to neutralise ARM's fundamental design advantages as far as they can; but with process technology rapidly approaching the CMOS endpoint, Intel's CMOS research advantage will soon suffer from a law of diminishing returns. The antiquated and excessively complex Intel x86 instruction set, once an asset of Intel, is becoming a net liability for Intel, yet this is a liability Intel cannot easily offload without losing even more market-share to ARM in semiconductor design and associated intellectual property. Other fundamental advantages conferred on ARM by their superior (simpler) instruction-set architecture include: Simpler design requirements for optimising compilers (so that good software development tools cost less to develop and are likely to produce more reliable and more efficient code), Simpler methods of verifying the correctness and security of ARM's comparatively open designs; meaning less chances of a product recall or security debacle. A less intricate and less complex end-product requiring less energy and less raw materials for its manufacture. Superior manufacturing yield. ARM's strategy of building broad and equitable industrial partnerships (e.g. in semiconductor fabrication) effectively neutralises Intel's scale and cash advantage and courts the attention of customers who like the inherent economy and security of a market of multiple competing suppliers with compatible products (and who dislike the monopolistic practice of vendor lock-in). ARM's strategy (supported by an increasingly mature software-based design technologies) of effectively decoupling the semiconductor design and fabrication industries into separate markets confers on the ARM ecosystem the strengths of any or all of its participants.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1363528396589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363528871710-28</Id><Title>Irresponsible for Intel to have plants in Israel</Title><Msg>Israel is getting closer to war each day &amp; Intel management decides to build a leading fab in the middle of that country. another absurd decision by Intel execs. Disservice to shareholders.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1363528871710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:01:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363529108358-29</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is Well-Positioned on Three Operating Systems</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363497134758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 01:12:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is nothing stopping Tizen from becoming an Android competitor. Android is basically a Linux derivative that can be replicated by anyone. Certainly there is a lot of work to be done to create a consumer-ready marketplace withs apps but Samsung can create its own "Android" clone, marketplace and even run Android apps. We should welcome the competiton because Google is guilty of bloating Android software with many apps designed to serve Google's interest and not that of consumers.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1363529108358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:05:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363529403101-30</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH assualt on Intel next Bread and butter product XEON ak Server Chips:UNIVA AUTOMATES ARM INFRASTRUCTURE FOR HADOOP</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1363528080868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:48:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What can you say about a company that puts out press release after press release about what it's going to do? All the success In smartphones and tablets ARM has experience in the past five has been from Apple. Either directly as in the case of iPhone and iPad sales or indirectly as in the case of most Android phones. Look at ARM's failures. Nobody, not even Samsung can make an iPad replacement that comes close in sales to the iPad. All the rival operating systems from HP/Blackberry/ and even Microsoft with ARM have been failures. Unless Apple wants to get into the rack mounted server world you are reading about the next big ARM failure. Intel eats competitors like ARM for breakfast in the server world. As has been said many times before this is at best 10% of the entire server market ARM can ever hope to go after. This press release is written for uninformed ARMH investors who need to buy into the fairy tail of why ARMH needs a P/E over 70 when the writing on the wall says differently.</Msg><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1363529403101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:10:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363529605078-31</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH assualt on Intel next Bread and butter product XEON ak Server Chips:UNIVA AUTOMATES ARM INFRASTRUCTURE FOR HADOOP</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1363528080868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:48:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM pounded press releases about RT, too. lolololololololol</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363529605078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:13:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363530292768-32</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Stats</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363476866048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 19:34:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The price of the stock doesn't entertain me all that much. Whenever ARMH perceives trouble in their stock price they simply create a new press release and tell the world how they will dominate servers in the next 12 months. What does entertain me more is their hitting the market with quadcore solutions to smartphones. It only proves that ARM is out of ideas about how to grow their technology.</Msg><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1363530292768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:24:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363530618225-33</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 Sucks!</Title><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1363490678531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 23:24:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, Windows 8 with Metro is a good fit for tablets and it should do well on touch-enabled portable devices, but it is difficult to overstate the stupidity of Microsoft forcing Metro on every x86 device with no ability to use Metro and no ability to restore the W7 desktop.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1363530618225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:30:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363530960027-34</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is Well-Positioned on Three Operating Systems</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363497134758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 01:12:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would say there is a 50% chance they warn this week.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1363530960027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:36:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363531739866-35</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH assualt on Intel next Bread and butter product XEON ak Server Chips:UNIVA AUTOMATES ARM INFRASTRUCTURE FOR HADOOP</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1363528080868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:48:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On emagic word is teh focus here: Margin hell future Revenue decline future And Fraud street Banksters reward what and punish what???? Don't be emotional fools in our Biggest Fraud Street Casino in USA</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1363531739866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:48:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363532073797-36</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH assualt on Intel next Bread and butter product XEON ak Server Chips:UNIVA AUTOMATES ARM INFRASTRUCTURE FOR HADOOP</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1363528080868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:48:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What can you say about a company that puts out press release after press release about what it's going to do? All the success In smartphones and tablets ARM has experience in the past five has been from Apple. Either directly as in the case of iPhone and iPad sales or indirectly as in the case of most Android phones. Look at ARM's failures. Nobody, not even Samsung can make an iPad replacement that comes close in sales to the iPad. All the rival operating systems from HP/Blackberry/ and even Microsoft with ARM have been failures. Unless Apple wants to get into the rack mounted server world you are reading about the next big ARM failure. ----- It's not an ARM press release....ARM in phones had nothing to do with the iPhone as it was in most phones before it was released. It was Nokia who started the ball rolling for ARM in phones. ARM is so far down the design cycle that it little or no influence on products such as tablets or servers. It's the SoC designers and the OEMs that drive these things.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1363532073797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:54:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363532181483-37</Id><Title>Ballmer has to be the dumbest CEO in tech-land</Title><Msg>Surface RT, Win 8, Almost any version of MS-Word....the only reason we have to tolerate this #$%$ is because they are a monopoly. I hope these new options start to take hold.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363532181483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363532254550-38</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Stats</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363476866048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 19:34:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does entertain me more is their hitting the market with quadcore solutions to smartphones. It only proves that ARM is out of ideas about how to grow their technology. ---- :) You give ARM too much credit, it's the SoC designers - they make the choices.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1363532254550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:57:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363532368297-39</Id><Topic><Title>Irresponsible for Intel to have plants in Israel</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1363528871710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:01:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ordinarily the location of a multi-billion dollar fab is not too much of a concern for shareholders but speaking purely from a business perspective one has to acknowledge the risk to a fab in Isreal is far greater than other locations Intel could choose. And the risk isn't just phyiscal assets. In a time of crisis employees understandably have to put the safety of their families first and they just may not be able to show up for work - nor would anyone expect them to. Still though, closures and temporary shutdowns can be costly. When Intel has so many good options for a multi-billion dollar fab why expose the company and shareholders to the risk?</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1363532368297</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:59:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363533129183-40</Id><Topic><Title>Importan info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>seanlacroix518</Username><Timestamp>1363042083166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 18:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks a lot</Msg><Username>jablonski.henry</Username><Timestamp>1363533129183</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:12:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363533657850-41</Id><Topic><Title>Calxeda’s first ARM server is a serious threat to x86 server domination</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363272697872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:51:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's your take on HPQ Project Moonshot as a Caldexa ally/competitor? From what I've read, HPQ kicked off the project with Redstone based on Caldexa-designed ARM chips, but since then has moved on to Gemini (announced for Q2/13 launch) that reportedly uses INTC Atom chip. Interestingly, TXN may also be jumping on board the HPQ program with its own design ARM chip. Will HPQ, DELL, or Quanta, with their huge financial and R&amp;D resources, steal the dense microserver market away from Caldexa and AMD-Seamicro with designs based on INTC chips? Even if ARM chips proved to be a competitor to INTC in the space, I'd expect a large company like TXN to develop ARM chips superior to those of Caldexa and AMD in short time. ---------------------------------- The word on the street is that HP will use the TI KeyStone II chips in its second-generation "Gemini" Moonshot servers, which the company previewed last summer. During that preview last June, the only processor that HP talked about was Intel's "Centerton" Atom S1200 server chip, which was announced in December last year, and it never mentioned ARM processors, not even once. (Funny that.) HP has not provided much in the way of feeds or speeds for the Gemini machines except that they will use the two-core Atom S1200 processor, which has 64-bit processing, supports VT virtualization assist, and ECC scrubbing on main memory and is certified to run server variants of Linux and Windows. It has not said, either, how the Gemini machines will stack up compared to the "Redstone" Moonshot boxes that HP launched in November 2011 using the 32-bit Calxeda ECX-1000 ARM chips, which include an on-chip distributed Layer 2 switch that is very clever.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1363533657850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:20:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363534069798-42</Id><Topic><Title>A post from Khitchdees other personality regarding Surface Pro</Title><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1363349088151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 08:04:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Khitchinlitte.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363534069798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:27:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363534108898-43</Id><Topic><Title>Irresponsible for Intel to have plants in Israel</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1363528871710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:01:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you for real? Israel has the smartest people &amp; the most profitable INTC division in the world!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1363534108898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363534131090-44</Id><Title>Calxeda’s ARM Server Tested ARM based servers hold the promise of extremely low power and excellent performance per Watt ratios. It’s theoretically possible to place an incredible number of servers into a single rack; there are already implementations with as many as 1000 ARM servers in one rack (48 server nodes in a 2U chassis). What’s more, all of those nodes consume less than 5KW combined (or around 5W per quad-core ARM node).</Title><Msg>Calxeda’s ARM Server Tested ARM based servers hold the promise of extremely low power and excellent performance per Watt ratios. It’s theoretically possible to place an incredible number of servers into a single rack; there are already implementations with as many as 1000 ARM servers in one rack (48 server nodes in a 2U chassis). What’s more, all of those nodes consume less than 5KW combined (or around 5W per quad-core ARM node). Read the full review from AnandTech.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1363534131090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:28:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363536855419-45</Id><Topic><Title>Calxeda’s ARM Server Tested ARM based servers hold the promise of extremely low power and excellent performance per Watt ratios. It’s theoretically possible to place an incredible number of servers into a single rack; there are already implementations with as many as 1000 ARM servers in one rack (48 server nodes in a 2U chassis). What’s more, all of those nodes consume less than 5KW combined (or around 5W per quad-core ARM node).</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1363534131090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:28:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was suprised that the 32-bit Calxeda cluster did so poorly against the year old Xeon Supermicro Sandy Bridge system. The power optimized ARM system with a 705W power supply drew less power than the Supermicro 1280W power supply. Measuring at the wall is what the customer wants, but even AnandTech even points out the problems with their comparison. The S1200 Atom cluster numbers or a similarly configured Xeon system will be more interesting for an ARM comparison.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363536855419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:14:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363538335215-46</Id><Topic><Title>A post from Khitchdees other personality regarding Surface Pro</Title><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1363349088151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 08:04:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's not even buyin what he's sellin.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363538335215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363538445446-47</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro sales hit 400K in a hurry</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363326581187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>khitchdee•Mar 15, 2013 2:13 AMFlag +The sales numbers have spoken. It looks like Microsoft has a veritable hit on their hands. With the intro of Haswell, some of the criticism around this PC will get addressed. Also, this leads the way for core series chips to be put to use in tablets which is probably a win for core series sales volumes. If I was Qualcomm or NVidia, I would be very scared about competition for tablet chips in this form which neither has a chance of competing with at least on the performance front. Windows 8 it seems is set to take off as a touch OS albeit a little slowly contrary to earlier reports. ______________ Great post and very accurate, KHITCHDEE.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363538445446</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:40:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363539240015-48</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro sales hit 400K in a hurry</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363326581187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis, Don't you think that number is alot better than Kindle's Fire sales? So Microsoft could be experiencing alot more interest in its Surface Pro when the price alont with volume is taken into consideration against the Kindle's price and volume. We may be even beating Kindle's Fire in volume alone. So even as Kindle is selling its tablets at below cost, they still are struggling, yet their stock price suggests that they may be having huge success. I think time will settle these confusing issues. The key for Microsofts success obviously is the versatility of the Surface Pro using Intel chips over the not Intel ones. The market need not look at tablet sales in general but the iPad sales only when it comes to non Intel based tablets. And before anyone cites the success of Galaxy tablets, I would question why Samsung has decided to start offerring at least one tablet with Windows 8 OS using and Atom chip. In other words, even with their tablet offerring, Samsung in some cases is choosing Intel's Atom over its own chips. That's telling alot about where this story could be headed in the near future.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363539240015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363540252064-49</Id><Title>Hp Elite Pad with Clovertrail targeted for India.</Title><Msg>HP ElitePad 900 review: Smart &amp; useful Ravi Sharma, TOI Tech Mar 16, 2013, 12.53PM IST NEW DELHI: HP has launched its ElitePad 900 tablet in India that is aimed at enterprise consumers. The company aims to make it the device of choice for business users who may oterwise opt for an Apple iPad because of the convenience it offers - merging a laptop and a tablet in a handy package with a number of hardware design and usage customization offerings. Design and hardware: HP has given a lot of thought to the design of its new ElitePad 900, as it looks very elegant. The machined aluminium body of the tablet appears classy and gives it premium looks. The designing is such that it is easy to hold and at 680gram, its weight is equal to that of iPad. The tablet sports a 10.1-inch LCD touchscreen with 1280x800p resolution. The touchscreen is quite responsive and we did not experience any problems while typing using the on-screen keyboard as compared to other tablets/hybrid laptops with Windows 8. It gives fantastic viewing angles, which are quite good (thank the IPS panel for that) and render true colours even at steep angles. The ElitePad 900 is available in two variants - one with 32GB storage and Windows 8 and the other with 64GB storage and Windows 8 Pro operating system pre-bundled. Both the variants are powered by a superfast 1.8GHz dual-core Intel Atom CloverTrail processor with 2GB RAM.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363540252064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:10:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363540292556-50</Id><Topic><Title>Hp Elite Pad with Clovertrail targeted for India.</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363540252064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:10:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It has a Power/Lock key, volume rocker, speaker grille, earphone jack, auto-rotation controller and a proprietary connector used for charging the battery (no universal charging!). The 8MP rear camera with LED flash of ElitePad 900 is a pleasant surprise as it is so uncommon with rivals. The only tablet with an 8MP unit is Sony Xperia Tablet Z, which is aimed at the mass market rather than enterprise users. Though this camera adds value to the spec sheet of this device, we are unsure how many users - and that too business consumers - use a tablet to take photos. What we like more is the front camera that can record HD videos, a must have for those who frequently partake in video conferences in large corporates with dedicated links. The camera settings allow you to lower the noise level and make the image more suitable to the environment, thus improving the video call quality.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363540292556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:11:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363540357742-51</Id><Topic><Title>Hp Elite Pad with Clovertrail targeted for India.</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363540252064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:10:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The battery of HP ElitePad 900 runs for approximately 10 hours on a single charge. If you want even more juice, you can plug it into the accompanying battery pack provided by HP and extend the life by another cool 7-9 hours (approximately). Software: On the Windows Experience Index, our Windows 8-powered unit scored 3.3 and was quite snappy during our review. We came across no lag or hanging during the tests, but were never felt overwhelmed by its computing capabilities. Some enterprise-oriented features of HP ElitePad 900 are Security Manager, Credential Manager, Password Manager, Device Access Manager with Just In Time Authentication and Drive Encryption. These are security solutions that can be crucial in enterprise environments so that your machine is never susceptible to cyberattacks. Connectivity and accessories: HP brings 3G mobile data to the table with ElitePad 900, a useful proposition for those who are frequently on the go. On the rear is a flap that houses a microSD and sim card reader; just insert the sim card in the tablet and you are good to go. Internet connectivity over 3G was smooth and we found no hiccups in the usage. Other communication features of this tablet include Wi-Fi and Bluetooth 4.0 and NFC.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363540357742</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363540462615-52</Id><Topic><Title>Hp Elite Pad with Clovertrail targeted for India.</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363540252064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:10:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10 hour battery life on single charge......Intel is gonna make a dumptruck load of money in India over the coming years. - Chump</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363540462615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:14:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363541038273-53</Id><Topic><Title>CONCLUSION:::LONG TERM ARMH Keeps the lead over Intel 2013 and beyond.................</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1363528396589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:53:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tired of seeing your negative posts, Nuff. It's all irrelevant. You should short it, sell or whatever. No one cares what you say. You are a #$%$.</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363541038273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:23:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363541480044-54</Id><Title>arm servers will not go anywhere</Title><Msg>because they are incompatible with existing software. Furthermore, Intel is already addressing power issues with the Atom-powered servers chips. The software incompatibility is why Windows RT is not selling and why arm servers will not make a dent.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363541480044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:31:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363541675882-55</Id><Title>Apple/Intel deal coming in May</Title><Msg>An interesting article from russ fischer talks about an Apple/Intel possibly coming in May once the Micron acquisition of Elpida (mobile DRAM maker) is completed.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363541675882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363541854627-56</Id><Topic><Title>arm servers will not go anywhere</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363541480044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ARM guys act like Intel is not going to advance their server technology, stand still and let ARM take their lunch money from them. Get real.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363541854627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:37:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363542065493-57</Id><Topic><Title>arm servers will not go anywhere</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363541480044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel, Facebook Collaborate on Future Data Center Rack Technologies Posted by IntelPR in Intel Newsroom on Jan 16, 2013 10:00:22 AM New Photonic Architecture Promises to Dramatically Change Next Decade of Disaggregated, Rack-Scale Server Designs NEWS HIGHLIGHTS Intel and Facebook* are collaborating to define the next generation of rack technologies that enables the disaggregation of compute, network and storage resources. Quanta Computer* unveiled a mechanical prototype of the rack architecture to show the total cost, design and reliability improvement potential of disaggregation. The mechanical prototype includes Intel Silicon Photonics Technology, distributed input/output using Intel Ethernet switch silicon, and supports the Intel® Xeon® processor and the next-generation system-on-chip Intel® Atom™ processor code named "Avoton." Intel has moved its silicon photonics efforts beyond research and development, and the company has produced engineering samples that run at speeds of up to 100 gigabits per second (Gbps).</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363542065493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363543954511-58</Id><Title>Intel Will enter US smartphone market this year</Title><Msg>Late last year, there were rumors that Bay Trail would not make it to market until sometime in 2014. However, at CES and MWC this year, Intel has confirmed that we will be seeing Bay Trail PRODUCTS available for the holiday shopping season this year. Bay Trail is a new REDESIGNED Atom architecture created specifically for the smartphone and tablet market. For the first time, the Atom line will be using Intel's 22nm tri-gate (FinFet) process. It will also have integrated Intel graphics. Intel has stated that bay trail will have twice the power and twice the battery life of Clover Trail+. Early benchmarks for the Clover Trail+ has shown that it is faster than the latest arm offerings eg. snapdragon 600 and exynos 5. With Bay Trail's release, Intel will have a clear lead over arm. Furthermore, at MWC, Intel announce that the XMM7160 baseband with LTE 4G, with multi-mode, will be shipping in the first half of this year. The XMM7160 is available for phone makers to pair with Clover Trail+. I believe it will be available to be paired with Bay Trail as well. This means we will see Bay Trail smartphones and tablets with LTE 4G enter the US market this year for the holiday season. My guess is it will make it's debut in the Google/Motorola X Phone and X Tablet.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363543954511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:12:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363544215640-59</Id><Title>What we know and what we do not know.</Title><Msg>Know Intel pushed out their old CEO Paul O because of his failure to land Intel into phones and tablets in volume. Intel's stock sucks and has sucked for 13 yearn now. Intel does pay a very good Div. Intel did completely kill off AMD. Intel does have the Best Fabs in the world. Intel is building massive capacity in the same Fabs. Intel's Chips are getting better and better fast. Intel's Net profit fell substantially from its over 3 billion a quarter. Intel has not ever gotten to 3.5 billion net profit. So profits and sales falling and capacity capability being added. What we DO NOT Know. Who will the new CEO be? Will the stock go up or down or stay in this never ending dead zone? Will Div continue to increase this year? Will Intel be able to defeat ARMH as did AMD? Will Intel sell fab use to Apple adding billions (3 to 5)in revenue to Intel? Will Cisco use Intel as a fab as well adding more billions? Will Intel chips continue to improve leaving others completely out of the game? When if ever will Intel grow its net profit to 5 billion a quarter or more? Will that 3.5 billion in Net profit be reached in a quarter this year? Why all the new capacity Intel? Are you smart or crazy?</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1363544215640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:16:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363544937352-60</Id><Topic><Title>Apple/Intel deal coming in May</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363541675882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:34:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like Russ Fischer articles but not sure he ever gets it right. we'll see.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363544937352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:28:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363546856793-61</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Will enter US smartphone market this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363543954511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:12:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's really scary (for arm) is that once bay trail is released, Clover Trail+ becomes Intel's low end product. This means that Intel's low-end built on cheap 32nm (which Intel would normally discard), will be competing with arm's very best; while Intel's bay trail will be reserved for the very elite products which it has no competition. What's even more scarier (for arm) is that Intel has stated that it plans to eventually bring the Atom line to be in the same manufacturing process as its CPU products. This means that in 2014, intel will be shipping out both Broadwell (Core products) and Atom on 14nm. The big big problem for arm here is that TSMC and GF (arm manufacturers) are still stuck at planar process and from recent reports may not even be able to get to the 20nm (still planar) process until 2015. This means that arm manufacturers may not get to 14nm until 2016! If this is the case then by 2014, even Intel's low end products will have a big lead over arm's very best! Scary indeed.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363546856793</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:00:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363547874204-62</Id><Title>This will make your day</Title><Msg>evenues approximately doubled last year as did earnings and I expect huge gains this year. Perfect size company w/ only 600 mil sales. It has a p/e of 22 and should have one of 40 just to get to the price of a typical fast growing company. Not only should the price rise for a higher p/e but also it should rocket up with the expected fast rise in earnings. We could easily see the price triple in one year considering these items. The SYMBOL: (AL) - a high profit airline leasing business. Company has billions of dollars in new jets ordered from Boeing and Airbus so obviously they expect a lot more business. I have 20 years experience evaluating hundreds of companies, this is one of the top 3 company stocks I have ever found. The company reported great earnings again and also leased 2 - Boeing 777's, and ordered 10 more Boeing 777's. Symbol (AL) Another interesting but more speculative stock is (edap). The company is big into ultrasound and they finished a study showing ultrasound works on prostate cancer without side effects like chemotherapy. The company is applying for approval with the FDA and it is expected to go through on a fast track because of the excellent results. This undiscovered company is priced at only $4.</Msg><Username>emsggim</Username><Timestamp>1363547874204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:17:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363551066664-63</Id><Topic><Title>CONCLUSION:::LONG TERM ARMH Keeps the lead over Intel 2013 and beyond.................</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1363528396589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:53:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“I warned against the hype in the first sentences. :-) ARM CPUs are still rather weak and not a good match for most applications. However, the fact that we could actually find a case where they do a lot better than the current Xeon systems was surprising to me.” Well t this rather ominous negative is what one reviewer said about ARM. But gee wiz, next time he does a review he ought to report that he just turned both ot the DXXXX systems completely off and they were equal in performance!</Msg><Username>herbwll</Username><Timestamp>1363551066664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:11:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363551930586-64</Id><Topic><Title>arm servers will not go anywhere</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363541480044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forget even software compatibility - Intel will have the better silicon.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363551930586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:25:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363552885126-65</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Will enter US smartphone market this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363543954511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:12:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suggest you read more about Clover trail+ : anandtechDOTcom/show/6790/intels-clover-trail-dualcore-cpu-and-graphics-unveiled-at-mwc-2013 The ARM SoC vendors wont be worried:)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1363552885126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:41:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363553406731-66</Id><Title>ARM Server Hype</Title><Msg>I love the ARM server hype. Because it means that they are out of ammo. They have at best a shot at a tiny portion of the server market. The fact that they lead with this in trying to counter the massive amount of positive Intel news and buzz indicates that they simply have run out of arguments in trying to rebut the notion that we have reached the tipping point in the mobility processor wars. Additional tips should be that they are talking about servers issues and not mobility at all and that they avoid fabrication discussions like the plague. They avoid the mobility discussions because they are constantly losing ground there. The bottom has fallen out for Apple and Nvidia won't have Tegra 4 products until the end of the year. Samsung and Qualcomm are the only bright spots and both are hamstrung by ARM's fading fabrication. Qualcomm is facing very substantial new competition in LTE and Samsung continues to try to deflect Apple's constant legal thrusts at its heart. There were very few high end ARM smartphone introductions at MWC 2013 and they have to have these to stay on top. Intel continues to gain traction with its mobility strategy with constant improvements in hardware, software and and vendor relationships. New introductions have been just announced from Lenovo, Xolo and Asus. Haswell will be here shortly. The imperfect but promising Surface Pro demonstrated how flawed the ARM RT concept was and we hear more and more talk about Microsoft ending the RT line. And there is absolutely nothing the ARM world can do about the big Intel deals that are in discussions and on the way. Any of these has the power to crush the ARM stock price and send it spinning out of control while Intel's moves up. Firmly in play is a big foundry deal with a major mobility player along with the Cisco deal whose announcement should come soon. In the meantime the ARM fanbois and press talk about servers. I love it...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363553406731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:50:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363553777527-67</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Will enter US smartphone market this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363543954511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:12:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The ARM SoC vendors wont be worried:)" [Because they have dual boot and FinFET, right? Oh, wait - they don't have either one. Um, why is it they aren't worried??? And Clover Trail is just the beginning. Say the words "Bay Trail" and be afraid. Be very afraid. The end isn't here yet. But you can see it from here if you take off those ARM-issued rosy-shaded spectacles...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363553777527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:56:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363554171431-68</Id><Title>Microsoft's first PC lives!</Title><Msg>[Intel goes where ARM can't follow. And it's just the beginning...] Microsoft's first PC, the Surface Pro, has survived Round One. A report this week said 400,000 Surface Pros were sold in about a month since its release. That's a decent start (contrary to the media's take). Remember, this is an $899-$999 tablet (though I prefer to describe it as a full-blown Windows PC compacted and stuffed into a tablet's chassis), not a $199 Nexus 7 or $329 iPad Mini. Also remember this is just the start. The Pro should evolve to the point where you can have a 1.5 or 2 pound tablet with all-day (at least) battery life -- and still get all of the performance of a mainstream Windows 8 laptop. And that's the deal-closer for me. It's fast. Don't believe me? Check out these benchmarks. "Surface Pro is easily the fastest tablet on the market today," Anandtech said. The basic point being that Intel's Ivy Bridge silicon crushes Apple's A6X-based iPad and ARM-based Android tablets in most benchmarks. And it's not just numbers -- you feel it. Everything pops and there's almost none of the lag you invariably run into with other tablets. I know this because I've been using the Pro and its speed is addictive -- despite the comparative heft and shorter battery life compared with other tablets (though I wouldn't call 2 pounds "heavy" and battery life isn't as bad as reviewers make it out to be if you tweak Windows 8 settings). I've said this before, but relocating the electronics behind the screen changes everything. That includes relegating the keyboard -- something reviewers over the decades have spilled untold oceans of ink evaluating because of its importance -- to second fiddle. The touch display rules. From Brooke Crothers</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363554171431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:02:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363556432538-69</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Will enter US smartphone market this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363543954511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:12:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[Because they have dual boot and FinFET, right? Oh, wait - they don't have either one. Um, why is it they aren't worried??? And Clover Trail is just the beginning. Say the words "Bay Trail" and be afraid. Be very afraid. The end isn't here yet. But you can see it from here if you take off those ARM-issued rosy-shaded spectacles...] ---- Read the link and see. Clover Trail+ is about the GPU. Bay Trail? I can assure you, the SoC vendors aren't afraid ;) Airmont and 14nm is another mater... Dual boot. Could become very important going forward. FinFET, no problem thanks to IBM. We'll have to see what TSMC's solution is like.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1363556432538</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363556988242-70</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft's first PC lives!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363554171431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:02:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Surface Pro with Haswell and all day batter life will change things forever and it won't matter what analysts say because Intel's quarterly numbers will begin to shut them all up.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363556988242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:49:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363558023036-71</Id><Title>New Lenovo Thinkpad is dynamite</Title><Msg>Lenovo ThinkPad T431s Boasts Dramatic Thin-and-Light Redesign By Michelle Maisto | Posted 2013-03-17 Email this article Email Print this article Print The Lenovo ThinkPad T431s is a 14-inch laptop that's the thinnest and lightest T series ever, and the result of extensive research. Lenovo took great pains in designing its newest ThinkPad, the T431. The computer maker undertook an extensive research initiative over nine months, across nine countries and in 11 languages. "It wasn't just surveys," Alysia Baker, Lenovo's worldwide product marketing manager, told eWEEK. "It included focus groups and was a very iterative process, where we would talk to customers, go back and revise, and get their thoughts again." Researchers spent thousands of hours shadowing users at work and at home, gathering feedback about how they interacted with their devices. The results led to a number of improvements.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363558023036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:07:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363558052985-72</Id><Topic><Title>New Lenovo Thinkpad is dynamite</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363558023036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:07:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For one, the T431s is the thinnest and lightest T series laptop ever made. It features a 14-inch HD+ display with a resolution of 1600 by 900, weighs 3.6 pounds and measures 13.03 by 8.89 by 0.80 inches. For context, its specs are exactly between those of the 13- and 15-inch Apple MacBook Pros with Retina displays. Click Here! The T431s features a more streamlined interior—Lenovo adjusted the placement of the keys on the keyboard and slimmed the bezel around the display. The company also—after trying out various colors on Lenovo users and users of competing products—tweaked the color from soft-touch matte black to a new shade called Graphite Black. Lenovo also gave it a carbon fiber top, to make it tough but light, and a magnesium exterior. The T431s also has a new trackpad, which is an evolution of Lenovo'sTrackPoint and TouchPad. The new trackpad has a larger, smoother, more responsive multi-touch glass surface, and is optimized for the touch-friendly Windows 8. Baker said that the increased real estate of the trackpad enhances the device's Windows 8 functionality, as does a row of Windows 8 function buttons for things like adjusting the volume and the brightness and the microphone, and putting the laptop into airplane mode.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363558052985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:07:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363558079737-73</Id><Topic><Title>New Lenovo Thinkpad is dynamite</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363558023036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:07:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It runs the latest third-generation Intel Core i processors—up to an i7—has a 100 percent improved graphic performance with Intel HD Graphics, a 40 percent faster boot-up time, and a USB 3.0 port for transfers 10 times as fast as with a 2.0 port. A built-in fingerprint reader can turn on the laptop with a swipe, there's a 720p HD camera with Polycom Ready technology for better audio clarity during video calls, and WiFi, WWAN and Ethernet connectivity, along with Mobile Hotspot capabilities. "It's the single biggest design change that we've ever had. ... We think it's just a great product," Baker said. In a deeply ailing PC market, Lenovo has continued to post growth and to aggressively outpace the industry average. During the fourth quarter of 2012, it held a 15 percent share of the market to longtime market-leader Hewlett-Packard's 16-plus percent share. More impressively, during the third quarter, according to Gartner (research firm IDC felt otherwise), for the first time in the company's history it slipped ahead of HP, which posted a 16.4 percent decline, to Lenovo's growth of 9.8 percent. Gartner noted in a Jan. 14 release that while Lenovo fell back into the second-place spot, it experienced the best growth rate among the top five vendors, performing well, thanks to its expansion into the retail market and defense of its position in the enterprise space. Lenovo will begin selling the ThinkPad T431s in April, starting at $949.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363558079737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:07:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363558699974-74</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>The strong uptrend among the major indexes tends to suggest that there will be more gains down the road. However, the market action in the week after the quadruple witching in the past year suggests that there could be more pullbacks in the next few sessions. The S&amp;P 500 finished lower in each of the weeks following a quadruple witching last year. It could be that the money managers had to reload put options as a protection for their portfolios after the prior options expired. This would cause the volatility to rise and prices to drop. It wouldn't be surprising to see the same thing happen this year.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1363558699974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:18:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363566629553-75</Id><Topic><Title>New Lenovo Thinkpad is dynamite</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363558023036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:07:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wait, so it doesn't run Windows RT and an ARM chip?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363566629553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:30:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363569254270-76</Id><Title>Reading news on other boards that the futures are tanking bad and there's big trouble in Europe...</Title><Msg>Anyone wiser than I know how this will affect Intel?</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1363569254270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 21:14:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363570061786-77</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Will enter US smartphone market this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363543954511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:12:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FinFET? IBM can give them the reciepe but the foundries are still going to have to operate the equipment. In your opinion, will the volume ramp be faster, slower or about the same as TSMC 28nm? Another question, how do you see the royalty stream wars to play out? I expect that the Intel patent buying spree is to protect them when the patent infringement lawsuits start. Intel has patents to protect itself cleanly or patents to be able to negotiate a cross licensing agreement with anyone. When Intel gets to Airmont with all Intel circuits with patent protection, what happens to the QCOM royalty revenue stream? QCOM royalty accounts for 40% of QCOM revenue but 80% of QCOM earnings. Every Airmont Intel sells will likely create a loss of QCOM royalty.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363570061786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 21:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363570417128-78</Id><Title>Asus Vivobook is a stick of Dynamite</Title><Msg>Asus Launches the Vivobook S500 3:00 PM - March 17, 2013 The VivoBook S500 is the latest release in Asus' line of Ultraportable laptops and features a 15.6" LED backlit capacitive touch display (1366 x 768), 3rd Generation Intel Core Processors (starting with the 1.7 GHz i5-3317U) and an advertised 2-second instant resume from sleep mode and standby battery life of up to two weeks. The laptop is also equipped with 6 GB of DDR3 RAM, Intel GMA HD graphics, a 500 GB hard drive paired with a 24 GB caching SSD, and an "oversized touchpad incorporating Asus' Smart Gesture technology." The latter feature is advertised by the company as providing "instinctive touch capabilities" when combined with the aforementioned multi-point touchscreen display. The VivoBook S500 is currently for sale in North America with a starting price of $699, a reasonable price given its features, slim profile and attractive design.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363570417128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 21:33:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363570557602-79</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Server Hype</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363553406731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:50:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung is hamstrung by fading fabrication? Seriously? Samsung is going to kick Intel's fat #$%$ at 14nm SoCs. Intel doesn't even have a CEO. That speaks volumes about Intel's ability to make decisions and execute. The mobile market moves too fast for old men.</Msg><Username>semiconductorguy</Username><Timestamp>1363570557602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 21:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363570792113-80</Id><Topic><Title>New Lenovo Thinkpad is dynamite</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363558023036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:07:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Wait, so it doesn't run Windows RT and an ARM chip?" **** LOL. No, it doesn't. Here's a Lenovo comment:: "We obsess over the pursuit of perfection -- as evidenced by more than 20 years of Lenovo ThinkPad design and engineering accolades. However, perfection cannot be achieved without a key ingredient: customer insight," said Dilip Bhatia, vice president and general manager, ThinkPad Business Unit. "The ThinkPad T431s is the first device featuring Lenovo's new design, which represents a comprehensive examination of user experience and input." That approach would obviously lead them directly away from RT and ARM...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363570792113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 21:39:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363571351392-81</Id><Topic><Title>Reading news on other boards that the futures are tanking bad and there's big trouble in Europe...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1363569254270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 21:14:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, of course this is a big, huge monstrous event. Because it's Cyprus, that behemoth of global commerce and manufacturing. Wait, what??? Cyrus??? Cyprus accounts for less than half a percent of the 17-nation euro economy, for god's sake!!! Well, we know Wall Street loves to price in a European collapse. After all, they've done it 24 times previous to this. This time just say no. But it will be very interesting to see what happens to ARM tomorrow since they do happen to be in Europe and are already slipping on a very slippery slope. Guess we get to see if those ARM investors truly have the courage (or the stupidity) of their convictions...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363571351392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 21:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363572078102-82</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Server Hype</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363553406731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:50:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Samsung is hamstrung by fading fabrication? Seriously? Samsung is going to kick Intel's fat #$%$ at 14nm SoCs. Intel doesn't even have a CEO. That speaks volumes about Intel's ability to make decisions and execute. The mobile market moves too fast for old men." [Um, Nenni - exactly when will that #$%$ kicking come? In about 4-6 years when Samsung has volume 14nm production? Because they have to do 20nm first. So we have some ho-hum years of yawn time before that happens. And then some more ho-hum years of yawn time before they reach volume production. And then maybe they can start on their half (not whole but half) #$%$-kicking step to 14nm. By which time it will be game over. Samsung doesn't have butkus on 14nm, Nenni and you know it. Fabrication moves too fast for old men and that means you and the rest of the ARM crowd like Morris. Next time you want to rain on Intel's FinFET efforts (which are already producing 14nm product) bring something stronger than mindless criticism of the CEO. Intel does have a CEO and he's the guy who developed the FinFET project that is crushing your family jewels....]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363572078102</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 22:01:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363572528053-83</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Will enter US smartphone market this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363543954511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:12:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"FinFET, no problem thanks to IBM." [Hahahahahahahaha. You're going to choke yourself if you keep swallowing that much Kool-Aid at one time. If you believe that FinFET will be no problem for ARM, then I have a watch, a bridge and some swampland that you are going to be very interested in!]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363572528053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 22:08:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363572902780-84</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Server Hype</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363553406731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:50:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>idiot.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363572902780</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 22:15:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363573014568-85</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Will enter US smartphone market this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363543954511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:12:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Common Platform Alliance is coming to some use after all.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1363573014568</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 22:16:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363573457395-86</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Stats</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363476866048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 19:34:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's see what happens tomorrow with this from Friday: ARM 52-Week High: 44.47 Price now: 41.91 Drop from 52-Week High: 2.56 Yesterday (Friday) ARM opened at 43.32, moved up a measly 6 cents to 43.38 and then began a day long decline all the way down to 41.86, a massive one market session decline of 1.52. It then rallied 5 cents. Now I don't have to tell you that a one session decline of 1.52 says bad things about a stock's strength. But even worse this is a continuation of the buyer exhaustion that has been evident for all of the last month. The stock failed to close above its 50-day moving average of 42.07. This isn't a disaster in and of itself. After all it's only 2.56 little dollars as one ARM fanboi called them. But it's a slippery slope. And it's slipping.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363573457395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 22:24:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363575087266-87</Id><Title>Will $20 hold tomorrow after the Europe news?</Title><Msg>Well, Cyprus is now the excuse for a major market correction. Every year, Europe destroys any bull run.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1363575087266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 22:51:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363575095483-88</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Will enter US smartphone market this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363543954511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:12:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UMC and TSMC to move to FinFET at 20nm by Lucian Armasu on Aug 01, 2012 Intel went FinFET (or tri-gate transistors as they call them) at 22nm with Ivy Bridge, and now the #1 foundry, TSMC, and the #2 foundry, UMC, will also go to FinFET for the next gen 20 nm process. However, mass production of 20nm ARM chips will probably not happen until 2014, considering 28nm is barely here in 2012, and it usually takes 2 years for the new process technology to be ready. Apparently, the planar FinFET technology that these foundries intend to use is better suited for mobile SoC’s, like the ones from ARM, and it should bring a performance improvement of at least 15%-20% over Intel’s own FinFET technology. Intel wants to make a 22nm Atom processor using their own FinFET technology next year, but ARM CEO Warren East thinks Intel Atom is not competitive with ARM chips for mobile use. “An 800MHz ARM delivers the same performance as a 1.6GHz Atom,” says East. “Bearing in mind that it is easier to make rectangular SOI FinFETs than rectangular bulk FinFETs, moving from triangular Intel bulk FinFETs to rectangular SOI FinFETs can deliver approximately 20% performance improvement,” says Professor Asen Asenov of Glasgow University who is the CEO of Gold Standard Simulations.. This is bad news for Intel as UMC has licensed the FinFET technology from IBM, just like Samsung and GlobalFoundries have, while TSMC is presumably building their own. “We are happy to engage with a recognized technology leader such as IBM for this technology advancement effort. UMC’s position as a world-leading foundry involves timely introduction of leading-edge processes to enable next generation customer chip designs. Leveraging IBM’s technology expertise to shorten our 20nm and FinFET R&amp;D cycle will create a win-win situation for UMC and our customers,” said IC Chen, vice president of advanced technology development at UMC.</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1363575095483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 22:51:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363575448464-89</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Will enter US smartphone market this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363543954511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:12:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC expects the move to the 20nm FinFET technology to offer them a 1.9x increase in density over the 28 nm process, -25% power consumption, and 15-20% increase in performance. The year 2014, when these FinFET chips will arrive in the market should be very exciting, because we’ll also get the new 64 bit ARMv8 architecture, and the next-gen CPU that comes after Cortex A15, which will be built with the 20 nm process. That’s the year when Intel should really start to fear ARM, because those chips will be used in a lot more types of devices and machines than just smartphones and tablets. androidauthorityDOTcom/umc-and-tsmc-to-move-to-finfet-at-20nm-104904/</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1363575448464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 22:57:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363576171162-90</Id><Title>Will The Turd Float on Monday?????</Title><Msg>Any thoughts... Will it float or sink??</Msg><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363576171162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:09:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363576515447-91</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Will enter US smartphone market this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363543954511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:12:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am totally amazed that you would post up an article so old and so completely wrong. This article is almost seven months old. It has things in it that are egregiously in error like ARM's 20nm being FinFET which it isn't. Seven months after this was written ARM is no closer to FinFET production now than they were then. ARM spent the time between then and now agonizing about their fabrication future. They almost decided to skip 20nm because the planar benefits are few and the costs are high. And there was no real consideration of doing FinFET at 20nm. So, ARM wanted to jump to 14nm FinFET. But they had no confidence that they could do it. So they decided to do a half-step to 14nm and tack in onto the backside of the 20nm product, creating something just as ugly as big.little in its own way. Well, these are the things you have to do when you don't have access to state-of-the-art fabrication. Bottom line is that it's a mess. Cobbling together this kind of misbegotten bailing wire, band-aid and chewing gum solution is simply all that can be managed and there is no assurance that the spawn of this process will even survive. It may be too little, too late to be viable. This is now the fabric of ARM's fabrication existence.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363576515447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363576521922-92</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Will enter US smartphone market this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363543954511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:12:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD First to 22 Nm, Challenges Intel . 6:30 PM - August 18, 2008 by Wolfgang Gruener - source: Tom's Hardware US Yorktown Heights (NY) - IBM and its chip development partners, including AMD, made a stunning announcement today, apparently beating Intel in the successful production of the first functional 22 nm SRAM cell. 22 nm processors are still three years out in the future, but IBM’s news is a good sign that chip manufacturer will be able to easily scale to this new level by the end of 2011. It appears that, for the first time in several decades, Intel may have to put some extra time into its research and development efforts to make sure it can keep its manufacturing lead at 22 nm and beyond. ================================== EASILY by 2011</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1363576521922</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363576600381-93</Id><Topic><Title>Will The Turd Float on Monday?????</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363576171162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:09:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It depends on how much milk you put in your bowl. Enjoy your breakfast!</Msg><Username>getanad61</Username><Timestamp>1363576600381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:16:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363576861678-94</Id><Topic><Title>Will $20 hold tomorrow after the Europe news?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1363575087266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 22:51:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Dow is not going to drop by 14,500 points just because of Cyprus financials!!! Sheeeesh!!</Msg><Username>getanad61</Username><Timestamp>1363576861678</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:21:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363576911186-95</Id><Topic><Title>Will The Turd Float on Monday?????</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363576171162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:09:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spare us your potty mouth and adolescence, DanaLucyVinniePCrandal...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363576911186</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:21:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363577782221-96</Id><Title>So how smart is Mr. Market</Title><Msg>Judging from the reaction to the Cyprus news not very smart. Here are some other indications: Nothing in the stock price for an Apple deal that could eventually result in Intel doing all of Apple's fabrication. Nothing in the stock price for Intel's highly profitable, cash cow deal with Altera, and the deal with Acronix. Nothing in the stock price for Haswell which will be arriving sooner than expected. Nothing in the stock price for Intel 14nm FinFET arriving at the end of the year. Nothing in the stock price for Clover Trail or Bay Trail. Nothing in the stock price for the new deal with ZTE. Nothing in the stock price for the new smartphones by Lenovo and Xolo. Nothing in the stock price for the FonePad by Asus. Nothing in the stock price for the success of the Surface Pro. Nothing in the stock price for the Cisco deal. Nothing in the stock price for ARM's delays at 20nm. Nothing in the stock price for ARM not having FinFET for years and years and years. Nothing in the stock price for Intel's web TV project. Nothing in the stock price for a potential iWatch deal. Nothing in the stock price for more big foundry deals. We know one big one is in the works. Nothing in the stock price for dual booting of both Windows 8 and Android. Nothing in the stock price for Intel's partnership with Samsung on Tizen</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363577782221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:36:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363577898296-97</Id><Topic><Title>Will The Turd Float on Monday?????</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363576171162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:09:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I really hate this wallis cleaver,, er I mean Wallis Weaver.... Go tell Ward and The Beaver that I said hello... And and btw... Flush this turd..</Msg><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363577898296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:38:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363577951500-98</Id><Title>US Futures are Much Worse than European</Title><Msg>Go figure. Ain't Wall Street something...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363577951500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:39:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363578373279-99</Id><Topic><Title>Will The Turd Float on Monday?????</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363576171162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:09:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When it comes to excrement, I defer to your much greater exposure and proximity, Mr. Blankenhorn. I just don't understand your need to rub yourself in it every day...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363578373279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:46:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>