<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359176663728-1</Id><Topic><Title>Why Big Deals Are Imminent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359172589896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel will have trouble taking off as a foundry even in a small way. They are a little late to the game and new at it.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359176663728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 00:04:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359178122329-2</Id><Topic><Title>Why Big Deals Are Imminent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359172589896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I remember thinking when I first heard how many 22nm Fabs Intel were going to build that it was ambitious and so it has proved. However in the long run it is not an issue with Intel now branching into low power mobility as it will give Intel the capacity in the long run to produce a lot of mobile tablet/phone chips. Think of all that 32nm capacity that is currently producing Sandy Bridge. Next year it could be pumping out cheap Medfields and Clovertrail(+)s for the cheap tablet/phone sockets after the premium 22nm Baytrail and Merifield are released. It does not matter if the chips are then priced so cheap that the profit on each is only a couple of dollars as the 32nm Fabs would then be depreciated by then and more importantly it denies an ARM vendor a sale and Intel has to pick them off one by one. Who in their right mind would pick a quad-core 1 GHz A7 when the alternative might be a dual-core 2 GHz Clovertrail+. Intel actually has a mobile roadmap now where the n-1 process product will still be competitive and can fill the old Fabs when it is priced to go. In the long run all of Intel's capacity will be used.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359178122329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 00:28:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359178652814-3</Id><Topic><Title>Why Big Deals Are Imminent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359172589896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're making the assumption that Intel will have more than 5% of the mobile market. That's a big assumption given where they're starting from and how competitive the market is already.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359178652814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 00:37:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359179299094-4</Id><Topic><Title>Why Big Deals Are Imminent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359172589896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5% will be easy to achieve considering they have 100% of the Windows 8 tablet market.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359179299094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 00:48:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359179592135-5</Id><Topic><Title>Why Big Deals Are Imminent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359172589896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That assuming 100% of the Windows 8 tablet market will exceed 5% of the overall tablet market that includes the iPad and Android based tablets.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359179592135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 00:53:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359180477643-6</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hans De Vries has measured the die sizes of certain cores, not including their L2 caches, and they are as follows forumsDOTanandtechDOTcom/showthread.php?t=2294334 28nm A7 0.45 sq mm 28nm A15 1.62 sq mm 28nm Jaguar 3.1 sq mm 32nm Atom 5.6 sq mm 22nm Haswell 14.5 sq mm It's obvious that cache and other SoC elements dwarf the core contribution to final die size and Intel is great at designing compact dense caches as AMD has found out over the years. 'True, but in the constrained world of power consumption I'de be shocked that you'de get both 30-40 increase from 3 way (and)</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359180477643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 01:07:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359181056615-7</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>last part got truncated so here it is again ... 'True, but in the constrained world of power consumption I'de be shocked that you'de get both 30-40 increase from 3 way and OoO and still be inside your power (and die) budget.' Firstly the 30-40% increase is either from 3-way OR OoO but having both would compound the improvement i.e. 70-90% which is why the Atom design still has great performance potential. You can mitigate power increases by say shortening the pipeline as ARM did going from A8 to A7. Also the new 22nm trigate process will help in reducing power.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359181056615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 01:17:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359181314369-8</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Firstly the 30-40% increase is either from 3-way OR OoO but having both would compound the improvement i.e. 70-90% which is why the Atom design still has great performance potential. You can mitigate power increases by say shortening the pipeline as ARM did going from A8 to A7. Also the new 22nm trigate process will help in reducing power. Intel doesn't have the experience in low power design. They're making things up as they go and then seeing how well they did. This why it has taken them 6 years to come this far and they still don't really know how far behind they are. They're pretty much blowing in the wind.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359181314369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 01:21:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359181352905-9</Id><Topic><Title>Why Big Deals Are Imminent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359172589896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'That assuming 100% of the Windows 8 tablet market will exceed 5% of the overall tablet market that includes the iPad and Android based tablets.' With corporate buyers added to the mix it might even be more ;-)</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359181352905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 01:22:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359181663262-10</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are not behind at all. In the same exact phone, Medfield beats one of the most power efficient ARM chips, Snapdragon S4 Krait, in both performance and power efficiency. You can pretend otherwise but these facts are out there now and no amount of hand waving from you can change that.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359181663262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 01:27:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359181851257-11</Id><Topic><Title>Up a freakin penny..When are the layoffs starting???</Title><Username>poppinmoremidols</Username><Timestamp>1359165741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 21:02:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they can't do anything else besides processor chips, everything else they try they fail at. Can;t compete in a free market. A sad story indeed.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1359181851257</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 01:30:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359182069870-12</Id><Topic><Title>Where would this be without the buyback?</Title><Username>tkell31</Username><Timestamp>1359174659231</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 23:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Since 2008 Intc's share count is down by roughly 600 million. That seems great, but they've spent about 29 billion doing it. How could that be you ask? well unfortunately they've issued about 700 million shares during that time so despite "buying back" about 1.3 billion shares management has seen fit to compensate themselves handsomely during a time the stock price has languished." Share count: it looks like you neglected to count the shares retired in 2012 but included the cost. My numbers show that $29.186b was used to repurchase 1.315b shares which reduced the shares outstanding count by 860 million. From the 5 years, Jan 2008 through Jan 2013, there was a reduction of shares by 860 million instead of the purchased shares of 1.315b 1.315 - 0.860 = 445m shares were issued by Intel into the market. There are two programs that Intel has that would account for these 455m shares. 1. Stock Purchase Plan (SPP). Employees are allowed to contribute up to 5% of their salary into a fund that is use to buy Intel shares at a 15% discount. That used to be 10% but was reduced to 5%. Search for " intel stock purchase plan " for more detailed information. 2. Stock options to Intel employees are part of their compensation package. All exempt employess participate. Search for " intel stock rsu option plan " for more detailed information. 3. When Intel buys a company they merge the compensation programs and this also generates some new shares. How much of the 455mil are generated from each of these programs? Hard to tell. I am pretty sure that 100% of the 455mil shrares created (after buybacks) are NOT from RSU awards to employees but it makes inflammatory reading. My calculations ... you can skip unless interested in the details. Intel share count taken from SEC Form 10k annual reports which are the share counts on Jan 1st of each year. Jan 2008 the share count was 5.788b shares. The share count has been reduced by 5.788b - 4.928b = .860b shares YEAR SHARES_OUTSTANDING(all number billions) Q4/2012 4.928 .......... reduced by 0.048 shares estimate from $1billion repurchase 10/2012 4.976 1/2012 4.996 1/2011 5.488 1/2010 5.524 1/2009 5.562 1/2008 5.788 xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx 1/2007 5.767 1/2006 5.883 1/2005 6.227 1/2004 6.484 1/2003 6.544 1/2002 6.703 1/2001 6.718 1/2000 6.684 1/1999 6.648 1/1998 6.504 YEAR QUARTER SHARES $mil 2012 Q4 47 1,000 2012 Q3 46 1,165 2012 Q2 41 1,100 2012 Q1 57 1,500 2011 Q4 174 4,133 2011 Q3 186 4,000 2011 Q2 93 2,000 2011 Q1 189 4,000 2010 Q4 70 1,500 2010 Q3 0 0 2010 Q2 0 0 2010 Q1 0 0 2009 Q4 0 0 2009 Q3 88 1,671 2009 Q2 0 0 2009 Q1 0 0 2008 Q4 0 0 2008 Q3 93 2,117 2008 Q2 109 2,500 2008 Q1 122 2,500 2007 Q4 57 1,500 2007 Q3 30 750 2007 Q2 4 100 2007 Q1 19 400 2006 Q4 7 150 2006 Q3 27 500 2006 Q2 54 1,000 2006 Q1 139 2,943 2005 Q4 118 3,137 2005 Q3 94 2,500 2005 Q2 99 2,500 2005 Q1 108 2,500</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359182069870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 01:34:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359182098546-13</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think your are mis-representing the facts a little.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359182098546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 01:34:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359182673719-14</Id><Topic><Title>Why Big Deals Are Imminent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359172589896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Excess capacity at Intel can only be used to produce Intel chips. If they take on an external customer such as Cisco as a foundry, it will take some time before they can re-align their production mechanism to the new chip design during which the plant will remain idle. As a ballpark, it takes 4 years to produce a new chip. Since Cisco already has a design, it may cut that time in half. So for 2 years, the plant will depreciate. If they wanted to utilize this excess capacity as a foundry, they should have been working on it for the last two years." [Once again you demonstrate that you have almost no facts at your disposal but it doesn't bother you. You just make stuff up. Intel rolls out a new node every 2 years. You must be thinking of ARM on that 4 years to produce a new chip. So, Intel isn't going to have anything sitting around idle for very long. And you don't know when the Cisco deal went down. Do you think they just negotiate these things and then start with no preliminary work? Your conclusions are not surprising from someone who doesn't understand why anyone would need more than an iPad for any computing purpose. Do you think engineers design new fabrication facilities on iPads too?] [Not to mention how you play both sides of this argument whenever it suits you. You alluded to ARM catching Intel on fabrication technology in 18 months but now say it takes 4 years to produce a new chip. Which is it, butkus? You can't have it be 18 months in one post and 4 years in the next. LOL]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359182673719</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 01:44:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359183139043-15</Id><Topic><Title>Why Big Deals Are Imminent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359172589896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You're making the assumption that Intel will have more than 5% of the mobile market. That's a big assumption given where they're starting from and how competitive the market is already." [You gotta be kidding. Have you ever seen Intel's track record when they target a new market? They usually end up with 80 percent within 4 to 5 years. Once LTE and 14nm get cranked up, it's all over but the crying and shouting for ARMH. You really need to spend a little more time studying up and less time making shiznit up...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359183139043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 01:52:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359183319620-16</Id><Topic><Title>Why Big Deals Are Imminent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359172589896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm waiting to see how your message changes when we get to 14nm and they have integrated 4G/LTE.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359183319620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 01:55:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359183398802-17</Id><Topic><Title>Where would this be without the buyback?</Title><Username>tkell31</Username><Timestamp>1359174659231</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 23:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. Hopefully that is right and almost 67% of the buyback money has actually reduced the outstanding stock, but that still means around 10 billion of it went right back into managements pockets. And it does make the stock performance even more pathetic. Really begs the question where will the stock be when the buybacks slow down. In its history INTC bought back 4.3 billion shares at a cost of close to 90 billion dollars. Want to let us know how much of that was just fighting dilution versus reducing the share count?</Msg><Username>tkell31</Username><Timestamp>1359183398802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 01:56:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359183477077-18</Id><Topic><Title>Where would this be without the buyback?</Title><Username>tkell31</Username><Timestamp>1359174659231</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 23:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, you smacked tkell31 down so hard I bet his relatives will pee blood tomorrow...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359183477077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 01:57:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359183776728-19</Id><Topic><Title>Where would this be without the buyback?</Title><Username>tkell31</Username><Timestamp>1359174659231</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 23:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tkell31, apparently you don't understand how technology companies compensate and retain talent. If companies don't do this, then top employees simply move to companies that do. Trying to bash Intel for an industry-wide practice is a little disingenuous don't you think?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359183776728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 02:02:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359184640150-20</Id><Title>The Future According to Intel</Title><Msg>More efficient CPUs, connected cars and wireless charging: find out what Intel's research teams have in store Intel is a company that’s always looking ahead – necessarily so, since it takes years to design and manufacture a new processor core. At September’s Intel Developer Forum, senior fellow Mark Bohr confirmed that, beyond the current 22nm Ivy Bridge architecture, work is already well underway towards 14nm chips in 2014, and 10nm around 2016 – with 7nm and 5nm chips to follow. These die shrinks tie in with a bigger plan: to drive down power consumption. Last year, CTO Justin Rattner promised “a decade-long effort to take computing to new extremes of energy efficiency and performance”, committing the company to an ambitious 300-fold increase in power efficiency over ten years. This isn’t just a green initiative. One benefit of energy-efficient cores is that it’s easier to multiply processing power. Intel’s recently announced Xeon Phi co-processor card points the way, offering more than 50 cores in a single package. For now, it’s aimed at specialists needing exceptional performance, but the concept could easily trickle down to end users. Personal assistants More interestingly, energy-efficient cores also allow devices to scale down. Intel envisages computing resources being so electrically cheap that smartphones and watches are as capable as modern desktops. With this sort of power, gadgets can work out what’s going on around them and become more like personal assistants. Intel aims to achieve this partly using electronic sensor data – gyroscopes and accelerometers to monitor movement, and GPS and Wi-Fi to pin down your location. It could also listen to ambient noise and discern what’s going on. Intel envisages computing resources being so electrically cheap that smartphones and watches are as capable as modern desktops What Intel calls “soft sensing” is fed into the picture as well: for example, a device might make use of the contents of your calendar, inbox and history to offer you a particular link at a particular time. Researchers are even working on ways to combine social and location information for multiple individuals, to identify how your device should behave when you’re with different friends. As Rattner explained at the launch of the initiative, it all points to more proactive services. “As your devices learn about your life, they can begin to anticipate your needs... Consider a context-aware remote control that determines who is holding it and automatically selects the Smart TV preferences for that person.” On the road One project that Intel is currently focusing on is what it calls the “Connected Car”. This isn’t necessarily a counterpart to Google’s driverless vehicles (see opposite), but an information system designed for the demands of being on the road, which learns from your activities and social context. All these knowledge sources working together will allow future vehicles to adjust to your driving behaviour Rattner promises that “technologies in development will allow the vehicle to know a non-trivial amount of information about the driver and other occupants. That knowledge will only increase as the vehicle is driven, making the car appear smarter over time.” “All these knowledge sources working together will allow future vehicles to adjust to your driving behaviour, anticipate where you’re going without explicit input, and help you manage your life while you’re driving,” he explained. Wireless charging Intel’s main business may be microprocessors, but its in-house research extends beyond the confines of the computer case. A recent lab demonstration showed off a bespoke wireless charging system allowing smartphones and peripherals to charge whenever they’re placed near a PC or laptop, at roughly the same rate as they currently do over USB. “The batteries will never again run out on your wireless keyboard or mouse once we get this technology to market,” promised Intel’s Kirk Skaugen. The batteries will never again run out on your wireless keyboard or mouse once we get this technology to market There’s also a projector-based gesture-recognition system that turns any wall into a gigantic “touchscreen” – a technology we’ve also seen developed by Ubi Interactive in our Kinect for Windows feature. And Intel also regularly demonstrates projects aimed at education, healthcare and industry. No matter what you do, there’s a good chance you’ll be affected by some aspect of Intel’s research in the next few years. From PC Pro</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359184640150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 02:17:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359185430911-21</Id><Topic><Title>The Future According to Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359184640150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 02:17:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel doesn't know diddly squat about how of if its chips are going to get used in the devices of the future. It's used to a bottom-up technology development model and the industry is switching to a top-down model.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359185430911</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 02:30:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359185501845-22</Id><Title>Why would I want a smartphone with a Intel chip?</Title><Msg>Well. I finally decided to settle for a non Intel smartphone, hoping by next year, I can upgrade to an Intel version. But after sitting down and waiting for the salesperson at Bestbuy to get me set up for a Razr M smartphone, I was asked for my Verizon password. Since I never used it before, I forgot. After giving alot of my personal information, I was still expected to give my password. So I had to call Verizon and go through some steps to reach a live person and reset my password. It lasted about 10 minutes. So why would I want a smartphone with an Intel chip? How about because it would have the powerful chip to read my fingerprint or eye retina to identify me so that I don't have to remember every password that I have across a huge number of media. Can't wait for the Razr i or Lenovo K900 type phones here in the U.S.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1359185501845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 02:31:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359185728750-23</Id><Topic><Title>Why would I want a smartphone with a Intel chip?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1359185501845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 02:31:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would try to come up with a scheme to help me remember my passwords rather than relying on retinal or fingerprint identification which can be done without my awareness of the fact.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359185728750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 02:35:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359194354606-24</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>28nm A7 0.45 sq mm 28nm A15 1.62 sq mm ---- Good link, thanks for posting. The A15 is a lot smaller than I was expecting, digging through the posts on the link it appears that the A15 number is based upon a tegra 4 die layout image from Nvidia so I'll take that size with a pinch of salt:) The A7 does look interesting, especially if that 75% IPC of the A9 is correct.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1359194354606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 04:59:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359195071572-25</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are not behind at all. In the same exact phone, Medfield beats one of the most power efficient ARM chips, Snapdragon S4 Krait, in both performance and power efficiency. You can pretend otherwise but these facts are out there now and no amount of hand waving from you can change that. ----- Performance wise, the Krait beats the Medfield in the I in: Geekbench Quadrant Vellamo AnTuTu CF-Bench Every Java based benchmark I could find Every Graphics based benchmark I could find Medfield beats in: Sunspider Browsermark Battery wise, the the I is better, lasted 9 hours V 8 in the M.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1359195071572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 05:11:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359195457967-26</Id><Topic><Title>Why Big Deals Are Imminent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359172589896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is something unprecedented about to happen, and it has to happen very quickly in order to use that capacity. By the time whatever this is is known, it will be too late to take a position in Intel to make the really heavy sugar. ----- Sounds great. Question: Why hasn't Intel moved it's baseband processors from TSMC's 40nm process to it's own LP 32nm?</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1359195457967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 05:17:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359208825572-27</Id><Topic><Title>Why would I want a smartphone with a Intel chip?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1359185501845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 02:31:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Razr M is a good phone. I have one. I still can't believe Iphones are so hot with the small screen. I just hope that 5 years from now every Motorola phone has Intel in it. Seems like battery life is the next complete game changer, whoever gets it right.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1359208825572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:00:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359208951401-28</Id><Topic><Title>The Future According to Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359184640150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 02:17:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel doesn't know diddly squat about how of if its chips are going to get used in the devices of the future. It's used to a bottom-up technology development model and the industry is switching to a top-down model. __________ I'm not quite sure why anyone responds to you since you slipped up and posted a VERY VERY pro-Intel post under this alias by mistake. What's your deal ??</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1359208951401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:02:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359209194274-29</Id><Topic><Title>The Future According to Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359184640150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 02:17:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a link to an old article that speculates on this switch happening: seekingalphaDOTcom/article/873421-computer-design-now-works-backward-to-intel-s-detriment?source=yahoo</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359209194274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:06:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359209444174-30</Id><Title>Yolo Smartphone launched in Kenya</Title><Msg>Yolo! Intel smartphone launched in Kenya 26 Jan 2013 07:50 - Arthur Goldstuck Kenya's Safaricom has announced the release of the Yolo smartphone, the first smartphone for Africa using the Intel smartphone platform.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1359209444174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:10:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359209587624-31</Id><Title>Kildare Intel Plant could see 800 jobs</Title><Msg>Kildare Intel plant could see 800 jobs Thursday, January 24 14:29:55 Chip giant Intel has been granted planning permission to develop a USD4bn 14 nanometer (nm) chip plant at their campus in Leixlip, Co Kildare with the potential to create 800 long term jobs and well over 1,000 jobs in the building phase. However, Intel has yet to decide whether to locate the next generation plant in Ireland. The company has an existing workforce of 4,000 in Kildare. Intel has said it is to develop next- generation facilities to handle future products and the planning permission means that this is one obstacle that Intel need not worry about should the decision fall in Ireland's favour. In May last year, Intel CEO Paul Otellini confirmed Intel Ireland's Leixlip plant is one of three global sites that has been chosen to produce its next-generation 14nm chips. The two other sites that have been chosen are Intel's Oregon and Arizona plants. Intel is moving from a 22nm process to a 14nm process and aims to create 10nm, 7nm and 5nm chips beyond 2015. Dublin is right on track to become a leading 'Smart' city at a global level and the potential for new jobs at Intel's campus at Leixlip underpins this, according to Dublin Chamber of Commerce. Following approval from An Bord Pleanala for a 40-hectare expansion at the plant in Leixlip, Gina Quin, Dublin Chamber Chief Executive said, "In the past few years we have seen a crop of leading technology firms like facebook, twitter and LinkedIn, choosing the region as their base for accessing the European market and utilizing a highly-skilled workforce. It is vital that we continue to attract this type of foreign direct investment to ensure we maintain our development as a 'Smart' open and internationalised city". (By Joe O'Connor)</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1359209587624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:13:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359209711490-32</Id><Topic><Title>How did you like the 8 millions shares purchased in the last 15 min TIC TOC. Can you tell the difference yet?</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1359147889186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 16:04:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that means 8 million were sold you idiot.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1359209711490</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:15:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359212629090-33</Id><Title>THE WORLD ACCORDING TO WALLIS</Title><Msg>All shorts are toast $30 is a slam dunk Anyone who disagrees with Wallis is Lucy HI-HO WEAVERINO!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1359212629090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 10:03:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359214198412-34</Id><Topic><Title>Intel powered Yolo smartphone keeps close to Samsung Galaxy S3</Title><Username>amd_end_of_days</Username><Timestamp>1359210205420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:23:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting review. The Intel-based Yolo delivers performance roughly equal to a Galaxy S3 and priced at about $130 for the African market. The S3 sells for what? $500-600? Intel's dual-core Medfield is matching Samsung's quad core. This is going to get interesting fast.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1359214198412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 10:29:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359215417324-35</Id><Title>I told all my clients to sell Friday before the the correction that coming</Title><Msg>That why the volume was high. We did own a lot of shares and will buy back when the share price goes down.</Msg><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1359215417324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 10:50:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359215674470-36</Id><Topic><Title>Intel powered Yolo smartphone keeps close to Samsung Galaxy S3</Title><Username>amd_end_of_days</Username><Timestamp>1359210205420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:23:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bravo! I agree with merlot about things getting real interesting real fast (as delivered by a David Lynch character detective or cop)</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1359215674470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 10:54:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359215833263-37</Id><Topic><Title>Intel powered Yolo smartphone keeps close to Samsung Galaxy S3</Title><Username>amd_end_of_days</Username><Timestamp>1359210205420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:23:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>things getting real interesting real fast ----------------------- Too bad you can't say that about the share price. TOOOOO FUNNNNNNY! HI-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1359215833263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 10:57:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359216329096-38</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget Kraken, V8, Octane and every other javascript benchmark which clearly show Medfield is the faster internet processor. Clovertrail+ will also reclaim a lot of those other benchmarks while still retaining a power efficiency lead as 4-thread multi-threading with 2 cores will ensure real life multitasking and multithreading is handled more power efficiently than just having 2 or 4 cores and without thermal throttling which the quad-core S4 Pro has been accused of. The previous Atoms were in hindsight a work in progress but the final 32nm generation Medfield/Clovertrail(+) are the real deal, a thoroughly competitive mobile processor with the best ARM products out there. It only gets better from here as Atom through the exact same architectural improvements already applied to ARM processors can potentially double its performance and Intel's continuing process improvements can ensure that does not come at the expense of excess power as happened in the ARM A9 to A15 transition. As someone who has studied computer architecture for many decades I know Intel has got the Atom design just right, now and going forward. ARM vendors really have serious competition now.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359216329096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 11:05:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359216369187-39</Id><Topic><Title>Intel powered Yolo smartphone keeps close to Samsung Galaxy S3</Title><Username>amd_end_of_days</Username><Timestamp>1359210205420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:23:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow nice INTC smart phone, everyone must have thier nuff shet filters on, good to see no reponses to that IDIOT.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1359216369187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 11:06:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359216550774-40</Id><Topic><Title>Intel powered Yolo smartphone keeps close to Samsung Galaxy S3</Title><Username>amd_end_of_days</Username><Timestamp>1359210205420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:23:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many people respond to Lucy every day here, it's just that they don't know it, buttwad.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1359216550774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 11:09:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359216941346-41</Id><Topic><Title>According to Annandtech, Intel's lexington low cost phone is sold for $126</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359148728914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 16:18:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously Intel can profitably sell Medfield, or Clovertrail even, for about $10 as I said they could. Paul Otellini: 'we will not lose a design win on price'</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359216941346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 11:15:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359217085256-42</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think ARM will continue to push the power/performance envelope at several different smartphone and tablet operating points with big.LITTLE on Exynos, Apple's A7 and Qualcomm's S800 with built in 4G/LTE. Enhancements on ARMs side of the fence more or less match those in Intel's side. Therefore, the likely scenario is they will maintain relative position. With commoditization starting to show its face in mobile devices, its not a great time for Intel to be entering this market. What's happening in mobile can easily extend to Intel's cash cow -- PCs with Microsoft opening up its franchise to the ARM architecture. I wouldn't be surprised if the next version of Windows support ARM PCs. Can you imagine going to Best Buy a few years from now and finding ARM PCs in the same aisle as Intel?</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359217085256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 11:18:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359217335529-43</Id><Topic><Title>According to Annandtech, Intel's lexington low cost phone is sold for $126</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359148728914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 16:18:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, really ??</Msg><Username>tasalarzin</Username><Timestamp>1359217335529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 11:22:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359217408808-44</Id><Topic><Title>According to Annandtech, Intel's lexington low cost phone is sold for $126</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359148728914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 16:18:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If $126 is too expensive for Kenya then the Kenyans sure won't be buying $600 Galaxy S3's will quad core ARM processors. And where is the freedom of choice for ARM? Everyone buys their license for ARM's proprietary technology from one company. At the end of the day, manufacturers will buy the technology they will believe will sell and make them money.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1359217408808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 11:23:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359217662445-45</Id><Topic><Title>Intel powered Yolo smartphone keeps close to Samsung Galaxy S3</Title><Username>amd_end_of_days</Username><Timestamp>1359210205420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:23:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice phone Chip maker Intel and mobile operator Safaricom have announced the Yolo, the first smartphone for the African market with an Intel processor. Intel claims the Android device is aimed for “cost-conscious and first-time buyers in Kenya,” but its specifications aren’t as shabby as that characterization might imply. It’s powered by the Intel Atom Z2420 processor which can reach speeds of up to 1.2GHz. It also comes with a 3.5-inch touch screen, a 5-megapixel camera with full HD video capture support, FM radio and HSPA+ support. “We are delighted to partner with Safaricom in bringing the first smartphone with Intel Inside to Kenyan consumers. The new handset extends the benefits of Intel technology to more smartphone users around the world and we believe that Kenyan consumers will welcome the increased functionality and overall value of the device.”</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1359217662445</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 11:27:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359218223993-46</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'With commoditization starting to show its face in mobile devices, its not a great time for Intel to be entering this market.' If this is true then why are all you ARMH pumpers claiming your asps will rise to justify your inflated stock price ? At least try to be consistent. 'What's happening in mobile can easily extend to Intel's cash cow -- PCs with Microsoft opening up its franchise to the ARM architecture.' Not only won't it happen easily it won't happen at all ! The best Core processor can easily handle the best ARM processor at a quarter of its native clock speed and can have double the cores in a single chip, 8, and four times the threads, 16. So that's about 20 times more computing power for Intel over ARM in each company's best high end chip, an order of magnitude times two ! So no chance, no chance at all !! 'I wouldn't be surprised if the next version of Windows support ARM PCs.' It already does, it's called Windows RT and it's dying at birth. Good luck on trying to get MSFT to continue with this experiment on the next Windows release. 'Can you imagine going to Best Buy a few years from now and finding ARM PCs in the same aisle as Intel?' Not really with all the slow processors they all have in their roadmaps.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359218223993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 11:37:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359218573579-47</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Not really with all the slow processors they all have in their roadmaps." You probably missed Warren East's rallying cry around "good enough" computing. The idea is simple. While you can buy Ferraris and Lambourghinis for the big bucks and get the great 0-60 times, most people buy Hondas. In the world of PCs, ARM licensees will build the Hondas that sell in numbers while Intel will continue to build the expensive high end systems.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359218573579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 11:42:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359219655524-48</Id><Topic><Title>Intel powered Yolo smartphone keeps close to Samsung Galaxy S3</Title><Username>amd_end_of_days</Username><Timestamp>1359210205420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:23:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>everyone must have thier nuff shet filters on, good to see no reponses to that IDIOT. ------------- More accurately, Buttplug, one person with multiple aliases stopped responding to Lucy. It's likely that one person is YOU! Thanks for the mention! U R SOOOOOOOOOO STOOOOOOOOOOPID!!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1359219655524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 12:00:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359219708243-49</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'In the world of PCs, ARM licensees will build the Hondas that sell in numbers while Intel will continue to build the expensive high end systems.' No, Intel will continue to build all the profitable PC systems at ALL price points. A15 displacing an old 45nm Atom in a Chromebook is as good as it's going to get for ARM as its window of opportunity will close when Haswell and Bay Trail are released and forever more afterwards will be forced back on the defensive on its own phone turf. Even AMD and VIA processors will continue to be faster than ARM. Forget these pipe dreams and get ready to dream up the arguments to defend your ARMH stock price when reality intrudes on it as it has on AAPL.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359219708243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 12:01:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359220022406-50</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"No, Intel will continue to build all the profitable PC systems at ALL price points. A15 displacing an old 45nm Atom in a Chromebook is as good as it's going to get for ARM as its window of opportunity will close when Haswell and Bay Trail are released and forever more afterwards will be forced back on the defensive on its own phone turf. Even AMD and VIA processors will continue to be faster than ARM. Forget these pipe dreams and get ready to dream up the arguments to defend your ARMH stock price when reality intrudes on it as it has on AAPL." I think you are missing the point -- speed is redundant after a certain level. If most of the time you're going to be stuck in New York traffic, what does it matter that your car can go really fast? As micro-architectures improve and with the progression of the feature shrinkage, there will come a point soon when ARM processors manufactured on low power processes will be able to perform all the tasks that 90% of user perform relating to their information processing. At that point, all these high speed systems will look like Crays.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359220022406</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 12:07:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359221192102-51</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'I think you are missing the point -- speed is redundant after a certain level. If most of the time you're going to be stuck in New York traffic, what does it matter that your car can go really fast? As micro-architectures improve and with the progression of the feature shrinkage, there will come a point soon when ARM processors manufactured on low power processes will be able to perform all the tasks that 90% of user perform relating to their information processing. At that point, all these high speed systems will look like Crays.' Best of luck with that sales pitch for a buying a slower processor because you are going to need it lol. If you have any luck please pass on any tips to AMD and VIA as they are not having much luck selling their 2nd rate processors profitably even when they are priced dirt cheap :).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359221192102</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 12:26:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359221348364-52</Id><Title>intc should put chips instead of codebars in groceries items for a fast check out service</Title><Msg>Just an idea</Msg><Username>fvelezdevilla</Username><Timestamp>1359221348364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 12:29:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359222530508-53</Id><Topic><Title>Intel powered Yolo smartphone keeps close to Samsung Galaxy S3</Title><Username>amd_end_of_days</Username><Timestamp>1359210205420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:23:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see three ignored message from him on this thread alone. The more you laugh at him, the more he tries to be relevant. Poor fool.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1359222530508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 12:48:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359222748322-54</Id><Topic><Title>Intel powered Yolo smartphone keeps close to Samsung Galaxy S3</Title><Username>amd_end_of_days</Username><Timestamp>1359210205420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 09:23:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many people respond to Lucy every day here, it's just that they don't know it, buttwad. +++++++++++++ Of course they do. After all, you bragged that Intel was the cornerstone of your portfolio when it reached 29. You are a Bagholder that takes his frustration out on other Longs while acting like you aren't Long. You're the definition of an Internet Coward.</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1359222748322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 12:52:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359222835707-55</Id><Topic><Title>Why Big Deals Are Imminent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359172589896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because they had already been designed for TSMC production and mosre importantly anolog devices do not scale very much. Not much real benfit to using advanced geometry.</Msg><Username>johnnelson1205</Username><Timestamp>1359222835707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 12:53:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359228570216-56</Id><Topic><Title>Why Big Deals Are Imminent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359172589896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could this extra capacity have something to do with Intel's plans for a virtual tv service?</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1359228570216</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 14:29:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359228909057-57</Id><Title>Does anyone have new information about Intel's plans for starting a cable TV service?</Title><Msg>The last news about this was in early January.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1359228909057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 14:35:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359229621162-58</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We're entering an era where computers are no longer designed bottom-up, starting from the microprocessor that is going to power them but top-down, starting from how the computer is going to be useful to its user and working down to the choice of chip from there. You can read more about this trend in this rather old article: seekingalphaDOTcom/article/873421-computer-design-now-works-backward-to-intel-s-detriment?source=yahoo</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359229621162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 14:47:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359229770938-59</Id><Topic><Title>I told all my clients to sell Friday before the the correction that coming</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1359215417324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 10:50:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares what you do, did, or intend to do ??? Loser !</Msg><Username>pentomic</Username><Timestamp>1359229770938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 14:49:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359230543530-60</Id><Topic><Title>Why Big Deals Are Imminent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359172589896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Intel strategy in a nutshell: 1. Deliver the most compelling processors and SOC's possible to the mobile market and every other market Intel aims to serve 2. Demonstrate absolute performance and price/performance superiority over competitors products with (2x, 3x, 5x, 10x...whatever) while maintaining 60% gross margins 3. Innovate faster than everyone else in the industry, ie; volume production 22nm 2013, 14nm in 2014, 10nm in 2015. 4. Develop sufficient capacity to be seen as a reliable supplier to the world's most successful device manufacturers and enable new ones with leading-edge products. 5. Forward price the products to a level that guarantees Intel price/performance advantage over competitors and make enough capacity for the margins to be favorable. No other company can replicate Intel's strategy because no one else is capable of that volume. That Intel's dual-core Atom for a $130 phone rivals Samsung's flagship quad-core ARM performance in a $600 phone is just a glimpse where Intel is going to take the industry.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1359230543530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 15:02:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359234945473-61</Id><Title>Asus VivoBook X202E With Touchscreen $499</Title><Msg>Incredible value for a full 64 bit Windows 8 notebook with touchscreen, Core i3 Ivy Bridge, 4GB RAM, and 11.6 inch display. This package is priced in the range of a tablet but instead of a limited functionality toy for games, or some disabled Windows RT package, this is the real deal. It's small, lightweight, good for work or entertainment and from a quality vendor. See Microsoft Store.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1359234945473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 16:15:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359235471578-62</Id><Topic><Title>intc should put chips instead of codebars in groceries items for a fast check out service</Title><Username>fvelezdevilla</Username><Timestamp>1359221348364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 12:29:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's another idea.... A Wallis Weaver Bobble-Head Doll, powered by an Intel chip, that says "$30 is a slam dunk." HI-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1359235471578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 16:24:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359235692048-63</Id><Topic><Title>Asus VivoBook X202E With Touchscreen $499</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1359234945473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 16:15:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Additionally, while the X202E-DH31T also has Intel's integrated HD Graphics 4000 processing, it couldn't run our Aliens vs. Predator test, and only ran Heaven at 1366-by-768 resolution and medium detail for an unplayable 4 frames per second. The real nail in the coffin, however, was battery life. Despite the sub-3-pound weight and ultra-low-voltage processor, the X202E-DH31T (and its 38Wh, 2-cell battery) only lasted 3 hours 50 minutes in our video rundown test.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1359235692048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 16:28:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359238360231-64</Id><Title>The real question is are there any ARM based phones that sell for less than $100.</Title><Msg>If not, Intel owns the smartphone market, Ex apple (which is a luxury brand).</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359238360231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 17:12:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359239586551-65</Id><Topic><Title>Why Big Deals Are Imminent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359172589896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And if Intel does need to compete on price at some point, their immense capacity will allow them to do so very effectively. Given this huge capacity, their superior technology and their highly sophisticated pricing strategies, it is unlikely to come to that...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359239586551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 17:33:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359240026260-66</Id><Topic><Title>Why Big Deals Are Imminent</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359172589896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:56:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Question: Why hasn't Intel moved it's baseband processors from TSMC's 40nm process to it's own LP 32nm?" [You're like one of those little dogs that runs out from behind a sofa to nip people on the ankles. You think you are pretty smart so you should be able to come up with a logical answer to this without the ankle-biting. If out of all that was said this is your best response, then I think the ARMH camp is out of ammo. Prepare to be over-run...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359240026260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 17:40:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359240079978-67</Id><Topic><Title>Is the 4% dividend a reason to hold?</Title><Username>jswinning</Username><Timestamp>1359134152570</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:15:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the mobile market Intel is interested in ??? What about the mobile market consumers are interested in ?? Intel has failed. Yeah not much competition in the pipeline,lol, You think they are just gonna let Intel take that CPU money ? BIG no. Stock prices are driven by growth, Intel's is slowing.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1359240079978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 17:41:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359240172288-68</Id><Topic><Title>Is the 4% dividend a reason to hold?</Title><Username>jswinning</Username><Timestamp>1359134152570</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:15:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They can't do anything about Intel taking the smartphone market. Their chips are just too expensive, slow and hog power. What are they going to do, sell smartphones at a loss?</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359240172288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 17:42:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359240515448-69</Id><Title>Aladiesright and Khitcdee, put your money where your big mouths are</Title><Msg>What price will you short Intel to from here? That's what I thought. AMD is dead and ARM has peaked, get over it.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359240515448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 17:48:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359240879125-70</Id><Title>VALV WILL RUN HARD MONDAY!</Title><Msg>Read that board for news now!</Msg><Username>vooodooodoc</Username><Timestamp>1359240879125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 17:54:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359241130172-71</Id><Title>Big Intel Deals Are Imminent But Here Is A Smaller One</Title><Msg>ET deals: $300 off HP Omni 27 all-in-one PC "As implied by the name, the Omni 27 is built around a 27-inch 1920×1080 display that looks stunning with its edge-to-edge glass design. The base of this all-in-one allows you to tilt the Omni 27 however you want. The standard specs won’t leave you wanting either, with a total of seven USB ports (two of which are USB 3.0), media card reader slot, Ethernet, Wireless-N, Bluetooth, and more. The base model comes equipped with a Core i5-3330S, which clocks between 2.7GHz and 3.2GHz with Turbo Boost. RAM comes in at an 8GB standard with a 1TB hard drive. The model is fully customizable, letting you choose upgrades like a Core i7 CPU, up to 16GB of RAM, Blu-ray drive, and even up to a Radeon HD 7670A graphics card. The base configuration starts with a list price of $1,199.99, but that drops down to $899.99 plus $9.99 shipping after a rare 25% off coupon. That coupon gives you a flat 25% off the final configuration price of your Omni 27, giving you a 25% discount on whatever upgrades you choose. This is a very low starting price for a premium 27-inch all-in-one PC and the discount certainly doesn’t make matters worse."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359241130172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 17:58:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359241219815-72</Id><Title>Very nice looking Panasonic 20" tablet with Intel processor</Title><Msg>Find the article on Google and look at the picture of the Tablet. Gorgeous. Panasonic Shows Off 20” Tablet with 4K Screen Resolution. Panasonic Demos 4K Tablet Concept with Microsoft Windows 8 [01/26/2013 12:40 PM] by Anton Shilov Panasonic, a major maker of consumer electronics, demonstrated a prototype of a 20” tablet PC with 4K-class screen resolution at CES trade-show earlier this month. The product comes with Intel Core i5 microprocessor as well as discrete Nvidia GeForce graphics chip. The slate conceptually resembles Lenovo IdeaCentre Horizon table PC that is set to be released in mid-2013, but will unlikely reach stores until late in the year. Panasonic’s prototype of 20” tablet with 3840*2560 screen resolution is based on Intel Core i7 3427U (1.8GHz) “Ivy Bridge” microprocessor and is equipped with an unknown Nvidia GeForce graphics adapter capable of 4K resolution, 4GB DDR3 RAM (expandable to 16GB), 128GB solid-state drive, stereo speakers, microphone, 720p web-cam, 802.11a/b/g/n Wi-Fi, Bluetooth 4.0, USB 2.0, microSD card reader and so on. The device weighs 2.4 kilograms (5.3lbs), just like a mainstream 15” notebook. “Panasonic is gearing itself up to propose new business value this feature-rich device will offer to its customers in a wide range of industries. 20” 4K IPS Alpha LCD Panel combines a high precision Anoto Live digital pen with it for super precise input, something valued by an architect, engineer or 3D multimedia content creator, not to mention the photo-video editing or digital painting gurus,” wrote Nebojsa Novakovic, who has seen the device in action, in a story at the Bright Side of News web-site. The 20” LCD panel with 3840*2560 and unique aspect ratio of 15:10, the tablet can display an A3-size paper in almost full size, making it ideal to show content such as newspapers and magazines, as well as pictures with the same aspect ratio. Moreover, the pen input, with a resolution as high as the panel itself, enables natural handwriting on the tablet. Panasonic’s big replacement for iPad is supposed to hit the market this year, but the price is clearly unknown.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359241219815</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 18:00:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359241277525-73</Id><Title>Smartphones could eventually sell for less than feature phones. Because</Title><Msg>of Moores law and digital chip prices coming down rapidly. Intel will be the largest smartphone chip seller in 5 years. Mark my words.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359241277525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 18:01:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359241490256-74</Id><Topic><Title>Smartphones could eventually sell for less than feature phones. Because</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359241277525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 18:01:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know from your past posts that you are Lucy Nuff. For your sake, let's hope Intel is the best in 5 years since Intel is the cornerstone of your portfolio, as you've said. Idiot.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359241490256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 18:04:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359242049079-75</Id><Title>Effects of Intel's Big CapEx</Title><Msg>Upgrades to 450mm: Intel will be there first with a massive economic benefit. Set up 14-nm capacity: 14nm production is literally game over for ARM. ARM has nothing to match it and won't for years. Intel takes the lead in power efficiency and increases its lead in performance. Expect big deals at 14nm and big gains in mobility market share. Research and development on 10-nm: Intel continues its blistering every eight quarter node cycle. 10nm will consolidate and extend Intel's technology and manufacturing lead and incorporate PC-like performance in smaller and smaller devices and form factors. Bear Bryant once said, "It's not the will to win that's important. It's the will to prepare to win." Intel has the will to prepare to win. If you don't believe it, go take a look at the 14nm fabs in Oregon and Arizona.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359242049079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 18:14:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359242486262-76</Id><Title>Intel's Outlook Has Never Looked More Utterly Transformative</Title><Msg>As Intel goes, so goes the entire desktop ecosystem, and hidden deep in the company's newly released financial statements are five portents for the PC industry of 2013 -- and beyond. 1. The PC is not dead This one's easy: Next time a pundit tells you the PC is going the way of the dodo, tell him to stuff it. Sure, general PC sales were down slightly in 2012--3 percent in the case of Intel's PC Clients Group, and an estimated 3 to 5 percent for the industry overall -- but desktops and laptops still do tremendous business. "If you're looking at 350 million units (shipped in 2012), that is not a dead market," says Patrick Moorhead, founder and principal analyst at Moor Insights and Strategy. "The PC industry may be slowing, but it's certainly not dead." As a whole, Intel managed to snag $53.3 billion -- yes, billion with a "B" -- in revenue in 2012. That's more than $1 billion week in and week out. Oh, and while Intel's PC revenues were down 3 percent in 2012, actual unit volume was only down 1 percent. Dead? Hah. 2. ...but the focus is changing No, the consumer PC hasn't given up the ghost, but its days of epic growth have definitely stalled. Intel only expects sales revenues to increase in the single digits in 2013 after the down year of 2012. Intel sees the writing on the wall and is working hard to diversify its lineup to match industry trends -- starting, of course, with those pesky tablets. During his intro to Intel's earnings conference, CFO Stacy Smith spent as much time waxing poetic about the company's 2013 mobile initiatives as he did talking up Ultrabooks and desktop processors. That itself follows a new trend for the company: At CES, Intel's Bay Trail tablet processors and Lexington smartphone processors enjoyed just as much limelight as the upcoming Haswell CPUs. The company is also placing a bigger focus on business customers, and, yes, the now-ubiquitous cloud. Intel's server-focused Data Center Group was the only division that saw revenues increase in 2012, and Intel expects DCG's revenues to grow in double digits this year. The new focus on servers and mobile technology give Intel a unique chance to double-dip the market. "Data center and cloud are Intel," Moorhead says. "Their big boosts in sales were driven by that. Every handset and tablet that gets sold connects to the cloud, and Intel is providing the cloud. People forget that their hardware is driving the cloud right now." 3. Blurring lines and blending uses The future, to hear Intel CEO Paul Otellini tell it to investors, lies in hybrids. (That shouldn't come as a surprise if you've been paying attention thus far.) The first round of Windows 8 hybrids hasn't exactly taken the world by storm, but Otellini expects mobile technology to split into two distinct camps going forward: tablets and phablets in the 5- to 7-inch range, and larger 10-inch-plus offerings. Otellini expects those larger hybrids to offer PC-like performance in a slim, tablet-like form factor thanks to power improvements found in the Haswell and Broadwell processors slated to launch over the next two years. Patrick Moorhead agrees. "All points converge on 2014," Moorhead says. "In 2014, you'll be able to have a very high performance, 9mm thin, fanless, low-cost tablet based on Haswell technology. At 10 inches and above, you'll be able to slide it right into a keyboard dock. Why on earth would you buy a separate tablet? Because you're not compromising as a notebook, and you're not compromising as a tablet, there really won't be a market for stand-alone 10-inch tablets." That doesn't sound good for Windows RT -- or for notebooks, really. Intel's already laying the base for the flipping, sliding, and oh-so-versatile future of laptops. At CES, the company announced that any laptops powered by Haswell processors will need to sport a touchscreen in order to also sport the Ultrabook name. 4. Racing towards the top One thing about hybrids, though: They're more expensive than their less-flexible counterparts. Despite recent howls for cheap touchscreen notebooks to boost Windows 8 sales, we're more likely to see manufacturers futzing around in the high end rather than duking it out for low-cost supremacy. Sales of touch-enabled Windows 8 models in the fourth quarter have convinced Otellini that "people are willing to spend a little bit more to get a more capable product. That's certainly been true in the Apple model for many, many years, and I think there is a model of getting paid for innovation." Get ready to whip out your checkbooks, folks. OEMs aren't dumb. They want in on that gravy train, and we've already seen manufacturers like Dell and Acer dump low-end products to focus on Ultrabooks and other products with higher margins, though that didn't exactly pay off in 2012. But fear not, budget-minded PC fans: cheap laptops aren't quite ready to doddle off into the sunset quite yet. "Intel's not saying they won't participate in the low-end market. In fact, they have parts like Atom and Pentium that prove that they will," Moorhead says. "What they're saying is that they're going to put their focus into new usage models that require higher performance and drive even better experiences." Those better experiences, Moorhead says, will culminate in Intel's " Perceptual computing" initiative, which blends computer control with human senses. Speaking of innovation... 5. Racing towards the top, part II: Moore continues laying down the law Consumer PC sales may be slowing, but Intel's focus on creating smaller, better, more efficient processors hasn't wavered. The company is still building towards a bright PC future, spending a whopping $18.2 billion -- again, that's billion with a "B" -- on R&amp;D and acquisitions last year. That number's expected to jump to $18.9 billion in 2013. Intel isn't just funding killer company parties with all that cash, either. The company plans to start production on the 14nm chip-making manufacturing process in 2013. "This puts us significantly ahead of the competition," CFO Smith said during the earnings conference. Intel's current Ivy Bridge chips are built using a 22nm manufacturing process, while AMD's processors have been stuck at 28nm. Expect 14nm Haswell chips to start showing up in 2014, but that's not all Intel has up its sleeve. In 2013, the company also plans to start initial work on the 10nm manufacturing process, the 2016 die-shrink "tick" following the new Skylake "tock" architecture planned for 2015. But while Intel's chips are getting smaller and smaller, the company's working hard to increase the size of the silicon wafers those chips are cut from. Current wafers measure 300mm, and Intel wants to move to 450mm. Bigger wafers mean lower production costs, which might -- just maybe -- result in lower CPU prices in the future. Although the move to larger wafers isn't expected to really start ramping up until the latter half of the decade, Intel has already begun investing in the transition process. Yep, Chipzilla thinks long-term. A key 2012 investment could pay off for both of those initiatives. In July, Intel gave ASML Holdings $3.3 billion to stimulate the development of both 450mm wafers and extreme ultraviolet lithography, a next-gen technology candidate that could help Intel make chips using ever-smaller CMOS manufacturing processes. Intel expects the immersion lithography process used to make current day chips to become ineffective in sub-10nm chips. Intel has said it doesn't expect the ultraviolet technology or 450mm wafers to be ready for the 2016 roll-out of 10nm "Skymont" chips, but Otellini declined to provide an update about 10nm chips and the possible use of EUVL when asked about it during the earnings conference. To infinity, and beyond! Sure, Intel's operating income may be down a bit in 2012, but taken overall, the company's earnings point to a vibrant, cutting-edge future for PCs, and hundreds of millions of PCs at that. That future might look different than the present we recognize, with more blurring of the lines and segmented niches, but the PC's outlook has never looked brighter -- or more utterly transformative.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359242486262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 18:21:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359242580236-77</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Outlook Has Never Looked More Utterly Transformative</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359242486262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 18:21:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To infinity, and beyond! Sure, Intel's operating income may be down a bit in 2012, but taken overall, the company's earnings point to a vibrant, cutting-edge future for PCs, and hundreds of millions of PCs at that. That future might look different than the present we recognize, with more blurring of the lines and segmented niches, but the PC's outlook has never looked brighter -- or more utterly transformative. From PCWorld</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359242580236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 18:23:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359245115399-78</Id><Title>Lucy aka</Title><Msg>D-a-n-a B-l-a-n-k-e-n-h-o-r-n</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359245115399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:05:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359245355544-79</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy aka</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359245115399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:05:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lucy has a new Intel bashing article on Insider Monkey. An appropriate place for Lucy to reside, I guess...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359245355544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:09:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359247665819-80</Id><Topic><Title>Does anyone have new information about Intel's plans for starting a cable TV service?</Title><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1359228909057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 14:35:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We hope they will announce another pump on the tv cable plans..We can't wait to bail out of this pig..</Msg><Username>pentomic</Username><Timestamp>1359247665819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:47:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359248529522-81</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy aka</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359245115399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:05:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is a Motly Fool article that was written 3-days ago on Jan 23. Dana Blankenhorn also wrote an article on Jan 13 about Apple. Stop the Apple Insanity! By Dana Blankenhorn01/14/13 - 06:30 AM EST and down at the end of the article, he discloses that he was long Apple and complaining about all the bearishness around Apple. Apple closed before the artcile at $520.30 and he said: "Yet technical analysts at Investorplace predict a move down on Apple, to $480/share, maybe $460. What gives? " "At the time of publication, the author was long AAPL." I can understand why someone with a BS in Journalism from Rice and no other technical or economic training could be upset that his profits in his Apple position had vaporized. I doubt that he is "lucy" and also doubt that his recommedation that Intel become a foundry is based on anything other than his current portfolio.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359248529522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 20:02:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359251427713-82</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy aka</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359245115399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:05:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe. Lucy could actually be his twin brother Dnenni. It would be a lot easier to identify Lucy if the pinheads in the family didn't all look alike and play the banjo...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359251427713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 20:50:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359251590739-83</Id><Topic><Title>Does anyone have new information about Intel's plans for starting a cable TV service?</Title><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1359228909057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 14:35:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We hope they will announce another pump on the tv cable plans..We can't wait to bail out of this pig.." [You live in a pig?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359251590739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 20:53:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359251814056-84</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy aka</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359245115399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:05:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I can understand why someone with a BS in Journalism from Rice and no other technical or economic training could be upset that his profits in his Apple position had vaporized." [We also know that Lucy went to a school whose football program was so bad that Lucy steadfastly refused to say where he went. I'm pretty sure they make everyone who went to Rice to agree to that before they give them their diplomas...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359251814056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 20:56:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359253714584-85</Id><Topic><Title>Asus VivoBook X202E With Touchscreen $499</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1359234945473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 16:15:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel HD Graphics 4000 renders popular video material at the popular 1080p and 720p resolutions very well. Good gaming performance requires capabilities in a graphics subsystem not necessary for general purpose use and PC buyers don't want to pay for features they'll never use. Any serious gamer today will buy dedicated graphics. Although Intel is pushing graphics improvements so quickly that even dedicated graphics will soon become unnecessary except for the most demanding gaming or video editing applications.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1359253714584</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:28:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359254962023-86</Id><Title>A new dangerous fraud that McAfee can't catch</Title><Msg>Google "Creepy Advertising Fraud Reaches New Levels".</Msg><Username>vincent64</Username><Timestamp>1359254962023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:49:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359255473236-87</Id><Topic><Title>Asus VivoBook X202E With Touchscreen $499</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1359234945473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 16:15:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody's gonna buy an Acer to game. Geez.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1359255473236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:57:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359255482226-88</Id><Topic><Title>Asus VivoBook X202E With Touchscreen $499</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1359234945473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 16:15:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I mean Asus..</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1359255482226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:58:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359256972827-89</Id><Topic><Title>A new dangerous fraud that McAfee can't catch</Title><Username>vincent64</Username><Timestamp>1359254962023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 21:49:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's equally creepy is you using Yahoo to direct traffic to your blog. Did Dnenni tell you to try this?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359256972827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 22:22:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359257918731-90</Id><Topic><Title>Asus VivoBook X202E With Touchscreen $499</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1359234945473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 16:15:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At this price point, why in the world would anyone buy an Arm-based Tablet?? Intel products will dominate the $500 price point. ARM is toast.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1359257918731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 22:38:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359262372612-91</Id><Title>So what does the future look like for Ultrabooks.</Title><Msg>Looks pretty good according to Intel. But let's see what iSuppli thinks. Global shipments of solid-state drives are expected to more than double this year, with a boost from a new generation of lower-cost ultrabooks with more appealing features, according to a report from industry researcher IHS iSuppli. Solid-state drives can serve as an alternative to hard-disk drives in personal computers and store data using NAND-flash memory chips rather than traditional rotating media. Shipments are expected to rise to 83 million units this year from 39 million in 2012. The forecast includes traditional solid-state drives as well as the cache variety, but doesn't include hybrid drives. Longer term, shipments are projected to reach 239 million units in 2016, comprising about 40% of the size of the market for hard-disk drives. "The fate of the SSD business is closely tied to the market for ultrabooks and other ultrathin PCs that use cache drives," said IHS analyst Ryan Chien. Though solid-state drive shipments more than doubled during 2012, "growth actually fell short of expectations because ultrabook sales faltered due to poor marketing, high prices and a lack of appealing features," Mr. Chien said. "However, if sales of the new generation of ultrabooks take off this year as expected, the SSD market is set for robust growth." iSuppli said that a newest wave of ultrabook loaded with Microsoft Corp.'s (MSFT) Windows 8 has started to generate enthusiasm and is expected to to pick up this year, while coming ultrabooks based on Intel Corp.'s (INTC) Haswell chip architecture also could boost potential for solid-state drives this year.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1359262372612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 23:52:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>