<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-28"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372392933536-1</Id><Title>Some Analyst is licking his chops waiting to bad mouth this pig tomorrow.</Title><Msg>Options expiration or something.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372392933536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:15:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372392998485-2</Id><Topic><Title>Some Analyst is licking his chops waiting to bad mouth this pig tomorrow.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372392933536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:15:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We need Mr Weaver to double his pumps to offset the bad mouthing Analysts.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372392998485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:16:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372394418013-3</Id><Title>Intel is becoming a growth stock</Title><Msg>Intel has entered or will enter into these new markets: - Smartphones - baseband - Foundry - Web TV - Solid-State Drives Revenues from these market are really "icing on the cake" as they will utilized manufacturing process already paid for by Intel's core products. For example, all the FABS that are producing Medfield/Clovertrail 32nm wafers would have been paid for by 32nm Sandy Bridge. All the 22nm FABS that will produce BayTrail would have been paid for by Ivy Bridge and Haswell. This is a major advantage Intel has over arm foundries and partners. It's important to note that revenue from these new markets are in *addition* to their other products, i.e., they're not cannibalizing other sales. Example: Apple may have cannibalized some of it's own iPad margins by introducing the lower margin iPad Mini.. But Intel selling smartphone chips (at less margin) is not taking business away from any other Intel division. So how is adding lower margin sales a bad thing when they are in *addition* to all other sales? Answer is they're not. Intel is going to grow BIG TIME.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372394418013</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:40:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372395005781-4</Id><Topic><Title>Lagging....</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372344184095</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 10:43:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh sure! INTC is dead money, PC is dead, Intel has no chance gaining mobile market share. That's why Intel is up 16% year to date while the super star of smart phones and tablets is down over 25% year to date. You make alot of sense dumb dumb.</Msg><Username>analysis101vp</Username><Timestamp>1372395005781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 00:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372398187348-5</Id><Title>Is there an unwritten rule that all intel contract engineering position are staffing by people that sound dumb as hell?</Title><Msg>just an observation while seeking employment over the last few years as a contractor.</Msg><Username>furyan.microsystems</Username><Timestamp>1372398187348</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:43:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372398511816-6</Id><Title>Earnings on July 17th</Title><Msg>The first with Brian Krzanich. It will be interesting to see how his style is different and to see how he inter-reacts with the analysts...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372398511816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:48:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372398699646-7</Id><Topic><Title>Is there an unwritten rule that all intel contract engineering position are staffing by people that sound dumb as hell?</Title><Username>furyan.microsystems</Username><Timestamp>1372398187348</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:43:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check out this guy's message history for a laugh...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372398699646</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:51:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372398767180-8</Id><Topic><Title>One trade + $4,500 On the day..</Title><Username>rogerwalker513</Username><Timestamp>1371785363137</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 23:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SDERT</Msg><Username>rollymager</Username><Timestamp>1372398767180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:52:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372399194296-9</Id><Title>The Bull Case for Intel</Title><Msg>Engineering wins, entailing superior performance and power consumption, will allow Intel chips to be sold even at a price premium to ARM derivatives. Intel is boasting that it has busted the “x86 power myth”, that is ARM devices are necessarily more power-saving at the same performance level. This is supported by a comparison from ABI Research, in addition to a side-by-side comparison of the Samsung ATIV Smart PC vs. Microsoft Surface RT by Anandtech. ABI found that “Intel’s [Clover Trail+] chip drew 0.85A of average current vs. 1.38A for the Samsung Exynos Octa, and 1.79A for the Qualcomm APQ8064T.” Anandtech was able to squeeze out a “17% battery life advantage, despite the 3% smaller battery” while web-browsing on the Intel-based Samsung ATIV compared to the ARM-powered Surface RT. Dual-boot devices running a full version of Windows 8 (non-RT) and Android, which is not possible with ARM, will become popularized. This would galvanize demand for Intel Clover Trail chips and beyond, which have this capability From mobilex86</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372399194296</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:59:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372401388258-10</Id><Title>INTEL looking real good!</Title><Msg>- Haswell making big waves with all day battery life and better than retina displays. Examples include the MacBook Airs, Samsung ATIV Q, Samsung ATIV Book 9 Plus, Asus Transformer Book Trio and Dell XPS 11 - Haswell Y-series parts coming up. HP already announce they will release a fanless tablet using the Y-series. Acer is also rumored to have a Haswell Y-series tablet named 'Bulgari' - Intel's 2for1 value proposition play picking up steam. The Lenovo Yoga was a tremendous hit. Other hybrid with detachable form factors such as the Lenovo Helix are getting rave reviews. Now, the Asus Transformer Book Trio and Samsung ATIV Q are taking hybrids to the next level by introducing "Dual Boot". These devices can run both Android and Windows 8 at the same time. - Bay Trail tablets and 2for1 devices are about to explode into the market. Bay Trail offer "twice the performance at the same power level or 4.3x less power at the same performance" compared to projected competitors including the snapdragon 800. Tablets with Intel inside will have a distinct competitive advantage over those that don't. - Intel now has an LTE solution. With the Samsung Galaxy Tab 3 win, Intel also announce that the tablet will come "equipped with Intel's XMM 6262 3G modem solution or Intel's XMM 7160 4G LTE solution". "Intel's XMM 7160 is one of the world's smallest and lowest-power multimode-multiband LTE solutions". With this news, it meansIntel will be able to equip all their future phones/tablets/hybrids/ultrabooks with LTE capability.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372401388258</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 02:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372401915260-11</Id><Title>15 milliseconds ahead of the official release time for the data: Intel is way too fast now?? lol</Title><Msg>The SEC is investigating the relationship between the news organization Thomson Reuters (Toronto Stock Exchange: TRI-CA) and the Institute for Supply Management, CNBC has learned. The two entities join forces to publish market-moving manufacturing data that is generated by ISM and published to high-speed data clients by Thomson Reuters. CNBC reported earlier this month that ISM's manufacturing data was inadvertently sent out early by Thomson Reuters on June 3rd to its high-speed clients, many of whom immediately traded on the information. There was a sharp market reaction to that burst of trading, which prompted downward moves in the SPY ETF, which serves as an investing tool for traders to bet on the overall direction of the market. That downward surge came 15 milliseconds ahead of the official release time for the data. In an era of super-fast computer trading, 15 milliseconds is more than enough time to profit from early knowledge of market moving information.</Msg><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1372401915260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 02:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372408997210-12</Id><Title>Only 3 reasons to sell INTC lower revenue, lower earnings, lower margins not to bad, OH sorry 4 good old boy system in place WOW thats bad</Title><Msg>Only 3 reasons to sell INTC lower revenue, lower earnings, lower margins not to bad, OH sorry 4 good old boy system in place WOW thats bad</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372408997210</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 04:43:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372416308592-13</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>Stocks have had three consecutive sessions of nice gains. However, the technical pictures of the major indexes still aren't pretty. Both the DJIA and the S&amp;P 500 were capped below their 50-day moving average at the close yesterday. Volume has been contracting on the upside. The S&amp;P 500 would need to break above the 1650 area to suggest a possible end to the down-leg started on May 22. Todays quarter-end adjustment is likely to bring big volume. Beyond that, expect trading to slow and stocks to go sideways into the holiday and the June jobs report.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372416308592</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 06:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372417574160-14</Id><Title>Two dishonest derivative players!</Title><Msg>Look at the tell signs on both the NASDAQ/NYSE. What is happening is stagnation in the major indices. This happens when the large derivative players are shifting their positions. They are now moving money and are going to bet against both markets. In the past this is when large corrections take place (over 10 percent). The large derivative players are the ones that run the indices. For example look at Warren Buffet; he is a heavy derivative player that has, over the last five years, substantially decreased his position in stocks and gone the derivative route. Smart, rich player. Derivative are an easy way to hide money.......so large losses can be covered up. The SEC does not understand this and they cannot track this. The result is no regulation. It will only take one major, dishonest derivative player to send our financial systems into ruin.</Msg><Username>geraldomcginty</Username><Timestamp>1372417574160</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 07:06:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372417595819-15</Id><Topic><Title>Two dishonest derivative players!</Title><Username>geraldomcginty</Username><Timestamp>1372417574160</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 07:06:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, there are!</Msg><Username>geraldomcginty</Username><Timestamp>1372417595819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 07:06:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372418422843-16</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel Will Beat Earnings Estimates</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371221336807</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:48:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is looking good, agree. But as a career Intel guy who has worked closely with the other half of the "Donner party" from Redmond,... I would not put too much faith in MSFT to be the catalyst. After so many years of Intel needing Microsoft more that Microsoft needing Intel I believe the shoe is on the other foot and we have seen some of the desperate acts for survival sake (Windows RT) that Ballmer has orchestrated. The one thing that is very clear about this firm is that:.... "At Microsoft quality is JOB 1.1"</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1372418422843</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 07:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372421320697-17</Id><Topic><Title>Only 3 reasons to sell INTC lower revenue, lower earnings, lower margins not to bad, OH sorry 4 good old boy system in place WOW thats bad</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372408997210</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 04:43:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>coinmaker has another up day to watch. poor ole coin</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1372421320697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 08:08:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372421339540-18</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel Will Beat Earnings Estimates</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371221336807</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:48:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds about right. INTC's dominance on cutting edge transistor technology has been good for everyone except its competitors.</Msg><Username>investor_graham</Username><Timestamp>1372421339540</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 08:08:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372425974998-19</Id><Title>INTEL troubles are far bigger than u folks willing to accept it: STOCK is a outright sell</Title><Msg>Trading range $25.5---$19.50 (2013) 2014 new lows coming up</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1372425974998</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372426129655-20</Id><Topic><Title>Two dishonest derivative players!</Title><Username>geraldomcginty</Username><Timestamp>1372417574160</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 07:06:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This seems to be a copy/paste of the last 5 identical threads you have started in the last 2 weeks. I would like some more detail to give this the weight you think it deserves. You say "look at the tell tale signs" .... what signs? You say "stagnation in the major indices" .... by what metric? You say this happens "when large derivative players are shifting their positions" ... how do you measure that? How can you tell they are "moving their money" so I can look for a cause and effect relationship you suggest? Warren Buffet plays derivatives through his insurance businesses but those are either reinsured or hedged. The credit default swaps clearinghouse does not show any unusual activity. What specifically are you looking at that makes you so fearful. Where, for example, do you think that Buffett is unhedged? I would like to do some DD on what you are saying but it makes no sense.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372426129655</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372426151152-21</Id><Title>ASRAF EASSA:Seeking Alpha Intel Pumper..................LOL</Title><Msg>Brings very creative pump spins for INTEL lol</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1372426151152</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:29:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372426160547-22</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL troubles are far bigger than u folks willing to accept it: STOCK is a outright sell</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1372425974998</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:26:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then again, I said Netflix was a sell at 80 on up to 200+, so what on earth do I know? I hope no little old ladies shorted Netflix at 82, like I did. Ouch!</Msg><Username>singhlion2011</Username><Timestamp>1372426160547</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372426350952-23</Id><Title>Morgan Stanley completly trashed PC sales this morning</Title><Msg>Lets face it. Windows 8 is garbage &amp; is causing people not to upgrade. There is no way Intel can meet 2nd half rosy forecasts. I'm tempted to buy Intel Puts for the 1st time ever.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1372426350952</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:32:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372426476216-24</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL troubles are far bigger than u folks willing to accept it: STOCK is a outright sell</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1372425974998</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:26:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sasrikal paraji, intel is way under valued. Sardar if you have patience and have a 2 year horizon, load up on intel anything below 24 and go hybernate for 2 years. Intel will tear every chip maker apart within this 2 year time frame. Past 2years nobody i mean none, zilch, semi chip makers will be able to compete or even come close to intel. Intel will dominate the mobile, tablet and smart phone business. QCOM NVDA AMD TSMC these will be the names that you will tell your kids " there was once upon a time when there were chip makers by the name Qualcom but they dont exist anymore" trust me brother. Intel will probably be trading in the 80-90 bucks a share by the year 2015-16. Goodluck and have a nice day.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372426476216</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:34:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372426496124-25</Id><Topic><Title>Only 3 reasons to sell INTC lower revenue, lower earnings, lower margins not to bad, OH sorry 4 good old boy system in place WOW thats bad</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372408997210</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 04:43:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Accenture missed which is affecting IBM. IBM takes down the DJI because of its price weighting. Expect a weak market on last day of quarter and VERY full day of coinspam. Multiple thread spam..</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372426496124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:34:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372426551668-26</Id><Topic><Title>Morgan Stanley completly trashed PC sales this morning</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1372426350952</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:32:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>go ahead and buy puts and throw yr money away. goodluck</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372426551668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:35:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372426919574-27</Id><Title>check out these picks</Title><Msg>I’ve grown and improved by a trader simply by following their picks. All you have to do is Text the word Alerts without quotes to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT and follow their picks. Easy money. Text the word Alerts without quotes to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT</Msg><Username>mccallcarlos117</Username><Timestamp>1372426919574</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:41:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372427030971-28</Id><Title>Markets Will End Green Today</Title><Msg>Markets will recover as the day progresses and the window dressing continues and the options trade. Profit taking hit when we ran into resistance but it will smoothen out and the day will end green. Intel will recover as well and close even.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372427030971</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:43:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372427583858-29</Id><Title>LOL - IHS REPORT TALKED ABOUT Q1 SHIPMENT! WE ARE IN Q2 FOLKS!</Title><Msg>Can't believe retail investors falling for this again</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372427583858</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:53:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372427621994-30</Id><Topic><Title>LOL - IHS REPORT TALKED ABOUT Q1 SHIPMENT! WE ARE IN Q2 FOLKS!</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372427583858</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:53:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IHS REPORT IS REAR VIEW ....HASWELL SHIPPING NOW!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372427621994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:53:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372427687487-31</Id><Title>ONLY FOOLS SELL/SHORT INTC NOW...WITH HASWELL/SILVERMONT INTRO</Title><Msg>AND BIG REFRESH CYCLE COMING!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372427687487</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372427737364-32</Id><Topic><Title>ONLY FOOLS SELL/SHORT INTC NOW...WITH HASWELL/SILVERMONT INTRO</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372427687487</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Institution investors stealing from retail investors again</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372427737364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:55:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372427859170-33</Id><Title>Intel Down 25 Cents, ARM Down 75 Cents</Title><Msg>Looks like things are finally getting back to normal. I didn't think ARM could get propped up for very long...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372427859170</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372428663747-34</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Down 25 Cents, ARM Down 75 Cents</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372427859170</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:57:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so much for the "manipulated" rally off the lows that stopped pretty much right where they needed to, the spy 500 50day. One bright spot, gold miners</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372428663747</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:11:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372428930475-35</Id><Title>OMG, my idjut clone is still here pumping this kkkrap?</Title><Msg>I see Wallis is still manning the con, pimping away. Wow, this is like time froze.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1372428930475</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372428994041-36</Id><Topic><Title>The Bull Case for Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372399194296</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>still underperforming the markets despite the non stop pumping, and once again all gains from holding over 3 years since 24 in 2010 have disappeared.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372428994041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372429333606-37</Id><Topic><Title>The Bull Case for Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372399194296</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe, but the joke is squarley on you. You spend your day chasing your tail/him around the internet and will go to your deathbed having changed nothing. Crazy stuff.</Msg><Username>wdblawboob</Username><Timestamp>1372429333606</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:22:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372429344263-38</Id><Title>Here Comes Earnings Season</Title><Msg>Intel shorts: No where to run, no place to hide. The continuous misjudgments are coming home to roost...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372429344263</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:22:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372429536514-39</Id><Title>Shorts scream, "I told you so!" Longs cry, "Buy on the dips!" Neither matter today...</Title><Msg>... until the last two hours. Then it's two and half weeks of waiting until earnings. Will the bears pull their heads out of the... "sand?" Will analysts start counting screens and not boxes? Will analysts be able to finally reconcile the end of the ARM ecosystem? Is the ability to only boot to Android better than dual boot? It's a tough choice for OEMs. These questions and more will be answered on July 17th, after market close.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372429536514</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:25:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372429556279-40</Id><Topic><Title>The Bull Case for Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372399194296</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To the shills, a day without stalking is like a day without sunshine. They must be really feeling their age because not a day goes by without them saying: "yadda, yadda, yadda something about the past..." I guess that's because their future looks so dim...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372429556279</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:25:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372430083345-41</Id><Title>Time Warner Cable to stream live TV to its customers</Title><Msg>TWC announces it will deliver up to 300 channels of live TV to its customers having Xbox. Microsoft chose to partner with cable companies instead of competing directly against them. This was always a better strategy.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372430083345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372430261842-42</Id><Topic><Title>Time Warner Cable to stream live TV to its customers</Title><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372430083345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh cool...that means more server chips will be needed.......Intel's highest margin chips.</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372430261842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:37:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372430328937-43</Id><Topic><Title>Time Warner Cable to stream live TV to its customers</Title><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372430083345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remind me which cable company you work for...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372430328937</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:38:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372430445654-44</Id><Title>An Impressive Fudd Fade Seems to be in Process</Title><Msg>Short disappointment is palpable...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372430445654</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:40:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372430799790-45</Id><Topic><Title>An Impressive Fudd Fade Seems to be in Process</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372430445654</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wait until you see volume over 60 million today and frenzied buying in the last two hours. I think end of quarter was the last hurdle for the breakout. take a nice 15% profit, then re-buy in volume.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372430799790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372431269236-46</Id><Topic><Title>Time Warner Cable to stream live TV to its customers</Title><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372430083345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Comcast already does it so who cares?? Intel will hurt both soon.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1372431269236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:54:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372431902095-47</Id><Topic><Title>Markets Will End Green Today</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372427030971</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:43:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congrats on the call for the turn around, not so sure about the end of the day. silver miners continue their rally off deeply oversold</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372431902095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:05:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372432963882-48</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts scream, "I told you so!" Longs cry, "Buy on the dips!" Neither matter today...</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372429536514</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:25:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thie second quarter earnings earnings report for INTC will not reflect the full effect of the new Intel products-Quarter three should more accurately reflect trends. If Intel beats earnings targets for the second quarter-great. If earnings are flat or slightly below I wouldn't be too disappointed.</Msg><Username>kip_castle</Username><Timestamp>1372432963882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:22:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372433628080-49</Id><Title>Repuke party is betraying it's base. The house will pass some kind of immigration bill kissing rump for Hispanic vote.</Title><Msg>Being a LIB--I find it funny. They are dammed if they do and Dammed if they don't. #$%$ off the base or #$%$ off the Hispanic vote is alll that is on the table. I predict a lot of name calling and a complete meltdown in the House Republican caucas. KKK religious nutjobs run the base and they want their country back don't you know.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372433628080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372433699191-50</Id><Title>For once, INTC is out performing the COMP</Title><Msg>Of course, one penny down for INTC from here will mean it lags once again. LOL</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372433699191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:34:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372434021957-51</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Seen Gaining Mobile Market Share With New Chips</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1372360370844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 15:12:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOD STUFF</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372434021957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372434045281-52</Id><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Msg>It has to go on the very high end or lose massive market share on phone sales. Once Apple goes, Samsung and others follow making Intel the top maker of phone CPUs.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372434201130-53</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL looking real good!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372401388258</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 02:36:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AGREE</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372434201130</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:43:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372434272519-54</Id><Topic><Title>Here Comes Earnings Season</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372429344263</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:22:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GUIDANCE FOR Q3 AND Q4 WILL BE STRONG</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372434272519</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372434315708-55</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IPAD WITH BAY TRAIL VERY POSSIBLE TOO</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372434315708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372434669442-56</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have Tim Cook. So they do have a choice. Do something essential or do something really stupid. I don't know what Cook will do.</Msg><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372434669442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372435339778-57</Id><Title>Investors Will Become Wealthy This Summer with This Stock!</Title><Msg>Nothing is hotter on Wall Street today than Big Data. Not only are Tableau (DATA) and Splunk (SPLK) currently up 82% and 176% from their IPOs already, both they're both trading at incredible multiples of 22X sales, despite not yet being profitable. Venture capital funds are pouring into Big Data start-ups on a daily basis - with Accel (who funded Facebook) launching their second $100mm Big Data Fund last week! You won't believe this but there is one undiscovered public Big Data Gem that is already extremely profitable and cash flow positive, and paying a big dividend, yet it's currently being valued with an enterprise value of 0.69X revenues and 6X cash flow! It has a huge cash position, no debt, and pays a 6.3% cash dividend yield! Research Concurrent (CCUR) immediately, it is perhaps the most experienced Big Data stock on Wall Street - with their Big Data clients including Time Warner Cable (TWC), Charter, Cox, Rogers, and Bright House. CCUR is allowing pay-TV operators to use Big Data to launch ad campaigns that follow users from TV to the web, while stopping users from migrating to Netflix. TWC (America's 2nd largest cable TV operator) has been using CCUR's Big Data Analytics solutions to determine the course of both their marketing efforts and network infrastructure! CCUR's EPS last quarter was up 175% year-over-year, and CCUR has successfully increased revenues, gross profits, operating income, and net income - every single quarter-after-quarter for 12 straight months! CCUR recently signed Virgin Media, the leading UK cable TV operator, as its brand new client - and doubled its cash dividend size! A business valuation of just 2X sales will only be a small fraction of the multiples DATA and SPLK are trading at, yet it'll value CCUR at $17 per share, up 125% from yesterday's close of $7.57!</Msg><Username>jowslir632</Username><Timestamp>1372435339778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:02:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372436517071-58</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts scream, "I told you so!" Longs cry, "Buy on the dips!" Neither matter today...</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372429536514</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:25:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm hoping for an attitude adjustment from the Q2 earnings. I want to see a modest beat, obviously bigger is better, a full pipeline, and some more design wins. I don't expect any new, big announcements like Apple, but a couple more tablets from Samsung, ASUS, and Lenovo would be nice. Raised guidance would be nice so the shorts start covering. We have been range bound for over a decade, so recognition that a fundamental shift in computing is underway would also be nice. The traditional PC, laptop, and server market has transformed into: PC, server, micro-server, photonic server, NUC, tablet, phablet, laptop (ultabook), all-in-one, and smart phone. Did I leave anything out?</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372436517071</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:21:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372436764955-59</Id><Topic><Title>An Impressive Fudd Fade Seems to be in Process</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372430445654</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the end of day volume will simply be due to russell rebalancing.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372436764955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:26:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372437520591-60</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even to this day Apple feels t he sum of the whole is greater than the parts. I think that they don't get that processors are all that important, and will put off making big decisions as long as possible.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372437520591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372437558798-61</Id><Title>Multicore</Title><Msg>will win from simplicity point of view that openCL .... INTC stands to gain if they do it right......</Msg><Username>swamb</Username><Timestamp>1372437558798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:39:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372438026275-62</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Down 25 Cents, ARM Down 75 Cents</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372427859170</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:57:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you really are sick</Msg><Username>m00nsh1ner</Username><Timestamp>1372438026275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:47:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372438290833-63</Id><Topic><Title>An Impressive Fudd Fade Seems to be in Process</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372430445654</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 50 day moving average, currently 24.15, is what is currently bounding this stock at the moment but that is a rising average and could top out around 24.5 soon. stockchartsdotcom/c-sc/sc?s=intc&amp;p=D&amp;yr=1&amp;mn=0&amp;dy=0&amp;i=t71013656169&amp;r=1372075747439</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372438290833</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372438767152-64</Id><Title>dont miss this, Alerts on stocks that run!!</Title><Msg>I’ve grown and improved by a trader simply by following their picks. All you have to do is Text the word Alert without quotes to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT and follow their picks. Easy money. Text the word Alert without quotes to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT</Msg><Username>mevan851</Username><Timestamp>1372438767152</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:59:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372438977737-65</Id><Title>get ready for the best stock alerts!</Title><Msg>If you’re trying to start out trading I highly suggest signing up for their free service. Text the word Alerts without quotes to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT</Msg><Username>alex.rivas4142</Username><Timestamp>1372438977737</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:02:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372439401272-66</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Seen Gaining Mobile Market Share With New Chips</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1372360370844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 15:12:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When IBD talks you'd better listen.</Msg><Username>r.idonius</Username><Timestamp>1372439401272</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:10:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372439835776-67</Id><Topic><Title>Here Comes Earnings Season</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372429344263</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:22:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is that a good thing (unless you are a stock pumper) ? Negative earnings pre-annoucements outpaced positive pre-annoucements 7 to 1, per CNBC. Can't wait to see you either ignore that or spin it into a pump.</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1372439835776</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:17:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372440060489-68</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mmm, wouldn't agree with you there. Apple's own in-house processors are actually very good.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1372440060489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:21:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372440288303-69</Id><Title>INTC &amp; BYOC Should Both Be Heading Higher</Title><Msg>I bought 3 million shares of BYOC on sheer speculation (a very low priced penny stock). &amp; Intel is a very important "core stock" to own, in my opinion.</Msg><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1372440288303</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:24:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372440599628-70</Id><Title>Intel Technology Chief Rattner quits (Why didn't Wallisweaver report this?)</Title><Msg>hmmmm</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1372440599628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:29:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372440865978-71</Id><Title>Good old CNBC PUMP so Wall Street can DUMP</Title><Msg>Good old CNBC PUMP so Wall Street can DUMP</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372440865978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:34:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372441056297-72</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>20nm risk lots have already hit the street. I don't have 20nm benchmark numbers but I can tell you silicon is correlating which means it is meeting expectations based on simulations. We will see FinFET risk lots next year but you are right, we will not see 14nm FinFETs in mobile devices until 2015. Intel will probably be first into products but the fabless guys will be close behind and in much higher volumes. The real challenge I see for 14nm is the glut of capacity. If everybody yields there is going to be a 2X+ capacity overage. That will be good for Samsung since they are used to dumping (DRAM). TSMC will be okay with lower margins but the rest of the foundries will struggle. Intel I'm not sure about. They are a high margin company. Will they be happy in a low margin ultra competitive mobile SoC business?</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372441056297</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:37:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372441260823-73</Id><Topic><Title>Good old CNBC PUMP so Wall Street can DUMP</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372440865978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:34:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW are you seeing what Wall Street is doing to BBRY down 26%</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372441260823</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:41:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372441440055-74</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not about the processor, it's about the user experience. Most people don't even know what is inside their phones. QCOM ran a Snapdragon commercial during game 7 of the NBA finals. It was pretty clever but not one person I asked knew if they had one in their phone and most did Apple licenses the ARM architecture like QCOM which is a very "sticky" technology. Is Intel going to become an IP company too? License the Atom instruction set?</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372441440055</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372441968436-75</Id><Title>BUY JKS sell INTC</Title><Msg>ha ha ha ....</Msg><Username>trade_4_somegreen</Username><Timestamp>1372441968436</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:52:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372442267040-76</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you talk about AAPL to use INTC's advanced process to fab AAPL's new SoC, yes it'll be very possible to happen. Be aware, TSMC's 20nm is getting more mature and 14nm FinFET on the way due in 2015. AAPL's own SoC not that bad, for uniqueness of their big volume mobile device, they will try to use their own chip if possible.</Msg><Username>satoricia</Username><Timestamp>1372442267040</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372442406016-77</Id><Topic><Title>Repuke party is betraying it's base. The house will pass some kind of immigration bill kissing rump for Hispanic vote.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372433628080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:33:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You post this stuff every single day.....you need to get out and get a woman, pal. Don't tell me you have one as your anger says you don't.. Don't bother trying to explain, not gonna listen. Just go get a lady, or a man if that's your preference (bet it is).</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1372442406016</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372442517175-78</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has TSMC shipped any 20nm production parts for revenue yet? I haven't seen any announcements yet. What quarter do you think TSMC will generate 2% of their revenues with 20nm production?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372442517175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372442675487-79</Id><Topic><Title>Lagging....</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372344184095</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 10:43:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where's the Lag? Where's 18 in June like you promised? Do your job and come apologize for being a loser. Thx.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1372442675487</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:04:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372442734701-80</Id><Title>Back to $26 soon</Title><Msg>Was just $25.98 a few weeks ago and now down around $24 with no bad news. After earnings will have momentum again!</Msg><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372442734701</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:05:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372443379984-81</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The real challenge I see for 14nm is the glut of capacity." Don't worry Putz - these ARM FinFets are based on 20nm design rules - there won't much of a shrink compared to 20nm planar</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372443379984</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372443941254-82</Id><Topic><Title>The Bull Case for Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372399194296</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being able to dual boot I say is key, each side can partake in the other side's fare. Heck, most folks are dualsystemers---deal with Wintel @ work and school and dable in Android @ other times and places.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372443941254</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:25:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372445079472-83</Id><Topic><Title>The Bull Case for Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372399194296</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 01:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The best bull markets have a simple thesis that everyone can understand and which can be communicated in one or two sentences. We're not at that point yet. The thesis behind Intel is still too eggheady for the average joe. It took me a couple of days just to figure out finfets and trigates were the same thing. Half-node, gate first, gate last --- oh boy, whenever I see a bull argument loaded down with this stuff, I know the train has barely left the station. Ashraf had a series of articles about gross margins that was way too MENSA. Not his fault, he had to defend himself against attack and everything tumbled into the deep end of the pool. But look at the mobile bull market which has helped ARM's stock price over the past few years. Major thesis: "The PC is dead" "Mobile is the future." "Intel can't produce power efficient chips" --- very, very simple slogans which are backed by cherrypicked data. Bull markets are deductive. You have an overarching thesis or paradigm that controls what information gets through. On the other hand, when a stock is fighting out of a hole or bear market, it is entirely an inductive process of slowly building up datapoints which will complete a picture that makes sense. That's where we are with Intel. Early, early stages. The sloganeering phase has not yet started, but it will. Then we will be off to the races. When I buy a stock, I'm not interested in selling it at a rational price but at an IRRATIONALLY HIGH price.</Msg><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1372445079472</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:44:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372445757324-84</Id><Title>Intel Sees Faster, More Flexible Future</Title><Msg>Yahoo won't let me post this...but VERY interesting article</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372445757324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:55:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372445863024-85</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Sees Faster, More Flexible Future</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372445757324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:55:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wbmw's commentary from ihub: Quote: -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- He disclosed that Intel has been working to offer customers blocks of specialized circuitry, along with its processors, so they can mix and match different combinations to create customizeable chips for their products. -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- One of the more interesting pieces was left out of your bold text. This implies that Intel would be willing to offer customers use of their manufacturing to build products with Intel IP, as well as "specialized circuitry" - i.e. 3rd party IP. So if Samsung or Apple wants to build a processor with Airmont core, plus their own internal media or imaging block, built on an Intel 14nm process - it might be possible. That would be HUGE towards winning some of these big customers, IMO. And it would mean that Apple or Samsung gets to keep their huge base of designers to keep their business advantage and unique value add, while still leveraging the best of Intel's assets, and Intel gets to charge a premium for their process PLUS their IP. Again - a potential HUGE business move.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372445863024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:57:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372445935154-86</Id><Title>Substantial Improvement for INTC. **MUST SEE**</Title><Msg>Has any individual taken a look at the articles being presented? Incredible information that will help any investor or trader. Link:- 7DOTly/pQz (Remove DOT &amp; use .)</Msg><Username>rbard46</Username><Timestamp>1372445935154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:58:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372446055763-87</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Improvement for INTC. **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>rbard46</Username><Timestamp>1372445935154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:58:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how about bounce trade?</Msg><Username>rbard46</Username><Timestamp>1372446055763</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:00:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372446084872-88</Id><Title>IBM has done nothing since Warren Buffett bought it</Title><Msg>Zilch.</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372446084872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:01:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372446497394-89</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"20nm risk lots have already hit the street. I don't have 20nm benchmark numbers but I can tell you silicon is correlating which means it is meeting expectations based on simulations." [28nm is still not fully ramped and here you are making mindless projections about 20nm based on "risk lots". Instead of "risk lots", it should be "lots of risk". Because that's what it is for foundry customers. It's a train wreck waiting to happen. Congestion at 20nm is going to destroy ARM when it arrives in that it will arrive at something substantially below volume production and without any indication when it will be available in volume. Just like 28nm except 20nm is much more complex and difficult. For Qualcomm, AMD, Nvidia and Apple is going to be their worst nightmare because there simply won't be enough to go around. As far as ARM FinFET goes, don't waste our time - it's too far in the future with too many unknowns to even think about yet.] [Still ARM should be perfectly okay because no one really knows that ARM's roadmap is a disaster. Oh, wait - ARM is down 70 cents today and $14.38 since its recent 52-week high. I guess the word is getting out...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372446497394</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:08:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372446526385-90</Id><Title>What is up with this stock?</Title><Msg>It is all over the place. It starts at -1% then rallies up to +1.3% and then crashes all the way back down. Its like every rally is sold into heavily. I guess no one wants to hold this stock anymore?</Msg><Username>ultravis66</Username><Timestamp>1372446526385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:08:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372446866151-91</Id><Topic><Title>What is up with this stock?</Title><Username>ultravis66</Username><Timestamp>1372446526385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very odd almost laughable. Owell as its worth the wait for everybody to wake up and realize where this is going. Up!!! This world is going more and more to technology and anybody that thinks Intel isnt going to keep up isnt thinking to straight</Msg><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372446866151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:14:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372447163364-92</Id><Topic><Title>What is up with this stock?</Title><Username>ultravis66</Username><Timestamp>1372446526385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>correction:</Msg><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372447163364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:19:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372447226810-93</Id><Topic><Title>What is up with this stock?</Title><Username>ultravis66</Username><Timestamp>1372446526385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try trading a 3x ETF, even more fun.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372447226810</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:20:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372447227561-94</Id><Topic><Title>What is up with this stock?</Title><Username>ultravis66</Username><Timestamp>1372446526385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>correction: [anybody that thinks Intel isnt going to **lead** isnt thinking to straight]</Msg><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372447227561</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:20:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372447261340-95</Id><Topic><Title>What is up with this stock?</Title><Username>ultravis66</Username><Timestamp>1372446526385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, just look at ARM to gauge how things are really being looked at. ARM down 70 cents today. The tipping point has been reached. More and more days of Intel up and ARM down. Expect this trend to continue...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372447261340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:21:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372447328711-96</Id><Topic><Title>What is up with this stock?</Title><Username>ultravis66</Username><Timestamp>1372446526385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo: GFYS</Msg><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372447328711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372447387477-97</Id><Topic><Title>What is up with this stock?</Title><Username>ultravis66</Username><Timestamp>1372446526385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better wording. Thanks! Anybody thinks that they are just going to sit back and fall back are blind</Msg><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372447387477</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372447552925-98</Id><Topic><Title>What is up with this stock?</Title><Username>ultravis66</Username><Timestamp>1372446526385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sometimes they show bullriding on ESPN. It doesn't look pleasant. Up and down and spinning to the left and then spinning to the right. The bull is trying his damndest to throw the rider and most of the time they succeed. Some CEOs try to tame the bull so that it's easier to ride. Jack Welch was famous for this at GE. He would hide some profits from exceedingly good quarters, and then sprinkle it on future quarters whenever needed. It's called "managed earnings" and is generally frowned upon.</Msg><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1372447552925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372448116084-99</Id><Title>buy NDLS</Title><Msg>easy double</Msg><Username>drhollars</Username><Timestamp>1372448116084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:35:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372448844798-100</Id><Title>Where oh where is coinmaker and his buddies</Title><Msg>lol not so bad being long on this great company huh?</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1372448844798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372450204335-101</Id><Title>Intel TV Service</Title><Msg>Looks like Krzanich is not fully convinced the Intel TV service is viable. SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Intel Corp's top executives said on Friday the microprocessor company would speed up development and roll-out of its Atom chips for mobile devices, as the computing world moves away from the traditional personal computer. The company is also being "cautious" on its Intel television service, as it continues to look at the business model, according to the company's new Chief Executive Officer Brian Krzanich.</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1372450204335</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:10:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372450908371-102</Id><Topic><Title>Markets Will End Green Today</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372427030971</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:43:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, not so much, just the NASDQ, and that barely, what with the SQQQ popping from 28.20 to 28.80 in the last twenty minutes. May 1 to June 30 and the indexes are essentially flat with a lot of volatility in the interim.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372450908371</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372450972285-103</Id><Topic><Title>Intel TV Service</Title><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1372450204335</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:10:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A couple of months ago, there was talk/rumors of Viacom (includes CBS/Paramount/Showtime) and TimeWarner (includes HBO) wanting to work with Intel Media. When you have 2 of the top 4 media conglomerates on Intel's side, I saw potential with Intel Media. Engadget (March 2013): "According to Bloomberg, Intel is getting close to offering such a service and is reportedly closing in on deals with Time Warner, Viacom and NBC that would allow them to offer both live and on-demand content over the internet. Sources are reporting that the broad terms of the deal have been agreed to, and its only a few fine details and some financial terms that need to be finalized. Intel is also allegedly in talks with Disney, CBS and News Corp. Though, those negotiations are in the preliminary stages. If Intel can successfully land deals for CNN, Comedy Central, MTV and other properties owned by its supposed new partners then its TV experiment could stand a legitimate chance at success." Now I hear about hostility from cable operators. Time Warner seems to be reasserting its ability to go it alone after spectacular successes (Superman and Game of Thrones' Red Wedding Episode which is the top watercooler event of the world of TV.) I don't know anymore if Intel Media is a good idea. It needs to have the content companies on its side for this to work. No way can Intel brute force its way to success in this sector.</Msg><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1372450972285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:22:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372451085305-104</Id><Title>WHY 9 MILLION PLUS SHARES CHANGING HANDS AFTER HOURS?</Title><Msg>ANY THOUGHTS?</Msg><Username>lostsheep797</Username><Timestamp>1372451085305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:24:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372451300228-105</Id><Topic><Title>WHY 9 MILLION PLUS SHARES CHANGING HANDS AFTER HOURS?</Title><Username>lostsheep797</Username><Timestamp>1372451085305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:24:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CORRECTION 18 MILLION SHARES?</Msg><Username>lostsheep797</Username><Timestamp>1372451300228</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:28:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372451632890-106</Id><Title>MAKE THAT 26 MILLION SHARES</Title><Msg>CHANGED HANDS AFTER HOURS?</Msg><Username>lostsheep797</Username><Timestamp>1372451632890</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:33:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372452089742-107</Id><Title>Today's differential: 84 Cents</Title><Msg>Intel ends the day up by 18 cents and ARM ends down 66 cents for a differential of 84 cents as in spite of this being the end of the month and the end of the quarter things appear to be returning to normal after Wall Street's silliness regarding Bernanke's comments.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372452089742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372452246094-108</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Technology Chief Rattner quits (Why didn't Wallisweaver report this?)</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1372440599628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:29:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you seen your doctor yet? The next thing ya'know there will be guns and ammo, screams and crying, blood and mayhem... go before it's too late.</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1372452246094</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372453745163-109</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Technology Chief Rattner quits (Why didn't Wallisweaver report this?)</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1372440599628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:29:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel CTO Justin Rattner steps down after hitting age limit CHIPMAKER Intel is looking for another CTO after Justin Rattner has been forced to stand down after reaching age 65. Intel's company policy is that no employee over the age of 65 can hold a corporate officer position. That means the company has to replace its CTO, with Rattner taking personal leave and the firm finding another position for him when he returns. [ghost_Fudd couldn't figure this out for himself? No surprise...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372453745163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 17:09:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372456311984-110</Id><Topic><Title>WHY 9 MILLION PLUS SHARES CHANGING HANDS AFTER HOURS?</Title><Username>lostsheep797</Username><Timestamp>1372451085305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:24:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now 37+ million shares. IMO: This being eom, I think shorts are starting serious covering. Keep in mind, the 3 day settlement and 2week lag in reporting (by nasdeq) will keep these covered shares 'hidden' until after earnings.</Msg><Username>livingsez</Username><Timestamp>1372456311984</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 17:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372457135474-111</Id><Topic><Title>WHY 9 MILLION PLUS SHARES CHANGING HANDS AFTER HOURS?</Title><Username>lostsheep797</Username><Timestamp>1372451085305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:24:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all it is is reblancing of the Russell indexes, nothing more</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372457135474</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 18:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372457363832-112</Id><Topic><Title>Today's differential: 84 Cents</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372452089742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:41:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, let's forget the fact that the dow ended down 100 points, the SPY failed to break through to the upside at resistance and closed down, but then, of course, you're probably 100 percent invested in INTC and pumping as usual</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372457363832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 18:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372457502887-113</Id><Title>Analyst bad mouthed this pig and the stock went up. Mr Weaver pumped</Title><Msg>a lot more today for sure. Yes we need the Weaver to counter the bad mouthing Wall St Analysts. Usually the Analysts win, but today was Mr Weaver day.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372457502887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 18:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372459480912-114</Id><Title>B.K. is right</Title><Msg>On the subject of Intel Media: “We’re being cautious. We’re experts in silicon, we’re experts in mobility, in driving Moore’s law,” Krzanich said. “But we are not experts in the content industry and we’re being careful.” I like a CEO who knows what the core of the company is and won't stray from it unless an outrageously fortuitous opportunity arises. If the major media conglomerates come to Intel and say, "Please help us distribute our content so that we can fend off the threat of Netflix and Amazon Prime" and are willing to make it a profitable venture, then pursue it by all means. However, it looks like that is no longer the case (or never was the case) and the Intel Media Project will be like pulling teeth trying to get content. It's looking like a loser. B.K. is looking good with the above quote. It's very bullish for Intel to have a CEO who focuses the company on what they are really good at.</Msg><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1372459480912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 18:44:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372460258199-115</Id><Topic><Title>Where oh where is coinmaker and his buddies</Title><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1372448844798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He jumped over to US Steel to ruin that board posting like a maniac a bunch of nonsense like usual. Would be nice to see something come from him that wasn't the same thing over and over. Glad to have the break though for now!</Msg><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372460258199</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 18:57:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372460673011-116</Id><Topic><Title>WHY 9 MILLION PLUS SHARES CHANGING HANDS AFTER HOURS?</Title><Username>lostsheep797</Username><Timestamp>1372451085305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:24:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I forgot about that. It is on my calendar for 6/28 from last year. It looks like from the market action today that the shares went INTO the Russell as if Intel is a larger % than last year. Doesn't make a lot of sense.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372460673011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:04:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372462133003-117</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FYI 28nm was 24% of TSMC revenue last quarter. If that is not a fully ramped node maybe you can provide a better definition?</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372462133003</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372462241608-118</Id><Topic><Title>B.K. is right</Title><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1372459480912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 18:44:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have translated his comment of saying he is being careful to mean that he is pulling out of the project. This is a non-supportable reach. He would be an idiot not to be careful. And to say that Intel went into this thinking it would be easy to get content and now wants to run in the other direction having found out otherwise is ridiculous. Intel knew it would be difficult. Is it more difficult than kicking ARM to the curb? Doubtful. So, Intel doesn't mind difficult. Nor do they mind small incremental progress as long as they consistently move ahead with their game plan. To say that they will now just cut and run is to misjudge the culture. The project is just getting started. It is not looking like a loser. It's not looking like anything but a start-up. If you think monumental start-up projects all get instant traction or die then you are naive about the nature of them. In other words, it is much too early to be drawing conclusions about its success or failure. You and the other critics on the board should give it a rest until more information is available.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372462241608</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372462308796-119</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"FYI 28nm was 24% of TSMC revenue last quarter. If that is not a fully ramped node maybe you can provide a better definition?" [One that meets customer demands. This one doesn't...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372462308796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:31:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372462499482-120</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What quarter do you think TSMC will generate 2% of their revenues with 20nm production?" I stated previously that it will be Q1 2013. TSMC has said Q2 2013. From what I know today I'm still betting on Q1 2013. I have not heard a thing about Samsung 20nm. Samsung 14nm is all the buzz in Silicon Valley.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372462499482</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:34:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372462624444-121</Id><Title>Intel's new CEO focused on mobile chips, cautious on TV</Title><Msg>Good Reuters article. Sounds like some sort of Intel wearable device coming before the end of year: Krzanich, who mentioned he had Google's Glass wearable device in his knapsack, said computing in the next few years would focus more on items for eyes and ears, as well as wristbands and watches. "I think you'll start to see stuff with our silicon toward the end of the year and the beginning of next year," Krzanich said. "We're trying to get our silicon into some of them, create some ourselves, understand the usage and create an ecosystem."</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372462624444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:37:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372462712057-122</Id><Title>Intel Vows to Pick Up Mobile Pace</Title><Msg>Intel's new leaders on Friday vowed to step up the chip maker's long-delayed penetration of mobile devices and other new product categories, starting by giving its inexpensive Atom chip equal billing with its pricier Core line. In another area, the company's new chief executive, Brian Krzanich, sounded a more cautious note about Intel's new plans to sell a set-top box and associated content service to deliver videos over the Internet. "We believe from a technology standpoint we've built a game-changing device," Mr. Krzanich said, in his first meeting with reporters since taking over the CEO post in May. But he acknowledged that the success of the service comes down to licensing attractive programming content, a field where Intel is not an influential or experienced player. "We are trying to evaluate what do we do now, and how do we best utilize this technology--and what is our business model," Mr. Krzanich said. "We are just being cautious." As for Intel's Atom chip line, originally sold for low-priced laptops called netbooks, it has been updated by the company for use in devices like smartphones and tablets. Some manufacturers have adopted Atoms already, but many more companies use rival chip designs based on technology licensed by ARM. The Core line of chips, which is used in personal computers, has long been considered Intel's flagship product line. For one thing, Core models sell for more than $100 while Atoms are closer to the $20 mark. But Renee James, Intel's newly appointed president, told reporters that the company's new strategy is based on putting Atom "on a level playing field" with Core. From the Wall Street Journal</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372462712057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372462813914-123</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Vows to Pick Up Mobile Pace</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372462712057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:38:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Continued: Among other things, that means that Intel will begin using the company's most advanced manufacturing processes sooner to produce the Atom chip, which will help drive down its power consumption, boost its performance and reduce the cost to make it. Up until now, Core chips typically got first access to new Intel manufacturing recipes. Mr. Krzanich gave new details of plans to use the Atom technology and other new building block components to step up the company's new "foundry" business, which makes chips for other companies. He disclosed that Intel has been working to offer customers blocks of specialized circuitry, along with its processors, so they can mix and match different combinations to create customizable chips for their products. While expecting to stick mainly with Intel's longtime-processor technology, Mr. Krzanich said he would not rule out building chips for major foundry customers who prefer ARM technology. "We will consider what it takes to land customers," Ms. James said. From the Wall Street Journal</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372462813914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:40:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372462878142-124</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's new CEO focused on mobile chips, cautious on TV</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372462624444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:37:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>B.K has a slightly different view on foundry business than P.O: "If there was a great customer that we had a great relationship with laptops and other mobile devices, and they said look, we'd really love you to build our ARM-based product, we'd consider it. It depends on how strategic they are," Krzanich said.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372462878142</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:41:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372463256901-125</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"FYI 28nm was 24% of TSMC revenue last quarter. If that is not a fully ramped node maybe you can provide a better definition?" [One that meets customer demands. This one doesn't...] Incorrect. Do not confuse capacity with ramp. TSMC 28nm is yielding 90% right now. TSMC has 90% 28nm market share. You are an accountant, read the quarterly reports and do the math. 28nm ramped faster than previous nodes by a long shot.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372463256901</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372463454446-126</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC's 20nm will happen in late 2014 (maybe). They are still working on 28nm HPM.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372463454446</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:50:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372465015125-127</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"incorrect. Do not confuse capacity with ramp. TSMC 28nm is yielding 90% right now. TSMC has 90% 28nm market share. You are an accountant, read the quarterly reports and do the math. 28nm ramped faster than previous nodes by a long shot." [You are being disingenuous. The goal is obviously meeting customer demand. If you can't the customers tend to want to go someplace else. You can congratulate yourself on the current 28nm yield all you want but the bottom line is that they didn't have capacity when their customers needed it and still don't. And the same thing is going to happen at 20nm, only worse...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372465015125</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 20:16:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372465328032-128</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"TSMC has 90% 28nm market share." [You say this like it's a good thing when it is not. It's a clear sign that the ARM fabless model is totally broken. At 28nm there is really only one choice for ARM shops. One shop with insufficient capacity. It's okay by me. It just provides Intel with many new opportunities to take business away from the ARM ecosystem. This illustrates just one of the 16 reasons why ARM's fabrication is toast...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372465328032</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 20:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372470151718-129</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the last 5 days since the intraday lows Monday, TSM rose over 10 percent, 16.60 to 18.32, outperforming INTC by a factor of three.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372470151718</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 21:42:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372474239947-130</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is the buzz about the SRAM-based chip? Samsung Tapes Out First 14nm FinFET Test Chips. Samsung Reaches 14nm FinFET Process Technology Development Milestone [12/20/2012 08:06 PM] by Anton Shilov "...As part of its 14nm FinFET development process, Samsung, and its ecosystem partners – ARM, Cadence, Mentor and Synopsys – taped out multiple test chips ranging from a full ARM Cortex-A7 processor implementation to a SRAM-based chip capable of operation near threshold voltage levels as well as an array of analog IP."</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1372474239947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 22:50:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372474915195-131</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>April 2013 Our outlook for both foundry and logic segments has not substantively changed either. Investments for 28-nanometer capacity have been strong, and we expect that to continue over the next 1 or 2 quarters prior to decelerating and broadening the number of customers in the second half of the year. The 20-nanometer investment should commence in earnest around that same time, with an estimated 30,000 to 50,000 wafer starts of capacity shipped to our customers by the end of 2013 across the industry. In the logic space, the second half story appears to represent a strengthening of original equipment additions, at least in our served markets, compared to the first half of the year. In this environment, Lam is executing our multiyear growth strategies in etch, deposition, clean and our installed base business.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372474915195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 23:01:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372476885134-132</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>with an estimated 30,000 to 50,000 wafer starts of capacity shipped to our customers by the end of 2013 across the industry. SHIPPED - looks like AMD u / monkey whatever it is is right - mid /end of 2014. Remember this info comes from a key supplier for TSMC - not from semiwiki</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372476885134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 23:34:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372477169022-133</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the last 5 days since the intraday lows Monday, TSM rose over 10 percent, 16.60 to 18.32, outperforming INTC by a factor of three. oxymoron/aqualang look at the 6 months charts</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372477169022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 23:39:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372478380619-134</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well then, one could also look at the 12 month charts. tsm still outperformed INTC year over year. Some have been bashing TSM all week which actually did hit oversold on Monday, rsi 30, and proceeded to bounce quite nicely, thus the note of the last week out performance. res ipsa loquitor</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372478380619</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 23:59:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>