<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-15"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368590823086-1</Id><Topic><Title>marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368588196458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leaks regarding Intel's upcoming Avoton 22nm Atom processor suggest that the company is serious about working to keep Cambridge-based rival ARM out of the microserver market, pointing towards a chip that has more in common with a high-end Xeon than its netbook- and mobile-oriented namesakes. According to an unnamed Intel source speaking to Chinese-language news site MyDrivers, the 22nm Avoton Atom processor - due to launch next year alongside Intel's Haswell chips for desktops and laptops - will include features designed to make it the darling of the burgeoning microserver market. First, the specifications: the first Avoton chips are expected to reach clockspeeds of 2.4GHz with Turbo Boost support to push the speed up to 2.7GHz if two cores are doing most of the work. An on-board DDR3 memory controller will provide dual-channel access to DDR3-1600 RAM, along with on-board controllers for up to four gigabit Ethernet connections, four USB 2.0 ports, two SATA III and four SATA II connections, and PCI Express 2.0 support for sixteen lanes. In other words: it's a true system-on-chip (SoC) design. More important than the clockspeeds and controllers, however, is the claim that Avoton will support out-of-order execution (OoOE,) a feature missing from other Atom chips which can significantly improve performance by making use of spare processor cycles during idle periods. Another serious shift is in the number of physical cores: where current Atom processors limit themselves to two cores, extended to four virtual cores with Hyper Threading, it's claimed that Avoton will pack up to eight physical cores in the highest-performance model. Assuming Intel includes Hyper Threading support, that will provide servers with sixteen logical processing cores per chip - and we're expecting to see plenty of these chips crammed into compact spaces. Despite all these features, and support for Intel's hardware virtualisation extensions and ECC memory, it's claimed that the parts will be available between 5W and 20W TDP. Intel will not comment on the accuracy of the claims, stating only that it doesn't comment on 'industry rumour or speculation,' but with Avoton due for a release towards the second half of next year we shouldn't have long to wait to see if the Atom chip can keep ARM's Cortex-A15 at bay.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368590823086</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 00:07:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368591794586-2</Id><Title>Apple dropped Intel</Title><Msg>Intel too big and bulky to respond to Apple needs. Intel will make that fastest boat anchors.</Msg><Username>stjdavis7</Username><Timestamp>1368591794586</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 00:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368592470213-3</Id><Topic><Title>Apple dropped Intel</Title><Username>stjdavis7</Username><Timestamp>1368591794586</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 00:23:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ON the contrary. Apple may go all Intel. Remember Apple's top engineer for the A chip, Raja Koduri, left recently. This is a DEAD GIVEAWAY youtubeDOTcom/watch?v=nZcRU0Op5P4</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368592470213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 00:34:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368593022924-4</Id><Topic><Title>Apple dropped Intel</Title><Username>stjdavis7</Username><Timestamp>1368591794586</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 00:23:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember, Apple is expected to make a deal with Intel after the Micron purchase of Elpida is completed. An Apple/Intel deal will push INTC over $30 overnight!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368593022924</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 00:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368593535348-5</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will win in foundry wars: Part I</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368572385922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 18:59:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope there is no double ordering. "Please, sir, I want some more." Quite possible - Intel's progress in regards to SoC is remarkable .... 14 Dec 2011 6:27 According to Piper Jaffray analyst Gus Richard, Intel is falling behind in the processor market thanks to their failure to compete in the lucrative mobile device segment. While Intel has continued to concentrate primarily on performance, says Richard, consumer interest has largely shifted to convenience and mobility. As a result, the SoC (System on a Chip) processor has become increasingly important. In a research note this week he wrote (via CNET):</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368593535348</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 00:52:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368594623200-6</Id><Title>market too high</Title><Msg>time to run out sell high buy low lol..............................</Msg><Username>minhtang326</Username><Timestamp>1368594623200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 01:10:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368595285148-7</Id><Title>If this company is so good then why</Title><Msg>this pos trading near its yearly low? while the market is trading at its all time high. don't bet on hadwell. this pos is doomed.</Msg><Username>philip_914</Username><Timestamp>1368595285148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 01:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368596130644-8</Id><Topic><Title>If this company is so good then why</Title><Username>philip_914</Username><Timestamp>1368595285148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 01:21:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>getting nervous shorty? You should be LOL. recommendation for tomorrow: cover early</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368596130644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 01:35:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368596168491-9</Id><Topic><Title>market too high</Title><Username>minhtang326</Username><Timestamp>1368594623200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 01:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shorts are panicking LOL. Wait till tomorrow before you wet your pants shorty</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368596168491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 01:36:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368596374843-10</Id><Title>First Haswell tablets expected by end of summer in time for 'back to school'</Title><Msg>That said, Reller insists that Microsoft's "relationship, and work we're doing with Intel, has never been stronger." In fact, Reller says that Windows 8 tablets built on Intel's new Haswell chip will be out by the end of summer in time for 'back to school." Haswell is all about better battery life and improved graphics performance." from businessinsider</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368596374843</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 01:39:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368596520582-11</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is Toast: 16 Reasons (Part I)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368589252225</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:40:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>from fudzilla: Outgoing Intel CEO Paul Otellini believes that the transition to 450mm wafers could virtually wipe out half of semiconductor companies. Speaking at a tech conference Otellini said transitioning to 450mm will be costly, simply too costly for small fish. “In general, every time there has been a wafer-size change in the industry, only half of [design and production] market players [survived],” said Otellini. Naturally, Otellini is confident about the transition to 450mm and EUV manufacturing, since Intel is leading the way in cutting edge manufacturing processes and it has done so for years. Transitioning to 450mm will result in cheaper chips, something that Intel desperately needs to take on the ARM alliance in smartphone and tablet markets. Of course, Otellini could be going into doomsayer mode just to scare smaller players and their investors.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368596520582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 01:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368596604397-12</Id><Topic><Title>First Haswell tablets expected by end of summer in time for 'back to school'</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368596374843</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 01:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Win8 Haswell tabs will have trouble competing with the iPad, a 4th gen category defining product. If they cant compete with it, they will be relegated to low volume also rans like most of the other tabs in the market. There's very little hope here.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1368596604397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 01:43:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368597707714-13</Id><Topic><Title>First Haswell tablets expected by end of summer in time for 'back to school'</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368596374843</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 01:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're a f&amp;u&amp;cken idiot. Haswell tablets/hybrids will be much more compelling than ipad. First off, Haswell will be able to run both Android and Windows 8 (dual-boot). And unlike RT, Haswell will be able to run legacy Windows software used by millions of current home users and more importantly in the corporate world. The main drawback to Intel's core products thus far have been price and battery life. Haswell will fix this with all day battery life and price point of $499 - $599. Haswell tablets/hybrids will spur a major PC refresh and cannibalize the larger ipad. The North Cape hybrid and Surface Pro running Haswell will sell like crazy!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368597707714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 02:01:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368597994948-14</Id><Topic><Title>First Haswell tablets expected by end of summer in time for 'back to school'</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368596374843</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 01:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, rumors going about that Apple will release a hybrid of their own running Haswell. They ipad/MacBook air hybrid will run ios when used as tablet and MacOS while in laptop mode.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368597994948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 02:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368599635219-15</Id><Title>iPad/MacBookAir Hybrid stories floating around</Title><Msg>ashraf.eassa may have been the first to make the suggestion in one of his articles. Is this the 'exciting new product category' that Tim Cook was talking about?</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368599635219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 02:33:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368602316790-16</Id><Topic><Title>marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368588196458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With respect, do you expect them to say anything else?</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1368602316790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 03:18:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368604044794-17</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tatoo a capital L on your forehead. LOSER</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368604044794</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 03:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368611579127-18</Id><Topic><Title>marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368588196458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FWIW in my decades following the industry Intel tend to be the most understated and matter of fact when it comes to performance estimates. They just have a tendency to tell it like it is because I suppose their engineers allow them that luxury. Looking at the estimates given so far Avoton will be a octo-core micro-server SoC with TDP under 10W, you might get 4-6 A15/A57s on a SoC for that TDP. Apart from floating point (which I have always said ARM licensees should concentrate more on applications as it is a natural RISC strength) Avoton looks like it has beat on performance/power just by cores/power nevermind the individual Avoton core performance which should be very strong at least on integer.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368611579127</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 05:52:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368614262519-19</Id><Topic><Title>marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368588196458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, I have to disagree on that one (I also have decades of experience). I've been 'burned' many times by various vendor (performance) estimates (this is high end stuff, not Atom) so as a general rule I don't believe any performance metrics from any vendor until it's been independently tested, ideally under our own benchmark suite. The performance/watt numbers of these servers isn't just about the SoC, but the entire server (cluster) and associated infrastructure (such as the switch) so we're not going to know what the final numbers are like until we know more about the SoC (and what's included on it) and how the clusters are built. The floating point comments are valid but it's a little more complex than that:) As an example, one of the targets for these microservers is various web work loads. In theory any workload that uses scripting languages (such as perl/php ect) are likely to be float heavy (as under the hood most math is using the double datatype) so you would think that these workloads would favor arm over atom. However, if you look at perl and it's implementation (stack based VM) it spends a huge amount of cycles messing around with the stack which is all integer based. You'll only know which is better if you test under your own workload. My comment to Ashraf was really about using your common sense. Even if Intel knew that Avoton would struggle in any metric (cost, power, performance, io, time to market etc) against, say against Calxeda's Quad A15 they aren't going to tell him.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1368614262519</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 06:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368617864832-20</Id><Topic><Title>marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368588196458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No body is keeping arm out of the micro server market . Arm is write on in this space. They will surprise many people. Including intels avoton 22nm. You will see.</Msg><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1368617864832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 07:37:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368618622854-21</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is Toast: 16 Reasons (Part IV)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368589541134</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:45:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Man you are dead wrong on arm they due have a roadmap they will have finfet and they will beat intel at there own game, you reading to many ashraf articles.the intel crybaby keeps watching arm go higher and higher.ashraf ate the cake shorting arm you will too.</Msg><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1368618622854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 07:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368618802194-22</Id><Title>Have you run out of excuses?</Title><Msg>Why did INTC lag the markets AGAIN yesterday. That is 4 out of the past 10 days. It was ex-div It was @sswell What now?</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368618802194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 07:53:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368619014062-23</Id><Topic><Title>Ashraf got burned listening to Wallisweaver</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1368588955984</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol</Msg><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1368619014062</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 07:56:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368619415570-24</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is Toast: 16 Reasons (Part IV)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368589541134</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:45:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Disagree Henry. The R&amp;D and CapEx required to catch Intel (forget about the 2-3 year lead Intel has for now), will never be spent by merchant market foundries unless they can get their customers to effectively pay for it. So even if the ARM solution providers agree to put up the 10's of billions of dollars (which they won't ), or by some miracle the foundries put up their own cash, once these FinFets theoretically do show up in a production worthy process, they will do so at tremendous cost overhead to their customers. So not only will these components be years late to the party but also not cost competitive with Intel's silicon offerings. Oh, and don't forget that Intel's process roadmap does not end today (with what ARM might achieve 2-3 years from now). Intel will be shipping at 14nm and test running 10nm by then. As Mr. Weaver has pointed out,... It is the beginning of the end for ARM's glory days. Good luck with your investing.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1368619415570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 08:03:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368620593313-25</Id><Topic><Title>Have you run out of excuses?</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368618802194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 07:53:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said Intel woudl see 18 before it saw 22 back when it was 21. Want me to repost it? It pretty much makes you a laughing stock.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1368620593313</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 08:23:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368622714562-26</Id><Topic><Title>Have you run out of excuses?</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368618802194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 07:53:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey dummy, if Intel continues to drop in price, it will hit 22 way before it hits 18, since it's higher than 22 now. Hate to point that obvious fact out.</Msg><Username>angstromatic</Username><Timestamp>1368622714562</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 08:58:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368622812681-27</Id><Topic><Title>SHORTS BEWARE</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368588031579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:20:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here we go. It's shorts get fried day!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368622812681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:00:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368623358754-28</Id><Topic><Title>Have you run out of excuses?</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368618802194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 07:53:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're so dumb that you can't understand that it went to 24 from 21 when he said it was going to 18 from 21.... which makes him terribly wrong.. Now can you understand it, dipstick?</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1368623358754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:09:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368623558175-29</Id><Topic><Title>marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368588196458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they knew that were the case, they would have simply refrained from answering my questions rather than make quite unequivocal statements :)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368623558175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:12:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368623601913-30</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>It was a new leg up for stocks yesterday. It suggests more gains to come, as short sellers buy to give up their positions. There is no telling when this overbought market will have a pullback or correction but any near term downside is likely to be limited. The uptrend will continue until it is broken. For now, the stock market is in a solid uptrend.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368623601913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368623736668-31</Id><Topic><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368623601913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:13:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for telling us nothing at all</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368623736668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:15:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368623850603-32</Id><Topic><Title>marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368588196458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow and you believe what they say ???? what else would they say ? How old are you ? AE you are a great guy, but ya just can not go on what these guys say.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1368623850603</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368624586734-33</Id><Topic><Title>marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368588196458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow you switched to your fembot Troll alias nuff ? how talented LOL...............</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368624586734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:29:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368624596143-34</Id><Title>RECOMMENDATION TO SHORTS: COVER EARLY</Title><Msg>seems like a bad-to-worse-to-terrible kinda day for shorties</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368624596143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:29:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368624801935-35</Id><Title>Walrus Beaver is palpably disappointed in giving up much of his gains in this huge market run.</Title><Msg>That there was some pitiful action the last few days.....Wally does not know what to do. Time to call SEC, Obama, Momma, someone....He is still way underwater from the 28 region. Will she go even lower ????</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368624801935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368624832169-36</Id><Title>Onward to 50.00</Title><Msg>5 stars to asraff, zero to waldo as ARMH hits yet another new high.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1368624832169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:33:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368625061289-37</Id><Topic><Title>Walrus Beaver is palpably disappointed in giving up much of his gains in this huge market run.</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368624801935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:33:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eph you Nuff. Stock up today. Thought you knew all. You D- wad. Why don't you comment on insider selling? Haven't heard that one for a while. Who is she?</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1368625061289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:37:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368625094414-38</Id><Topic><Title>Onward to 50.00</Title><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1368624832169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:33:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Russ Fischer says short ARMH over $50. If it gets close to $51 I will short it.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368625094414</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:38:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368625596443-39</Id><Title>Still Waiting</Title><Msg>On Nenni to address the 16 reasons why ARM fabrication is toast. LOL He couldn't even handle the first one...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368625596443</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368625606542-40</Id><Topic><Title>Walrus Beaver is palpably disappointed in giving up much of his gains in this huge market run.</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368624801935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:33:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK Wally.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368625606542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368625952832-41</Id><Topic><Title>RECOMMENDATION TO SHORTS: COVER EARLY</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368624596143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:29:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is very little need for shorts to cover. There is too much liquidity in the stock and in the options market. I can sell a Jan 2015 $30 PUT today for $7.75 right now. That would provide and exit price of $22.25. If I wanted to make sure I got out cleanly, I would also buy an OCT $30 CALL for 7 cents for a total of $22.32. Since I can exit for nearly $2 below the trading price, what is the pressure? If Intel jumps $2 per share, my exit price become $24.32 instead of $22.32. What is the pressure? The shorts are large institutional investors/traders who have a strategy they are moving on. Intel has a BETA of less than 1. It is unlikely to move fast. Shorts may get banged up but the probability is VERY, VERY low.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368625952832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:52:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368626080472-42</Id><Title>All the Reasons Why ARM Is Up Big Today</Title><Msg>1.) The sun came up - why shouldn't ARM be up. 2.) Someone on Wall Street pressed the wrong button. 3.) People in Britain think Haswell is a tea. 4.) New ARM fabrication facility just opened. Part of the marketing department. Fabricating like crazy. 5.) You really, really, really just can't fix stupid.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368626080472</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:54:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368626154590-43</Id><Topic><Title>Still Waiting</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368625596443</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:46:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pretty funny. Wally you already admit in other posts ARMH is not going away. Now they are toast you claim. You are like a small child that just is looking to find one story that sticks.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368626154590</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368626380037-44</Id><Title>My Sincere Advise To Shorts</Title><Msg>Buy puts its safer but don't short as you can get burned. Learn from my experience it can be nasty. goodluck.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368626380037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:59:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368626445770-45</Id><Topic><Title>All the Reasons Why ARM Is Up Big Today</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368626080472</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:54:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM does not trade with its fundamentals. ARM stock is up because people think ARM stock will continue to go up. The last ER was not really worth adding $5B+ to the market cap.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368626445770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:00:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368626450798-46</Id><Topic><Title>All the Reasons Why ARM Is Up Big Today</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368626080472</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:54:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what happened to all that great T and A you were spewing ??? You are a clown.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368626450798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:00:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368626494638-47</Id><Title>INTC 09:59am EDT 24.16 0.30 +1.32%</Title><Msg>Eat it short jaccccckooffffs. Nobody gives a rat's what Congress says, the markets are going higher.</Msg><Username>amdsuckks</Username><Timestamp>1368626494638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:01:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368626555952-48</Id><Topic><Title>Walrus Beaver is palpably disappointed in giving up much of his gains in this huge market run.</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368624801935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:33:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>eat it</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1368626555952</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:02:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368626561919-49</Id><Title>Mkt Correction might come</Title><Msg>when all the shorts have covered. LOL Presently I think the mkts have been #$%$ around with the shorts and yesterdays rally was a lot to do with short coverings and this mornings early jump as well.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368626561919</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368626738859-50</Id><Topic><Title>Walrus Beaver is palpably disappointed in giving up much of his gains in this huge market run.</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368624801935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:33:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now Wally ...play nice...I mean I know you have lost a lot of money, but still.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368626738859</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368626777602-51</Id><Topic><Title>Walrus Beaver is palpably disappointed in giving up much of his gains in this huge market run.</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368624801935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:33:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not wally- you a hole</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1368626777602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:06:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368626814908-52</Id><Title>1 million ARMv8-A to my RECEIVING DOCK</Title><Msg>What would it cost me if I wanted to have 1 million ARMv8-A CPU delivered to my receiving dock? How long would it take from DECISION to parts RECEIPT? Assume that I am a startup company with infinite funds or a new division in a large company. There are some phase I think I would have to go through. staffing. design testing order</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368626814908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:06:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368626823272-53</Id><Title>178 days of Rally</Title><Msg>so far without a pullback. Kind of makes you scratch your head.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368626823272</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:07:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368626915746-54</Id><Topic><Title>All the Reasons Why ARM Is Up Big Today</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368626080472</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:54:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM investors also believed that ARM's low-power designs would scale up in performance with the same energy efficiency as their low-power models. The belief that ARM will be able to capture Intel's traditional markets rests on this assumption. Of course this is as clueless as believing the car that gets 28 mpg while driving 30 mph is going to get the same mileage while driving 100mph. Like Mark Twain said, "It's not what you don't know that gets you, it's what you know with absolutely certainty that just ain't so".</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1368626915746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:08:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368627082035-55</Id><Title>It will end in the red today</Title><Msg>There have so many of these headfakes the past decade.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368627082035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:11:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368627189247-56</Id><Topic><Title>178 days of Rally</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368626823272</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:07:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tepper suggested that Q2 was draining the lake on safe places to put your money and the deficit was disappearing rapidly and their was $400bil looking for a home over the next 12 months. When $400b is chased out of the bond market, there are not too many places to go. Expect more and expect that technical charts will sing "EXTREMELY OVERBOUGHT" and it will not mean much. Tepper suggested the rally would continue.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368627189247</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368627324864-57</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Holdings: Learning From My Mistakes by Ashraf</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368554568522</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:02:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Here's the link: There's a list of the dropping number of ARM foundries on slide #27 as well as copious other information which you will be helpless to refute." FIRST, that slide deck in one man's OPINION, A Professor out of Beiijing, yet you present it as fact. I work with the GSA Global, I have access to all of their reports, they are a sponsor of SemiWiki. SECOND, you are misrepresenting slide #27. That slide includes IDMs as well as foundries. You really need to understand the difference. THIRD the list of 14nm foundries is incorrect. GF is already developing 14nm as is UMC. I know this from first hand experience not from a slide (opinion) of an academic. In fact, all of the foundries at 20nm will be at 14nm in my opinion. The mobile business is too profitable for them not to be. So again, you cut and paste other people's opinions and represent them as fact. I on the other hand speak from direct experience. You are a 64 year old man yet you act like a school yard bully with name calling and attempts at belittling. Learn how to have a grown up discussion and it may open your mind up and allow you to make better investment decisions. That is my opinion of course, and not a fact, so yes I know the difference.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368627324864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:15:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368627336596-58</Id><Topic><Title>It will end in the red today</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368627082035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:11:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My dividend MUDDLE predicts that Intel will end at $24.00. My MUDDLE does not have any "headfake" parameter. It was not designed to predict based on the past.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368627336596</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:15:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368627361395-59</Id><Title>Check out MISM right now! It is about to go on a massive run</Title><Msg>MISM is starting to move. Do your DD asap!</Msg><Username>matthewsc775</Username><Timestamp>1368627361395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:16:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368627466085-60</Id><Title>Hey "Itakebackmyapology"</Title><Msg>....thanks for paying my Dividend against this quarter. Heading to the beach, on you.......chump.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1368627466085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368627657116-61</Id><Title>Chinese Professor Says ARM Fabless Model Fall Down, Go Boom</Title><Msg>And he's got the facts and figures to prove it. gsaglobal dot org/events/2012/1107/docs/slft2012_wei.pdf</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368627657116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:20:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368627666137-62</Id><Title>ARMH over 50, only Wallace is still running his mouth</Title><Msg>Defiant til the end. All other ARM bashers tipped their cap and moved on. But not Wally, he wants you to short it and help him out of his mess. He has no shame.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368627666137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368627666312-63</Id><Topic><Title>Wallisweaver is a great man</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368574215858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:30:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Prove it :).</Msg><Username>thebluereddork</Username><Timestamp>1368627666312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368627729627-64</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH over 50, only Wallace is still running his mouth</Title><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368627666137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:21:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many ARM shares did you buy today? Oh, none. Put your money where your mouth is, butkus...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368627729627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368627845295-65</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese Professor Says ARM Fabless Model Fall Down, Go Boom</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368627657116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey you sound like a 3rd grader ! Dont be stealin my lines.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368627845295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368627904231-66</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Holdings: Learning From My Mistakes by Ashraf</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368554568522</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:02:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You call that a rebuttal??? That's putting a bunch of words on a page and moving them around. This guy has your head in a basket. But go ahead. Let's see you address the other 15 reasons why ARM fabrication is toast...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368627904231</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368627918683-67</Id><Topic><Title>It will end in the red today</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368627082035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:11:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will INTEL announce a dividend raise tomorrow? ;^)</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1368627918683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:25:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368627931321-68</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH over 50, only Wallace is still running his mouth</Title><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368627666137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:21:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have no interest in ARM, this is the INTEL board. You've wrecked it... oh, and as far as ARMH, I've watched you bash it all the way up from the low 20's, call people names and refuse to accept responsibility for your own ignorance. Keep bashing, it's fun to watch your desperation.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368627931321</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:25:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368628128532-69</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Holdings: Learning From My Mistakes by Ashraf</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368554568522</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:02:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"FIRST, that slide deck in one man's OPINION, A Professor out of Beiijing, yet you present it as fact. I work with the GSA Global, I have access to all of their reports, they are a sponsor of SemiWiki" [Show us something, anything that demonstrates that his "facts" are wrong. I've never seen anyone talk out of both sides of his mouth so much in two sentences. You try to get credibility from saying you know these guys and then you immediately throw them under the bus. It's hilarious to see you twist and turn with no idea how to respond...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368628128532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368628129528-70</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Holdings: Learning From My Mistakes by Ashraf</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368554568522</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:02:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THIRD: What is the size of the mobile business (revenue and profits) for the foundries? GF is probably already "developing" 10nm and 7nm and .... nm ....as is UMC and ..... What year will a production released product ship to a retail customer using a 20nm, and 14nm GF produced part? I am interested in an estimate for a pure 20nm and pure 14nm part but if you only want to estimate for the 20nm with 14nm transistors .... that will be OK.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368628129528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368628160349-71</Id><Title>Why the nonsense from the Right and left have no affect.</Title><Msg>The stock market ignores them all because in the end, it is demographics that are driving the nation's political roads. Each year, there are more DEMs as a percentage and fewer Repubs. It is called the changing demographics. Mr. Taco Bell is not voting for you KKK teaparty clowns. The Dems could run any idiot and that person would win the Hispanic vote by a 3 to 1 ratio. You see--old white trash GOP, they hate you as much as they hate you. Then we of course have the Black vote and it too will NOT switch to your KKK party because NO person on earth is that stupid. OK--then we have young people--they hate you rightwing gay hating religious KKK nuts. So basically, your base is old and dropping dead from old age is it not GOP. Obummer could drop his pants and screw a dog, and the Left wing of the Dem party would still vote for him over and Republican. You see, they hate you. So you are going after Obummer in hopes of hurting the Dems but you just do not get it. You idiots will not pass immigration reform and therefor you are going to lose 80% of the Hispanic vote in the 2014 elections and come 2016, ANY DEM can win the White House because you lost before it even begins. You can tune into Fuxed up news and believe them but I think even you rightwing niiimmrods understand you are on the wrong side trying to battle upstream.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey7</Username><Timestamp>1368628160349</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368628225818-72</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH over 50, only Wallace is still running his mouth</Title><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368627666137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:21:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, so you didn't buy any shares and all your opinions are after the fact. You're just an ankle biter. I knew that...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368628225818</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368628227285-73</Id><Topic><Title>Wallisweaver is a great man</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368574215858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:30:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally writing love letters to himself ....pretty strange .....</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368628227285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:30:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368628278691-74</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH over 50, only Wallace is still running his mouth</Title><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368627666137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:21:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many did you short ?</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368628278691</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:31:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368628331328-75</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH over 50, only Wallace is still running his mouth</Title><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368627666137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:21:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't bash or pump stocks. It's called having a backbone. You have none, and prove it daily. Are you ever gonna apologize to Ashraf for getting him caught up in your ARMH disaster? Didn't thank so.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368628331328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368628536784-76</Id><Title>MISM is looking like it is about to go on a massive run</Title><Msg>Keep an eye on MSIM, A little birdie told me that this thing is about to get a huge awarness campaign.</Msg><Username>trich264</Username><Timestamp>1368628536784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:35:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368628883144-77</Id><Topic><Title>RBC Capital Upgrades Intel (INTC) to Outperform Raises Target To $29</Title><Username>keiretsunikkei</Username><Timestamp>1367845718534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:08:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>upgrades taking affect</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368628883144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:41:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368628931076-78</Id><Topic><Title>Walrus Beaver is palpably disappointed in giving up much of his gains in this huge market run.</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368624801935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:33:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and I am not nuff. rim licker</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368628931076</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:42:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368628940936-79</Id><Topic><Title>It will end in the red today</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368627082035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:11:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmmm. Annual meeting is tomorrow and BOD is together with new CEO. BTW, it will be webcast. Could be. The last two have been announce in early May as they meet for the Annual Shareholder meeting. The shareholder meeting is always held in mid-May. They may want to talk it over with Brian and Rene. IMO, the normal window has past looking only at historical data. IMO, I think a small raise might be in the cards for the Nov dividend but they will likely wait until there is some visibility. May 7, 2012 – Dividend Increased to 90 cents Per Share on an Annual Basis May 11, 2011 – SANTA CLARA, Calif., May 11, 2011 – Intel Corporation today announced that its board of directors has approved a 16 percent increase in the Nov 12, 2010 – Intel Announces 15 Percent Increase to Quarterly Cash Dividend Dec 11, 2009 –Intel announces dividend increase for Q1 2010</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368628940936</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368629249163-80</Id><Topic><Title>It will end in the red today</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368627082035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:11:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"My dividend MUDDLE predicts that " I really meant: My OPTION muddle predicts that There is option trading that drains the BETA from Intel and has it trade around the strike points. IMO, it is probably an abusive options market maker. I filed a formal SEC complaint and was contacted by them that they would be investigating it. I was informed that it might take time and that I might not hear back but the agent did say that something did look strange. If I win, you will be able to read about the reward.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368629249163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:47:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368629315528-81</Id><Topic><Title>It will end in the red today</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368627082035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:11:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks like large put volume again on 23.5 and 24. That was with the last drop a few minutes ago.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1368629315528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:48:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368629577533-82</Id><Topic><Title>Walrus Beaver is palpably disappointed in giving up much of his gains in this huge market run.</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368624801935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:33:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sure as H are. Just one of your many aliases. You not foolin anyone. Same krap every day.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1368629577533</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368629613171-83</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH over 50, only Wallace is still running his mouth</Title><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368627666137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:21:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would wallisweaver apologize to me? I came to my conclusions on ARMH entirely independently of wallisweaver's views. That being said, ARMH's stock price really seems like it's going out of control due to factors entirely unrelated to ARM the company.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368629613171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368629763606-84</Id><Topic><Title>1 million ARMv8-A to my RECEIVING DOCK</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368626814908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it really depends on what else is on the SoC. If just a CPU core and little else,,,?</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1368629763606</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:56:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368629923710-85</Id><Title>Intel Short Exit Strategy Fails - After Two Days</Title><Msg>My how far the mighty Intel bashers have fallen...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368629923710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368629963112-86</Id><Topic><Title>First Haswell tablets expected by end of summer in time for 'back to school'</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368596374843</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 01:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Worth a repeat: Haswell tablets expected by end of summer</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368629963112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:59:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368630043811-87</Id><Topic><Title>Walrus Beaver is palpably disappointed in giving up much of his gains in this huge market run.</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368624801935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:33:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok Wally you know everything....I keep forgetting.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368630043811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:00:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368630071767-88</Id><Topic><Title>Intel chip gives new hope for Windows 8 tablets</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368064057258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:47:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Silvermont is a game-changer</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368630071767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:01:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368630075648-89</Id><Topic><Title>It will end in the red today</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368627082035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:11:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There was nearly an IDENTICAL 11,000 contract option trade. GOOD CATCH !!! When that happens, that is nearly 100% likely a single trader. If you take just those two trades along and assume they are not paired with any other .... If they SOLD the $24 and BOUGHT the $23.50, that is a BULL PUT SPREAD. They assume INTC will go UP and the higher priced PUT they SOLD would become worthless and the lower priced PUT they BOUGHT was insurance. If they BOUGHT the $24 and SOLD the $23.50, that is a BEAR PUT SPREAD. They assume INTC will go DOWN and the higher priced PUT they BOUGHT will increase in value as the share price drops. YOU CANNOT TELL which it by the numbers. HOWEVER, the option market maker is on the other side of that trade and he will HEDGE the position to lock his profits. If it was a BULLISH trade, the OMM will be buying some shares to hedge. If it was a BEARISH trade, the OMM will be buying some shares to hedge. If Intel ended a little lower after the trade, it was likely a BEARISH position. If Intel ended a little higher after the trade, it was likely a BULLISH position. Most of the time ONLY THE OMM and the trader know for sure.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368630075648</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:01:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368630129446-90</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Short Exit Strategy Fails - After Two Days</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368629923710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean like the ARMH bashers ? hehe</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368630129446</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368630162296-91</Id><Title>Nenni</Title><Msg>I'll send Dr. ShaoJun Wei a note informing him that you represented him in a public forum as a charlatan who posts false and misleading information. I'm sure he'll want to talk to you the next time he sees you...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368630306769-92</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>much like you Walmart wally.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368630306769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:05:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368630343216-93</Id><Title>GOOGE I/O EVENT STARTS IN 1 HOUR</Title><Msg>ANY DESIGN WIN ANNOUNCEMENT(S) will pop this thing towards $30. $40 by end of year</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368630343216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:05:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368630717954-94</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Short Exit Strategy Fails - After Two Days</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368629923710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ARMH bashers are on the ARMH message board where the ARMH investors are. The Intel basher are here and they are simply using the ARMH club. ARMH is a small rather illiquid stock that has a rich valuation. They will continue to get license fees and royalty payments even if their customer markets "went to zero units" because of the pipeline. My thermostat will still need a CPU to run it. My bathroom scale will still need a CPU. My car key will still need a CPU. My lawnmower will still need a CPU. ARMH will do fine. I just wish for a little less and less emotional ARMH information.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368630717954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:11:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368630751552-95</Id><Topic><Title>GOOGE I/O EVENT STARTS IN 1 HOUR</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368630343216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:05:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they don't announce who built what dimwit. jeezzzz. It will be all about Google. Now go eat another bag of sugar donuts ya lard #$%$. Wally do you ever stop eating junk food ?</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368630751552</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368630937162-96</Id><Topic><Title>178 days of Rally</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368626823272</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:07:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi Alex, This time around the strong dollar will kill us as the Japanese yen is free falling. Look at their export numbers for April, huge. Look at the ISM numbers this morn was negative 1.4 instead positive. I know all this means nothing presently but will catch up someday. Yep bro the technical don't mean nothing anymore at least for now.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368630937162</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:15:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368630966314-97</Id><Topic><Title>GOOGE I/O EVENT STARTS IN 1 HOUR</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368630343216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:05:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how's your INTC short doing today? better cover shorty</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368630966314</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:16:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368631501979-98</Id><Title>Bad Sign for Microsoft as Dell Discounts Windows RT Tablet</Title><Msg>ARM's future ... http://www.thestreet.com/story/11924328/1/bad-sign-for-microsoft-as-dell-discounts-windows-rt-tablet.html?puc=yahoo&amp;cm_ven=YAHOO</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368631501979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:25:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368632395113-99</Id><Topic><Title>It will end in the red today</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368627082035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:11:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the interesting insight. I believe Friday has 24 max pain and it will be affected if or if not INTEL raises or fails to raise the dividend. I believe they will raise it by 2.5 cents per quarter, making it an even dollar.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1368632395113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:39:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368632495399-100</Id><Topic><Title>Bad Sign for Microsoft as Dell Discounts Windows RT Tablet</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368631501979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:25:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oddly, Microsoft still isn't ready to pull the plug on RT: "Speaking specifically about Microsoft and ARM related devices, Tami Reller was adamant on Microsoft's needs to maintain the flexibility of having ARM devices along side your more traditional x86 and x64 platforms. It's clear that even with Intel's new low-power devices hitting the market soon, ARM will certainly be challenged in the areas it has traditional done well. But, Microsoft is committed to the platform, based on Reller's statements, so it would seem that Windows RT is here for the long-haul and that the company has no plans to abandon the platform at this time." neowinDOTnet/news/microsoft-039we-need-the-flexibility-of-arm039</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1368632495399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:41:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368632642251-101</Id><Title>HIGH FLYERS SCORE</Title><Msg>GOOG 909 +22 NFLX 245 + 11 PCLN 804 + 11 Fing unbelievable. This mkt is crazy ig WAG at 50 and LOW at 43 and many more in the stratosphere, I am in cash for now. Screw this BS.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368632642251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:44:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368632876882-102</Id><Topic><Title>Bad Sign for Microsoft as Dell Discounts Windows RT Tablet</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368631501979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:25:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Almost no one was interested in ARM-RT tablets even when RT devices competed against Intel's five year old Atom. If the public didn't want it then, they surely won't want it now.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1368632876882</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:47:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368633100195-103</Id><Title>Samsung scores 95% of Android smartphone profits</Title><Msg>From CNET: "Samsung took home almost all of the profits generated in the Android smartphone world last quarter, according to a report out today from Strategy Analytics. For the first quarter, global Android smartphone profits totaled $5.3 billion. Samsung captured a hefty 95 percent, or $5.1 billion, of that amount. Strategy Analytics senior analyst Woody Oh pinned Samsung's success on an "efficient supply chain, sleek products, and crisp marketing." Second place LG Electronics snagged 2.5 percent of Android's global earnings and is far behind Samsung in the volume of its smartphone devices. Samsung could even use its dominance to gain an edge over LG and other rival Android vendors." Google/Moto, ZTE and Lenovo, all predominantly Android are apparently not making any profit.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1368633100195</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368633138471-104</Id><Topic><Title>Bad Sign for Microsoft as Dell Discounts Windows RT Tablet</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368631501979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:25:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am sure MSFT never had plans to abandon Alpha/MIPS/Itanium on Windows either, the customers made the choice for them as they will with ARM kit. Nobody in the ARM world is prepared to do the heavy duty legacy software porting job and as the hardware is no better all that is left to compete with is price as seen with Dell. Sure Qualcomm/Nvidia might propose new WinRT tablets but the OEMs once burned with inventory they can't sell will just ignore them. WinRT died at birth like we all said it would, the actual public funeral will take place a few years down the line.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368633138471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368633236962-105</Id><Topic><Title>1 million ARMv8-A to my RECEIVING DOCK</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368626814908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about an estimate for just a CPU core for a base price per chip. How about then adding some commonly available IP to it for what the cost of stirring the pot. Would my burdened cost be $1 per device or $10 per device or .... I would be fine if you want to craft an example similar to what I am describing if my question is dumb since my question is just to understand what the cost for a new entrant to get to a simple product. I wanted to test the assumption about the difficulty in just stirring up a pot of ARM for solving a problem where I needed 1 million devices. About how many people would I have to hire. Tools would I have to buy. Timing. Costs for the first time through the process .... barrier to entry and then incremental cost.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368633236962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:53:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368633392069-106</Id><Topic><Title>178 days of Rally</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368626823272</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:07:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So if Tepper is right and there will be $400 bill looking for a home, where will it go?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368633392069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:56:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368633467009-107</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung scores 95% of Android smartphone profits</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1368633100195</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:51:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Intel bring out their LTE chip in volume, Samsung will stop using Qualcomm Snapdragons all together and just pair the XMM 7160 with an Exynos chip in the US market as they do with Intel's 3G chip in international markets.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368633467009</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368633583538-108</Id><Topic><Title>Bad Sign for Microsoft as Dell Discounts Windows RT Tablet</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368631501979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:25:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel's 5-year Atom had to become evolved enough though at 32nm to give all day battery usage, that was the killer. There was a slight chance WinRT might have established a small foothold before Clover Trail but none after it.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368633583538</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:59:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368633723094-109</Id><Title>Gloom and Doom for the Day - LOL</Title><Msg>The domestic equity markets are in a holding pattern after returning to record highs yesterday, with a plethora of disappointing global data subduing sentiment. US industrial production fell more than expected and regional manufacturing activity unexpectedly contracted, while the eurozone economy posted its sixth-straight quarterly contraction. Gold and crude oil prices are seeing some pressure, while the US dollar is moving higher. Treasuries are higher amid the disappointing data, along with another tame reading on wholesale inflation and a decline in mortgage applications, which are more than offsetting a stronger-than-forecasted read on homebuilder sentiment. In equity news, Deere &amp; Co topped the Street's quarterly expectations, but offered a cautious outlook, while Macy's Inc bested analysts' profit forecasts, while boosting its dividend and share repurchases. Overseas, Asian stocks finished mostly to the upside, led by the continued rally for Japanese stocks, while most of the European equity markets are shrugging off recessionary data out of the eurozone.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368633723094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:02:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368633986956-110</Id><Topic><Title>Bad Sign for Microsoft as Dell Discounts Windows RT Tablet</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368631501979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:25:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a huge cut in price. They are obviously liquidating and losing money on these. How will MSFT sell surface RT's against this price. MSFT also has a large inventory of RT platforms.. Potentially they can put new 7SDP Ivy's into their inventory of surface RT chassis with full windows 8..</Msg><Username>redwood1205</Username><Timestamp>1368633986956</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:06:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368634045949-111</Id><Title>ZTE Grand X2 In debuts with a 4.5″ HD display, 8MP camera and 2GHz Intel Atom Z2580 processor</Title><Msg>In Europe? Is this new? ZTE Grand X2 In debuts with a 4.5″ HD display, 8MP camera and 2GHz Intel Atom Z2580 processor 15 May 2013 ZTE has unveiled the Grand X2 In, a new mid-range Andoid smartphone sporting a 4.5-inch HD display (1280×720) and an Intel Atom Z2580 processor clocked at 2Ghz. The device was unveiled at the MedPi conference in Monaco today and comes with an 8-megapixel rear-facing camera, contrasted with a 1-megapixel version on the front. ZTE says the “socially-smart” camera has one of the quickest burst modes on the market, capturing up to 24 frames per second with no shutter lag whatsoever.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368634045949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:07:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368634073606-112</Id><Title>Momentum Picking up in MISM</Title><Msg>MISM looking like it is ready to go. So undervalued here. Look at their site. They have some huge properties with proven reserves. Check it out</Msg><Username>wigginsdaniel718</Username><Timestamp>1368634073606</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:07:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368634320407-113</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Short Exit Strategy Fails - After Two Days</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368629923710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's your short exit strategy on ARM, boob???</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368634320407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:12:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368634536101-114</Id><Title>MONSTER MOVE--CERP BREAKING NEWS</Title><Msg>MONSTER MOVE</Msg><Username>tedpoo3drew</Username><Timestamp>1368634536101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:15:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368634692749-115</Id><Topic><Title>Bad Sign for Microsoft as Dell Discounts Windows RT Tablet</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368631501979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:25:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you had better prove it *wink*. RT benchmarks are far better than their actual performance, :) indubitably, verifiably so. *wink*</Msg><Username>thebluereddork</Username><Timestamp>1368634692749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:18:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368634749712-116</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE Grand X2 In debuts with a 4.5″ HD display, 8MP camera and 2GHz Intel Atom Z2580 processor</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368634045949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:07:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As new as it gets http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20130515005998/en/Global-Premiere-ZTE-Grand-X2-%E2%80%93-ZTE%E2%80%99s</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368634749712</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368634878066-117</Id><Topic><Title>Bad Sign for Microsoft as Dell Discounts Windows RT Tablet</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368631501979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:25:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't disagree with any of that, just surprised they haven't kicked it to touch already.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1368634878066</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368635045661-118</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Short Exit Strategy Fails - After Two Days</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368629923710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What's your short exit strategy on ARM, boob???" [I don't need one, butkus. I'm not short, I have puts. I have until options expiration in January for ARM to come crashing back to earth. There are some good investment web sites for novices where you can learn about how options work...] [How many ARM shares did you buy today? Oh, none. You're not a player so you have no right to an opinion. Now run along - you're bothering the investors...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368635045661</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368635121472-119</Id><Topic><Title>Bad Sign for Microsoft as Dell Discounts Windows RT Tablet</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368631501979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:25:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice PR double speak. Like I've said many times before the concept of Windows RT was conceived years ago when the "PC era is dead" idea was more believable. In that time we saw WebOS come and go, and the Playbook do nothing, More importantly we saw Apple who made 85% of its margins from ARM based devices store away more cash than the net worth of 1/3 of the countries on the planet. The stock soared to over $700 only to watch it fall well into the $300 price range in the same year. The real problem with Windows RT is that it's four years too late to the party. Had it been around during the time of the iPad introduction it would have stood a change. Did Apple have a head start? No, Microsoft had a tablet back in 2000. Not only that but they had a 15 year working history with Windows Mobile. Microsoft's relationship with ARM dates back to the mid 90s. I was using Windows Mobile devices in the late 90's. With the rich history of code Microsoft would be silly to abandon Windows RT (Mobile). Synch, the in car entertainment system is based on Windows Mobile. There may be some embedded apps with ARM processors that Microsoft has it's eye on in the future that can help it make back the money it has lost on RT. But to be very clear, ARM added nothing to Microsoft's bottom line. The outstanding quarter it's seeing is due mainly to sales of computers with Intel processors (AMD and XBox withstanding). This gives proof that the PC era isn't over by a long shot. Windows Phone and RT are on the books in the meantime. Microsoft is currently rethinking the future. Windows 8 was meant to be one interface from server to phone. Nobody can better deliver on this than Intel, and Microsoft is slowly realizing it.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1368635121472</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:25:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368635203760-120</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Short Exit Strategy Fails - After Two Days</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368629923710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody's running along anywhere and since you feel the need to run your mouth here all the time, anyone viewing this board will also know that you are a desperate twit that's bashed ARM since it was priced at 25. I've got some DOOZIES to repost of you saying the end of the ARM era occurred over 100% ago. LOL @ YOU.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368635203760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368635373838-121</Id><Title>"It will take a miracle for ARMH to stay over 40" - Wallisweaver, March 2013</Title><Msg>LOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368635373838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:29:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368635386195-122</Id><Topic><Title>Bad Sign for Microsoft as Dell Discounts Windows RT Tablet</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368631501979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:25:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would look embarrassing straight away. Their aims were noble, to increase their TAM and have cpu competition but legacy software is important in the Windows world. Also notice all the heavy lifting Intel did in about a year to shift from Meego to Android including having a translator, none of the rich ARM licensees put a similar effort into Windows, some rich diverse ARM ecosystem lol ! The only real hope for WinRT in the long run is *IF* in a couple of years time Nvidia produce a worthwhile Project Denver chip to reignite interest, otherwise it is soooo dead !</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368635386195</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:29:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368635446474-123</Id><Title>Only a complete DA loser is short Intel now. And you know who you are.</Title><Msg>Did James C tell you 16 price target? What? You believed him? You are indeed a LOOOOOOOOSERRRR! My pet dog "buttlickkkk" is smarter than you Intel shorts. Yeah he occasionally eats sheet but at least he looks good.</Msg><Username>amdsuckks</Username><Timestamp>1368635446474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:30:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368635511699-124</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE Grand X2 In debuts with a 4.5″ HD display, 8MP camera and 2GHz Intel Atom Z2580 processor</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368634045949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:07:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>During the 2013 Beijing IDF; ZTE Geek (Atom Z2580 Clovertrail+) smartphone is smoking fast, spanks the top ARM SoCs Reported by Lennard Seah on Thursday, April 11 2013 1:17 pm By all accounts, the ZTE Geek should be an unremarkable phone - its unimaginative, plasticky and has decidedly mid-ranged specs. But just like the Lenovo K900, the 2GHz Atom Clovertrail+ SOC in it delivers ARM beating performance. In the standard AntTuTu Benchmark that we ran on the show floor, the ZTE Geek scored an impressive 29401, better than the scores found in the public domain of the HTC One (Qualcomm 600) and Samsung Galaxy S IV (Exynos 5410). Naturally, one should reserve judgement and not entirely formulate opinion based on benchmarks done on the show floor (who knows what shenanigans could be happening behind the scenes). We would love to get our hands on one of these in our labs to do a proper analysis especially on the battery drain characteristics of the Clovertrail+ SoC, which actually matters more than raw performance to most people. vr-zoneDOTcom/articles/zte-geek-atom-z2580-clovertrail--smartphone-is-smoking-fast-spanks-the-top-arm-socs/19619.html#ixzz2TNaeKcVA</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1368635511699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368635564741-125</Id><Topic><Title>"It will take a miracle for ARMH to stay over 40" - Wallisweaver, March 2013</Title><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368635373838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:29:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>....OL</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368635564741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:32:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368636111556-126</Id><Topic><Title>Bad Sign for Microsoft as Dell Discounts Windows RT Tablet</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368631501979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:25:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>marsavian, How would "Project Denver" solve the fundamental problems here? PD will be a 2015/2016 affair on the fake "16nm" TSMC process, right around the time when Intel's "Core" products are full SoCs at the high end and then Atom has continued to march forward from below. Denver could make for strong competition in the Android space, but in Windows, no backwards compatibility = no go for anything but 7" tablets.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368636111556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:41:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368636204972-127</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE Grand X2 In debuts with a 4.5″ HD display, 8MP camera and 2GHz Intel Atom Z2580 processor</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368634045949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:07:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw the Geek but did not know if it was the same market and/or phone since the name was different and I thought the Geek was being released in China.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368636204972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:43:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368636475249-128</Id><Topic><Title>"It will take a miracle for ARMH to stay over 40" - Wallisweaver, March 2013</Title><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368635373838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:29:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is a never ending source of how to lose money that is for sure.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368636475249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:47:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368636747641-129</Id><Title>There Is NO MORE RESISTANCE</Title><Msg>Resistance is just a figure of speech and a mkt game play. With the Global Central Banks flooding the mkts every resistance which a technician would indicate as the charts is being rolled over with a John Deere Tractor. Just pile in and ride it high and when everyone is done buying or the fed starts to pullout then we shall see a rollover BUT until that happens its back to the races. The mkt is looking at all this wall of worry and the economic numbers and with the inflation data being tame the fed is just sitting cozy and the mkts keep riding high.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368636747641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368636967188-130</Id><Topic><Title>Bad Sign for Microsoft as Dell Discounts Windows RT Tablet</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368631501979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:25:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only way a new Windows ISA will take hold without major legacy porting is if it is a good gaming chip which will then create new demand. If anyone can produce a good ARM gaming chip it is Nvidia. Not saying they will do it compared to x86 SoCs but that is the only slim chance for WinRT and of course they will be relying heavily on the gpu for this.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368636967188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368637613954-131</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Short Exit Strategy Fails - After Two Days</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368629923710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparantly, you haven't learned very much. Even a long dated option fluctuates in value. But never fear, the correction that will inevitably come with take your beloved INTC share along for the ride, and then you will likely ride them down again. Your biggest investment for years appears to have been in time spent pumping INTC. It most certainly has not been in making good investment decisions.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1368637613954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:06:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368637650600-132</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Short Exit Strategy Fails - After Two Days</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368629923710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love how upset you are, stalker boy. It just means that Intel has moved higher. Now be a good boy and post up some more to let us all know that your anger and frustration level has moved even higher. Pretty sure we can get blood to run out of your nose today. Wait - I hear noise! Is that you banging your head against the wall???</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368637650600</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:07:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368637720140-133</Id><Title>Well, Wallis, maybe if the market continues up another 3 years ...</Title><Msg>do you think you might see $30?</Msg><Username>muxuhmillyanprob</Username><Timestamp>1368637720140</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:08:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368638098394-134</Id><Title>Using my T and A indicators Intel will not keep it up</Title><Msg>flaccid fashizzle. It will take a MIRACLE to hit 25.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368638098394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:14:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368638236167-135</Id><Topic><Title>Gloom and Doom for the Day - LOL</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368633723094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dble checked the arbeter note from last Friday, the upside quoted was 1650-1660. the belief was the upside was limited, with head and shoulder type topping or dbl topping formation forming. I'm looking for the turn down in the signals for confirmation to enter long sqqq for a buy and hold . Though I did buy some for the IRA today.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1368638236167</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:17:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368638563015-136</Id><Topic><Title>"It will take a miracle for ARMH to stay over 40" - Wallisweaver, March 2013</Title><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368635373838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:29:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A nice call, like $30 is in the bag and $3 eps. The flock is so dumb, this guy blows.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1368638563015</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:22:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368638622907-137</Id><Title>if u lost money shorting ARMH due to WALeyed Beaver's advice..please</Title><Msg>contact the firm of Dewey Scroeem and Howe. We will make things all better.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368638622907</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:23:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368638688345-138</Id><Title>Wallrus! The NDX is going RED!</Title><Msg>You think your precious INTC can maintain $24+ so the homegamers still "look fine" after 36 months?</Msg><Username>muxuhmillyanprob</Username><Timestamp>1368638688345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:24:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368638781663-139</Id><Title>#$%$ Happened</Title><Msg>was 15.3K or S&amp;P1661 too high??</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368638781663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368638836190-140</Id><Title>MISM looks like it could see $1+ in the near future</Title><Msg>Keep an eye on MSIM, A little birdie told me that this thing is about to get a huge awarness campaign.</Msg><Username>jeremiah.boone3475</Username><Timestamp>1368638836190</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:27:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368638956610-141</Id><Topic><Title>if u lost money shorting ARMH due to WALeyed Beaver's advice..please</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368638622907</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:23:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>~~We will make things all better.~~ Who told you to put a balm?</Msg><Username>muxuhmillyanprob</Username><Timestamp>1368638956610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:29:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368639150331-142</Id><Title>dive dive</Title><Msg>under 24 again wow bad T and A man.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368639150331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:32:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368639529088-143</Id><Topic><Title>Bad Sign for Microsoft as Dell Discounts Windows RT Tablet</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368631501979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:25:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unlikely that it would spur demand; Core i5/i7 laptops + Nvidia discrete would beat up any such chip and steal its lunch money, all while being able to play the latest, x86-only compiled games.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368639529088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:38:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368639837305-144</Id><Topic><Title>Gloom and Doom for the Day - LOL</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368633723094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good morning, I just feel its way too overdone here. there is nothing left as resistance and at this pace of travel we cud hit 1700 on the s&amp;p by this weekend LOL. When these hedge fund guys and fund mgrs. come and say things to drive the mkts I get skeptical. Maybe they are right with the global central bankers flooding the mkts with cash we could go higher but there shud be some kind of fundamentals to justify the prices/PE. I will be looking at the SQQQ myself by the end of the day today. Thanks for the response and have a nice day.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368639837305</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:43:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368639913308-145</Id><Title>Looks like MISM is about to run. Forget (board)!</Title><Msg>I am getting all the MISM I can at these levels. Check their website and financials. This thing is so undervalued here.</Msg><Username>jacobpeterson399</Username><Timestamp>1368639913308</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:45:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368640179428-146</Id><Title>wdblawgrow</Title><Msg>it is absolutely safe to by the SQQQ. The RSI and the Slow and Fast Stockhastics as well as the MACD are almost ZERO. There is plenty of upside to it by that the mkts gonna take a hit here. goodluck</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368640179428</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:49:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368640416626-147</Id><Topic><Title>dive dive</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368639150331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:32:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bite the big one Nuff. You need to post about insiders selling, poss. div cut and low margins. Haven't heard about these things for quite some time- (at least 10 min). Go Nuff Go, you _astard. "_"= b</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1368640416626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:53:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368640548641-148</Id><Topic><Title>Gloom and Doom for the Day - LOL</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368633723094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Twas a nice run in the SQQQ from the low down at 26.58 to 26.88 ish, gotta be careful with these, but sure maximizes gains during a downturn.correction.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1368640548641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:55:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368640714803-149</Id><Topic><Title>Gloom and Doom for the Day - LOL</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368633723094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I wanted to listen to prattle like yours I'd turn on CNBC. Yechh. I am therefore turning you OFF.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368640714803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:58:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368640856915-150</Id><Title>GOOG is Killing AAPL Today</Title><Msg>with their conference about Android and their various new devices</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368640856915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:00:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368640931638-151</Id><Topic><Title>dive dive</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368639150331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:32:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You _ipc$hit. { _ = d } _iss drinker { _= p}</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1368640931638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:02:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368641377211-152</Id><Topic><Title>Using my T and A indicators Intel will not keep it up</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368638098394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're an eph wad and a damn idiot. Expect to see alias coinmaker in a panic soon over your short position. Hoping your screwed up the rump beyond comprehension.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1368641377211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368642223272-153</Id><Topic><Title>Using my T and A indicators Intel will not keep it up</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1368638098394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 13:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too little money to be gained shorting INTC, much more to be gained buying a nice dbl or triple short etf. cause the party just getting started</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1368642223272</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:23:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368642789711-154</Id><Title>Commodity Slumped</Title><Msg>Basically killing the large banks trading commodities.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368642789711</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368643475791-155</Id><Title>Intel: What's Going On With Haswell?</Title><Msg>fun article about Haswell secrecy and some guesses. Lets see if Yahoo allows me to post this. Hard to tell if it is censoring or Yahoo just craping out.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368643475791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368643900564-156</Id><Title>Alex_dum....</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/news/david-teppers-appaloosa-reduces-apple-175700791.html David Tepper who is bullish and advocated Finians trims his holdings albeit not much but these folks say a lot of things but don't know how much they can be trusted.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368643900564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368644327878-157</Id><Title>an analyst friend told me</Title><Msg>intel is dead</Msg><Username>philip_914</Username><Timestamp>1368644327878</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:58:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368644405801-158</Id><Topic><Title>Alex_dum....</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368643900564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:51:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would not trust him any more than a source of data that you crunch into information. Roubini was a god when he predicted 666 on SP500. When SP500 bottomed at 666, exactly as he called it, he lowered his target to 600. He just had a back of the envelop calculation that suggested a $400 billion pile of available cash floating around looking for a home.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368644405801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:00:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368644429169-159</Id><Title>Hey Littlestewie</Title><Msg>You're a greedy loser for trying to time the market and for trying to scare people. You can't time the market and make money long term and you have clearly shown that. Again, you're greedy and have no dignity. Carry on.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368644429169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:00:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368644516759-160</Id><Topic><Title>an analyst friend told me</Title><Username>philip_914</Username><Timestamp>1368644327878</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:58:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>52 billion a year, even when the PC is declared dead. Sukk on that.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368644516759</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:01:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368644870755-161</Id><Title>Todays Mkt Action Doesnt Bode Well</Title><Msg>The Mkt fell off the cliff when the DOW hit 15.3k. It will most likely end up negative and I don't think the dip buyers will step in this time around.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368644870755</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:07:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368645343519-162</Id><Title>the market is going up everyday</Title><Msg>can you imagine where intel would be if the market were to go down for while. 18 or 12?</Msg><Username>philip_914</Username><Timestamp>1368645343519</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:15:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368645702816-163</Id><Title>Haswell is coming!</Title><Msg>Google TV!</Msg><Username>wallis_boll_weevil</Username><Timestamp>1368645702816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:21:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368646183468-164</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or you can be an adult and admit you are wrong. If not I have Dr. Wei's email if you need it. You presented his opinions/observations as facts. You misrepresented his data. His presentation was last year and things are rapidly changing in the fabless semiconductor ecosystem. Dr. Wei is in fact wrong about the 14nm foundry list and he is sure to correct that next time around because, unlike you, he is a credible person. So that is 1 of your 16 points that have been debunked. Ready for round #2?</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368646183468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:29:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368646653713-165</Id><Title>PC shipments down 20.5% in Western Europe</Title><Msg>Nothing important...keep buying.</Msg><Username>think5pm</Username><Timestamp>1368646653713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:37:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368646733875-166</Id><Title>Juhhny Chambers has a surprise for you homegamers after the close!</Title><Msg>Enjoy!</Msg><Username>wallis_boll_weevil</Username><Timestamp>1368646733875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:38:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368646860656-167</Id><Topic><Title>PC shipments down 20.5% in Western Europe</Title><Username>think5pm</Username><Timestamp>1368646653713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>source?</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1368646860656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:41:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368646892958-168</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis is a dirtbag, so whenever he opens his mouth he simply announces it to the world. Not sure I've ever seen such a clutz as one Wallisweaver.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368646892958</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368646916563-169</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"and things are rapidly changing in the fabless semiconductor ecosystem..".hey ASML making new all time high ...appreciate the business...can't scale the back end...the "market" is not even close in anticipating the raising cost the "ARM eco system" will have to face... to make it worse EUV won't be ready ... 3. New routing layers At 28nm and above, the manufacturing flow consists of two parts: front-end-of-the-line (FEOL) and backend-of –the-line (BEOL). The FEOL involves the formation of the transistors and logic, while BEOL handles the vias, interconnects and other structures. At 20nm, the foundries are now talking about a third layer of interconnect. That layer — or MOL — will become another challenge in the manufacturing flow, Capodieci said. As a result, the industry will require “new methodologies” to address the new routing layer, said Cadence’s Beckley.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368646916563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:41:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368646944750-170</Id><Topic><Title>Juhhny Chambers has a surprise for you homegamers after the close!</Title><Username>wallis_boll_weevil</Username><Timestamp>1368646733875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow that's original nuff..............</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368646944750</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368646946574-171</Id><Title>FNMA is up 20 per cent again?</Title><Msg>Who is buying</Msg><Username>roseosowski</Username><Timestamp>1368646946574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368647026595-172</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL DOWNGRADED $2 PRICE TARGET PC MARKET COLLAPSING</Title><Username>nasdaqczar2</Username><Timestamp>1365692696048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>new lows for intel coming</Msg><Username>goldmansuxtrader</Username><Timestamp>1368647026595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368647121301-173</Id><Title>Marcorubio, aintezbeingreen (lucy_nuff), Itakebackmyapology (lucy_nuff)......SUKK IT</Title><Msg>GREEN</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368647121301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:45:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368647180933-174</Id><Topic><Title>Juhhny Chambers has a surprise for you homegamers after the close!</Title><Username>wallis_boll_weevil</Username><Timestamp>1368646733875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cisco ROLLLLLLLLLLLLZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZ...............over since you bought it in 2010.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368647180933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:46:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368647292403-175</Id><Topic><Title>the market is going up everyday</Title><Username>philip_914</Username><Timestamp>1368645343519</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:15:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has a BETA of 1 so an INTC price of $18 would need a market correction of $6 for Intel which is a down market of over 30%.. With Intel buybacks, value investors, Silvermont, Hasell and PHI introductions .... the only reason that Intel went below $20 was a SHORT INTEREST that was increasing by 1 million shares per day. IF someone wants to short 1 million shares a day, they can probably get Intel to $18 by the end of this year. Absent the shorting, IMO, Intel will not see sub-$20 prices again .... unless there is shocking news that exceeds the PC IS DEAD drum beat.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368647292403</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:48:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368647664366-176</Id><Title>Low volume headfake</Title><Msg>Watch the weak hands sell tomorrow</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368647664366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:54:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368647690482-177</Id><Title>coinmaker/nuff pumping CSCO on that board</Title><Msg>Personally I hope CSCO hits it out of the park,good for the entire market.........</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368647690482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:54:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368647694795-178</Id><Title>ciscooooooooooorOLLLZ up 11 cents since Lucy Nuff bought it in 2010</Title><Msg>ROFL!</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368647694795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368647801084-179</Id><Title>Poor Lucy_nuff, disgraced and run off this board</Title><Msg>He killed his own alias so his dumb stock picks couldn't be reposted anymore. LOL! Run off of a message board! ROFL!</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368647801084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:56:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368648427734-180</Id><Title>Great for CSCO!</Title><Msg>Good numbers! Some people seem to forget they are an INTEL client. Very childish to wish your clients ill.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1368648427734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368648531797-181</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"At 20nm, the foundries are now talking about a third layer of interconnect. That layer — or MOL — will become another challenge in the manufacturing flow, Capodieci said." [This is why predictions of when ARM will have volume production on 20nm are useless. The (ARM) predictions are all based on everything going perfectly. Not going to happen...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368648531797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:08:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368648671323-182</Id><Topic><Title>Great for CSCO!</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1368648427734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody here against Cisco. Nobody. It's that little weasel Lucy_Nuff getting laughed at. Thx.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368648671323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:11:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368649036514-183</Id><Topic><Title>Great for CSCO!</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1368648427734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cisco is a great co - I own some. Glad they did well :)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368649036514</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:17:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368649124813-184</Id><Topic><Title>1 million ARMv8-A to my RECEIVING DOCK</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368626814908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you google calxeda (an ARM based startup) you might get some idea on how much cash is burned and staffing. I'de imagine north of 200 million and I've read (no idea how true) that their chip sells for $69. Calxeda add a lot to the SoC so it may not be a normal case. As for your million devices, it depends on a lot of things, process, CPU etc. If an 'old' node and an 'old' CPU and you are adding very little IP, you should be able to do things on the cheap. A high end CPU licence 10 million or so, but a cheapy a fraction of that (less than a million) and the tools would be simpler/cheaper/quicker on more mature nodes. There was a programme (no idea if it's still running) where you basically get the IP for free, but you have higher royalties on any shipping products which was more cheaper for small runs.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1368649124813</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:18:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368649216577-185</Id><Topic><Title>Great for CSCO!</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1368648427734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, Cisco is a very able company. They should do well as long as business is doing well. They are also a INTC client and it will help INTC perception wise. It should lift tech again tomorrow.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1368649216577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:20:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368649331376-186</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"So that is 1 of your 16 points that have been debunked. Ready for round #2?" [You didn't bebunk anything. You gave your opinion with no support whatsoever. You did nothing to refute that the number of ARM foundries has dropped dramatically. All you did is a character assassination routine on Dr. Wei who posted up a heck of a lot of real information as opposed to you posting absolutely no information. I didn't misrepresent anything. Anyone who looks at the slide will see that I just took information directly off the slide. Sure, go ahead and address the other 15 reasons why ARM's fabrication is toast. I look forward to further opportunities to expose you as a fraud who is not even conversant with basic fundamentals...] [PS. You said that Dr. Wei's information was not just fictitious - you said it was laughable. No one who looked at slide 27 is laughing - except at you...] [What has rapidly change in the semi business? Any more ARM foundries? Nope? Anybody making or selling FinFET? Nope. Any of them going to have FinFET any time soon? Nope? So, what is it that has changed???] [Once again you present Dr. Wei as credible and then attempt to throw him under the bus. You are the poster child for duplicious...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368649331376</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368649439006-187</Id><Topic><Title>Great for CSCO!</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1368648427734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm looking forward to it. Owning good, solid tech companies with good earnings has worked out for me :)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368649439006</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:23:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368650114090-188</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL DOWNGRADED $2 PRICE TARGET PC MARKET COLLAPSING</Title><Username>nasdaqczar2</Username><Timestamp>1365692696048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're the lowlife character that posts the same trash on the CSCO board as well.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368650114090</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:35:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368650254613-189</Id><Title>CSCO Climbing - 52 weeks high in after hours...</Title><Msg>BUY BUY BUY CSCO</Msg><Username>investorindividual</Username><Timestamp>1368650254613</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:37:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368650954974-190</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell is coming!</Title><Username>wallis_boll_weevil</Username><Timestamp>1368645702816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:21:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google is not that stupid.</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1368650954974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:49:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368651368826-191</Id><Topic><Title>Juhhny Chambers has a surprise for you homegamers after the close!</Title><Username>wallis_boll_weevil</Username><Timestamp>1368646733875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya really shoulda listened, Bozo.</Msg><Username>wallis_boll_weevil</Username><Timestamp>1368651368826</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:56:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368651542819-192</Id><Topic><Title>Juhhny Chambers has a surprise for you homegamers after the close!</Title><Username>wallis_boll_weevil</Username><Timestamp>1368646733875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like we should have listened when you bought traded Intel at 21 in 2010 for Csco at 21, watched Intel then spike to 29 as CSCO crashed to 14? LMAO! How's it feel to have to bury your precious Lucy alias, MUTT?</Msg><Username>lucy_mutt</Username><Timestamp>1368651542819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:59:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368651939129-193</Id><Title>Chambers Otellini</Title><Msg>A least he could move the stock 10% with a beat.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368651939129</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 17:05:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368652911200-194</Id><Title>Quanta Computer expects 2H13 notebook shipments to rise 50% from 1H13</Title><Msg>Quanta Computer expects its notebook shipments in the second half of 2013 to increase by 50% from the first half, company vice chairman CC Leung said at an investors conference on May 14</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1368652911200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 17:21:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368653471148-195</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[PS. You said that Dr. Wei's information was not just fictitious - you said it was laughable. No one who looked at slide 27 is laughing - except at you...] Not true, the presentation is fine. I said your interpretation of his presentation is laughable. The number of semiconductor manufacturers is absolutely decreasing but it is due to IDMs going fabless. It is not due to ARM Foundries decreasing. In fact your ARM Foundries label is laughable as there is no such thing. The two largest manufacturers of wafers with ARM IP inside are Samsung and TSMC and both of those companies just released PDK 0.5 for their FinFET processes. If history repeats it means FinFET tape-outs (PDK 1.0) are 6 months away, and FinFET production silicon is 1 year away. I keynoted an IEEE conference on FinFETs last month. People from TSMC, GF, ARM, QCOM, Xilinx, Intel, Oracle, Cadence, Synopsys, etc... were all there for two days of presentations and discussions. Just be open to the possibility that I may know more about FinFETs than you Mr Weaver. Now look at the final slide of Dr Wei's presentation where the girl kicks the guy in the testicles. That guy is you Wallis Weaver every time you try and talk about technology you know nothing about. So mark your calendar for Q1 2015 for another FinFET testicle kicking.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368653471148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 17:31:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368653517230-196</Id><Topic><Title>Juhhny Chambers has a surprise for you homegamers after the close!</Title><Username>wallis_boll_weevil</Username><Timestamp>1368646733875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 15:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nuff you don't have a clue what anybody here holds or for how long so kindly keep your bizarre alias cSucker shut.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368653517230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 17:31:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368654267620-197</Id><Topic><Title>Bad Sign for Microsoft as Dell Discounts Windows RT Tablet</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368631501979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:25:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember that the Metro interface (or what ever its called these days) is ISA neutral so if you are only are interested in Metro...The reality is that as soon as you give the option of the legacy UI (such as office) and not allow other legacy apps to go with it, you shoot yourself in the head. You confuse everyone:)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1368654267620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 17:44:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368658468712-198</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nenni is a fud. Was caught many times in the past lying including here.</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1368658468712</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 18:54:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368658681828-199</Id><Title>Intel-Cisco Foundry Deal bodes well for both. CSCO up 8.2$ AH</Title><Msg>on ER</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1368658681828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 18:58:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368659253802-200</Id><Topic><Title>Intel-Cisco Foundry Deal bodes well for both. CSCO up 8.2$ AH</Title><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1368658681828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 18:58:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm glad they are working together. It's a 2-way endorsement for these companies. However - I think you meant % instead of $ :-) Maybe by next year it will be up by $8.2..</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1368659253802</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 19:07:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368661856048-201</Id><Topic><Title>1 million ARMv8-A to my RECEIVING DOCK</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368626814908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. Using Calxeda as a baseline is a good idea. Most of the product breakdowns have the CPU chip price as the price from the foundry but do not seem to add in the burden of the developer. For a QCOM or NVDA, the staff can be amortized over a large number of chips. If a company wanted to build an ARM solution, they would want to have the volume needed to be sufficiently large that they could amortize the burden, like the $200mil, without being a dominant part of the cost.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368661856048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 19:50:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368662502132-202</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" In fact your ARM Foundries label is laughable as there is no such thing." [Really? Why doesn't ARM know? The clip below is from ARM's web site, dufus...] "The ARM Processor Foundry Program is an innovative business model that enables fabless semiconductor companies in emerging markets to gain access to ARM processor technology, for use in the design and manufacture of advanced system-on-chip (SoC) solutions." [So, there is an ARM Foundry Program but no ARM Foundries. LOL So, now you think the ARM web site is laughable. You just keep getting further and further into the tar pit. Have you even heard of the ARM Foundry Program?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368662502132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 20:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368663077155-203</Id><Title>How come no Analysts bad mouthed INTC today. Mr Weaver is here</Title><Msg>pumping this stock up, so it should have gone down. Oh well, there's always tomorrow.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1368663077155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 20:11:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368663313762-204</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The number of semiconductor manufacturers is absolutely decreasing but it is due to IDMs going fabless. It is not due to ARM Foundries decreasing. In fact your ARM Foundries label is laughable as there is no such thing." [Let's see now. An IDM going fabless means that they were doing fabs but no longer do fabs. So this means one less fab or foundry. In other words the number of foundries is decreasing. Thank you for proving my case. So, if you want to say that TSM and Samsung aren't ARM foundries, well then okay. But that would be really, really stupid....]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368663313762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 20:15:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368663544680-205</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I keynoted an IEEE conference on FinFETs last month. People from TSMC, GF, ARM, QCOM, Xilinx, Intel, Oracle, Cadence, Synopsys, etc... were all there for two days of presentations and discussions. Just be open to the possibility that I may know more about FinFETs than you Mr Weaver. Now look at the final slide of Dr Wei's presentation where the girl kicks the guy in the testicles. That guy is you Wallis Weaver every time you try and talk about technology you know nothing about. So mark your calendar for Q1 2015 for another FinFET testicle kicking." [Did you ever do any debating or ever take a logic course? If so you would know that you can't prove an argument by reputation, experience or character assassination. But that's all you ever do. You don't actually have the ability to mount an argument about whatever the issue is or at least you never have. This is why I will kick your rear end in every debate we ever have. You don't even understand the basic principles...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368663544680</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 20:19:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368663948450-206</Id><Topic><Title>Intel-Cisco Foundry Deal bodes well for both. CSCO up 8.2$ AH</Title><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1368658681828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 18:58:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many times has the Cisco deal been confirmed on this board, but nowhere else? 18? 20?</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1368663948450</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 20:25:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368664122198-207</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The two largest manufacturers of wafers with ARM IP inside are Samsung and TSMC and both of those companies just released PDK 0.5 for their FinFET processes. If history repeats it means FinFET tape-outs (PDK 1.0) are 6 months away, and FinFET production silicon is 1 year away." [The funniest part of this is the "if history repeats". ARM fabs don't have any FinFET history, butkus. They don't even have any 20nm planar history and half of the half-step ARM FinFET has to come from that. The projection of ARM having FinFET production in a year is so ludicrously non-believable that I'm surprised that your nose doesn't grow an extra yard every time you say it. ARM is years and years away from volume FinFET production. Stop with the lies already. ARM has a better chance of getting FinFET from aliens in a year than they do making it themselves...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368664122198</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 20:28:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368664889013-208</Id><Title>Google is giving a free Chromebook Pixel (with Intel Inside) to all I/O attendees</Title><Msg>Google has announced at I/O, its annual developer conference held in California, that everyone attending the first keynote this morning will receive a free Chromebook Pixel. Sundar Pichai, Google SVP of Chrome and Android, revealed the news on stage: “Our goal behind the Pixel was to literally to build the best laptop possible out there,” he said. “Do you have any idea why there’s one up on the screen and why I’m holding one in my hand?” At this point, the crowd goes into overdrive; it’s fair to say they knew what was coming next. “We are going to give each and every one of you a brand new Pixel – I’ve been told to say that it’s not ready until 2pm so please do’t leave int he middle of the keynote! But we’re very excited,” Pichai added. The Chromebook Pixel comes with a 12.85-inch high resolution IPS display (2560×1700), equal to 239 PPI, at a rather unorthodox 3:2 aspect ratio. Under the hood is an Intel Core i5 Ivy Bridge processor with Panter Point PCH, along with 4GB of DDR3 RAM. There’s only 32GB of storage via an SSD, but that’s bolstered by 1TB of additional cloud storage through Google Drive. Jealous yet? We are. From TNW</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368664889013</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 20:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368665047814-209</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[Let's see now. An IDM going fabless means that they were doing fabs but no longer do fabs. So this means one less fab or foundry. In other words the number of foundries is decreasing. Thank you for proving my case. So, if you want to say that TSM and Samsung aren't ARM foundries, well then okay. But that would be really, really stupid....] A Fab is not a foundry. Look it up. Or you can wait until my book "A Brief History of the Fabless Semiconductor Industry" is out this fall. There will be contributed sub chapters from TSMC, GF, ARM, Synopsys, Cadence, Mentor, and Xilinx. I will save you an autographed copy.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368665047814</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 20:44:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368665391354-210</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The ARM Processor Foundry Program is an innovative business model that enables fabless semiconductor companies in emerging markets to gain access to ARM processor technology, for use in the design and manufacture of advanced system-on-chip (SoC) solutions." [So, there is an ARM Foundry Program but no ARM Foundries. LOL So, now you think the ARM web site is laughable. You just keep getting further and further into the tar pit. Have you even heard of the ARM Foundry Program?] Seriously? That is laughable logic.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368665391354</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 20:49:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368665842977-211</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[The funniest part of this is the "if history repeats". ARM fabs don't have any FinFET history, butkus. They don't even have any 20nm planar history and half of the half-step ARM FinFET has to come from that. The projection of ARM having FinFET production in a year is so ludicrously non-believable that I'm surprised that your nose doesn't grow an extra yard every time you say it. ARM is years and years away from volume FinFET production. Stop with the lies already. ARM has a better chance of getting FinFET from aliens in a year than they do making it themselves...] The history of PDKs Wallis. A PDK is a process development kit which is what fabless companies use to design to a specific process. The first PDK to be released is version 0.1 which is very preliminary but useful for companies such as ARM, QCOM, Apple, etc... to start the design process. Next comes PDK 0.5 which companies can design to with an element of risk as process changes are still coming. PDK 1.0 people can design to with reasonable confidence future changes will be minor. So yes the status of PDKs is a good data point in judging when production silicon will start.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368665842977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 20:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368666297498-212</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"So yes the status of PDKs is a good data point in judging when production silicon will start." [Funny it didn't seem to help TSMC so many times in the past and in particular on 28nm. There have been articles documenting that the ramp times get longer and longer for ARM to reach the same yield as the nodes move to smaller sizes. This just means that 20nm will take longer to ramp and FinFET will take even longer. FinFET will have many unique problems and particularly because of the mating to the 20nm for the half-step. In short, predictions weren't good at 28nm and are likely to be worse at 20nm and even worse than that with FinFET.]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368666297498</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 21:04:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368666934466-213</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A Fab is not a foundry. Look it up." [From Wikipedia: A business that operates a semiconductor fab for the purpose of fabricating the designs of other companies, such as fabless semiconductor companies, is known as a foundry.] [From a presentation by Professor Ali Javey from Berkeley: Foundry (also called a fab for fabrication plant) is used to refer to a factory where devices like integrated circuits are manufactured.] [Maybe you should look this stuff up. You are the one who seems to be making it up as you go...] [Writing books now I see. No surprise as your consulting and web site work seem to be circling the drain...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368666934466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 21:15:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368670068518-214</Id><Topic><Title>Intel-Cisco Foundry Deal bodes well for both. CSCO up 8.2$ AH</Title><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1368658681828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 18:58:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh, it's passing.gas again. keep passing it.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368670068518</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 22:07:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368670371834-215</Id><Title>FinFETs still not ready for prime time</Title><Msg>Opinions/concerns expressed by ARM eco system The consensus among participants at the annual Synopsys User Group meeting is that FinFETs hold both promise and peril and are not yet ready for mainstream use. The 3D transistor structures coming at the 14nm node promise either performance increases or power consumption reductions of more than 60 per cent compared to today's 28nm process, according to a Globalfoundries technical executive. However, they increase gate capacitance on a per micron basis, raising a handful of old and new design issues, said others on the panel. FinFETs bring a 66 per cent increase in gate capacitance per micron compared to today's 28nm process, back up to the level of the 130nm planar node, said Anil Jain, vice president of IC engineering at Cavium Networks. Capacitance will limit both performance increases and dynamic power scaling for high-end chips, he said. "We have these beautiful [3D] transistors, but we can't run them too far," Jain said, noting "dynamic power [is] getting out of hand." In addition, "those of us in high performance devices have not seen much improvement in core voltage scaling," he said. Jain asked EDA vendors for tools that do a better job controlling switching power and isolating electro-migration faults. "FinFETs are not a no-brainer migration—at the end of the day we have to pay for it, so please don't blow up our costs," he added. Michael Campbell, a vice president of engineering in Qualcomm's chip design group, said FinFET structures in one foundry are "similar, but not the same" as those in another foundry. "You can only etch in certain directions and etch tools are common—that drives some similarities—but [foundries] use different in tricks in spatial walls and diffusion," he said. Campbell noted pictures of Intel's 22nm FinFETs show irregularly tapered walls that could impact planar fault models. "It takes new test technologies and incredibly deep partnerships to do design for test properly," he said.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368670371834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 22:12:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368670476854-216</Id><Topic><Title>FinFETs still not ready for prime time</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368670371834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 22:12:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In EDA, Synopsys "Yield Explorer is a great tool, but it still looks planar—it needs to evolve into a 3-D tool," he said. "Tools from Synopsys and others are woefully lacking in compressing a simple ATE pattern that can step backwards to find faults," he added. Jain and Campbell both expect to see some of the first 14 nm FinFET chips hit the market in late 2014 if the current issues get addressed. "I would say the processes are close to being ready but the design flows still need work," said Campbell. "Today we build [14nm FinFET] test chips with 20 million gates, but a commercial SoC may have is two billion gates," he said giving one measure of the work ahead. Joachim Kunkel, general manager of Synopsys' IP core group, provided another snapshot of the progress to date. His group taped out a 20nm test chip in April 2012 that showed working MIPI, PCI Express and USB interfaces using double patterning. A follow up 14nm chip was a simpler device mainly focused on memory, and has not yet come back from the fab. "The design parameters for FinFETs are very different from those of the planar nodes," Kunkel said. "The differences between the various FinFET processes available from the foundries today are significant enough that we have to start over [with IP development] each time," he said. "Also, most FinFET processes and design kits are still in the development phase, adding to the effort," he added. FinFETs "will drive a complete re-evaluation of your architecture—how you separate out devices and optimise them—it's a big change," Campbell said. Nevertheless, "the whole industry is trying to pull in the first generation of FinFETs in terms of time to volume," said Subramani Kengeri, vice president of design solutions at Globalfoundries.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368670476854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 22:14:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368670935595-217</Id><Topic><Title>FinFETs still not ready for prime time</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368670371834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 22:12:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the race to catch up with Intel's 22nm FinFET process, now in production, foundries have agreed to take two separate steps, he said. First they are tackling at 20nm the need for double patterning with 193nm lithography. Then they are adding 14nm FinFETs as "front end" devices in a node that still uses 20 nm "back end" interconnects, he said. Kyu-Myung Choi, senior vice president of Samsung's infrastructure design centre for logic, reiterated the Korean giant's promise to have a 14nm FinFET process ready for "risk production" by the end of 2013. Both Choi and Kengeri said work on the 14nm node is on track in terms of yields and performance. - Rick Merritt EE Times Another excellent article was published by SemiMD: Top Five Design and Manufacturing Challenges at 20nm . keep in mind Intel processed megatons of TriGate silicon - that's how complex and complicated technology gets "debugged" - Intel published a paperon reliability issues in regards to FinFet/TriGate - NOBODY in the world has this kind of info - a nice leverage to pick some foundry customers</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368670935595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 22:22:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368672539816-218</Id><Title>Whatever happend to google I/O catalyst.. LOL. Bark Bark Bark, thats what Mr Weaver</Title><Msg>does on this board.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1368672539816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 22:48:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368672750666-219</Id><Topic><Title>Intel-Cisco Foundry Deal bodes well for both. CSCO up 8.2$ AH</Title><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1368658681828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 18:58:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>unlike you with a constant constipation. lol oh my.</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1368672750666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 22:52:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368674323614-220</Id><Topic><Title>Whatever happend to google I/O catalyst.. LOL. Bark Bark Bark, thats what Mr Weaver</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1368672539816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 22:48:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess the same thing happened to it as happened to all your daily forecasts of 19, Dana. And as today demonstrated Intel didn't need it to move up. That's the bad news for you and the rest of the Intel bashers. Now Haswell is two weeks out and the short exit strategy has fallen apart. Back to the content-free posting for the shill drill team. What else do you have? Nada. Zip. Zilch...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368674323614</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 23:18:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>