<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359782138491-1</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People did not buy the iphone for the number of apps, rather for the ease of use. Windows 8 is coming at a time, when people are differentiating on the basis of apps. Times change.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359782138491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 00:15:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359789600143-2</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" I say BOO to INTC for trying to mandate what consumers should want." [You obviously don't get out much. Every company on the planet is doing some form of this. Have you ever heard of Apple? It took them what? Ten years to put a number pad on a keyboard?] "how many apps did AAPL have for the release of their 1st iphone?" [Apple was the first. Don't you think now that we've been shown how to do it that it shouldn't take so long now?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359789600143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 02:20:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359789788379-3</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The fact that you consider AngryBirds to be a 'big app' makes anything else you say a 'big joke'." [Angry Birds, Instagram and Facebook continued to be among the most downloaded apps of the year in 2012. The fact that you consider an app in the top three not to be a big app means you must not be able to dress and feed yourself... ]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359789788379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 02:23:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359789896229-4</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Unleashes Rack Server Design with Silicon Photonics Interconnections</Title><Username>wdgrowblaw</Username><Timestamp>1359771796976</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:23:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, Intel photonic racks! Cool...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359789896229</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 02:24:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359808008147-5</Id><Title>GOOD MORNING. Make some money. Go long Intel. Forget politics and go get some pretty loving.</Title><Msg>Winter still snowing on us but spring is coming soon. OK--you might be a blue kind of guy. Your nation--you scram to it--I want my country back. But your friends look at you and laugh and you know you like them and they are not going to be giving it back to you. You watched fox news and they told you for certain that the polls were wrong and the silent majority was going to rise up and defeat Obummer in a large landslide. Then election night, yo were watching Fox and Megan Kelly, that hot Irish girl, comes on and starts laughing at Rove. He is doing a meltdown like the brothers in the movie trading places. NO) NO--I demand another count--OHIO--NOOOOOOO. Megan walks down to the vote counters and asks them whether they are sure Ohio is going to Obummer and they say YES! You throw your beer to the ground and your phone starts ringing. it is your friends calling up to laugh at you. Well forget about it. Things have been plucked up in America ever since the year 2000. NO---you will not get rightwing neo Nazis elected and your GOP party is in meltdown, but your Intel Long has a very good chance to make you look smart again. Yeah--you are an idiot when it comes to political stuff but when your 40,000 shares of Intel go to 80, somehow nobody will be talking to you about political stuff anymore. Everyone knows you own those shares and they have called you an idiot for doing so countless times and still you never gave up the faith. Your leftwing #$%$ Intel long friends too have held on to Intel. NOW---Huge announcements will take Intel to levels not seen since the year 2000. Those chip shrinks and fabs do matter and that is what all Intel longs have kept as a faith all along. The way Intel tore AMD apart and destroyed it is the same way it will devastate Qualcomm and the others. Shrink it--make it in super fabs and sell it is VOLUME! Three years from now there will be two kinds of companies selling smart phones. Those who make money and have Intel CPUs inside their phones and those companies that have been destroyed in the phone markets. Tick Tock Tick Tock. YES---You were right Intel longs. Have a beer and smile.</Msg><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1359808008147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:26:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359809225832-6</Id><Topic><Title>GOOD MORNING. Make some money. Go long Intel. Forget politics and go get some pretty loving.</Title><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1359808008147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:26:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that would be a cool outcome. hope you're right. hope it isn't just more "magical thinking."</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1359809225832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:47:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359809493370-7</Id><Topic><Title>GOOD MORNING. Make some money. Go long Intel. Forget politics and go get some pretty loving.</Title><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1359808008147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:26:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you ever just say and read the #$%$ppp being written about Intel. No wonder it is trading so low. Intel is given virtually no chance of breaking into the phone and tablet markets. You are told by so called experts how it is impossible and Intel faces a slow meltdown because it is OLD! Even the net revenue and net profit is shrinking--not good. BUT enter 2013. Intel shrinks to 14 nm chips and then 10 nm chips in mid 2014. These chips turned into Full force phone chips with all the pretty add ons and all integrated in early 2014. If you were a maker of phones, what would you do? Would you keep your slower chips or switch to Intel. You see, because Intel does not care what you do. it will be selling the chips to makers of phones all over the planet in 2014 and in America the Google Motorola phones with Intel inside will be ripping into marketshare of the two big dogs, Apple and Samsung in phone sales. Yes--Intel wants them both but it is up to them. Same with Nokia--up to them. Intel will have its chips in the top selling phones in China and SE Asia early 2015. Its phones in Europe will have taken huge share by then too. Intel--like in the Field of Dreams movie--says--make them and they will come. Try and sell second rate trash for 800 dollars when benchmarks on a google phone show it killing you phones on all tests. Nexus and Motorola--both owned by Google---will take North America by storm. There is nothing Apple and Samsung can do to stop it. BUT--they can at least compete if they switch to Intel. The announcements are likely coming this year. Intel to 80.</Msg><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1359809493370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:51:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359812922857-8</Id><Topic><Title>I Have The Answer</Title><Username>lurlineviolette450</Username><Timestamp>1323872349000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2011-12-14 09:19:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting observation.</Msg><Username>henryjoshep</Username><Timestamp>1359812922857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 08:48:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359820619944-9</Id><Title>QCOM??? Will someone please explain how their biz plan lasts beyond 2013?</Title><Msg>They use someone else's design software and some else's fab. All this to make low performance chips. They seem to have "roadkill" scribed on their T-shirts to me. That doesn't stop Motley Fool from k-r-a-pppp-n out the usual sewage from their spleens.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1359820619944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 10:56:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359821169113-10</Id><Topic><Title>We sold all our shares at 20.00 today</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1354207408344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 11:43:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for those $20 shares. Great dividend and I think, great future !!</Msg><Username>htfdgbrwn9</Username><Timestamp>1359821169113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 11:06:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359824982666-11</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So according to you Angry Birds is essential to boost Win8 tablet sales? I thought assurances that MSOffice would be ported to Win8RT a much bigger factor for prospective buyers.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1359824982666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:09:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359824982723-12</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So according to you Angry Birds is essential to boost Win8 tablet sales? I thought assurances that MSOffice would be ported to Win8RT a much bigger factor for prospective buyers.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1359824982723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:09:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359825259234-13</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>APPL makes the end-product. INTC makes the chip that goes inside the end-product. Why should INTC have any say over how their chips are used by the companies making the end-products? Don't you think the OEMs know what consumers want? AAPL was the first to have applications running on a phone? Do you realize how stupid you sound saying that?</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1359825259234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:14:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359825704943-14</Id><Topic><Title>GOOD MORNING. Make some money. Go long Intel. Forget politics and go get some pretty loving.</Title><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1359808008147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 07:26:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SHORT INTC, THE ONLY WAY TO WIN HERE.</Msg><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359825704943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:21:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359825862723-15</Id><Title>One year chart INTC vs QCOM.....INTC -20% QCOM +15%</Title><Msg>INTC bagholders lose</Msg><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359825862723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:24:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359826208484-16</Id><Title>Qualcomm Crushes It in 2012 (LOL how did INTC do)</Title><Msg>Evaluating a company's Strengths, Weaknesses, Opportunities, and Threats (SWOT) allows us to develop a detailed picture of company's resources and competitive position in the market. Today, we take a look at chip maker Qualcomm (NASDAQ: QCOM), who's robust performance over the last three years has made it one of the most dominant names in Tech. Strengths OEM agnostic: Qualcomm chips are featured in iPhones, Galaxy IIIs, Nexus 4s, and Lumia 920s. No matter who wins – Apple, Samsung, Google, or Nokia – Qualcomm wins. Market Leader: Qualcomm chips are increasingly being deployed in high end devices, allowing it to seize a dominant share of the fast growing mobile components market. The company recently surpassed chipmaking legend Intel by market cap. High Volume: There are 300 million smart phone shipments coming up in 2013. Consistant Growth: Since 2005, Qualcomm's Market Cap has grown by +82%; Revenues have increased by +312%; EPS +177%, and Cash and ST Securities by +239%. War Chest: Qualcomm has $12.37 billion in cash and short term investments. Bumper Year: Record revenues, earnings and MSM chipset shipments driven by increasing global consumption of wireless data across a diverse range of devices, particularly smartphones. Revenues have increased +28% YoY, Non-GAAP EPS (+16%), MSM chip shipments (+22%), Total Reported Device Sales (+25%). Royalties: Qualcomm receives royalties on 1 billion-1.07 billion units. (And counting...) Emerging Markets: Emerging markets are increasingly shifting to content friendly 3G, which helped Q3 global smartphone shipments increase 44% TO 173.7 million units, according to Canalys. Since Qualcomm supplies the market leaders, this shift has given Qualcomm a big boost. Company forecasts 14% 3G/4G unit growth in 2013 Dividends/Buybacks: Since 2003, Qualcomm has returned $19.5 billion to stockholders. QCOM shares soared from around $19 to $63 per share in the same period. $2.5 billion in stock repurchases remain under the Board's current authorization. Qualcomm Crushes It in 2012 By Kyle Spencer - November 29, 2012 | Tickers: INTC, QCOM | 0 Comments Share on email Email Print Kyle is a member of The Motley Fool Blog Network -- entries represent the personal opinions of our bloggers and are not formally edited. Evaluating a company's Strengths, Weaknesses, Opportunities, and Threats (SWOT) allows us to develop a detailed picture of company's resources and competitive position in the market. Today, we take a look at chip maker Qualcomm (NASDAQ: QCOM), who's robust performance over the last three years has made it one of the most dominant names in Tech. Strengths OEM agnostic: Qualcomm chips are featured in iPhones, Galaxy IIIs, Nexus 4s, and Lumia 920s. No matter who wins – Apple, Samsung, Google, or Nokia – Qualcomm wins. Market Leader: Qualcomm chips are increasingly being deployed in high end devices, allowing it to seize a dominant share of the fast growing mobile components market. The company recently surpassed chipmaking legend Intel by market cap. (Source: Gartner, Company Data, Nomura Estimates) High Volume: There are 300 million smart phone shipments coming up in 2013. Consistant Growth: Since 2005, Qualcomm's Market Cap has grown by +82%; Revenues have increased by +312%; EPS +177%, and Cash and ST Securities by +239%. War Chest: Qualcomm has $12.37 billion in cash and short term investments. Bumper Year: Record revenues, earnings and MSM chipset shipments driven by increasing global consumption of wireless data across a diverse range of devices, particularly smartphones. Revenues have increased +28% YoY, Non-GAAP EPS (+16%), MSM chip shipments (+22%), Total Reported Device Sales (+25%). Royalties: Qualcomm receives royalties on 1 billion-1.07 billion units. (And counting...) Qualcomm Q4/2012 results vs. Q4/2011 (Source: Qualcomm IR) Emerging Markets: Emerging markets are increasingly shifting to content friendly 3G, which helped Q3 global smartphone shipments increase 44% TO 173.7 million units, according to Canalys. Since Qualcomm supplies the market leaders, this shift has given Qualcomm a big boost. Company forecasts 14% 3G/4G unit growth in 2013 Dividends/Buybacks: Since 2003, Qualcomm has returned $19.5 billion to stockholders. QCOM shares soared from around $19 to $63 per share in the same period. $2.5 billion in stock repurchases remain under the Board's current authorization. (Source: Qualcomm IR) Institutionally Owned: 82.60% of QCOM stock is held by Institutions. Weaknesses Supply bottlenecks: Qualcomm has had to trim it's Q4 estimates due to lack of supply of its 28 nm chips. Where AAPL goes, QCOM follows: Despite its platform agnosticism, Qualcomm's stock tends to exhibit a strong correlation with Apple's performance. Bellweather Stock: Qualcomm's stock price closely mirrors the market as a whole. Opportunities 1000x: Global mobile traffic roughly doubled from 2010-2011. The mobile industry is currently preparing for x1000 mobile traffic growth by 2020. This surge in volume which will require additional spectrum as well as infrastructure. Qualcomm is in an ideal position to provide the latter. 3G China: China's 3G subscribers only account for 19% of its total subscriber base. China's top 3 mobile service providers are currently adding 10 million+ 3G subscribers a month. Threats</Msg><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359826208484</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:30:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359826313225-17</Id><Title>Qualcomm a Winner in Mobile vs. PC Debate</Title><Msg>Qualcomm ( QCOM ), a leading CDMA chipset maker, sits at the center of a trend we see where traditional technology industry rivalries, such as AMD ( AMD ) vs. Intel ( INTC ) or AMD vs. nVidia ( NVDA ), are being overshadowed by the growing rivalry between mobile vs. PC. In the mobile vs. PC debate, the main drivers to a company's value are: 1) the size of the addressable market - or its "market opportunity" (number of chips sold x average price), and 2) the company's market share. We believe that prospects look brighter for companies in the mobile chipset business vs. those in the PC notebooks and desktop businesses, and we forecast that if Qualcomm can grow its market share to 75% from around 69% currently, this adds 11% to the current Trefis price estimate of $48.12 . Rising CDMA Penetration A Key Qualcomm's mobile chipset business is worth $35 billion, which is equal to 40% of Intel's notebook and desktop businesses combined and greater than our estimated values of nVidia and AMD combined - worth $6.7 and $5.6 billion respectively. Rising penetration of phones using CDMA technology, largely driven by emerging markets demand, is helping buoy Qualcomm's business. Qualcomm currently makes CDMA and WCDMA chips for cell phones competing with Texas Instruments ( TXN ), Infineon (PINK:IFFNY) and Broadcom (BRCM). We expect the number of CDMA chips sold to increase from 1.3 billion in 2010 to 1.8 billion by 2016, a 38% increase, and for pricing to stay relatively flat - from $16.30 to $15.30. This represents a 30% growth in market opportunity from $21 billion to nearly $28 billion. CDMA Mobile Chipset Market Catches up to PC Market The desktop business looks less attractive in the near term as we expect chip sales to increase from 136 million in 2010 to 139 million and for average prices to drop from $79.70 to $56.80 - a decrease in market opportunity of 27% from $10.8 billion to about $8 billion by 2016. For notebooks, we expect chip sales to increase from 177 million to 260 million and average prices should drop sharply from $101 to $81.50. This translates to a gain in market opportunity from about $18 billion to $21 billion, representing a healthy 18% climb but still smaller in market size and growth rate than Qualcomm's mobile business. This implies that the overall PC chipset market (desktops plus notebooks) is expected to remain about flat at around $29 billion over our forecast period while the mobile CDMA chipset market catches up, reaching $28 billion by the end of our forecast period. Upside from Higher Qualcomm Chipset Market Share If we assume Qualcomm can achieve 75% market share by 2016, similar to Intel's market share of PC chips, this adds 11% to the current price estimate. This would be a slight reversal from our current estimates and bring market share inline with 2007 levels. See our chart below.</Msg><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359826313225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:31:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359826479721-18</Id><Title>A Value Comparison Between Intel And Qualcomm</Title><Msg>Intel (INTC) stock has had a rough time of late, falling over 16% year to date and over 30% from its 52-week high of $29.27 set earlier this year. On top of that, Paul Otellini announced that he will be stepping down as CEO next year, creating even more uncertainty among shareholders. This all comes as the company faces intense pressure in its chip business from the mobile and tablet markets. Qualcomm (QCOM), which recently took away Intel's position as the world's largest chip maker, is leading the way with its smartphone chips. Qualcomm chips are in basically all mobile devices, ranging from the Google's (GOOG) Droid RAZR M to Nokia's (NOK) and Microsoft's (MSFT) Lumia 920. This loss in market share has resulted in a contracting of margins for Intel. Intel's margins, which used to be as high as 65%, are now averaging 55%. As more and more consumers make the move to mobile devices, PC sales will continue to decrease, which ultimately has negative effects on the overall revenue that Intel can realize. Qualcomm, on the other hand, currently is in a perfect position to capitalize on this move to mobile devices, and consequently has seen its margins continue to expand. Even though it already seems clear that Intel is not adapting to the times, it is rumored that the company is proposing the idea of supporting Apple (AAPL) with all of its ARM chips. With tensions currently high between Apple and Samsung Electronics Co., Intel is hoping to capitalize on this opportunity to increase overall market share and gain penetration into the mobile market. Unfortunately, the overall consensus from the analyst community is that the total impact to Intel's bottom line would be minimal.</Msg><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359826479721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:34:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359826593356-19</Id><Topic><Title>We sold all our shares at 20.00 today</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1354207408344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 11:43:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>smart move.</Msg><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359826593356</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:36:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359828312793-20</Id><Topic><Title>We sold all our shares at 20.00 today</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1354207408344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 11:43:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When you win, brag gently. When you lose, weep softly." ---- grandmother of Rep. James Clyburn of South Carolina</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359828312793</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:05:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359829697419-21</Id><Topic><Title>A Value Comparison Between Intel And Qualcomm</Title><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359826479721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:34:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some additional color .... "Qualcomm (QCOM), which recently took away Intel's position as the world's largest chip maker" Market cap. Intel is still 2x QCOM in revenues. A big chunk of revenues and bigger percentage of profits are from licensing and royaltys on QCOM IP. "This loss in market share has resulted in a contracting of margins for Intel. Intel's margins, which used to be as high as 65%, are now averaging 55%." Intel gross margings have been as high as 65%. Do the Intel gross margins look like they are "now averaging 55%"? Quarterly Gross Margin Dec. 31, 2012 58.00% Intel idled fabs to bring inventory back in line. Sept. 30, 2012 63.28% 30-Jun-12 63.36% 31-Mar-12 64.04% Dec. 31, 2011 64.46% Sept. 30, 2011 63.36% 30-Jun-11 60.64% 31-Mar-11 61.38% Dec. 31, 2010 64.64% Sept. 30, 2010 65.94% 30-Jun-10 67.21% 31-Mar-10 63.39% Dec. 31, 2009 64.72% Sept. 30, 2009 57.56% 30-Jun-09 50.84% 31-Mar-09 45.32% Intel paid the $1.45b EU fine out of cash flow, market bottom Dec. 31, 2008 53.11% Sept. 30, 2008 58.91% 30-Jun-08 55.43% 31-Mar-08 53.83% Results lower during financial crash</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359829697419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:28:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359830028308-22</Id><Title>Khan Gets One Year in Prison in Insider Trading Case (INTC needs this to keep above water) LOL</Title><Msg>Roomy Khan, the former Intel Corp. (INTC) executive twice convicted of passing illegal tips to Raj Rajaratnam, was ordered to serve one year in prison for obstructing justice after she agreed to help the U.S.</Msg><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359830028308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:33:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359830129311-23</Id><Title>Changes in the Chip Market (INTC doomed)</Title><Msg>With smartphone and tablet sales through the roof, and lagging laptop sales that don’t show signs of resurgence any time soon, some companies are taking the hit—namely, PC-chip companies. Advanced Micro Devices (NYSE: AMD), Texas Instruments (NASDAQ: TXN), and Intel (NASDAQ: INTC) all have bad news for investors: the fourth quarter numbers weren’t great. For many, this shouldn’t be a surprise. Now, let’s look at Intel. Fourth quarter profit numbers revealed a 27% slide, another sign of lagging PC demands. Formerly so successful due to their market dominance in the PC chip field, Intel is now in a bind and facing the question about what to do to adapt to the way of the world. A shift in consumer interest towards tablets and smartphones has sent Intel spiraling downwards. Hopes that Microsoft’s new Windows 8 devices would spur sales haven’t exactly followed through. Sales numbers for the new devices haven’t shown enough to revive the PC market for Intel. So, what now? Intel revealed that revenue from its PC chip division sank 6% from a year earlier, pulling down total revenue 3% at a time when the company usually releases its best results. Intel predicts a further 6% slide in the current quarter.</Msg><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359830129311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:35:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359830245887-24</Id><Title>AMD to take market share away from Intel.</Title><Msg>Intel has an 85% market share while AMD has only 15%. The PC market is slowing down fast and the PC makers will want to find a way to decrease cost. The best way to cut costs is to start using more AMD chips that work as well and much cheaper to push Intel to lower their costs. Either way, it is a lose for Intel. I am looking for the PC makers to start using more AMD chips and allowing AMD to gain market share away from Intel. It will be much easier for AMD to gain market share than for Intel to.</Msg><Username>yuorbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1359830245887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:37:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359830599248-25</Id><Title>STINKTEL SHARE PRICE UNCHANGED FOR 10 YEARS</Title><Msg>Stinktel is a stock that only a mother, and/or Wallis, could love. HI-HO WEAVERINO!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1359830599248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:43:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359831976817-26</Id><Topic><Title>One year chart INTC vs QCOM.....INTC -20% QCOM +15%</Title><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359825862723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:24:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It gets worse if you do a 2 year 5 year and max on the charts. QCOM just kicks INTC butt as far as return to shareholders.</Msg><Username>panting_lustre</Username><Timestamp>1359831976817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 14:06:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359831989556-27</Id><Topic><Title>AMD to take market share away from Intel.</Title><Username>yuorbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1359830245887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:37:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmm... IDC forecasts don't match your statements. Per IDC: "tabletop [desktop] computer unit sales are projected to grow 1.2% between 2012 and 2016." "Laptop sales are sailing towards perky 31% unit growth over the next four years" Hardly dead. Mature market? Yep. Will they need some network and remote storage support (servers)? Yep. WIll some of these system be AMD? Yep Will most be Intel? Yep. Does IDC think the "PC is Dead" ? Nope. IDC projections for PC and laptop sales look extremely weird – again Dec. 11, 2012 10:35 AM IDC published a new report on connected devices this week. It was largely devoid of surprises, but one very strange aspect of IDC’s forecasting immediately popped out: Once again, IDC is projecting PC and laptop growth that is cheerfully out of sync with everything we know is happening in the computer industry. In IDC’s wacky world, tabletop computer unit sales are projected to grow 1.2% between 2012 and 2016. Laptop sales are sailing towards perky 31% unit growth over the next four years. Sure enough, tablet sales are projected to grow by 131% during the same time period — but IDC tells us that in 2016, tablet sales are going to beat laptop sales by just 14 million units: 283 million vs. 269 million. With $200 tablets already to proliferate in 2013, is there anyone in the real world who actually believes this? Last March, IDC published a note trumpeting that it expects “desktop, laptop sales to take off in the second half of 2012.” In October, Gartner noted that global PC sales volume actually declined by a staggering 8% in the third quarter of 2012. Nasty warnings by key PC suppliers like AMD and Intel have devastated their share price even as the NASDAQ posted healthy gains in 2012. Anyone trusting IDC’s forecasts about the PC and laptop markets is missing one of the most obvious and clear trends the consumer electronics industry has seen in decades. Tablet sales are in the process of demolishing laptop unit growth and dealing a fair amount of damage to tabletop PC sales as well. In the U.S. market, the ground zero for the tablet phenomenon, PC unit sales crashed by an astonishing 14% during the third quarter this year compared to autumn of 2011. Of course, this was the eve of the Windows OS upgrade. But the idea that the PC market is just hitting a temporary speed bump and is about to return to rude health seems truly bizarre. Yet somewhere in the IDC headquarters, this is the baseline scenario that underpins the entire global modeling of connected device sales for the next half a decade. People blaming major research houses for always playing it safe should keep this in mind: IDC is going out on a limb like a squirrel on meth with its core industry prediction.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359831989556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 14:06:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359838921854-28</Id><Topic><Title>One year chart INTC vs QCOM.....INTC -20% QCOM +15%</Title><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359825862723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:24:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet I can #$%$ farther &amp; longer than you can.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1359838921854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:02:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359839108805-29</Id><Topic><Title>AMD to take market share away from Intel.</Title><Username>yuorbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1359830245887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:37:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Why did Intel give a statement at the CC indicating the PC sales are expected to continue slowing down. I believe 6% for Q1 2013. " Q1 is only part of 2013. Q3 and Q4 are holiday seasons and a number of purchasers will be delaying until Haswell is released during the year. "It will be easier for AMD to take market share away from Intel and Nvidia" "This is already happening with AMD landing the new Wii U, PS4 &amp; Xbox 720." Intel is not in the Wii, PS4 nor Xbox. That did not take any market share from Intel. If the game consoles take market share from PC's, then these AMD design wins will do two things. They will cannibalize some AMD PC sales and some Intel PC sales. Do you think that the cannibalization will take place at the LOW end of the PC market (AMD) or do you think that it will take place at the HIGH end (Intel)? Businesses will not replace PC's with Wii consoles. At least I know that the company I work for will not. I hope that AMD survives as an independent company. They have stumbled badly several times recently. Intel will have to help for them to survive. AMD credit rating was downgraded 3 levels recently. The cost of money for them is much higher now and cash will be tight for some time. Congrats on the design wins they will help.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359839108805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:05:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359841349088-30</Id><Topic><Title>STINKTEL SHARE PRICE UNCHANGED FOR 10 YEARS</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1359830599248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:43:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one will ever get rich simply buying and holding a semi stock, those heady days are long gone. Fine to trade, deplorable investments. Poor souls who bght at the height of the pc chip cycle in 2004 at 34 are still underwater,</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1359841349088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:42:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359843450643-31</Id><Title>Smartphones and tablets are already at $99 at Bestbuy and Walmart.</Title><Msg>These will be coming down even further in the next few months. Other than Apple, all vendors won't make very much $$ on smartphones and tablets. Intel's low priced smartphone should sell for $69 by Christmas in India.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359843450643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:17:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359844440605-32</Id><Topic><Title>Smartphones and tablets are already at $99 at Bestbuy and Walmart.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359843450643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:17:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>then poor AMD...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1359844440605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 17:34:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359846235244-33</Id><Title>WHERE'S WALLIS TODAY???</Title><Msg>Maybe he saw his shadow this morning! TOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1359846235244</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 18:03:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359846848336-34</Id><Title>Dell going private on Monday - not good for Intel</Title><Msg>Dell wants to get out of the consumer PC business &amp; focus just on IT services. Now, they can do it without worrying about their shares going to single digits. A real CEO would have made Intel a brander PC retailer by now. Paul O. has been a joke. Always reactive &amp; 2-steps late.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1359846848336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 18:14:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359847123400-35</Id><Topic><Title>Dell going private on Monday - not good for Intel</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1359846848336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 18:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Smart move for M Dell. He knows that his company is severly undervalued. So is Intel and most PC companies. The Wall St perception, is that the PC is dead. Thats not true. 10" tablets are dead, and convertibles will take its place. Intel's growth is in servers, not PC's.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1359847123400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 18:18:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359852730679-36</Id><Title>Can new dual-core Medfields be used for Android tablets?</Title><Msg>Pros / Cons anyone?</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359852730679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 19:52:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359854034545-37</Id><Topic><Title>Dell going private on Monday - not good for Intel</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1359846848336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 18:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"..A real CEO would have made Intel a brander PC retailer by now " ---------------------------------------------------------------------------- backbay, do you think a little before you spew your posts ? It's good that you are not running any company much easier to be a paid shil isn't it. lol</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1359854034545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 20:13:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359854676315-38</Id><Topic><Title>One year chart INTC vs QCOM.....INTC -20% QCOM +15%</Title><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359825862723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:24:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>para, you forget the huge dividend intel was giving all these years compound that and then get back to us.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1359854676315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 20:24:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359854829545-39</Id><Topic><Title>Dell going private on Monday - not good for Intel</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1359846848336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 18:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>backbay has my vote as the most whining after the fact spineless poster to grace the INTC board.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1359854829545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 20:27:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359855581860-40</Id><Topic><Title>Surface RT plagued by high return rates, slow sales</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359758536051</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:42:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>imo, 680,000-750,000 is not so bad under the circum stances. Penetrating a mature market is never easy, Microsoft will do much better with Surface Pro for sure. As for the learning curve, it's true; just the same, what ever you can do with iPad UI you can easily do with the Surface and more since Surface is more sophisticated UI with more options (charms for example ) .</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1359855581860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 20:39:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359855938269-41</Id><Title>dell going private would be good for intel</Title><Msg>it will show how undervalued intel is</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1359855938269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 20:45:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359856322326-42</Id><Topic><Title>One year chart INTC vs QCOM.....INTC -20% QCOM +15%</Title><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359825862723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:24:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you asked: LOL 12/16/1991 QCOM was $0.47 split and dividend adjusted...now $66.73. 12/16/1991 INTC was $1.10 split and dividend adjusted now $21.36 Need I say more ???? Have a nice weekend bagholder.</Msg><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359856322326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 20:52:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359858672331-43</Id><Topic><Title>One year chart INTC vs QCOM.....INTC -20% QCOM +15%</Title><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359825862723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:24:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Over the lifetime of both companies INTC has gone up twice as much with the peak in Y2K being eight times as much. A visual integration of the comparison shows four times as much appreciation on average. Although sluggish since Y2K INTC has clearly returned more money to its shareholders than QCOM. You do also know that Atom is going to Snap your Dragons in half as each year goes by and this will negatively affect QCOM price in the future ;-) googleDOTcom/finance?chdnp=1&amp;chdd=1&amp;chds=1&amp;chdv=1&amp;chvs=maximized&amp;chdeh=0&amp;chfdeh=0&amp;chdet=1359857931531&amp;chddm=3538550&amp;chls=IntervalBasedLine&amp;cmpto=NASDAQ:QCOM&amp;cmptdms=0&amp;q=NASDAQ:INTC&amp;ntsp=0&amp;ei=1MgNUcGrMIOPwAPzZw</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359858672331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 21:31:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359858909336-44</Id><Topic><Title>One year chart INTC vs QCOM.....INTC -20% QCOM +15%</Title><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359825862723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:24:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>p.s. forgot to post the numbers for those who can't be bothered to look at the graph ... INTC +854,100% i.e. 8541 times QCOM +379,048% i.e. 3790 times</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359858909336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 21:35:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359861216416-45</Id><Topic><Title>Can new dual-core Medfields be used for Android tablets?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359852730679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 19:52:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huge batteries</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359861216416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 22:13:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359861660857-46</Id><Topic><Title>Can new dual-core Medfields be used for Android tablets?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359852730679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 19:52:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, for a 2W chip ?! In your dreams ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359861660857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 22:21:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359861824393-47</Id><Topic><Title>Can new dual-core Medfields be used for Android tablets?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359852730679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 19:52:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has the cpu performance of an iPad4 and the gpu performance of an iPad3 at the power consumption of an iPad2. What's not to love ? ;-)</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1359861824393</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 22:23:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359863184086-48</Id><Topic><Title>One year chart INTC vs QCOM.....INTC -20% QCOM +15%</Title><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359825862723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:24:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Need I say more ???? Have a nice weekend bagholder." [Why yes, PL (parabolic_lover), you could have said more - you could have shared some of your previous posts like the one below. It clearly indicates that you got burned on Qualcomm saying things like, "Where's the bottom. I need to get that money back fast and shorting looks like the only way."] [Maybe you still are trying to get that money back. LOL But one things for sure. You're no genius, Gump...] Prior post: QCOM Down Toilet: What? by parabolic_lover "What's going on? Is Q going to tank? Is this a good time to short again? It's had a fearce runup and you're still making bucks here. Can I get back the $$ from that $360 maneuver that cubicle recommended? Where's the bottom. I need to get that money back fast and shorting looks like the only way. Help! You're the only short that makes sense that's still here. What do you predict? Where's the top? bottom?"</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359863184086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 22:46:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359863729079-49</Id><Title>Notice the Qualcomm Fanbois</Title><Msg>Notice that the Qualcomm fanbois never talk about fabrication and that the ARM roadmap ends after the not-ready-for-prime time 20nm planar, which might be here in 2014/2015. The gap after ARM 20nm looks like the Grand Canyon as the ARM world prepares to sail into the fabrication abyss... Intel FinFET: the game changer</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359863729079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 22:55:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359864850873-50</Id><Topic><Title>STINKTEL SHARE PRICE UNCHANGED FOR 10 YEARS</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1359830599248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:43:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And tooofunny has been and absolute jerkoff for 20</Msg><Username>sanjitkumar23</Username><Timestamp>1359864850873</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:14:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359866806157-51</Id><Topic><Title>One year chart INTC vs QCOM.....INTC -20% QCOM +15%</Title><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359825862723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:24:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL check the ggraph, tell me who is on top, it ain't INTC LOL glad you liked my old posts. ahahhahhahaha U R the bagholder. http://finance.yahoo.com/q/bc?s=INTC&amp;t=my&amp;l=on&amp;z=l&amp;q=l&amp;c=qcom</Msg><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359866806157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:46:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359866965307-52</Id><Topic><Title>One year chart INTC vs QCOM.....INTC -20% QCOM +15%</Title><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359825862723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 12:24:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>check the chart, tell me who is on top, it ain't INTC bagholder. Glad you enjoyed my OLD posts. Since then I bought QCOM at about 13.60 in 2003 now it's 66+ sorry the same CAN'T be said for INTC. Looks like the death spiral for you guys. ahhahhahahhahhahhaha</Msg><Username>parabolic_lover</Username><Timestamp>1359866965307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:49:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>