<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367729194547-1</Id><Topic><Title>Two BIG announcements on Monday!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367719837761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 22:10:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope all this seriously deflates ARMH stock. That stock is one inflated piece of #$%$.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367729194547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 00:46:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367732269451-2</Id><Topic><Title>Battery life of Motorola Razr M.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367694536817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just checked the talk time. Talked about 34 minutes and it used up between 5% to 6% of battery life. That comes to about 10 to 11 hours talk time. So already the 20 hour is exagerrated. As for 17 days standby time. Who really cares? People don't get smartphones to do nothing for a period of hours, let alone days, let alone over 2 weeks. Not even worth mentioning that efficiency. What's interesting is that surf time was not in specs at best buy website. I'm testing that now by watching a youtube video.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367732269451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 01:37:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367732533855-3</Id><Title>Always remember to take some profits before they are gone, Profits go away very very fast</Title><Msg>Always remember to take some profits before they are gone, Profits go away very very fast</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367732533855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 01:42:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367732733048-4</Id><Topic><Title>Two BIG announcements on Monday!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367719837761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 22:10:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>May 6: Intel to announce Silvermont - Buzz should last all year There will be Intel customers of the new Bay Trail that will also be announcing new products at the Intel webcast.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367732733048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 01:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367733194949-5</Id><Topic><Title>Battery life of Motorola Razr M.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367694536817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watching youtube, during 15 minutes of video, battery drained by 5% to 6%. That's about 4 to 5 hours of streaming video with a full charge. I also remember in the past doing some surfing the net and playing some video games. That was causing the quickest drain of battery for me at about 1% a minute. That's less than 2 hours on a full charge.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367733194949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 01:53:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367735612189-6</Id><Topic><Title>Always remember to take some profits before they are gone, Profits go away very very fast</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367732533855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 01:42:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also, always remember to limit your losses to what you can emotionally and financially tolerate. It seems like your position in Intel has exceeded your loss limits. I truly hope that everything that you have cast upon the water, returns to you and your family many times multiplied.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367735612189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 02:33:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367737686106-7</Id><Topic><Title>Battery life of Motorola Razr M.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367694536817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sweetheart, you could have been more helpful. If a phone is draining that much there is a problem, either a hardware fault (return it and get it replaced) or a badly behaved app. Check the battery meter app and it'll tell you where the power is being used.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367737686106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 03:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367739187694-8</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The cross OS/Cross architecture is one of the big points of geekbench:) Yes, there is an issue using the single number to compare, especially when the number of threads/cores is different. As all the numbers are available you can drill down and compare single threaded results and do real like-for-like. As for Malloc and family on windows 8 - I've no idea - but I do know these tests do show how poor ARM SoC's memory io can be:) There are scores for other Saltwell based SoCs on Android (Z2480 Z2460) and they should have the same memory io interfaces, so you can see if the memory scores are better. What benchmark do you suggest we use instead of geekbench?:)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367739187694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 03:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367740305922-9</Id><Title>Sell in May and go away? Mr Weaver and his other personalities are here</Title><Msg>punmping, so it should go down.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1367740305922</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 03:51:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367752437305-10</Id><Title>PC market decreasing?</Title><Msg>Is the decline impacting Intel? For the most part analysts we have rated highly have recommended a Hold currently. Do you agree? which recommendation is best to follow?</Msg><Username>tipranks2</Username><Timestamp>1367752437305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 07:13:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367752850866-11</Id><Topic><Title>PC market decreasing?</Title><Username>tipranks2</Username><Timestamp>1367752437305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 07:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes it is and they are trying to hide their numbers behind highly technology focused product announcements. But they have no solution to the eroding market size of PCs. Sell is the best recommendation.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367752850866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 07:20:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367756127632-12</Id><Topic><Title>PC market decreasing?</Title><Username>tipranks2</Username><Timestamp>1367752437305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 07:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The recent figures are misleading as netbooks were lumped into the PC market when really they were the ancestor of the tablet market and really should have be lumped into that market all along. Atoms are now sold as tablets rather than netbooks often with optional keyboards which fundamentally still makes them a netbook but of course that now means they are no longer registered as a PC sale. This reporting anomaly will disappear next year. p.s. like the way your INTC sentiment flips from bearish to bullish back to bearish depending whether you are long or short at the time. Cute and not in a good way as it exposes you as fundamentally unprincipled and lacking any real conviction or belief either way.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367756127632</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 08:15:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367757294176-13</Id><Topic><Title>PC market decreasing?</Title><Username>tipranks2</Username><Timestamp>1367752437305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 07:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're confusing the issue with terminology</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367757294176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 08:34:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367758382431-14</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Getting results across OS/architectures is a strong point. Anyone can download and run it, independent of what else is running on their system. The problem is that a benchmark result is a "proxy" for something else. If the score of one machine is 2x another machine, what does it mean? Since geekbench runs a different number of tests on the x86 than ARM, how are the extra tests combined? Does x86 see a benefit or a penalty? I don't know of any benchmark that can be used to compare across OS (stdclib type problems) nor 32-bit versus 64-bit nor CPU architecture where the workloads are different. I will probably whine about this and I appreciate your civil response. IMO, the general model that I have "today" is: ARM is generally faster on FP x86 32-bit is slower because of low number of registers x86_64 alleviates register problem and usually bus width problem. When my preconceived model is violated, I go digging. Just like you do. 8-) BTW, did you get to see the thermal die photos? Search for phrase below and it shows some of the results of Intel's work in power reduction posted on hothardware. I love those thermal die photos that show the die is COLD blue. Thermal images are of Clover Trail, Intel 32nm SoC in active and standby states</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367758382431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 08:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367759737209-15</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>March 25, 2013, 3:03 P.M. ET ARMH: Pondering the 64-Bit Server Future Email Print smaller Larger By Tiernan Ray ARM Holdings (ARMH) director of marketing Ian Thornton was in town today and was kind enough to stop by the Barron’s offices. We talked a bit about one of the next substantial frontiers for the company and its partners, 64-bit memory addressing, which is most likely to show up in server and equipment products, although Thornton also had some thoughts on 64-bit in mobile devices, which you can read in an earlier post. ARM’s 64-bit architecture is coming with the “Cortex A50” series, which now exists in microprocessor designs designated “A53″ and “A57.” To give you a sense of the timeline, licenses started to be signed with partners two years ago, and ARM has only lately “taped out” its first microprocessor designs. “They’ve gotten to the Verilog stage, but they’re not quite at the Netlist stage at this point,” says Thornton. That would imply first samples of chips from partners sometime toward the end of this year, with volume production in 2014, notes Thornton. The leading partners signed so far are startup Calxeda, ST-Microelectronics NV (STMPR), Broadcom (BRCM), Samsung Electronics (005930KS), and the semiconductor design unit of China’s Huawei, which makes equipment in addition to mobile devices. There will be a cost and a power savings from the up-front price of these devices as well as the performance they enable in servers and equipment, said Thornton. At this point, though, it’s difficult to quantify all that relative to Intel (INTC) Xeon server processors or Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) Opteron parts because none of the partners has produced a part yet. X86 rules the majority of volume of server shipments today. (Mind you, AMD is also in the ARM camp, see below.) One can make an analogy to Intel‘s “Atom” chip for mobile devices, in comparison to ARM-based smartphone chips based on the “Cortex A9” style parts. Atom takes three times the number of transistors to implement functional blocks that perform similar workloads, a sign of being less efficient than ARM-based designs, for example, contends Thornton. And the Intel x86 architecture uses the “variable length instruction word” approach, making it harder to streamline aspects of what are “monolithic” server processors, in his words. But “that’s just an analogy,” and not really a fair comparison until 64-bit silicon appears, says Thornton. His larger point about the competition between Intel and AMD and ARM partners is that the Intel server world is monolithic in its overall approach. “Today, in some cases, you’ve got just 10% of Xeon being used” in a server, contends Thornton, because the bottleneck is in other parts of the system. If, for example, a server is doing streaming video, and it is mostly passing through bits from an external memory system, then between the time waiting for those bits to come off of a wire, and sending them out to the Internet, the microprocessor itself may not have a lot of work to do. That, says Thornton, suggests that it may be possible for the entire collection of partners — there are 17 licensees of 64-bit ARM, and parties such as Nvidia (NVDA) have talked about getting into servers in a big way — could provide specialized parts that fit the job for different kinds of servers. “It’s almost like an application-specific integrated circuit [ASIC],” quipped Thornton, although in that sense it seems more like an “application specific standard product [ASSP],” I suggested, though in reality such a system-on-a-chip(SOC) might not really be either. Of course, there remain those niggly little details: Software. That huge chunk of the server market running on x86 still uses a lot of legacy applications, such as back-office financial software, even though some workloads have shifted to newer Internet-style applications. Thornton says that when customers tell large application providers such as SAP AG (SAP) or Oracle (ORCL) that they want to run their apps on an ARM-based server, the natural response from the software giants might be “What’s in it for me?” when it comes to all the expense involved in porting software to ARM. Still, he thinks that “eventually everyone comes together to do what’s right for the industry,” which, in ARM’s view, includes moving to ARM processors, obviously. Notes Thornton, there is the open-source software project called Linaro, involving upward of 200 engineers from ARM and its partners, that is helping to standardized Linux for ARM in a variety of contexts, including networking and other equipment. ARM shares today are up $1.35, or 3.4%, at $41.45. Update: Note that I failed to mention above that AMD is also making a push into ARM-based server chips. The company last year bought micro-server designer SeaMicro and has talked extensively about its intentions for ARM-based systems.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1367759737209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 09:15:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367760314215-16</Id><Title>INTEL CAN HYPE 14nm but INTEL Business Model Monoply has dismantled by ARMH forever</Title><Msg>MY TRADING Range now tweaked ( $24.50 --$19.50) Old range here was $23-$18 It is not technology but business model. ARM design core only. ARM CPU suppliers design products of the same core thus limited differentiation - price war. If you are a device maker, do you like a CPU supplier listen to you or one never learned to appease its customers (only customers to appease it). Also, INTC's huge overhead on R&amp;D, etc. plus bureaucracy accumulated during its hey days work strongly against it in this environment. People arguing on technical front is like those arguing whether AAPL or GOOG comes with better technology. GOOG wins not on GOOG's technologies but on business model. Samsung fight with AAPL? no matter what, ARM get license fee. -------------- The problem with going to lower nm size is leakage and below 14nm becomes a serious problem, they are rushing and it won't be good. I would not be suprised if Intel would not able to solve 14nm problems in next 5 years since there are a lot of problems involving it. ARM won't die, it does things that Intel does not and since AMD has ARM license now we can expect some amazing products that will hurt Intel. AMD has reserved 28nm fabs from TSMC. Favoring Intel is just criminal, they destroyed the industry with their bribery and rebates. Market is oversaturated with their "high end" products that only yearly give just 10% of improvement. ARM won't be doomed, it seems so called "brokers" and other people yell the same thing as they did with AMD. That is going to die and still AMD din't died and will again give a deserved smack to Intel. When AMD starts getting cash from consoles and other products that they produce I would not be suprised if they buy Zilog or ARM its self, maybe both of them.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1367760314215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 09:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367760709046-17</Id><Topic><Title>Khitchdee's greatest hits, in Chronological order</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367681543194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:32:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great posts, Khitchdee. We agree that Intel is a beast.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367760709046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 09:31:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367760812950-18</Id><Topic><Title>PC market decreasing?</Title><Username>tipranks2</Username><Timestamp>1367752437305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 07:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Khitchdee has no morals, hahaha.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367760812950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 09:33:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367764104061-19</Id><Topic><Title>Acer W700 with Dual Boot (Android 4.2.2 and Windows 8)</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367701936840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:12:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Acer product illustrates my point. When consumers can purchase a tablet that gives them access to both Windows and Android and their respective app ecosystems, hardware benchmarks become less relevant to the purchase decision. Dual boot is an immediate recognizable difference between Intel and ARM based tablets that buyers can understand. Now when the Intel products also deliver the best performing hardware and battery life consumer expectations for tablets will have been reset to what Intel offers. Single OS tablets with limited flexibility will move to the discount table.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367764104061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 10:28:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367765913418-20</Id><Topic><Title>Always remember to take some profits before they are gone, Profits go away very very fast</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367732533855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 01:42:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>coinmaker77, feel sorry for you man. Think of your family and cover now before INTC shoots to $40</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367765913418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 10:58:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367766028824-21</Id><Title>coinmaker77, REMEMBER YOUR FAMILY IS COUNTING ON YOU, COVER BEFORE INTC SHOOTS TO $40</Title><Msg>Coinmaker77, remember your family is counting on you, cover before intc shoots to $40</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367766028824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367766832607-22</Id><Topic><Title>Acer W700 with Dual Boot (Android 4.2.2 and Windows 8)</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367701936840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:12:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is Intel's own nightmare Move to $30 SoC and hurt its own $100 Processor business?LoL Revenue must decline at Intel in coming years and margins too Intel is now growth stock.....4% dividend yield is must range bound $24.50- $19.50 in 2013 2nd half 2014 we wi break down .........ARMH 64Bit Server SoC commodity suppliers flood the markets</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1367766832607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:13:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367768076787-23</Id><Topic><Title>Acer W700 with Dual Boot (Android 4.2.2 and Windows 8)</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367701936840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:12:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>7" tablets (and smartphones and fabbing) are icing on the cake fool. Revenue could double now that intel enters these new markets.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367768076787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:34:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367768389459-24</Id><Title>INTEL GROSSLY UNDERVALUED, REVENUE COULD DOUBLE IN NEXT 2 YEARS</Title><Msg>SMARTPHONES, SMALL TABLETS, FABBING, INTEL TV. These are all new markets for Intel. Intel is taking advantage of their manufacturing process for PC &amp; server businesses in order to fund these new businesses - great advantage. REVENUE CAN DOUBLE when Intel makes great inroads into these new markets</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367768389459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367768942939-25</Id><Title>Wallis, Ashraf, will there be fireworks?</Title><Msg>You have extolled the grandeur of the launch of Silvermont. Will I see the evening sky illuminated by a brilliant star? Or will this be a peut on a windy day?</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367768942939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:49:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367768993465-26</Id><Topic><Title>Acer shows off Aspire P3 Ultrabook, Aspire R7 laptop with innovative designs</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367698849354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:20:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THE PC IS EVOLVING. These new form-factors with touch, two-for-ones (hybrids), 7" tablets All these devices coming into the market will finally make investors and ANALyst realize this fact: THE PC IS EVOLVING, not dead. SENTIMENTS WILL CHANGE. $40 by end of year.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367768993465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:49:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367769194896-27</Id><Topic><Title>Two BIG announcements on Monday!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367719837761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 22:10:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ACTUAL PRODUCTS IS REALLY WHAT'S IT'S ALL ABOUT. SENTIMENTS WILL CHANGE TOWARDS INTC once people see the actual products</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367769194896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:53:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367769206378-28</Id><Topic><Title>Acer shows off Aspire P3 Ultrabook, Aspire R7 laptop with innovative designs</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367698849354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:20:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But it says on Motley Fool that the PC is dead? How can that be?</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367769206378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367769406254-29</Id><Title>Just one bad market day and the stock price will tumble</Title><Msg>5-10%. There is nothing holding up the price except for general market conditions.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367769406254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:56:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367769595408-30</Id><Topic><Title>Just one bad market day and the stock price will tumble</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367769406254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:56:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I recommend you cover early monday morning before the silvermont announcement. Intc could go parabolic after that. Parabolic.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367769595408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:59:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367769702027-31</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL GROSSLY UNDERVALUED, REVENUE COULD DOUBLE IN NEXT 2 YEARS</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367768389459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:39:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTEL'S SILVERMONT ANNOUNCEMENT on Monday could signal the beginning of major upturn for INTC. $40 by end of year.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367769702027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367769852529-32</Id><Topic><Title>Just one bad market day and the stock price will tumble</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367769406254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:56:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah...just like it did on Thursday and Friday. Those were two of the strongest rally days of 2013 and INTC went up a few pennies. No excuses. This is a laggard.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367769852529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:04:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367769914019-33</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL GROSSLY UNDERVALUED, REVENUE COULD DOUBLE IN NEXT 2 YEARS</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367768389459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:39:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Could"...that says it all.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367769914019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:05:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367769949852-34</Id><Topic><Title>Two BIG announcements on Monday!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367719837761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 22:10:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know, I actually don't mind it at all. I know that one day, at some even more absurdly high pps ARMH will crash and burn. I want it to be clear at that point that INTC did it to them. I would never get into a short on something like this. I remember friends who lost their panties in Snapple shorts. Eventually Newton's Law "what goes up.." does apply, but you simply can't predict it and few people have the nerves of steel needed to bet against the house for a sustained period of time. I think even INTC could catch a major updraft and see $100 in a few years. I hope I am not as stupid as I usually am and just keep holding when that happens. Newton's Law will one day catch up with INTC too.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367769949852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:05:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367770027119-35</Id><Title>itakebackmyapology, singhlion2001, coinmaker77 - ALL THE SAME PERSON</Title><Msg>itakebackmyapology, singhlion2001, coinmaker77 - ALL THE SAME PERSON</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367770027119</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367770317533-36</Id><Topic><Title>Just one bad market day and the stock price will tumble</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367769406254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:56:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC has been up 13 out of the last 14 trading days fool. Way out performing the market. ready paul.otellini post for more info</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367770317533</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:11:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367770388135-37</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, Ashraf, will there be fireworks?</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367768942939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the Silvermont technical details won't do much to move the stock on announcement day, but it will give people who understand what's coming even more confidence :)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367770388135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:13:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367770535279-38</Id><Title>INTC UP OVER 4% TWO WEEKS AGO, OVER 3% LAST WEEK - NEXT WEEK MORE HURTING FOR SHORTS</Title><Msg>With silvermont announcement and new bay trail products announcement, intel can go parabolic. $40 by end of year.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367770535279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:15:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367771912721-39</Id><Topic><Title>itakebackmyapology, singhlion2001, coinmaker77 - ALL THE SAME PERSON</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367770027119</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe and then maybe not. What does it matter?</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367771912721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367772178036-40</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, Ashraf, will there be fireworks?</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367768942939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>btw, nice article on the histroy of AMD vs INTC. The Hector Ruiz interview on Bloom is also well worth a "see."</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367772178036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:42:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367772261958-41</Id><Title>Q3 AND Q4 EARNINGS WILL INCREASE 12% AND 35% RESPECTIVELY YEAR OVER YEAR</Title><Msg>STOCK MARKET TRADES 6 MONTH IN ADVANCE</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367772261958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:44:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367773510201-42</Id><Topic><Title>Q3 AND Q4 EARNINGS WILL INCREASE 12% AND 35% RESPECTIVELY YEAR OVER YEAR</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367772261958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:44:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Revenue will grow to above $54 billion this year, a new record for intel. as intel take market share in smartphone, baseband, small tablets, fabbing, intel tv (all new markets for intel), revenue can double in the next 2 years.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367773510201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367774671674-43</Id><Topic><Title>Just one bad market day and the stock price will tumble</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367769406254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:56:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He needs to takebackhiscommments about Intel going to 19 right after earnings....lol.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367774671674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 13:24:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367776798389-44</Id><Topic><Title>Just one bad market day and the stock price will tumble</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367769406254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:56:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would be nice. I'd buy some shares on sale then. I would much rather they go on sale for 20-30%, however.</Msg><Username>bot_feeder</Username><Timestamp>1367776798389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 13:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367776848407-45</Id><Topic><Title>Just one bad market day and the stock price will tumble</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367769406254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:56:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone knows about silvermont. I don't see a spike coming. However, I do see the stock doing well in the long term.</Msg><Username>bot_feeder</Username><Timestamp>1367776848407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 14:00:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367778261112-46</Id><Topic><Title>Just one bad market day and the stock price will tumble</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367769406254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:56:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>uh no. if everyone knows about silvermont, stock would be at $30 now</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367778261112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 14:24:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367779849847-47</Id><Topic><Title>Just one bad market day and the stock price will tumble</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367769406254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:56:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We had a bad market day last week and INTC didn't crash. Care to say how that fits in with your theory?</Msg><Username>robmxaa</Username><Timestamp>1367779849847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 14:50:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367780592451-48</Id><Topic><Title>Just one bad market day and the stock price will tumble</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367769406254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:56:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would apply my dividend arbitrage activity on both the up and down days. My dividend arbitrage theory answers why Intel has such a low BETA and does not match the market on up days and does not drop as much on down days. For the past year, someone or group has been increasing their short interest by nearly 1mil shares per day. IMO, the shorting pattern has ended and there will some buyers and short interest that is dropping. That will lead to INTC having a strong RSI. The relative strength will even be enough for the chart watchers to mistakenly say OVERBOUGHT.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367780592451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 15:03:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367781624726-49</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, Ashraf, will there be fireworks?</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367768942939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. I think "Hector the Wrecker" is still somewhat full of it, claiming that Intel should let go of the fact that it "missed" phones. Absolutely not. There is plenty of volume there, and there's no reason why Intel *can't* take significant share here.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367781624726</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 15:20:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367784394555-50</Id><Topic><Title>Just one bad market day and the stock price will tumble</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367769406254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:56:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We had a bad market day last week and INTC didn't crash. Care to say how that fits in with your theory?" [And recently Intel went up for a week when the NASDAQ went down. Much to the distress of shorts who expected to apply the big beatdown after earnings regardless of the results. Dunno, has Mr. Market finally recognized the incredible strength of Intel's roadmap, fabrication and manufacturing capacity?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367784394555</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367785052598-51</Id><Topic><Title>Just one bad market day and the stock price will tumble</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367769406254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:56:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Everyone knows about silvermont. I don't see a spike coming. However, I do see the stock doing well in the long term." [Wall Street knows about as much about Silvermont as it does about fabrication - which is almost nothing. It takes translation into something Wall Street can actually understand. Here are two such translations: Intel tablet sales are doubling each quarter. Windows 8 touch devices will drop to $200 says the CEO. But at least we are seeing some translations. It's nice that the Silvermont announcement is arriving at the same time as the Lenovo K900 release. That should help Wall Street to continue to get its feeble mind around the Intel roadmap. Better yet is that tomorrow's announcements are just part of a pipeline that is pretty full right up through the Haswell release on June 3rd: May 10: Lenovo K900 in India May 15-17; Google I/O Developers Conference - Buzz depends on announcements. Good potential. May 16: Intel's Annual Stockholder Meeting June 3: Intel to release Haswell - Buzz should last all year] 2013: Year of the Intel Tablet 2014: Year of the Intel Smartphone</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367785052598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:17:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367785623385-52</Id><Title>Saying this is dead money last 10 years is fiction</Title><Msg>If you bought at 15.66 in January 20003, you received $ 5.12 of Dividends for the last 10 years. So you bought at 15.66 and the stock-adjusted price after dividends is $ 29.08. You doubled your money through the financial crisis.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367785623385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:27:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367785698053-53</Id><Title>Acer Design Event in NY on Friday Was a Nice Lead-in to Tomorrow's Intel Events</Title><Msg>Acer dropped a design first at its event in New York City: a laptop-tablet hybrid with a rotating display that can “float” above the keyboard. The Acer Aspire R7 is certainly unlike any notebook we’ve seen before with a unique “Ezel hinge” that allows the display to move above the keyboard, fold backwards into a presentation display, and even fold into a tablet. Of course, a device this futuristic even has a tie-in with Star Trek. We’ve got everything you need to know about this unique laptop. From digitaltrends [This is just a tiny indication of what is coming and will be hastened by Haswell and Bay Trail in the way of an enormous flood of new form factors and designs. Haswell will open the floodgates and product releases will continue all year and be particularly strong for the holiday season as Intel has a roadmap and pipeline that is chocked full of exciting developments...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367785698053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:28:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367785891738-54</Id><Topic><Title>Saying this is dead money last 10 years is fiction</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367785623385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:27:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If you bought at 15.66 in January 20003, you received $ 5.12 of Dividends for the last 10 years. So you bought at 15.66 and the stock-adjusted price after dividends is $ 29.08. You doubled your money through the financial crisis." [One can't fail to notice that the shills have to go back ten years to find a metric that works for them. They, of course, avoid a comparison to last November and the stock's 25 percent move up since then...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367785891738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:31:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367785897524-55</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, Ashraf, will there be fireworks?</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367768942939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi, nice articles, though why do you need to explain to the ARM bag holders the fault in their investment theory. Sure ARM dominates the phone arena, though as we are finding out there are other areas of expansion ARM is into. Though how successful this will be time will tell. Intel is sure to make a dent into tablet market, especially hurting apple. MS is almost certain to ditch WinRT, apart from tablets, I haven't seen a WinRT notebook, with even the tablets now being offered with discounts and free giveaways to try and shift these lemons. Intel is poised to attain some real penetration in the mobile phone market. What I find interesting of late is the lack of mantra by the analyst "PC is dead, End of the PC era". Simply intel is and will penetrate the fast growing Tablet , and Ultramobile, markets. So much analyst proclamations about how huge the tablet world is expanding and how little intel has a share of this expansion. So much emphasis on intel selling into a shrinking PC market. My point is in the past there was a clear difference between PCs (Desktop, notebook, netbook) and Tablets. Intel simply did not have an acceptable mobile, touch, power efficient, and most importantly fashionable, internet access device. Though intel always had decent devices that could do the math, surf the web, run apps, and lately touch enabled. This month will be different, we WILL have mobile Tablet-PCs, touch, power efficient, and most fashionable, internet access device. So when does a Tablet become a PC? Or, when does a PC become a tablet? ARM camp lemon WinRT and to a lesser extent iPad has proven an ARM powered Tablet CANNOT be a computer. These are simple low power, internet access devices, that are fashionable. For example, lady friend of mine bought iPad a year ago, complete with keyboard, and desktop stand, and now went back to, and uses more her notebook to do the things that are important. Biggest loser in this wave will be Apple, with or without MacTouch.</Msg><Username>gooddigger</Username><Timestamp>1367785897524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:31:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367786522875-56</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, Ashraf, will there be fireworks?</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367768942939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great post. Very telling example from your female friend. MANY of the analysts said the PC was dead to drive the price down.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367786522875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:42:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367786585429-57</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, Ashraf, will there be fireworks?</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367768942939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To put into perspective I have yet to see any ARM device marketed as a FULLY FUNCTIONAL COMPUTER. Cleaver marketing from ARM tablet vendors imply that these toys are computers, hell you can do anything with them! Right?...UHH WRONG! Intel's needs to step up it's marketing, as in the past it's been abysmal.</Msg><Username>gooddigger</Username><Timestamp>1367786585429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:43:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367786921988-58</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, Ashraf, will there be fireworks?</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367768942939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Indeed we are seeing some important changes of the guard: The "End of the PC Era" is giving way to the "Beginning of the Processor Era". And Intel is clearly at the top of the processor food chain with superior technology, fabrication and manufacturing. We are seeing the "End of the iPad Era". Don't get me wrong - the iPad is a fine product and a benchmark in all of computing. But we are finally seeing the end of its complete dominance of the tablet market. Apple has done all it can to milk its shelf life but the iPad is simply slowing down as technology, performance and form factors change and evolve. Windows 8 tablets are showing terrific demand from both consumers and IT professionals who have waited a long time for a performance product. Well, the wait is over. Solutions will now flood the market. Apple has few ways to prolong the dominance of the iPad line. And switching to Intel fabrication is amusingly one of the best available to them. The "End of the ARM Era" is upon us. ARM's fabless model has finally caught up with them and left them without the R&amp;D and new fab money to continue to compete effectively at the high end. ARM 20nm is a year or two out and no one can accurately predict when ARM FinFET solutions will arrive, if ever. The number of ARM foundries has dwindled as a result of the fabless model. ARM's fading fabrication has resulted in the end of the ARM era more than any other factor. These dynamics will likely drive developments for at leas the next several years...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367786921988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:48:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367787237407-59</Id><Topic><Title>Saying this is dead money last 10 years is fiction</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367785623385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:27:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you had INTC at 28 and ARMH at 28, 1 is now 48, 1 is now 23, which would you rather have? f'n idiot!</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1367787237407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:53:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367787669102-60</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, Ashraf, will there be fireworks?</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367768942939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel could milk its relationship with Motorola/Google with game changing products like the XPhone and try to compete head on with the iPhone and Samsung's Galaxy line. If they go after the flagships, they have the best chance of making an impact, because they are competing on technology, not on cost or something else. Its a huge risk that Intel and Google can both afford to be on the wrong end of for the next five years let's say.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367787669102</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 17:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367788135358-61</Id><Topic><Title>Saying this is dead money last 10 years is fiction</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367785623385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:27:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think an idiot would be someone that responded rudely to a post that had nothing to do with ARM. Sorry you are an unhappy person. Try to keep your misery away from my posts. Ok?</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367788135358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 17:08:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367790775575-62</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, Ashraf, will there be fireworks?</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367768942939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel could milk its relationship with Motorola/Google with game changing products like the XPhone and try to compete head on with the iPhone and Samsung's Galaxy line." [I think that you have set a new record for ignorance in one sentence. First no one knows if the X Phone is going to be a game changing product. Second, Motorola is not in the top five in the world. Third, Apple showed its lowest smartphone sales rate growth ever in Q1. So, your strategic suggestion is nonsense. You totally left out ZTE which doubled its global sales in Q1 over the prior year while Apple barely showed any increase. Intel is working with Google/Motorola and ZTE and Lenovo amongst others. And Intel is working with Samsung on Tizen. It's clear that the smartphone market is too complex for someone who has never heard of ZDNET or Semimicro, to get his head around. Why you continue to offer your simplistic strategic vision with nothing to back it up is a total mystery...] "If they go after the flagships, they have the best chance of making an impact, because they are competing on technology, not on cost or something else. Its a huge risk that Intel and Google can both afford to be on the wrong end of for the next five years let's say." [Intel can and is competing on both technology and price. And I'm sure that Intel and Google can figure out the competitive risks without your assistance. Going after the flagships is not a strategy. It's a hairball, incoherent expulsion of erratic, over-generalized thinking. You would be better off providing Apple with your advice. They are the ones whose strategic approach is clearly foundering at the moment. Samsung is eating their lunch every single day. If there is an approach that Intel should not emulate at the present time it would be Apple's. You apparently don't even know who the flagships are these days. Do you ever do any research before posting? Try starting with some of the articles on current global smartphone market share...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367790775575</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 17:52:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367791163914-63</Id><Topic><Title>Saying this is dead money last 10 years is fiction</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367785623385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:27:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"if you had INTC at 28 and ARMH at 28, 1 is now 48, 1 is now 23, which would you rather have? f'n idiot!" [No one bought at those prices, dufus. You're down 5 bucks since November on Intel. I don't blame you for being upset. 2013 is going to be your worst nightmare. You had better pace yourself and save some of the bile and venom for later...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367791163914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 17:59:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367793421451-64</Id><Title>Why in the world does Intel have Fabs in Israel?</Title><Msg>Totally irresponsible. Israel is a target for so many nations &amp; Intel execs thinks its a good idea to put $5B Fabs there. Hopefully, the new CEO has sense to move all critical manufacturing out of Israel.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367793421451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:37:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367794743057-65</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the world does Intel have Fabs in Israel?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367793421451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:37:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because Israel has the brain power, literate and smart working force. The Israeli facility 85 percent of the folks that work there are all ex military. Israeli factories supplly the whole of Europe and Mideast. The main reason is also the ex intel bosses were jews and am not sure if Israel has any investments in intel. have a nice weekend.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1367794743057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367795731186-66</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the world does Intel have Fabs in Israel?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367793421451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:37:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has one fab in Israel. Fab 28 was built as a 45nm, 300mm fab in 2008 and funded in large part by Israeli government grants and tax concessions. The Israeli government got involved in the 22nm upgrade. In 2012, Israel was responsible for 10% of Intel shipments. It makes a lot of sense from both the brain power and financial point of view.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367795731186</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 19:15:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367797364905-67</Id><Title>Mr Weaver has been pumping Silvermont announcment. SELL the news on INTC</Title><Msg>tomorrow? Sell in May and go away is upon us, and Mr Weaver and his multiple personalities are still pumping this stock.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1367797364905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 19:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367798666965-68</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the world does Intel have Fabs in Israel?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367793421451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:37:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The INTC plant in Israel is their most profitable division I believe.....</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1367798666965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:04:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367799042903-69</Id><Topic><Title>Mr Weaver has been pumping Silvermont announcment. SELL the news on INTC</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1367797364905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 19:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"tomorrow? Sell in May and go away is upon us, and Mr Weaver and his multiple personalities are still pumping this stock." [And, Dana, your psychological dysfunction continues to result in you posting childish stupidity on a daily basis instead of any reasoned support for your positions. Get some therapy if you need it to get well and stop using this board as a palliative for your never ending angst. How can you have failed to notice that even when Intel is down, your condition never improves? Your angst isn't related to Intel - it's related to your internal self-loathing. No amount of posting and no change in the Intel stock price is going to ever fix it...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367799042903</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:10:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367799323012-70</Id><Topic><Title>Just one bad market day and the stock price will tumble</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367769406254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:56:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares? I'm holding Intel for the next 50 years. 5-10% fluctuations don't bother me much.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367799323012</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:15:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367799506308-71</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the world does Intel have Fabs in Israel?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367793421451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:37:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Totally irresponsible. Israel is a target for so many nations &amp; Intel execs thinks its a good idea to put $5B Fabs there. Hopefully, the new CEO has sense to move all critical manufacturing out of Israel." [Backbay_bstn, your cup of antisemitism overfloweth. You continue to destroy opinions of your courage, ethics, credibility, and intelligence...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367799506308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:18:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367799648567-72</Id><Title>Apple to switch to haswell</Title><Msg>is it just a rumor?</Msg><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1367799648567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367799860017-73</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to switch to haswell</Title><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1367799648567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:20:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a done deal for their IMacs, but they used Intel processors before anyway. The question is whether or not they will shift to Intel for tablets and phones.</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1367799860017</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:24:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367799863151-74</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to switch to haswell</Title><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1367799648567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:20:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, it's BS you made up. Shame on you, little stunted growth of the swamp.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367799863151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:24:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367799985553-75</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, Ashraf, will there be fireworks?</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367768942939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Crotchpee, I've had enuf of you and your genome.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367799985553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367800006552-76</Id><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Msg>Think about it...how will Apple continue to fight the onslaught of Intel powered, high performance Haswell tablets? It won't end well for Apple if OEMs can make Windows 8 tabs with Haswell that are about as thin as the iPad but much more powerful but w/ the same battery life. My guess is MacBook Air replaces the flailing 10" iPad, and the only think Apple uses its custom SoCs in are the iPad Mini and the iPhone. Thoughts?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367800280369-77</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the world does Intel have Fabs in Israel?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367793421451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:37:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how dumb dumb dumb thou art. learn a little history. read Tompkin's "Peace to End all Peace." Israel is the lynchpin of the mideast. They are beloved by their enemies. They are the cause celebre, and the 51st state. Only a few fanatics dream of a deranged rock star kind of hall of fame thing nuking Tel Aviv, but there isn't a serious brother of the judeo-christian family that doesn't love us. And we love them. The future is the middle-east. In 100 years the arab-jewish axis will dominate planet earth.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367800280369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:31:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367800285738-78</Id><Topic><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where does MacBook Air touch capability come from?</Msg><Username>redwood1205</Username><Timestamp>1367800285738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:31:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367800333236-79</Id><Topic><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, there have been several articles already including one from "Patently Apple" which I posted...that have indicated that a hybrid/convertible Mac is in the works. Apple can ignore the twofer market only to its own peril.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1367800333236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367800668085-80</Id><Topic><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you say so, my lord.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367800668085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:37:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367800825140-81</Id><Topic><Title>Saying this is dead money last 10 years is fiction</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367785623385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:27:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am happy to be on autopilot and collect a handsome dividend while the geniuses I own are designing AND FABBING the highest technology on the planet. What are you good for? Are you the guy who collects a quarter everytime I peeo at the urinals in Madison Square garden?</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367800825140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367801566761-82</Id><Topic><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"My guess is MacBook Air replaces the flailing 10" iPad, and the only think Apple uses its custom SoCs in are the iPad Mini and the iPhone." [Knowing Apple they will probably try to milk the 10 inch iPad as long as possible. Their present course seems to apply this concept across the board with marginal improvements. I'd be surprised to seem them EOL anything until it actually stops getting traction, i.e. making a profit. Until they come out with something big and new, how can they get rid of anything old? I can see them offering a hyrid or convertible MacAir as an additional product. But my real question is when will they redefine the Mac by creating a hybrid of Mac OS X and iOS with a built-in keyboard and a touch screen. I just read an article where all the Mac fanbois said a notebook or Ultrabook would never ever ever need a touch screen because a mouse works so great. But, um, who carries a mouse all of the time or wants to dig one out? I think the absence of a touch screen product hurts them. So, unless they plan on giving up the whole MacBook line it seems that they have to move in some direction. I'm not holding my breath. I'm hugely disappointed with Apple and Tim Cook. Everything in Apple's line seems to be winding down. iPads winding down. iPhone declining dramatically in growth rates. Apple is losing the "cool" factor and once that's gone it will be big trouble in River City. Well, Cupertino I guess...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367801566761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:52:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367801650630-83</Id><Topic><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Where does MacBook Air touch capability come from?" [Exactly...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367801650630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:54:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367801742331-84</Id><Title>INTC is lower than it was last year, last 5 years and last 13 years and it will be lower next year with the PC sales falling offer a cliff</Title><Msg>INTC is lower than it was last year, last 5 years ago and last 13 years ago and it will be lower next year with the PC sales falling offer a cliff</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367801742331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:55:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367802600517-85</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is lower than it was last year, last 5 years and last 13 years and it will be lower next year with the PC sales falling offer a cliff</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367801742331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:55:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>coinmaker77, think about your family, cover Monday morning before INTC shoots to $40</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367802600517</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367802761394-86</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is lower than it was last year, last 5 years and last 13 years and it will be lower next year with the PC sales falling offer a cliff</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367801742331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:55:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is about to make a huge run to 30$ similarly to Microsoft run. you might want to check MSFT chart</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367802761394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367802860252-87</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is lower than it was last year, last 5 years and last 13 years and it will be lower next year with the PC sales falling offer a cliff</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367801742331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:55:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"INTC is lower than it was last year, last 5 years ago and last 13 years ago and it will be lower next year with the PC sales falling offer a cliff..." [Correct me if I'm wrong but last year did have a November in it didn't it? And isn't the stock price now 5 bucks higher than it was in November while you have continued to say things just like those above?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367802860252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:14:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367802924021-88</Id><Topic><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tim Cook did say 'new product category' coming in the fall. thevergeDOTcom/2013/4/23/4258272/apple-tim-cook-teases-exciting-new-product-category</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367802924021</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:15:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367803062094-89</Id><Topic><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being that the Mac Book Air is tapered, if they can criss cross the ends to give the consumer a flat tablet, it can be a powerful cool looking laptop or a very slim tablet that may be just slightly thicker than the iPad. They will slightly price it higher than existing Mac Book Air prices. Maybe about $100 more. However, as the iPod still exists due to a much lower price point, so will the iPad. So the Mac Book Air convertibles will be about $1100 starting price while the Mac Book Air may drop to $900 starting price. A market will still be for them to have a much cheaper iPad. But the iPad will slow down in sales depending on the popularity of the convertible. Similar to what is currently happenning to the iPod because of the iPhone's success. Mac Book convertible will have to have an Intel processor in it, but for the long term continuing success of the iPad, Apple has to build it around Intel processors as well. Either that or seriously drop the price by 50%. I think they will pick the higher price point with Intel processors.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367803062094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:17:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367803221562-90</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the world does Intel have Fabs in Israel?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367793421451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:37:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When I worked at Intel, I was surprised that their Hillsboro facilities are all built on major earthquake fault lines.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1367803221562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:20:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367803334545-91</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the world does Intel have Fabs in Israel?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367793421451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:37:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You just made 2 lies in one sentence jack#$%$*s***s</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367803334545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:22:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367803409232-92</Id><Topic><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Tim Cook did say 'new product category' coming in the fall." [Just think. In the fall we will be counting down to the arrival of Intel's 14nm FinFET production just like we are now counting down to Haswell. Intel's 14nm FinFET is the real ARM-killer. I'm guessing behind the scenes that a lot of companies are already trying to get in line to be a recipient of this game changing production. What company in their right mind would want to compete with another company deploying 14nm FinFET?] 2013: Year of the Intel Tablet 2014: Year of the Intel Smartphone</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367803409232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:23:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367803554334-93</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the world does Intel have Fabs in Israel?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367793421451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:37:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When I worked at Intel, I was surprised that their Hillsboro facilities are all built on major earthquake fault lines." [Were you as surprised as when you got fired?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367803554334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:25:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367804296656-94</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the world does Intel have Fabs in Israel?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367793421451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:37:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Backbay, are you surprised that the fab is in Israel, or is it rather that they are hiring Jews?</Msg><Username>canuckkk</Username><Timestamp>1367804296656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:38:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367804695038-95</Id><Topic><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The MacBook Air is already slim and light. I see no benefit in making it a convertible and lot of unnecessary added complexity. If Intel or Microsoft made the MacBook Air, they might have done this.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367804695038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:44:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367804765442-96</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the world does Intel have Fabs in Israel?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367793421451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:37:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of the earthquake risk, according to the USGS, seems to be concentrated in the last 1,600,000 years. A few faults have had activity in the last 780,000 years and none during the last 20,000 years. There are some small fault lines in Washington County Oregon. That is the county Hillsboro is located. None of the faults that have been active for the last 20,000 years. There are a couple of small fault lines that have had activity in the 780,000 years. Most fault lines have had activity in the last 1,600,000 years.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367804765442</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:46:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367804815314-97</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is lower than it was last year, last 5 years and last 13 years and it will be lower next year with the PC sales falling offer a cliff</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367801742331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:55:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What makes you think I am short I told you, I sold my share last week before the dividend INTC ran up a lot more than the dividend and it was time to take some profits. You always on INTC take the profits before there gone, INTC profits go away so fast</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367804815314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:46:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367804877041-98</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is lower than it was last year, last 5 years and last 13 years and it will be lower next year with the PC sales falling offer a cliff</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367801742331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:55:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC had a 20% run up into the dividend, It was time to take some profits</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367804877041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:47:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367805190945-99</Id><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Msg>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367805221041-100</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is lower than it was last year, last 5 years and last 13 years and it will be lower next year with the PC sales falling offer a cliff</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367801742331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:55:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What makes you think I am short .." [I have no idea what made us think that but maybe the non-stop Intel bashing ever since Dana created this user ID had something to do with it...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367805221041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367805267995-101</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JUST the FACTS</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805267995</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:54:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367805308722-102</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Always remember to take profits , before there gone</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805308722</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:55:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367805590914-103</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good.." [You say that as if all of those things hadn't already been priced in and as if the roadmap going forward didn't look fabulous. And remind of us when you bought that share of Intel you said you sold last week. We need a laugh...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367805590914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367805711154-104</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"JUST the FACTS" [Uh, oh. The use of the all caps confirms that this is a Dana ID and that Dana is getting upset. More upset?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367805711154</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:01:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367805886379-105</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With news planned for tomorrow, I am surprised that the bashers waited so late in the day. Expect them to go full time with "JUST the FACTS" until the webcast tomorrow.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367805886379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:04:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367805997274-106</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gO BACK AND LOOK I THINK IT WAS 19.36</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805997274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367806049586-107</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"With news planned for tomorrow, I am surprised that the bashers waited so late in the day. Expect them to go full time with "JUST the FACTS" until the webcast tomorrow." [Yeah, Dana must have had a hard weekend or he would be filling the board with content-free postings. He can't seem to find an ID he likes tonight...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367806049586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367806192321-108</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>coinmaker77, think about your family, cover Monday morning before INTC shoots up to $40 and put you and your family in financial ruin.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367806192321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:09:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367806242956-109</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, Intel is forecasting record breaking revenue this year.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367806242956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:10:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367806321142-110</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"gO BACK AND LOOK I THINK IT WAS 19.36" [So, you want us to believe that you were long Intel since November and yet bashed the stock non-stop the entire time. I'm not sure if doing that or telling us your did that would be the most unintelligent thing I've ever heard.] [Come on, Dana - don't garbage the board up all night with this kind of nonsense. No one is buying your "coinboy" character...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367806321142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:12:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367806327130-111</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is also forecasting margins to remain at 60% despite the one-time excess inventory charges</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367806327130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:12:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367806356743-112</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel also forecasting margins for Q3 and Q4 to be well over 60%</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367806356743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367806400108-113</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Q3 and Q4 earnings will grow by 12% and 35% respectively year over year.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367806400108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:13:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367806423711-114</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What that Apple is going with AMD should be any day, lower cost for Apple</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367806423711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:13:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367806606511-115</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just the Facts INTC still has to lower Q3 and Q4 how's that going to help your stock price</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367806606511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:16:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367806689427-116</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a total idiot. Q3 and Q4 will be the strongest two quarters in the history of Intel.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367806689427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367806809027-117</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Always remember to take your PROFITS if you have any , You both have been pumping INTC all the way down from 29.25 when I told you last time to take your profits</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367806809027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:20:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367806940165-118</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not when they still have to be lowered</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367806940165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:22:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367807078105-119</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>coinmaker idiot, how much you lost on alcoa. lol</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367807078105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:24:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367807119435-120</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Computer sales falling off a CLIFF down 14% and still falling like a rock</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367807119435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:25:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367807149270-121</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to switch to haswell</Title><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1367799648567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:20:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a switch to Haswell is likely</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367807149270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367807178305-122</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the money priced in at 8.17</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367807178305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:26:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367807280203-123</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>coinmaker loser tell us, how much you lost on alcoa.</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367807280203</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367807310245-124</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your one of the idiots that did not sell INTC at 29.25 right, You never take profits right</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367807310245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367807363213-125</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is lower than it was last year, last 5 years and last 13 years and it will be lower next year with the PC sales falling offer a cliff</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367801742331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:55:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol, okay.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367807363213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367807444285-126</Id><Topic><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you fail to see a lot lately Convertible is the future</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367807444285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367807625346-127</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have been telling you to buy AA when it was below 8,50 go look , My average price is 8.17 and AA has more upside than INTC because they have lower all Q's to #$%$, Any good news AA will go higher INTC still has to lower Q3 and Q4 and that is not priced into INTC yet</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367807625346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367807833349-128</Id><Title>Samsung galaxy S4 overheating rumors spreading on social media</Title><Msg>From thenewstribe . from comments section, seems to be translated from Chinese site which contains an interesting you t u b e video showing unusual heat generated from S4 phones youtubeDOTcom/watch?v=XqssJdMXjvI LONDON: Social media especially Twitter is after Samsung galaxy S4 these days because just after the launch of the new S4 many users are experiencing an overheating issue with the device and they are expressing their concern openly and blatantly which is going against the marketing campaign of Samsung galaxy S4. Sources say that these days many shoppers are using social media to decide whether they should buy S4, Sony Xperia, HTC one or iPhone 5. And when they listen to social media,they find many users of Samsung galaxy S4 complaining about the device. They discover that there are numerous mentions of Samsung’s Galaxy S4 devices which are suffering from overheating issues. The flagship device, which has to fight with likes of HTC One and Apple iPhone 5 is in the fiercely contested smartphone market,however,has so far the Samsung device has generated only negative PR. The commentators say that this overheating issue is not going to help the product in the market. Thought it is true that the overheating issue is not that unusual and it is common observation that all the devices heat up after a certain amount of time,however,what YouTuber SuperFreshTech and others have found is that the brand-new Samsung device perhaps warms up a little more than ordinary. Now potentially shoppers are a little cautious about the future of the product They have doubt that there may be some inherent fault in the design of the Samsung Galaxy S4.Lets see how Samsung brand custodians tackle the situation.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367807833349</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:37:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367807859617-129</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you were pumping AA at 9.3 you liar</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367807859617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:37:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367807898769-130</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just the FACTS in the money in both AA and BIG X now and I still can take profits in both if I want to, The Same INTC pumpesr that were pumping INTC at 29.25 and never sold are still pumping today and they are still underwater, Why I am taking profits again</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367807898769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:38:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367807943696-131</Id><Topic><Title>Two BIG announcements on Monday!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367719837761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 22:10:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>May/June Calendar: May 6: Intel to announce Silvermont - Buzz should last all year May 6: Lenovo K900 release in China May 10: Lenovo K900 in India May 15-17; Google I/O Developers Conference - Buzz depends on announcements. Good potential. May 16: Intel's Annual Stockholder Meeting June 3: Intel to release Haswell - Buzz should last all year June 4: Computex - Buzz depends on announcements. Good potential June 10-14: Apple's WWDC - Macs about to get a major upgrade thanks to Intel’s (NASDAQ:INTC) new “Iris” graphics processors? June 26-28: Microsoft's Build Developer Conference - Rumors of next Surface Pro announcement 2013: Year of the Intel Tablet 2014: Year of the Intel Smartphone. ------------------------------------------------------------- thanks.</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367807943696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:39:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367808213700-132</Id><Title>Apple to announce they are going to us AMD chips, Lower priced chips will help Apple margins</Title><Msg>Apple to announce they are going to us AMD chips, Lower priced chips will help Apple margins</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367808213700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:43:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367808392373-133</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC still has to lower Q3 and Q4</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367808392373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:46:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367808892334-134</Id><Title>Always remember to take SOME PROFITS after you stock has run up over 25% INTC is up from low $19's to over $24 , It is time to take some.</Title><Msg>Always remember to take SOME PROFITS after you stock has run up over 25% INTC is up from low $19's to over $24 , It is time to take some</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367808892334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:54:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367809084120-135</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Taking Profits and catching $ H I T from all the PUMPERS that never sold any INTC stock at 29.25 and road it all the way back down last time</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367809084120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:58:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367809168116-136</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung galaxy S4 overheating rumors spreading on social media</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367807833349</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:37:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, this could be a translation from Korean site? If so, then it is the Exynos 5 octa with the heating problems.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367809168116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:59:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367809329096-137</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to announce they are going to us AMD chips, Lower priced chips will help Apple margins</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367808213700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:43:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You piece of #$%$ liar, just go away you loser</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367809329096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:02:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367809598910-138</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to announce they are going to us AMD chips, Lower priced chips will help Apple margins</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367808213700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:43:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are not AMD chips lower priced than INTC and If Apple went to AMD chips won't that not help Apples margins?</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367809598910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367809617395-139</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to announce they are going to us AMD chips, Lower priced chips will help Apple margins</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367808213700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:43:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just the FACTS</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367809617395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:06:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367809663019-140</Id><Topic><Title>Always remember to take SOME PROFITS after you stock has run up over 25% INTC is up from low $19's to over $24 , It is time to take some.</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367808892334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:54:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just the Facts</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367809663019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:07:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367809874901-141</Id><Title>Sell in May and go away could happen starting tomorrow. CNBC will at first say</Title><Msg>its profit taking.. Indices at all time highs. Mr Weaver keeps pumping and everyone knows he is a contrarian indicator.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1367809874901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:11:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367809997567-142</Id><Title>Dana Garbaging Up the Board as CoinMaker</Title><Msg>Dana, your psychological dysfunction continues to result in you posting childish stupidity on a minute-by-minute basis instead of any reasoned support for your positions. Get some therapy if you need it to get well and stop using this board as a palliative for your never ending angst. How can you have failed to notice that even when Intel is down, your condition never improves? Your angst isn't related to Intel - it's related to your internal self-loathing. No amount of posting and no change in the Intel stock price is going to ever fix it...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367809997567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:13:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367810001904-143</Id><Title>coinmaker77 is obviously panicking because INTC could jump in pre-market before he has a chance to cover</Title><Msg>coinmaker77 is obviously panicking because INTC could jump in pre-market before he has a chance to cover</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367810001904</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367810046389-144</Id><Topic><Title>Sell in May and go away could happen starting tomorrow. CNBC will at first say</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1367809874901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:11:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're an idiot</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367810046389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:14:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367810362367-145</Id><Title>WOW we all must be an idiot, because we know to take some profits after a 25% run up. I think we know who the IDIOT is don't we</Title><Msg>WOW we all must be an idiot, because we know to take some profits after a 25% run up. I think we know who the IDIOT is don't we</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367810362367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367810943212-146</Id><Title>Who Has the Best Roadmap?</Title><Msg>Intel/ARM Roadmap Comparison Intel (All FinFET): 22nm: Haswell June 2013 14nm: Broadwell: End of 2013/Start of 2014 14nm: Skylake: 2015 10nm: Skymont: 2016 7nm: 2018 5nm: 2020 ARMH Planar 28nm: Production has been increasing but is still insufficient to meet market demand. Substantially all of the production is coming from TSMC, which is a significant bottleneck. 20nm: Volume production in 2014/2015. TSMC has promised to ramp 20nm faster than 28nm but this appears to be nothing more than rhetoric as 20nm will be yet another level of complexity when trends have show each successive ARM die shrink to ramp significantly slower than the previous. FinFET 14/16nm: ARM foundries will pursue a half-step to FinFET by making it half FinFET and half 20nm. This clearly illustrates their lack of confidence in bringing a full step online in a reasonable time frame. There are so many unknowns with the half-step process, that any prediction of volume production cannot be reliably made. Conclusions 1.) Intel will continue to have significant opportunities for high margin foundry work, as illustrated by the Altera deal. 2.) Intel's fabrication economics will continue to improve just as ARM's are degrading. ARMs 20nm planar and the half-step to FinFET both have inferior economics to the Intel nodes. 3.) Intel will reach 450mm wafer implementation well ahead of ARM, giving them significantly improved economic benefits. Intel's lead in fabrication and manufacturing is increasing in virtually every area.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367810943212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:29:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367810968123-147</Id><Topic><Title>WOW we all must be an idiot, because we know to take some profits after a 25% run up. I think we know who the IDIOT is don't we</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367810362367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:19:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>coinmaker77, remember you have family that depend on you, cover before INTC shoots to $40 and ruin you financially forever.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367810968123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:29:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367811122689-148</Id><Title>Futures</Title><Msg>Looking pretty green. Maybe ARM's P/E ratio will break the century mark tomorrow. LOL</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367811122689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:32:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367811264008-149</Id><Topic><Title>WOW we all must be an idiot, because we know to take some profits after a 25% run up. I think we know who the IDIOT is don't we</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367810362367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:19:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your not to smart are you. I have to keep telling you that I am not shorts. I sold last week and will BUY back in after the drop, INTC is up over 25% If I didn't take some Profits , I would have lost them as I(NTC falls back some.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367811264008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367811485565-150</Id><Title>Don't buy the headfake</Title><Msg>it is headed back down.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367811485565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:38:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367811486961-151</Id><Topic><Title>Always remember to take SOME PROFITS after you stock has run up over 25% INTC is up from low $19's to over $24 , It is time to take some.</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367808892334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:54:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JUST the FACTS and I can always BUY back in , But if INTC drops you can not always take your profits before there gone</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367811486961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:38:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367811613902-152</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL GROSSLY UNDERVALUED, REVENUE COULD DOUBLE IN NEXT 2 YEARS</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367768389459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:39:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$40</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367811613902</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:40:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367811679826-153</Id><Topic><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MacBook air convertible with Intel inside will sell like crazy</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367811679826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367811925612-154</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K900 Smartphone confirmed, May 6th in China</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1366832924136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 15:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>launching tomorrow</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367811925612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:45:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367811990118-155</Id><Topic><Title>May and June Intel Catalysts</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367645980626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 01:39:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>big 2 months coming</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367811990118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:46:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>