<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-21"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374379502689-1</Id><Title>intels equity stake in ASML made a sheetload compared</Title><Msg>to the hedge fund monkeys from Nomura Nomura Securities maintains a 'Neutral' on ASML Inc. (NASDAQ: ASML) price target of EUR42.00. Analyst, Carmen Boyero, said, "ASML reported Q2 results that were in-line with previous guidance and consensus expectations. Systems sales were 5% below expectations, however, driven by lower ASP. Q2 sales were primarily driven by foundry and logic continuing the trend in previous quarters. Net bookings increased qoq to 949m and 43 systems, although backlog continued the declining trend to EUR 1,503m and 55 systems (from EUR 1,598m and 56 systems)...Guidance for the full year 2012 is seen at between EUR 4.6b and EUR 4.8b, or 3% below market expectations of EUR 4,863m." Note: Nomura downgraded ASML from Buy to Neutral on July 13th. To see the report, click here For an analyst ratings summary and ratings history on ASML Inc. click here. For more ratings news on ASML Inc. click here. Shares of ASML Inc. closed at $51.50 yesterday, with a 52 week range of $30.65-$53.30.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1374379502689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 00:05:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374381913479-2</Id><Topic><Title>The biggest catalyst of all for Inte to go upl.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1374375765087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 23:02:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see one for April. But nothing for July. Are you saying Romit Shah was on CNBC interview with Karen Tso on July 17?</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1374381913479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 00:45:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374390861364-3</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Major Catalyst Coming On July 22</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372652892849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 00:28:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brian Krzanich and Stacy Smith sounds EXTREMELY confident Data Center group will grow by double digits this year: Brian M. Krzanich - CEO Sure. This is Brian. I'll answer that one. Yeah, so we're still confident in the second half growth of our data center business overall. As we mentioned, we're seeing strong growth in the cloud, the high performance computing, our networking and our storage. We think those continue through the second half of this year. What was down as Stacy mentioned was – the enterprise data centers were down a bit in the first half. We think as the macroeconomics continue to improve through this year that picks up a bit. When you put that all together, we believe that – absolutely our view is that we can continue through this year with that low double digit growth. Stacy J. Smith - EVP and CFO Yeah. And from a [wonky] finance standpoint, realize there's also kind of prior period comparisons been going on in the first half of last year. We were in the steep part of the ramp for Romley. In the second half of this year, we'll be launching other versions of Ivy versions of the data center. So the short answer to your question is yes, I would expect some pretty steep quarter-on-quarter and year-on-year comps in the back half of this year. That is what we're planning for.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1374390861364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 03:14:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374392072340-4</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Major Catalyst Coming On July 22</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372652892849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 00:28:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was looking at the "Trended Financial Statements" at Intel's investor relation website and did some simple calculations in terms of revenues. If Data Center group grows by 11%-12%, then the PC Client group would only need to be flat (year-over-year) for second half to meet Intel's guidance of flat revenues. This is extremely unlikely given that "Haswell along with Bay Trail will power more than 50 different two-in-one devices in the pipeline, including the very first fanless Core design." Not to mention addition revenues from Bay Trail 7"-10" Android tablets, a market Intel did not participate in last year. I think BK and SS were being extremely cautious with their lowered guidance.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1374392072340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 03:34:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374393572214-5</Id><Topic><Title>Two very large, dishonest derivative players will bring down the world financial markets.</Title><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1374264464908</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 16:07:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will happen shortly now.</Msg><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1374393572214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 03:59:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374410430846-6</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 is what is killing PC's</Title><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1374325993795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 09:13:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Completely agree. If Windows 7 supported touch Ultra-books would have taken off and ramped beyond anyone's expectations. Having to wait for Windows 8 stalled the market, and when it arrived turned people off because it is so terrible. (lest we forget,... At Microsoft Quality is Job 1.1) Ballmer is the last man standing from the folks who started Microsoft, and he was a Gates, and Allen hanger on with nothing of genuine value to offer. And he has done nothing if not for having nurtured a culture of over the top corporate arrogance that makes you want to root with all your heart for their utter demise. The sooner the computing industry rids itself of the last vestiges of Microsoft's bloatware the better off all will all be.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1374410430846</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 08:40:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374411151895-7</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 is what is killing PC's</Title><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1374325993795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 09:13:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's good that at least for tablets and smartphones, Intel is supporting Android which gets its chips into a whole new dimension far removed from Microsoft's dictatorship.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1374411151895</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 08:52:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374415159784-8</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 is what is killing PC's</Title><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1374325993795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 09:13:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>amen.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1374415159784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 09:59:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374421400215-9</Id><Title>Two very large, dishonest derivative players will bring down the world financial markets.</Title><Msg>Opened my eyes just in time to see a rather large nurse holding a syringe. As two orderlies wrestled me to the ground, felt a needle jab deep inside my arm. Next, my arms were stuffed into a jacket that looked backwards to me. Soon I felt immobilized as the straps from the jacket were tightened. Before I knew it, I was lying on a table in a room that had a funny burning smell. A strange looking machine was wheeled close to me. What looked like electrodes were attached to both sides of my head. A wooden stick was placed inside my mouth and was told to bite down. As I glanced up, one of the attendants dressed in white pulled down a large lever ........ What seemed like only seconds, I went whirling back in time and was back at the pool party in Long Island. Kate Upton led me into a bedroom and began to unzip my pants...........I smiled broadly as she began to kneel... I ......,</Msg><Username>geraldrncginty</Username><Timestamp>1374421400215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 11:43:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374423563023-10</Id><Topic><Title>Two very large, dishonest derivative players will bring down the world financial markets.</Title><Username>geraldrncginty</Username><Timestamp>1374421400215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 11:43:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please continue. Just starting to get interesting. Want to hear more about what happened with Kate Upton.</Msg><Username>jblown87</Username><Timestamp>1374423563023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 12:19:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374424914461-11</Id><Topic><Title>Two very large, dishonest derivative players will bring down the world financial markets.</Title><Username>geraldrncginty</Username><Timestamp>1374421400215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 11:43:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My gawd man, don't you have any decency? You sick pervert. This was just a side story. More important is the derivatives issue. shu ...sssh, ...., just calm down and we'll get to more about what happened. You guys need to figure some of this out. For now, I'll give you a hint and say that the interaction was a "happy ending".</Msg><Username>geraldrncginty</Username><Timestamp>1374424914461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 12:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374425097860-12</Id><Topic><Title>Two very large, dishonest derivative players will bring down the world financial markets.</Title><Username>geraldrncginty</Username><Timestamp>1374421400215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 11:43:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Am I the only man who thinks her body is bad? those high fat hips, I don't get the attraction to her. She looks awful in a 2 piece bikini.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1374425097860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 12:44:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374426290915-13</Id><Topic><Title>Two very large, dishonest derivative players will bring down the world financial markets.</Title><Username>geraldrncginty</Username><Timestamp>1374421400215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 11:43:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nuff, Is Gerald McGinty one of your aliases? Has to be one of the most bizarre so far. Like today's post though but don't think it was written by the real McGinty. Sounds like one of those scams that hits this board occasionally.</Msg><Username>jblown87</Username><Timestamp>1374426290915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 13:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374426567807-14</Id><Topic><Title>Two very large, dishonest derivative players will bring down the world financial markets.</Title><Username>geraldrncginty</Username><Timestamp>1374421400215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 11:43:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>geraldrncginty, #$%$ , STOP REPOSTING THIS #$%$</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1374426567807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 13:09:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374426660641-15</Id><Title>geraldrncginty, F**** U</Title><Msg>#$%$****hOLE</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1374426660641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 13:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374426756526-16</Id><Topic><Title>Two very large, dishonest derivative players will bring down the world financial markets.</Title><Username>geraldrncginty</Username><Timestamp>1374421400215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 11:43:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee I wonder who you could be? nuff if I ever get my hands on you &amp; I know I'm not the only one that feels this way, I will ring your neck!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1374426756526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 13:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374429198560-17</Id><Topic><Title>geraldrncginty, F**** U</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1374426660641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 13:11:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, won't post any more. Mr. Jerry Blown created me as a scam to counter the twisted Nuff. Are you the real Vinnie?</Msg><Username>geraldrncginty</Username><Timestamp>1374429198560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 13:53:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374430843016-18</Id><Topic><Title>geraldrncginty, F**** U</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1374426660641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 13:11:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>put him on ignore as i did. it's simple.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1374430843016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 14:20:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374430935858-19</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 is what is killing PC's</Title><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1374325993795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 09:13:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 7 is not designed for tablets. You need the tiles.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1374430935858</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 14:22:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374431708100-20</Id><Title>Madam's prediksyone:</Title><Msg>INTC will hit rock bottom at about $2o.31 (U.S.). Avoid the rust end don't be the last to stand in line.</Msg><Username>madam_hillary_o8</Username><Timestamp>1374431708100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 14:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374433013611-21</Id><Title>Technicals point to MM manipulation on Friday and another down day Monday.</Title><Msg>Just technicals here-- deep put options needed to be wiped out, so it got walked up to 23.04 by close. Would have been 23 even, but someone must have made a play for the cheap $23 options in the last 3 minutes. Only MM manipulators held this stock up in light of all the tech misses on Friday. I think intc is worth more than $23, but short-term we'll see $22 or even $20 before we see $24.</Msg><Username>agamemnus_0</Username><Timestamp>1374433013611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 14:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374436610587-22</Id><Title>Zombies Prepare for Sunday Night Posting</Title><Msg>As I type the zombies are doing their intense preparation for their Sunday night post - Oh, wait - it doesn't take any preparation to do content-free repetitive posts. Never mind... I had a dream last night That I was piloting a plane And all the passengers Were drunk plus insane I crash landed in a Louisiana swamp Shot up a horde of zombies But I come out on top It just reflects my mood Sitting in the dirt Feeling kind of hurt All I hear is doom and gloom. Come on, people - wallowing in doom and gloom isn't what made America great. Beating the bejesus out of the doom and gloom crowd is. And besides, it's fun...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1374436610587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 15:56:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374438009562-23</Id><Title>What We Know Now: The Big Deal Issue</Title><Msg>Here's what we know now (from the headline): Intel on Track with Volume 14nm (FinFET) Production This Year "Intel to Produce Broadwell Chips Later in 2013" And this provides the upside and Intel's wildcard and ace-in-the-hole for this year. Intel is going to sign some big deals. Some very big deals. They aren't building all that 14nm FinFET capacity for nothing. And no company is going to let the competition leap two years ahead on process technology if they can help it. This advanced technology is going to be very much in demand. Why haven't we heard about them yet? Because that's how it's done. In order to avoid souring relations with existing vendors, announcements are closely guarded. We already know about one such deal that was confirmed by Intel with a major mobility player. We also know that Intel is working on smartwatches with somebody. There will be these and others. And when it happens, it is going to blow the socks off of the shorts. What we also know now is that it is going to become much clearer this year that Intel is taking market share from ARM. The shipment of Intel's 14nm FinFET is going to dramatically emphasis this trend. Look for this recognition to knock the stuffing out of ARM's P/E ratio and to enhance Intel's P/E ratio. I believe that this year , P/E ratios will drive the Intel stock price as much or more than earnings. 2013: Year of the Intel Tablet and Year of the Lumpy Intel Big Deal Announcements and Stock Price Surge 2014: Year of the Intel Smartphone and More Lumpy Intel Big Deal Announcements and Stock Price Surges</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1374438009562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 16:20:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374438906257-24</Id><Topic><Title>Madam's prediksyone:</Title><Username>madam_hillary_o8</Username><Timestamp>1374431708100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 14:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a quote from one of your #$%$ &amp; bull predictions "Madam downgrades MRK to "SELL"; New Target $33.oo (U.S.)" MRTK is almost $50 as I type, so much for this self serving Troll cretin's credibility for predicting future prices.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1374438906257</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 16:35:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374439192412-25</Id><Topic><Title>Madam's prediksyone:</Title><Username>madam_hillary_o8</Username><Timestamp>1374431708100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 14:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typo, make that MRK .</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1374439192412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 16:39:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374439238912-26</Id><Title>Haswell chips can give a laptop workstation power</Title><Msg>I'm not really sure why Intel isn't pushing the new Haswell-based chips a little harder, as they seem to have been released with a whisper. When the first i-generation of chips was released -- the i3s, i5s and i7s -- there was a huge campaign to show how revolutionary they were compared to previous models. But now we are seeing the fourth generation Haswell-based chips, and almost nothing is being said about them. But then again, perhaps the performance speaks for itself. Yes, they are amazing. For such low-power consumption, there’s more raw power than most people know what to do with. And even when they’re not running at maximum speed, they’ll still help extend battery life. Laptops with Haswell chips could help enable mobile computing and teleworking for agency employees who need a powerful system. The latest product to take advantage of the Haswell Intel Core i7 processor is the Scorpius 2.0 notebook from Eurocom. Even without the Haswell processor, the Scorpius is an impressive unit. It's got dual Nvidia GeForce GTX 780M graphics cards and 8G of DDR5 video memory driving its 17.1-inch screen. There are a lot of options for connecting devices into it too, including HDMI 1.4, Thunderbolt, four USB 3.0 ports and an eSATA/USB 2.0 combo port. But what really blew us away was the performance. It scored 4,576 on the Passmark Performance Benchmarks without any overclocking at all. For a notebook, that is about as impressive as it gets today. Consider the fact that the powerful Tiki workstation got up to 5,618 last year using a previous generation processor, or the fact that the most modern workstation we've ever benchmarked, the Origin Systems Chronos Pro got 6,131 just last month. But they didn't have access to this new chipset, which apparently gives mere notebooks access to workstation-level performance. But it's important to note that despite the lack of fanfare, another great leap forward has occurred. From gcn</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1374439238912</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 16:40:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374440088559-27</Id><Topic><Title>Madam's prediksyone:</Title><Username>madam_hillary_o8</Username><Timestamp>1374431708100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 14:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guys that give financial advise on this thread do not impress me and probably no one else.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1374440088559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 16:54:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374441240616-28</Id><Title>Wallis, regarding Surface Tablet sales.</Title><Msg>For the latest Microsoft quarter, did they or any other research company give any numbers as to how many Surface RT tablets sold and how many Surface Pro Tablets sold? I know Surface RT is really bad, but haven't seen actual numbers posted. Just wondering if you heard of any specifics.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1374441240616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 17:14:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374443405686-29</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, regarding Surface Tablet sales.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1374441240616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 17:14:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've seen numbers but maybe not from last quarter. Ashraf might know...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1374443405686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 17:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374444624578-30</Id><Topic><Title>geraldrncginty, F**** U</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1374426660641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 13:11:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just to clarify: Jerry Blown created gerald-r-ncginty (a spoof on the original). All the other geraldmcginty was most probably Nuff baloney.</Msg><Username>geraldrncginty</Username><Timestamp>1374444624578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 18:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374444990954-31</Id><Title>Tomorrow the analysts are gonna bad mouth the pig. What will Mr Weaver</Title><Msg>and his bossom buddies do?</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1374444990954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 18:16:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374445512934-32</Id><Title>High end smartphone boom ending. But for Intel its just begining.</Title><Msg>Mr Essa should use this in one of his articles. Pump it up!!</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1374445512934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 18:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374445821681-33</Id><Topic><Title>geraldrncginty, F**** U</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1374426660641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 13:11:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another note: this board has practically no sense of humor, is a little thick headed (posts generally go way over everyone's head) and generally hate it when someone pokes fun at Nuff, the board idiot.</Msg><Username>jblown87</Username><Timestamp>1374445821681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 18:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374447764507-34</Id><Topic><Title>Tomorrow the analysts are gonna bad mouth the pig. What will Mr Weaver</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1374444990954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 18:16:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This bossom buddy will just hold the stock and watch it go back up and collect my dividend and buy more. Now you know.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1374447764507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 19:02:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374448584387-35</Id><Topic><Title>geraldrncginty, F**** U</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1374426660641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 13:11:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh? how do you figure that, he has been right more than almost anyone here.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1374448584387</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 19:16:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374448722965-36</Id><Topic><Title>Zombies Prepare for Sunday Night Posting</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1374436610587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 15:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WW, you have pwered INTC to where it is, all the way from 23 in 2010 to 23 in 2013, you're the best, give us more leadership. Hey what do you think of gays in the military?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1374448722965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 19:18:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374449477576-37</Id><Topic><Title>geraldrncginty, F**** U</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1374426660641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 13:11:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aren't you maybe a little bit biased since you're an alias of Nuff? and, would you not seriously agree that I'm brilliant? My spoof on your Gerald Mcginty alias was beyond exceptional.</Msg><Username>jblown87</Username><Timestamp>1374449477576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 19:31:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374449498682-38</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>The DJIA has put together a four week win streak that entered the weekend overbought. Investors seem comfortable with the Feds withdraw of easy money stimulus and signs that Europe and some of the emerging markets are gaining traction are helping to push stocks higher. New money is coming into the market at a record pace and the economic outlook looks stronger than anticipated. Looks like nothing can go wrong! That may be the fly in the ointment. Although the second half outlook remains strong, bullish sentiment is getting overdone. Going into another strong week of earnings any pullback in the market will be bought quickly and downside seems limited but, any time the crowd gets overzealous a round of profit taking might be in the cards. The summer rally may be due for a short term pause. Have a nice weekend.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1374449498682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 19:31:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374449654576-39</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, regarding Surface Tablet sales.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1374441240616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 17:14:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I remember this correctly, in Q1, 2013, they sold 250,000 RTs and 750,000 Pros.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1374449654576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 19:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374450379174-40</Id><Topic><Title>Note to Board</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1374276309283</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 19:25:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I make no assumptions about when you bought INTC, if I thought about it I would say you own none. I figure you're a paid psoter because no matter how bad things go you always post positive on Intel. It would be good for you to show some common sense at at times admit what P O S ! INTC has been. Do you admit you once said $30 was in the bag? do you admit bragging how sure you were 3 years ago that INTC would ceratinly hit $24, do you admit you said Intel would earn $3 eps about 2 years ago? Who care if you have INTC at $17.?? Heck I own some BAC at 3.38, 3.99, cvx at 68, etc etc etc but nothing matters here about Intel. This really blows when you remember how great Andy was and where Intel is now. Sure they are huge, sure they are great, sure they money but just what they could have been. They obviously f'd up with a boat load of R &amp; D money. How could they have misjudged mobile so badly? My ego, I have no ego. I am younger than you but old enough to know who &amp; what I am by now. I lean right, I expect no handouts, I hate this current liberal handout regime that you love.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1374450379174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 19:46:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374450994510-41</Id><Topic><Title>Note to Board</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1374276309283</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 19:25:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tiglet2l, WHY DON'T YOU JUST SELL YOUR INTC SHARES???!!! YOu f**u**k**e***n idiot....you are the ONLY P O S here. i'll put you in my ignore list too</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1374450994510</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 19:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374451493880-42</Id><Topic><Title>Unfortunately, we are down tomorrow</Title><Username>typea1948</Username><Timestamp>1374178883280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 16:21:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>orco, 40% payout on $1.60 in earnings, do you think that's 90 cents? I come up with 64 cents. You don't think it could get cut in 2014 or 2015 the way things are going?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1374451493880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 20:04:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374452802244-43</Id><Title>Sorry guys I've been running the streets naked, screaming FIRE! since 2008</Title><Msg>Just look at my post history. I do NOTHING but cry and moan and yell at people. My life sux, I prove it every day. Thanks guys.</Msg><Username>tiglet3l</Username><Timestamp>1374452802244</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 20:26:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374453321126-44</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are trapped with over 300 million shares short....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1374145749155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 07:09:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good move as the shorts should spend a couple of minutes and read the CEOs remarks on the CC.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1374453321126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 20:35:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374453501743-45</Id><Topic><Title>Note to Board</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1374276309283</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 19:25:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I hate..." [Yes, tiglet2l, it's exceedingly clear that hate, anger, prejudice, bile, venom and frustration drive you forward rather than judgment, common sense and human decency. Yours are the characteristics of someone extremely unhappy with extremely low self-esteem. You should get some professional help instead of venting your angst on this board every day...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1374453501743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 20:38:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374453602930-46</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are trapped with over 300 million shares short....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1374145749155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 07:09:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Good move as the shorts should spend a couple of minutes and read the CEOs remarks on the CC." [Shorts can read???]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1374453602930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 20:40:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374454017387-47</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Major Catalyst Coming On July 22</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372652892849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 00:28:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(Tomorrow) *** I cannot stress this enough, but there is a major upside catalyst coming for Intel (INTC) on July 22. When I checked Intel's investor relations site for any upcoming events, I saw the following: Reimagine the Datacenter 07/22/13 -8:00 AM PT Speaker: Diane Bryant, SVP, General Manager, Datacenter and Connected Systems Group While this seems innocent enough, and for most investors it may not appear to be of consequence, I believe that on this webcast Intel will be announcing its next generation micro-server and networking infrastructure parts based on the Silvermont core known as Avoton and Rangeley, respectively. I believe that many investors are completely unaware of the magnitude of these launches, particularly as the sell side has remained mum in light of their promotion of ARM Holdings' (ARMH) data-center aspirations. These launches will dramatically change the investing landscape, and I will detail why in this article. From Ashraf Eassa</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1374454017387</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 20:46:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374454321068-48</Id><Title>Apple Earnings on Tuesday</Title><Msg>Should be interesting although I don't expect any announcements of any new products. Heck, I never expect any announcements of new products out of Apple anymore. I guess they will talk about the new software. LOL</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1374454321068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 20:52:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374455267069-49</Id><Title>iPhone 5S/6 To Use Intel....</Title><Msg>The Apple’s AX processors will soon become obsolete. According to the new reports, an alliance between Apple &amp; Intel is taking place, and it is for sure bad news for Samsung. According to some sources, Intel &amp; Apple are amidst of a deal that involves production of a complete new range of ARM processors specially meant for mobile devices. Apple’s processors such as A5 &amp; A6 are pretty good and are doing fine with iPad 4 &amp; iPhone 5, but they are manufactured by the Samsung…its chief rival. And each year Apple is shelling out eight figure sum to Samsung to keep iPads &amp; iPhones running in the market. We will very soon be hearing about an iPhone 5S or an iPhone 6 release with Intel mobile processor this very same year.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1374455267069</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 21:07:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374455524810-50</Id><Topic><Title>Refresh Cycle For Servers Is Three Years....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1373417107875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 20:45:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And this is why Intel CEO is very bullish on Datacenters going forward.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1374455524810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 21:12:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374455671539-51</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, regarding Surface Tablet sales.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1374441240616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 17:14:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't have numbers, but I'll dig into that.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1374455671539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 21:14:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374456137713-52</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, regarding Surface Tablet sales.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1374441240616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 17:14:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I don't have numbers, but I'll dig into that." [Thanks!...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1374456137713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 21:22:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374456552487-53</Id><Title>Futures</Title><Msg>NASDAQ futures just jumped up by about 18 points from about 7 down to 11 up.. This is terrible news as it means we will have to wade through zombies tonight and in the morning. Nothing panics the zombies like a jump in the NASDAQ futures...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1374456552487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 21:29:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374458357287-54</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone 5S/6 To Use Intel....</Title><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1374455267069</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 21:07:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Published on March 14, 2013 by Mathieu Louis</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1374458357287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 21:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374458955104-55</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are trapped with over 300 million shares short....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1374145749155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 07:09:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am probably one of the longest here; we seem to be trapped by 300 million shares short too.</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1374458955104</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 22:09:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374460969989-56</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone 5S/6 To Use Intel....</Title><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1374455267069</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 21:07:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>from wsj Mr. Krzanich gave new details of plans to use the Atom technology and other new building-block components to boost the company's budding "foundry" business, which makes chips for other companies. He disclosed that Intel has been working to offer customers blocks of specialized circuitry, along with its processors, so they can mix and match combinations to create customizable chips for their products. -------------------------------- from Reuters "If there was a great customer that we had a great relationship with laptops and other mobile devices, and they said look, we'd really love you to build our ARM-based product, we'd consider it. It depends on how strategic they are," Krzanich said.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1374460969989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 22:42:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374465444754-57</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are trapped with over 300 million shares short....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1374145749155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 07:09:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, when are we going to see all this supposed short covering? Time will tell if what you expect will happen at all. All I know is that Friday shares were modestly down from the drop on Thursday. Doesn't seem shorts are concerned at all.</Msg><Username>arts.crafts2</Username><Timestamp>1374465444754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 23:57:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>