<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360991280976-1</Id><Topic><Title>Where's Moe, Lary and Curly (Wallisweaver, Ashraf and Marsavian)</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1360953194752</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 13:33:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"As I already explained, I don't have any INTC holdings but may open a long position. I am here to gain insights into INTC not ARMH. So once again I say screw u." [You bash Intel in every single post and expect us to believe that you are considering opening a long position. What part of this is believable? None...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360991280976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 00:08:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360991712225-2</Id><Topic><Title>New iPad Coming</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360979684434</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 20:54:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"First of all this question was not directed to you so but out! I notice you like to bash ARMH here as much as you like to praise INTC. I thought this was the INTC board not the ARMH bashing board. Screw u." [Any company with a P/E of 85 is fair game. Especially when their fanbois show up here and bash Intel non-stop. If your criticism was well thought out and well supported I would consider it. But it's nothing more than your half-baked unsupported opinions. Your fake outrage runneth over... ]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360991712225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 00:15:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360991999628-3</Id><Title>Haswell will render Surface RT pointless</Title><Msg>Microsoft Corporation (NASDAQ:MSFT)'s Surface Pro has arrived, to mixed reviews and criticisms of its weight and compromises. I expect this to change once Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC)'s next-generation processor, code-named Haswell, arrives later this year. Haswell will allow Surface Pro to be as light and compact as ARM processor tablets such as the Surface RT. It will also render Surface RT pointless. I've actually been surprised by the critical response to the Surface Pro, which runs the Windows 8 Pro OS on the latest gen Intel Core processors (code named Ivy Bridge). This is the first genuine tablet to run a 64-bit OS, which means it's capable of just doing just about anything a desktop can do. Running Windows 8 also endows this Surface with the ability to run Windows 7 software, which Surface RT can't do. Despite the critical reception, I expect Surface Pro to do far better than Surface RT, despite its higher price tag. According to IDC, only 900,000 Surface RT tablets were shipped in Q4 2012, giving it a worldwide tablet market share of 1.7%, behind the Barnes and Noble Nook, whose market share collapsed from 4.6% in Q4 2011 to 1.9% in Q4 2012. I believe the value proposition for the Surface Pro is much more compelling than for Surface RT. Surface Pro will appeal to the millions of Windows users who want a tablet, but not an iPad, which they consider merely a toy. Surface Pro will join the growing ranks of Windows 8 tablets and Ultrabooks (all of which will be touchscreen-based from now on), which I expect to propel Windows 8 licensing in the coming quarters. Unlike RT, Windows 8 is off to a strong start, with over 60 million licenses sold as of Microsoft Corporation (NASDAQ:MSFT)'s earnings report on Jan. 24. From Insider Monkey</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360991999628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 00:19:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360993419921-4</Id><Title>MWC 2013</Title><Msg>Tizen According to the Korean Times, Samsung will be demonstrating the first of its smartphones to run the mythical Tizen operating system. Tizen is co-owned by Samsung and Intel and is seen as the successor to Samsung's Bada platform. It will be interesting to see how Tizen compares to Android. If all goes well for Tizen maybe we'll even see Samsung ditching the Google OS from its phones in the future! From Softonic</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360993419921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 00:43:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360994447448-5</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell will render Surface RT pointless</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360991999628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 00:19:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haswell may improve the battery life of the Surface Pro by 10-20%, but its not going to get to the ballpark battery life of Android or iOS based ARM tablets. People who buy future versions of Windows 8 tablets will buy them as replacements for their laptops. So its not going to grow Intel's market share in any way.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360994447448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 01:00:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360994525044-6</Id><Title>Apple Faces Manufacturing/Fabrication Delays</Title><Msg>[Apple wanted to bring out the iPhone 6 in October of this year but will not make that date due to unknowns at TSMC regarding their 20nm production. It will therefore be sometime in 2014 or possibly further out if the ramps and yields do not go as planned. The continuous delays and problems with ARM fabrication clearly allow Intel a huge market opportunity to fill this void. Intel expects to have volume production of 14nm at the end of this year with huge capacity. Intel even while bringing out the revolutionary FinFET technology has not experienced the ramping and yield problems that have plagued the ARM camp...] "Apple will shift its chip making process from 32 nanometer to 20 nanometer process in order to add about four to eight cores. "While TSMC (Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company) is targeting a 2014 ramp in its 20nm production we think that issues like double patterning could make it a more complicated transition than the 28nm ramp, which had its own substantial ramp and yield issues," Misek added. From mobileapps</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360994525044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 01:02:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360996753354-7</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell will render Surface RT pointless</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360991999628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 00:19:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Haswell may improve the battery life of the Surface Pro by 10-20%, but its not going to get to the ballpark battery life of Android or iOS based ARM tablets." [Your usual pack of lies and distortions. From xbitlabs: "The fourth-generation Intel Core i “Haswell” processor family will enable true all-day battery life, representing the most significant battery life capability improvement in Intel history, the company revealed earlier this month. “In the first half of this year, we will launch Haswell, enabling one of the most significant changes to the PC since Centrino in 2003. Haswell was designed from the ground up to enable breakthrough innovation in form factor, battery life and usability. It will deliver the single largest generation-to-generation battery life improvement in Intel's history and it is inspiring a new wave of ultra-sleek, convertible, touch-based designs across our customer base,” said Paul Otellini, chief executive officer of Intel. The fourth-generation Intel Core i “Haswell” processor family will enable true all-day battery life, representing the most significant battery life capability improvement in Intel history, the company revealed earlier this month."] [And from Fudzilla recently: "Our sources close to Intel claim that we can expect as much as up to 70 percent more battery life compared to an equivalent Chief River (Ivy Bridge) platform. This is a huge success. Compared to an existing generation platform and even in the Shark bay Ultrabook baseline feature Intel dares to share that we can expect whole-day battery life."]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360996753354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 01:39:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360997131555-8</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell will render Surface RT pointless</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360991999628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 00:19:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's all "according to the company".</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360997131555</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 01:45:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361009087116-9</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Faces Manufacturing/Fabrication Delays</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360994525044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 01:02:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This post is false. TSMC 28nm did not have yield problems. Apple will be at Samsung 28nm this year and TSMC 20nm next year. Intel is still working on 22nm SoC. No way do they ship 14nm SoC by the end of the year.</Msg><Username>semiconductorguy</Username><Timestamp>1361009087116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 05:04:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361010387967-10</Id><Topic><Title>Semiconductor guy - have fun at tech conference</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360981203156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 21:20:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw Handel at Common Platform last week. No comment on FDSOI. TSMC owns 28nm. 20nm is not going to be a big node but TSMC should do okay with Apple. Samsung is my bet on 14nm. Samsung is Intel's biggest threat on all fronts. Samsung is gunning for Intel. Why do you say that about ARM? Where is they disarray? Intel's CEO was forced out without a replacement. That is what I call disarray.</Msg><Username>semiconductorguy</Username><Timestamp>1361010387967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 05:26:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361026657894-11</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell will render Surface RT pointless</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360991999628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 00:19:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't predict the chip market nobody can,just wishful pesimestic thinking on your part,in fact anything that would better INTC or compete with your precious ARMH your against thats obvious.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1361026657894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 09:57:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361029919058-12</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell will render Surface RT pointless</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360991999628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 00:19:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wally should close his INTC position, take the loss, and use the proceeds to go all in short armh if he's so convinced it's a bubble, though the pe as an indicator is absolutely meaningless</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1361029919058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 10:51:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361031011684-13</Id><Topic><Title>Semiconductor guy - have fun at tech conference</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360981203156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 21:20:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel's CEO was forced out without a replacement. That is what I call disarray __________________________________ Dagger</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1361031011684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 11:10:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361033846845-14</Id><Title>Extrem Ultrabook</Title><Msg>Gigabyte Unveils U2442F 14-Inch Ultrabook With “Supreme Power” by Adrian Diaconescu on February 15, 2013 at 12:31 pm Sections: Computers, Laptops 2 Share Print Friendly ↑ Gigabyte showed off a couple of Windows tablets in January, a 17-inch gaming laptop a couple of days ago and now it’s ready to debut a 14-inch ultrabook. Not too shabby for a PC manufacturer that’s not exactly a leading name in the industry, right? And this latest computing machine looks like a beast. Advertised as an “extreme” ultrabook or a laptop with “supreme power and supreme graphics”, the Gigabyte U2442F comes with a lot of heat beneath its hood. And we do mean a lot. You can choose between two state-of-the-art third-gen Intel Core i7 CPUs, 4 or 8 GB of RAM and a 128 or 256 GB SSDs. The NVIDIA GeForce GT 650M graphics card is mandatory, but we don’t think we’ll be hearing any complaints. Meanwhile, the 14-inch panel boasts a 1,600 x 900 pixels resolution, the battery is a hefty 47.73 Wh unit and connectivity options include Wi-Fi, Bluetooth 4.0, Ethernet, USB 2.0, 3.0 and HDMI. The U2442F is a beauty on the outside too, weighing just 1.59 kg, so you shouldn’t be surprised to hear it’s set to cost $1,100 and up.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1361033846845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 11:57:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361034464789-15</Id><Title>How do you preview before posting ?</Title><Msg>Is yahoo serious?</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1361034464789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 12:07:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361035106412-16</Id><Title>Aggressive impulses of an evil empire</Title><Msg>Former AMD boss Hector Ruiz has written a new book dealing with AMD’s never ending rivalry with Intel. The book is called “Slingshot” and subtitled “AMD’s Fight to Free an Industry for the Ruthless Grip of Intel.” In the book Ruiz reflects on the David vs. Goliath battle against AMD’s (much) bigger rival. He recalls his decision to file an antitrust case against Intel back in 2005. The case was settled after Intel agreed to cough up a $1.25 billion settlement in 2009, but from today’s perspective, it seems like a small price to pay for unchallenged dominance in the CPU market. Much of the book deals with AMD’s decision to take on Intel in court, in an effort called Project Slingshot. It cites numerous examples of big US and Asian PC makers being forced to reduce their orders of AMD products following Intel’s threats and sweetheart deals. The book also states that Nvidia was AMD’s first pick when it chose to get into the graphics game. However, Nvidia President Jen-Hsun Huang priced the company too high and on top of that wanted to take over leadership of AMD. As we all know, AMD chose to buy ATI instead. Other saucy details reveal the background of AMD’s Abu Dhabi deal, which eventually resulted in the Globalfoundries spinoff. “If the Abu Dhabi deal were to fall through, AMD would not survive,” Ruiz writes. “I had to do everything in my control to make it happen.” AMD survived, Globalfoundries is doing well, if not better than AMD itself. But the Intel antitrust settlement was a Pyrrhic victory and Ruiz says he found the decision disappointing. “Although I never expected the lawsuit to go to trial, I harbored hopes that Intel would admit wrong-doing,” he writes. “I also believed AMD merited damages well beyond the $1.25 billion.”</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361035106412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 12:18:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361035224061-17</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Web TV Getting Some Positive Spin</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360809161308</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:32:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your posts with factual data and or insightful analysis about Intel's products are informative and useful. But what is the above? It's a list of article headings in the form of questions "Has Intel cracked.....:, "Could Intel be......". We all know Intel is so influential in the industry that it will get press no matter what it does. It also generated tons of press when it promoted WiMAX and the investment in the wireless carrier Clearwire, when it entered the web hosting business, when it launched the media PC, etc. Today those projects ie on the trash heap of failed efforts. And they failed not for lack of good technology but poor business judgement and inexperience in the targeted market. The point is that not everything Intel does is perfect and it's OK not to drink the Intel Kool-Aid all the time. Intel does enough things right where it counts and to become hugely successul in all things mobile. Will the web TV box be successful? We shall see. First the consumer behavior monitoring and spying feature is so intrusive and so reprehensible that that feature alone could sour public sentiment against the entire effort. Further, if Intel doesn't take action to isolate the potential negative impact of this product from the rest of the company's efforts it could easily taint Intel's brand in core products where it really counts like Ultrabooks, tablets and smartphones. Consumers shouldn't have to worry about Intel spying on them via their Intel tablets and smartphones too just because its profitable to do so. However, Intel can easily fix the web TV product. All it has to do is remove the camera from the box. It serves no other purpose than to spy on the consumer. If the business model Intel created for this product rests on revenue generated from spying, then they really aren't adding enough value to the consumer and the product will die a natural death. As for Intel's web TV taking Netflix customers I'm doubtful. A lot of people purchased Netflix to reduct the cost of video programming. Netflix customers pay $20/month or less and cable HDTV packages start at about $80 and can run much higher. Intel stated this isn't a value play which means the monthly fee for the Intel service is likely to be no lower than current cable HDTV service. Therefore if one wasn't paying for cable HDTV service already they probably aren't going to become a customer of Intel's service. This product will be for those that are already cable HDTV customers and might want the additional flexibility of viewing the programming on second or third devices without having to have a settop box for each TV, plus perhaps the possibility of viewing the video content on other Intel-based portable devices. Also, what no one has talked about yet is the cost impact of using one's Internet connection to deliver all the live video programming and movies to the consumer via the Internet. Fixed price unlimited Internet service is no longer guaranteed by federal regulation. Today the FCC allows broadband ISP's to charge high usage Internet customers more. The only thing assured in the video programming business is that the cable and content companies aren't going to lose.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1361035224061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 12:20:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361036444725-18</Id><Topic><Title>Semiconductor guy - have fun at tech conference</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360981203156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 21:20:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Samsung is my bet on 14nm" It's 14nm transistor technology on a 20nm die - performance improvement will be offset by cost "Samsung is Intel's biggest threat on all fronts." Samsung is an even bigger threat to the fabless ARM players and ARM foundries. Consolidation within ARM is already taking place "Samsung is gunning for Intel" Server will be one of the growth drivers and so will be LPDRAM - server memory is extremely lucrative for Samsung and both Intel and Samsung work closely together on setting up specs. Besides Samsung has to prioritize: they face stiff competition from SNDK/Toshiba and Micron - both LPDRAM and NAND are growing "Intel's CEO was forced out without a replacement " Why would they force him out without replacement - it does not make sense. Besides that's your opinion - my opinion is that he laid all the seeds (somewhat late) to turn Intel around. Glofo, Samsung and TSMC are racing to catch up with Intel manufacturing and process technology.To me it confirms that manufacturing capabilities and process technology have become a most valuable asset. Intel is making steady progress in closing the performance gap while leveraging its manufacturing capabilities. Once again ARMs 14 nm Finfet is transistor technology on 20nm die - I think people are so afixiated on FinFet and they oversee to shrink the backend (interconnect) as well A</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361036444725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 12:40:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361036607127-19</Id><Topic><Title>Semiconductor guy - have fun at tech conference</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360981203156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 21:20:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Usually, when someone is "forced out", they are not allowed to work 6 more months until the annual shareholder meeting. They are escorted to the door immediately. The notion of being "forced out" is silly. Since Intel has a CEO until May, they will not announce their choice until nearer the May date. The choice may already be made and inked. The candidate is likely an internal candidate and the transistion may already be in progress right under the noses of everyone. ADAM LASHINSKY of CNN wrote a good article about Paul in 2005. "Is This The Right Man For Intel?" "This is why, since as far back as 2001, Otellini has been pushing for Intel to make a "right turn." No longer should it focus on processor speed for speed's sake alone. Instead it should listen to what customers want--the way a marketer, not an engineer, would approach designing products. "People still want performance, but they want other things, and we need to deliver and discuss performance in a different way," says Otellini. Now that he is becoming boss, Intel engineering is all about catering to customers. Call it the Otellini amendment to Moore's law: "This is the first time in Intel's history where the product orientation of Intel is outward-facing," he says."</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1361036607127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 12:43:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361037253064-20</Id><Topic><Title>Semiconductor guy - have fun at tech conference</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360981203156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 21:20:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They are escorted to the door immediately. The notion of being "forced out" is silly". No kidding Otellini joinded Intel when Intel was in DRAM business.... Working years in this industry are dog years...multiply by 7 . He must be one of the most senior executives in the industry</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361037253064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 12:54:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361037318026-21</Id><Title>Obama rolling on the floor laughing at those that elected him</Title><Msg>Obama, Butch Harmon to tee it up Updated: February 16, 2013, 12:02 PM ET Associated Press PALM CITY, Fla. -- Tiger Woods' former swing coach says he'll play and practice with President Barack Obama on Saturday Obama is at the Floridian resort in Palm City, Fla., for a weekend of golf with friends. Woods' coach, Butch Harmon, tells The Associated Press in a text message that he'll be with Obama on Saturday afternoon, playing nine holes and practicing. Harmon was Woods' swing coach when Woods turned pro and reached what many believe to be the peak of his game in the early 2000s. Harmon was Greg Norman's coach when he was No. 1 in the world in the 1990s. Harmon has instructed a number of top golfers and he annually ranks No. 1 on magazine lists of golf's best teachers.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1361037318026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 12:55:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361037546478-22</Id><Topic><Title>Semiconductor guy - have fun at tech conference</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360981203156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 21:20:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No more cheap ARM SoC's - that's only in addition to the increasing capital intensity the ARM ecosystem is facing...only pick the battles you can win GlobalFoundries, in its recent 14nm announcement, disclosed that the back-end will be unchanged from 20nm. This suggests a similar die size and respective increase in per-transistor cost. Further, STMicro in the Fully Depleted Transistors Technology Symposium (11 December 2012) also acknowledged that their 14nm node will have a 20nm node metal pitch and, just like GlobalFoundries, a similar die size and increase in per-transistor cost</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361037546478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 12:59:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361040419288-23</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Web TV Getting Some Positive Spin</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360809161308</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:32:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting commentary from both you and merlot 1. Unfortunately, I'm more of a pragmatist. Our share price is barely above $21. Steve Jobs always saw INTC as a bit stodgy and slow. Now you want me to believe that the tiger can change the color of its stripes....possibly, but like the good folk from Missouri, show me</Msg><Username>typea1948</Username><Timestamp>1361040419288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 13:46:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361041732317-24</Id><Topic><Title>Semiconductor guy - have fun at tech conference</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360981203156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 21:20:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"No more cheap ARM SoC's -" How much more will it cost for the same die area going forward ??</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361041732317</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 14:08:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361043430090-25</Id><Topic><Title>Semiconductor guy - have fun at tech conference</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360981203156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 21:20:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In an article about a year ago, EETimes estimate of cost increase per wafer was 90% from 28nm (not 20nm). The increase in wafer cost drops to 60% with EUV. Does that match your estimates. If the hybrid 14nm devices are similar in size to the 20nm parts, then they would be about 30% smaller in die per side than the 28nm parts. We have more data at 28nm than 20nm. "The cost of 14-nm wafers made with today’s 193-nm immersion lithography systems will be more than 90 percent greater than the cost of today’s 28-nm wafers. EUV would shave that increase to just under 60 percent, van den Hove estimated in his talk" IEDM: Moore’s Law seen hitting big bump at 14 nm Rick Merritt 12/11/2012 12:01 AM EST</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1361043430090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 14:37:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361043794562-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama rolling on the floor laughing at those that elected him</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1361037318026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 12:55:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't blame Obama for practicing for the Senior tour. He doesn't have any other pressing manners.....</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1361043794562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 14:43:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361046073408-27</Id><Title>Intel Wins X2Y Patent Case Said to Threaten U.S. Jobs</Title><Msg>Intel successfully defended itself against X2Y in patent lawsuits. Intel didn’t infringe the three patents and two are invalid. These were targeting Core i7 systems but it apeared that if upheld, they could also be applied to SoC with VTR, radios, .... Intel Wins X2Y Patent Case Said to Threaten U.S. Jobs By Susan Decker - Feb 15, 2013 5:04 PM PT The U.S. International Trade Commission upheld, with modifications, trade Judge David Shaw’s findings that Intel didn’t violate the patent rights of closely held X2Y Attenuators LLC. Hewlett-Packard Co. and Apple Inc., which use Intel chips, were also named in the ITC complaint. Notice of the decision was posted yesterday on the agency’s website. X2Y asked the trade agency to block Intel’s chips using its technology from entering the U.S. The case drew the attention of lawmakers from both political parties who said a loss for Intel could harm U.S. jobs, because Intel does initial manufacturing work in the U.S. and final assembly in other countries. The X2Y patents cover ways to overcome electromagnetic interference that can damage electronics. The company, which develops methods for improving the performance of circuits, licenses its inventions to Samsung Electronics Co., the world’s biggest maker of computer-memory chips. It doesn’t make any chips of its own. Shaw said Intel didn’t infringe the three patents and two are invalid. The commission altered the judge’s interpretation of some patent terms without changing his underlying finding. The commission said it would more fully explain its reasoning in an opinion to be issued later.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1361046073408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 15:21:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361048227782-28</Id><Topic><Title>Where's Moe, Lary and Curly (Wallisweaver, Ashraf and Marsavian)</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1360953194752</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 13:33:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're not very bright are you? Why else would I be tracking INTC's technical chart if not to identify the best possible entry point. The idea when investing is to buy low and sell high... a basic fact that seems to elude you according to what others say about your INTC investment record.. Anyway, believe whatever you want... I don't care.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1361048227782</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 15:57:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361050100944-29</Id><Topic><Title>Semiconductor guy - have fun at tech conference</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360981203156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 21:20:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the hybrid 14nm devices are similar in size to the 20nm parts, then they would be about 30% smaller in die per side than the 28nm parts. Which which leads to the question how would it compare to 14nm SoC Intel part? When Glofo goes from 20nm to 14nm hybrid there would be still the same number of dies because they can't shrink the interconnect portion.... Fabless-Foundry Model Under Stress Intel has taken a big lead in the process race and the foundries are struggling to keep up. In addition, the cost-per-transistor curve has been falling at about 29% per node (I would assume this implies a real shrink and not a hybrid approach) to enable cheaper systems. At 28nm and 20nm, however, the curve is leveling off at the foundries (inceasing capital intensity and all the 16 points quoted in slide presentation posted WW). “The fabless companies at the leading-edge, such as Nvidia and Qualcomm, are visibly concerned about their foundries’ ability to keep up with Moore’s Law,” said G. Dan Hutcheson, president of VLSI Research. “To stay in the game, they need a steady decline in cost-per-transistor. If (the curve levels off), this certainly puts into question the common wisdom that the fabless-foundry model is impenetrable.”</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361050100944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 16:28:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361052264607-30</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Web TV Getting Some Positive Spin</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360809161308</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:32:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, let me begin by saying that I am very protective about a person's right to privacy. I myself am a very private person and I am against all forms of government and corporate invasion of privacy. But you seem to be accusing Intel of having developed its web TV project of the sheer purpose of spying on people and I don't think that's the case. I think their motive is the normal one for a corporation - profits and expanding the ecosystem. You also seem to believe that this is a novel and new capability being used in a nefarious way. It's not. Cameras are everywhere today including most cell phones. It's just an expansion of technology beyond voice to video. Even the identification part of it is not new and is currently being used in many, many places. I would be more concerned it one couldn't simply turn the camera off. And if that is considered a leap of faith one could simply put the device in an opaque box or put something in front of or over it. I'm pretty sure the camera will not see through solid objects or the Intel stock price would be 1600 by now. I don't believe Intel will get bad press because of the camera simply because it can be turned off or incapacitated and because similar devices are in common use. If you have a big problem with Intel's web TV camera, then you should have an equally big problem with Skype or cell phone cameras. Do you have a problem with Skype? As far as the criticism goes of this being a distraction or that it is not in Intel's expertise, I don't agree with it. The project isn't being done by the processor development group. It's being done by a new and separate group and their credentials, background and experience appear to be quite good. Because it's a separate group I don't believe it will be a distraction from core activities. As the upside is about $19 billion a year in revenues it seems like it is worth a shot. I applaud Intel for attempting to free themselves of prior non-performance with a new team and a new approach. It would be an extremely useful addition to Intel's ecosystem. It's the kind of thing Apple would be applauded for doing. If I am so lucky as to have access to Intel's web TV, I will probably just throw a box on top of it except for those explicit times when I need its capability. You might consider this approach it its non-camera capabilities appeal to you. Regardless, thank you for your comments...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361052264607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 17:04:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361052889457-31</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Faces Manufacturing/Fabrication Delays</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360994525044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 01:02:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This post is false. TSMC 28nm did not have yield problems. Apple will be at Samsung 28nm this year and TSMC 20nm next year. Intel is still working on 22nm SoC. No way do they ship 14nm SoC by the end of the year." [It's an established fact that TSMC had problems ramping their 28nm production. There is such a huge volume of knowledge supporting this that I'm surprised that even you would do something so stupid as to deny it. I'm still waiting on you or any of the other ARM shills to refute any of the 16 points of why ARMs fabrication is toast. The conclusion is inescapable - the fabless model is broken. Declining economics, ramps, number of players, funding, designs supported and on and on. Go ahead, address each of them point by point. But try to skip the gross distortions like TSMC didn't have any problems ramping 28nm... ] [Dnenni, it you need to make stuff up then you can probably get DanaLucy and the merry band of paid shills to help you...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361052889457</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 17:14:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361053772595-32</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell will render Surface RT pointless</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360991999628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 00:19:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's all "according to the company"." [Intel announced a month ago that Haswell was in production. After it comes out you can come back here and eat your words. Plan on a big meal...] You, Dnenni and DanaLucy remind me more and more of Baghdad Bob: Actual Quotes From the Iraqi Information Minister (aka 'Baghdad Bob') "There are no American infidels in Baghdad. Never!" "My feelings - as usual - we will slaughter them all" "Our initial assessment is that they will all die" "I blame Al-Jazeera - they are marketing for the Americans!" "God will roast their stomachs in hell at the hands of Iraqis." 'We have destroyed 2 tanks, fighter planes, 2 helicopters and their shovels - We have driven them back." "Surrender or be burned in their tanks." "No I am not scared and neither should you be!" "We have them surrounded in their tanks" Britain "is not worth an old shoe." Of U.S. troops: "They are most welcome. We will butcher them." "We will welcome them with bullets and shoes."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361053772595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 17:29:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361054331125-33</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Faces Manufacturing/Fabrication Delays</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360994525044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 01:02:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Walllisweaver can you provide a link that verifies that Apple is experiencing delays or is this someone's Seeking Alpha opinion?</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1361054331125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 17:38:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361055802886-34</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Faces Manufacturing/Fabrication Delays</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360994525044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 01:02:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google: Apple's 4.8-Inch iPhone 6 Reportedly Not Launching Until Mid-2014 Lots of posts on this Or try: tomshardwareDOTcom/news/iOS-iPhone-6-iPhone-5S-IGZO-OLED,21091.html</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361055802886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 18:03:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361056386569-35</Id><Title>"Apple faces manufacturing delays" is a RUMOR</Title><Msg>Wallisweaver posted this like it was a fact. Somebody please clean this board up. It's become a disgrace.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1361056386569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 18:13:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361058233002-36</Id><Topic><Title>"Apple faces manufacturing delays" is a RUMOR</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1361056386569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 18:13:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tomshardwareDOTcom/news/iOS-iPhone-6-iPhone-5S-IGZO-OLED,21091.html</Msg><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1361058233002</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 18:43:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361059957892-37</Id><Topic><Title>"Apple faces manufacturing delays" is a RUMOR</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1361056386569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 18:13:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, it's a rumor posted on tons of tech web sites. On top of that it's merely confirmation of what we already knew. We knew that TSMC 20nm production in the volumes Apple needs wasn't going to be available in 2013. Well, I guess you didn't know because no one printed on your forehead in reverse print so you could read it in the mirror. If you want to clean up this board start with some of the myriad ARM fanboi lies, distortions and fabrications. You obviously have no problem whatsoever with them...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361059957892</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 19:12:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361061711010-38</Id><Title>Note to board: BEWARE of WALLISWEAVER</Title><Msg>All three have an agenda and aren't afraid to flat out lie or post rumor as fact. I've watched Wallisweaver say Intel was a strong buy at 29, I've watched him say ARM was a strong sell at 22 and now he's just flat out posting rumors as fact. All he does is cut and paste articles from the internet as if they are the gospel. He's been HIDEOUSLY wrong on his Intel and ARM stock price predictions and is exactly what is wrong with message boards.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1361061711010</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 19:41:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361062287814-39</Id><Topic><Title>Note to board: BEWARE of WALLISWEAVER</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1361061711010</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 19:41:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Meant to say beware of WALLISWEAVER, GETANID61 and KHITCHDEE. Wally would sell his mother to see Intel at 30 and the other two are ARM employees.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1361062287814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 19:51:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361062705358-40</Id><Topic><Title>Note to board: BEWARE of WALLISWEAVER</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1361061711010</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 19:41:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Post of the decade. Pin it, and ask Wally to dispute any of the facts you laid out. He can't.</Msg><Username>walrusweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361062705358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 19:58:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361065444807-41</Id><Title>TSMC 28nm Yield was very good actually</Title><Msg>Just to make the point again that Wallis Weaver doesn't know what he is talking about. You folks are mostly financial types so look at the financial side of TSMC process ramps: 28nm % of Revenue Q1. 2% (Q1 2012) Q2. 7% Q3. 14% 4Q. 20% (my guess) Compared to 65nm and 40nm: 65nm Q1. 1% Q2. 3% Q3. 7% Q4. 10% 40nm Q1.</Msg><Username>semiconductorguy</Username><Timestamp>1361065444807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 20:44:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361069073241-42</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC 28nm Yield was very good actually</Title><Username>semiconductorguy</Username><Timestamp>1361065444807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 20:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Compared to 65nm" kind of a low bar....kind of embarrassing 10% within one year time frame. No? Bottom line acccording to DD time (couple weeks ago) Mediatek still can't secure sufficient number of 28nm wafers - and new smart phone launch delayed by several months and regards yields - keep in mind I keep a very close ear what vendors like LRCX, NVLS and KLAC were saying about this...</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361069073241</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 21:44:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361069257039-43</Id><Title>Subject</Title><Msg>Gahh, why don't these guys get it? 1920x1080 or bust.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1361069257039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 21:47:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361069615857-44</Id><Topic><Title>Extrem Ultrabook</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1361033846845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 11:57:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I really wish this came with a 1920x1080 display. The screen is what makes or breaks the quality of these devices.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1361069615857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 21:53:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361070365696-45</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Faces Manufacturing/Fabrication Delays</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360994525044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 01:02:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wallisweaver, Just to clarify: TSMC noted on its CC that 20nm would begin production in 2014.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1361070365696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 22:06:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361070963390-46</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC 28nm Yield was very good actually</Title><Username>semiconductorguy</Username><Timestamp>1361065444807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 20:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It looks like the ramps are about the same IF you consider revenue. There was probably less demand for 65nm and 40nm than their was for 28nm. TSMC could charge higher prices relatively for the 28nm. 28nm is 100% on 300mm which should increase the volume of 28nm die. 28nm % of Revenue Q0 1% (My guess) Q1. 2% (Q1 2012) Q2. 7% Q3. 14% Compared to 65nm and 40nm: 65nm Q1. 1% Q2. 3% Q3. 7% Q4. 10%</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1361070963390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 22:16:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361071188602-47</Id><Topic><Title>Obama rolling on the floor laughing at those that elected him</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1361037318026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 12:55:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pressing manners? You must have had a brain cramp.</Msg><Username>northvisitor34</Username><Timestamp>1361071188602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 22:19:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361071256992-48</Id><Topic><Title>Obama rolling on the floor laughing at those that elected him</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1361037318026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 12:55:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good for Obama. Needs to get out an relax after having to put up with blockheaded, lazy Republicans.</Msg><Username>northvisitor34</Username><Timestamp>1361071256992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 22:20:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361071327647-49</Id><Topic><Title>Note to board: BEWARE of WALLISWEAVER</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1361061711010</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 19:41:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah, I see - a lame after-the-fact attempt to be fair and balanced. And how about the Lucy et al crowd, Mr. Fair and Balanced. Was he (they) ever "HIDEOUSLY wrong " like me? He has recommended shorting Intel ever since 17.67, even when Intel ran all the way up to 29+. How exactly is it that you missed identifying him for your bile and venom explosion? But I'm sure you'll get some nice supportive responses from one of the DanaLucy crowd IDs, if this isn't one itself. In the meantime, enjoy your cup of hypocrisy. I see you actually bought a six-pack...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361071327647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 22:22:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361071979721-50</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC 28nm Yield was very good actually</Title><Username>semiconductorguy</Username><Timestamp>1361065444807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 20:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One last comment: you need to differentiate between SiON and HKMG - the problem related to HKMG. Many customers QCOM?) selected the more conservative approach: SiON therefore TSMC probably experienced a combination of HKMG yield issues as well as capacity shortage. The vast majority of TSMC 28nm wafers in 2012 were SiON</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361071979721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 22:32:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361072167798-51</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Faces Manufacturing/Fabrication Delays</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360994525044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 01:02:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the clarification. I wish I could remember whose article said that TSMC needed volume 20nm production by the middle of this year to satisfy Apple's needs and stay competitive. It wasn't yours was it? Obviously just beginning production in 2014 is going to open the door wide for Intel...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361072167798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 22:36:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361072525649-52</Id><Title>How Good Was TSMCs 28nm Ramp?</Title><Msg>Yeah, here's how good it was. Check these headlines: TSMC Admits 28nm Ramp Up Is Taking Longer than Expected ... Nvidia suffers as TSMC's 28nm ramp steeper than expected TSMC profit soars despite 28-nm supply shortage TSMC's 28-nm process in trouble, says analyst - EE Times Multiple Foundries Face Slow 28nm Ramp Due to Manufacturing ... MC: Will 28nm Ramp Have Yield Problems as 40nm? | AMD ...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361072525649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 22:42:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361073045526-53</Id><Topic><Title>How Good Was TSMCs 28nm Ramp?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361072525649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 22:42:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As I said, Dnenni, there is a great body of evidence of how TSMC struggled with 28nm. Go ahead and make my day by continuing to draw attention to their ramp failure. PS. Still waiting on you to address any of the 16 reasons why ARMs fabrication is toast...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361073045526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 22:50:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361074429299-54</Id><Topic><Title>How Good Was TSMCs 28nm Ramp?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361072525649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 22:42:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anybody that thinks that TSMC's 28nm ramp wasn't tough is delusional.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1361074429299</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 23:13:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361075363537-55</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Faces Manufacturing/Fabrication Delays</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360994525044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 01:02:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wallisweaver, I actually think that was Mr. Russ Fischer, but I agree: Apple switching to TSMC makes very little sense...they're running full capacity trying to service everyone as it is. I still think Apple sticks with Samsung. JMHO, though.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1361075363537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 23:29:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361076652673-56</Id><Title>When Apple announces Intel Atom chips in its Ipad, this stock should spike up.</Title><Msg>And its coming.. If I were Apple, the choice is simple, TSMC or Intel. I know I'd go with Intel, especially since ARM is performance limited.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361076652673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 23:50:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361077003905-57</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Faces Manufacturing/Fabrication Delays</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360994525044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 01:02:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't find the article that I was referring to (yet) but here is some of what Russ had to say on 28nm: "As a foundry, TSMC has the responsibility to maintain leading edge manufacturing technologies as well as a multitude of older technologies suitable for less advanced customers. The latest leading edge technology at TSMC is 28nm. TSMC has had a great deal of trouble getting the 28nm (and the preceding 40nm) processes into volume production with high yield. TSMC is about 1 1/2 nodes behind Intel. As such, their customers, such as QCOM and NVDA will also be 1 1/2 nodes behind with their products, thus putting TSMC customers at a large disadvantage to Intel." From: Intel: The Semiconductor Winner In The Mobile War</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361077003905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 23:56:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>