<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374465612181-1</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone 5S/6 To Use Intel....</Title><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1374455267069</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 21:07:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel should be peddling their foundry service on Silicon Valley's major players. If they strategically market what advantages they can provide via quantity price, and chip superiority, then we could have a big win for Intel.</Msg><Username>arts.crafts2</Username><Timestamp>1374465612181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-22 00:00:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374466207725-2</Id><Topic><Title>Unfortunately, we are down tomorrow</Title><Username>typea1948</Username><Timestamp>1374178883280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 16:21:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, because you are obviously defending Obama-miscare, that doesn't give a cr-p about our own military, which they have proven time and time again. It's all about stealing the money from the real citizens of the US to provide for the moochers who crawl over the border and continents to rape the US for everything they can benefit from. With a raving socialist-Markist in control of the US, backed by a sick Democratic-controlled Senate of morons, anyone who defends Obama and his destruction of the US needs a brain transplant.</Msg><Username>arts.crafts2</Username><Timestamp>1374466207725</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-22 00:10:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374466663305-3</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone 5S/6 To Use Intel....</Title><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1374455267069</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 21:07:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel should be peddling their foundry service" What makes you think that Intel is not "peddling their foundry service" ?? Any significant contract would be protected by a non-disclosure clause that would prevent Intel from releasing information. Any information that reached the public would appear to be a rumor.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1374466663305</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-22 00:17:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374467738387-4</Id><Topic><Title>Unfortunately, we are down tomorrow</Title><Username>typea1948</Username><Timestamp>1374178883280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 16:21:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is it that conservatives hate everyone that disagrees with them? Do you think words like raping and stealing lead to civil discourse? If you continue to engage in this kind of rhetoric you are never going to win another election.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1374467738387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-22 00:35:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>