<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357016798671-1</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking News: Deal reached, we open up 1000 Wednesday</Title><Username>backstreetboy_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357008479495</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 21:47:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually the republicans have taken the advantage from Obama, because now they can demand huge spending cuts before raising the debt ceiling.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1357016798671</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 00:06:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357016975930-2</Id><Title>If the GOP demands too much spending cuts before raising the debt ceiling, Obama</Title><Msg>will have to declare the debt ceiling unconstitutional and let the supreme court decide. The constitution says the U.S will pay all its debts.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1357016975930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 00:09:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357021765676-3</Id><Title>Wednesday SHORTY BLOOD BATH HA HA HA HA!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>YOU DESERVE IT FOR ALL THE BASHING YOU BSTDS NOW LOOSE EVERY PEENY YOU HAVE IN PRKS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>fairwarning50</Username><Timestamp>1357021765676</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 01:29:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357023409612-4</Id><Title>Wallis, did you read HP article?</Title><Msg>It says that HP may dispose of units that don't meet targets. Which units do you suppose are at risk? I find it hard to believe that it will be the personal system and printing group. They just recently combined them to reduce costs to allow for increased profit margin. So I wonder which ones. What do you think? Or is this something that the articles are putting too much emphasis on.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357023409612</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 01:56:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357049805927-5</Id><Topic><Title>Bought 1,000 @ $20.32</Title><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356735827470</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:03:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am holding 750 shares which I paid $21.05. I sold 1,400 shares because I would like to buy at lower if it goes. 1,000 was b0ught at $20.32 and 400 was bought at $20.20.</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1357049805927</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 09:16:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357050580545-6</Id><Title>Intel TV setup-box - best article</Title><Msg>from theverge Intel reportedly plans to launch its internet TV service in a limited number of cities By T.C. Sottek on December 29, 2012 05:47 pm Email @LaughingStoic Citing a video industry source, TechCrunch reports that Intel plans to offer its TV service in a limited number of markets after facing difficulty signing deals with content owners. Earlier this year, reports from The Wall Street Journal and Reuters indicated that Intel could enter the content distribution business with its own Intel-branded, web-based TV service and set-top box by the end of 2012; the service is said to blend traditional TV offerings like sports with streaming services that are all delivered over a customer's existing internet connection. It wasn't clear at the time if Intel would deliver on that schedule — the WSJ said in March that the company hadn't made any content deals yet — and it looks like the company will have to make some concessions to get content providers interested in its plans. Ambitious features could be holding back Intel's service Intel's plans are said to include some ambitious features, which could be a cause for the media industry's reluctance to provide their content. For instance, TechCrunch says that Intel's service could let users watch any programming aired within the last month for channels they subscribe to. By comparison, Dish Network's PrimeTime Anytime feature allows users to record all primetime content from ABC, CBS, Fox, and NBC nightly and store it for eight days. It's also said to be working on innovative set-top box technology, including a system that would allow it to broadcast targeted ads using facial recognition, which could provide information like age and gender to marketers. There still doesn't seem to be a solid timeframe for an announcement, but TechCrunch says that Intel plans to rollout the service "soon."</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357050580545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 09:29:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357051587088-7</Id><Title>A few words about yesterdays Outperform by Wells Fargo.</Title><Msg>Yesterday Analyst David Wong reiterated an Outperform rating on the shares of Intel. According to TipRanks Add-On here are a few interesting statistics that they collected: 1) his average return on each of his stock recommendations (compared to the S&amp;P500) is -4.7% 2) out of 27 recommendations of his only 13 outperformed the market 3) he is ranked pretty among other analysts. TipRanks is a browser add on that automatically displays financial experts statistics when reading relevant texts so that individual invesors will know if they should listen to an analyst or not.. In his case i would do the opposite :-)</Msg><Username>donnapinkwater</Username><Timestamp>1357051587088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 09:46:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357051901469-8</Id><Topic><Title>If the GOP demands too much spending cuts before raising the debt ceiling, Obama</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1357016975930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 00:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem is that the sum of the approved, authorized expenditures exceeds the debt celing. If more spending is approved than is authorized by the ceiling, which approved law takes precedence holds: the ceiling or the spending authorization for all the passed laws ? The US debt started early in the republic as a way to pay for wars, especially the War of 1812. In 1917, the US Congress passed the Second Liberty Bond Act to get away from individual approvals and established the ceiling. It is about 100 years since the last major revision in the US debt mechanism and I think we are in for another change. The ceiling negotiation process is not good for the US credit rating and some other mechanism is needed. I would like to see the "ceiling" be changed to an accounting total so Congress and the people will know what commitments have been made. The Senate Fiscal Cliff Roll call vote: Measure Number: H.R. 8 (Job Protection and Recession Prevention Act of 2012 ) Measure Title: An act entitled the "American Taxpayer Relief Act of 2012". Vote Counts: YEAs 89 NAYs 8 Not Voting 3 NAYs ---8 Bennet (D-CO) Carper (D-DE) Grassley (R-IA) Harkin (D-IA) Lee (R-UT) Paul (R-KY) Rubio (R-FL) Shelby (R-AL) Not Voting - 3 DeMint (R-SC) Kirk (R-IL) Lautenberg (D-NJ)</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1357051901469</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 09:51:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357051983494-9</Id><Topic><Title>Intel TV setup-box - best article</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357050580545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 09:29:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What this article says that other articles did not mention is that the TV service will be thru IP protocol ie. thru the internet. This is what I think it means: 1) Aside from offering streaming services like Netflix, hulu, amazon prime....and movie rental streaming, Intel will be offering customers the choice to pick only the channels they are interested in. The kicker here is that the live TV channels will be shown thru the internet thereby Intel is by-passing the cable operators. This is like circumventing Cable TV as we know it! So as long as you have ANY internet connection you can sign up with the Intel TV service! This also means that Intel won't be negotiating with cable operators, but will be negotiating with content providers (eg. fox network, espn). 2) There may be a back-end piece to this service. In order to allow customers to watch any programs of their selected channels in the last month, there must be some massive data center to store all these programs.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357051983494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 09:53:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357052919994-10</Id><Topic><Title>A few words about yesterdays Outperform by Wells Fargo.</Title><Username>donnapinkwater</Username><Timestamp>1357051587088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 09:46:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another interesting insight is that higher ranked analysts with 75% success rate recommend selling Intel. google out TipRanks.</Msg><Username>donnapinkwater</Username><Timestamp>1357052919994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 10:08:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357053275201-11</Id><Topic><Title>Bought 1,000 @ $20.32</Title><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1356735827470</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:03:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the way, you made a wise choice. INTC will easily go over $22.00. In the meantime, it could go lower.</Msg><Username>stocks2mm</Username><Timestamp>1357053275201</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 10:14:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357053291475-12</Id><Topic><Title>If the GOP demands too much spending cuts before raising the debt ceiling, Obama</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1357016975930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 00:09:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>14th amendment. Yes, I think Obama should do that anyway. These GOP's are the worst thing since Osama Bin Laden.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1357053291475</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 10:14:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357053353996-13</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, did you read HP article?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357023409612</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 01:56:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The real HP walked 12 years ago with Agilent.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1357053353996</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 10:15:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357054226893-14</Id><Topic><Title>I'm surprised there were no more news regarding Merrifield (redhookbay)</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1356990264045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 16:44:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks...this is interesting.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357054226893</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 10:30:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357054807125-15</Id><Title>THE ONE-MAN PUMPER PARADE</Title><Msg>Will he continue the non-stop pumping in 2013? His work is cut out for him as Smelltel is poised to return to the teens. HI-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1357054807125</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 10:40:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357054988462-16</Id><Topic><Title>A few words about yesterdays Outperform by Wells Fargo.</Title><Username>donnapinkwater</Username><Timestamp>1357051587088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 09:46:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where does Goldman's James Covello rank? just curious.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357054988462</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 10:43:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357055220208-17</Id><Topic><Title>A few words about yesterdays Outperform by Wells Fargo.</Title><Username>donnapinkwater</Username><Timestamp>1357051587088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 09:46:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you are short right here. Let's see how you do. What price will you cover at?</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357055220208</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 10:47:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357055453545-18</Id><Title>SMELLTEL WAS THE 2nd WORST PERFORMER IN THE DOW IN 2012</Title><Msg>Only worse performer was HPQ. Smelltel lost more than $3 per share in 2012.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1357055453545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 10:50:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357055613702-19</Id><Topic><Title>SMELLTEL WAS THE 2nd WORST PERFORMER IN THE DOW IN 2012</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1357055453545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 10:50:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does this mean INTC will perform poorly again in 2013? We will have to wait and see.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357055613702</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 10:53:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357056118418-20</Id><Topic><Title>SMELLTEL WAS THE 2nd WORST PERFORMER IN THE DOW IN 2012</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1357055453545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 10:50:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Original poster's history: Traded Intel for Cisco at 20 in 2010, watched Intel go to 29.....watched Cisco go to 13 and makes this board pay for that dreadful mistake every minute of every day.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357056118418</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 11:01:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357056412360-21</Id><Topic><Title>I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1293550442000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-12-28 10:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice trade. Intel rose 50% and Cisco dropped 50 percent since that trade and in 2 years you still haven't made a dime. Other than Intel longs, who's your daddie?</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357056412360</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 11:06:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357056482623-22</Id><Topic><Title>A few words about yesterdays Outperform by Wells Fargo.</Title><Username>donnapinkwater</Username><Timestamp>1357051587088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 09:46:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many of the analysts have a high rating (4- or 5-star) on their Intel calls. Virtually all of them are within the Intel forecast range and rarely move outside the Intel +/- $500mil revenue range. Their value added seems to be the translation of that revenue into profits and profit margin. For the last two years, Intel has beat their mid-point revenue and profit results. The analysts have simply said "Oooops! Intel did better than expected but the future for them looks dim." When they change their Intel revenue forecasts, they change it by $100mill and the new value is still within the Intel range but they reiterate or add more bad news. This game allows them to spin their negative and also keep a high rating.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1357056482623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 11:08:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357056505524-23</Id><Topic><Title>I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1293550442000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-12-28 10:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL at Lucy_nuff aka Toooofunnny Re: I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO by nuff105.Dec 31, 2011 9:54 PM.Permalink LOL! That was the Intel that he said was a BUY at 24.....after he capitulated (loss #1) that he then sold at 20(loss #2)........got into CSCO and road that down as well to 13 (loss#3). HA! You can't make this stuff up! LUCY is SCORCHED with losses yet claims to be "the only one that ever gets anything right around here." PRICE-FREAKING-LESS !</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357056505524</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 11:08:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357057073882-24</Id><Title>Proof positive that the Republicans got screwed in the end.</Title><Msg>".President Obama Praises Senate Agreement on Bill to Avert Fiscal Cliff." Bend over Fux news watching losers. Listen to Fux tell you that you won but look at the President with his BIG freaking smile and then KNOW that you LOST again. I think Fux was telling you that Romney was going to win. They were telling you that there was NO way for Obama care to get made into law. They were telling you that the Supreme Court would of course make same unconstitutional. Basically, Fux laughs at you losers and just makes money spewing propaganda that makes you feel good but like a bad girlfriend, in the end Fux screws you and walks away.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1357057073882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 11:17:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357057454165-25</Id><Title>Sweet Joe Biden walked in and made a deal and THE GOP kissed Obummers rump.</Title><Msg>The final vote count on the deal in the senate was 88 votes for. I am pretty sure that the big smile on Obummers face is not a good sign for you repukes.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1357057454165</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 11:24:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357057482269-26</Id><Topic><Title>Proof positive that the Republicans got screwed in the end.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1357057073882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 11:17:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only you and your undeducated breatheren would cheer for a guy that is going to raise the National Debt from 11 trillion to 22 trillion in eight years...........after he condemed Bush for raising it....called him unpatriotic. What did you win? The right to ruin the future for our children and their children in eight short years? You go, girl.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357057482269</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 11:24:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357058382111-27</Id><Topic><Title>Proof positive that the Republicans got screwed in the end.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1357057073882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 11:17:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This forever trainwreck started with Ronald Reagan, who TRIPLED our national debt. HWB and CLinton were good Pres's adnd I need not remind you that Clinton ran a surplus in his last 2.5 years. This, of course, was followed by the disastrous spending spree and tax cuts of W. who delivered this economic disaster, followed by your Tea-Baggers who are the witless agents of the bad billionaires (everyone below Buffet and Gates on the list) . Even if you won't pin the tail on the GOP, Obama will only have doubled the debt, pale in comparison to your hero, Ronny Altzheimers Reagan, the worst president of the US.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1357058382111</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 11:39:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357061392589-28</Id><Topic><Title>Intel TV setup-box - best article</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357050580545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 09:29:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's an even better article Intel Reportedly Showing Internet Based Cable Box at CES According to TechCrunch, Intel may very well be showing a new cable box at CES, designed to be supported not by lines on the poles, but by the internet connection you already possess (or, you know, hopefully a slightly faster one). Tied to an Intel-manufactured box, this service would hypothetically pass the savings on to customers, and directly compete with the traditional cable providers who currently have a stranglehold on the market. The problem is of course, that the big boys like Comcast and Time Warner don’t especially want competition, and if Intel is going to be offering more for less money, they could run into problems: Intel wants to keep its costs down by licensing smaller packages of TV networks instead of replicating the basic cable TV bundle of more than 100 channels. But network owners won’t agree to smaller bundles without being paid a premium for the channels they choose to license. “Why would I want you to take subscribers away from another distributor at a lower price?,” asked the same media executive who spoke with Reuters on condition of anonymity. To change that mindset, Intel has assembled a team of television industry veterans well-schooled in negotiating distribution deals. Leading the group as head of Intel Media is Erik Huggers, who worked on media at Microsoft before going to the BBC. Huggers enlisted as an adviser Garth Ancier, who most recently served as president for BBC Worldwide America and before that worked at NBC, FOX, and Disney. The big advantage that Intel is offering in exchange for reduced licensing fees is laser-targeted advertising, which we’ve covered before. By using built-in cameras to recognize gender, age, and other features, Intel’s tech could allow content providers to charge more for ads that are more likely to appeal to the viewer, because a 75-year old probably isn’t interested in Halo so much as Polygrip. Intel’s tech also includes the potential for an interactive layer, allowing viewers to click on ads for more information about the products, but that’s not a feature that has proven particularly popular in other mediums like Apple’s iAd. While Intel is certainly interested in making a lot of settop boxes, and selling a lot of servers to support them, it remains to be seen if they can actually cut enough deals to make it practical, or offer enough channels to be appealing to consumers. At some point, there will be a company that cracks the Internet cable thing, likely in the form of smaller packages of channels that cost more (but will probably end up costing you less), but I think it’ll be more likely to be Hulu, Netflix, Amazon, or some other company that already has extensive content deals, and enough clout and money to gain a foothold. And I’m sure Intel will be there to capitalize on it when it does. Via: [TechCrunch]</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357061392589</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:29:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357061434115-29</Id><Topic><Title>Proof positive that the Republicans got screwed in the end.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1357057073882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 11:17:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis cornholed his sister! In return, Wallis got cornholed by INTC!!! HI-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1357061434115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:30:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357061471261-30</Id><Topic><Title>Intel TV setup-box - best article</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357050580545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 09:29:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The target marketing will eventually be seen as beneficial to viewers ( no ED commercials or racy movie trailers screened to young children, for instance). When answering machines were first deployed, people recoiled and refused to 'talk to a machine'. Get used to the future. Big brother only wants to sell you stuff to improve your life; and that's a good thing for everyone. 2013 may prove to be quite transformative for this "boring old" chip company.</Msg><Username>livingsez</Username><Timestamp>1357061471261</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:31:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357061898252-31</Id><Title>Intel TV will fail miserably if they still intend on spying on people</Title><Msg>Unbelievable that they haven't scrapped that idea.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357061898252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:38:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357062189612-32</Id><Topic><Title>Proof positive that the Republicans got screwed in the end.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1357057073882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 11:17:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>got screwed in the end ---------------------- That's Waldo's dream! TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1357062189612</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:43:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357062228059-33</Id><Topic><Title>Intel TV will fail miserably if they still intend on spying on people</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357061898252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:38:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you always been a Luddite? Or, is this where you draw the line? I suspect the former :-)</Msg><Username>livingsez</Username><Timestamp>1357062228059</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:43:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357062725086-34</Id><Topic><Title>Intel TV will fail miserably if they still intend on spying on people</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357061898252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:38:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I fear Technology because I don't want to be spied on by advertisers in my own house who's only goal is to separate me from my money? You an your vocabluary can G.F.Y.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357062725086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:52:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357062848069-35</Id><Topic><Title>Great news !</Title><Username>webereddie696</Username><Timestamp>1357062184364</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:43:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks !</Msg><Username>guilfordleo</Username><Timestamp>1357062848069</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:54:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357062965176-36</Id><Title>Google to bring the most advanced smartphone yet</Title><Msg>Written by Damir Brodjanac According to the Wall Street Journal, Google is preparing the ground for the launch of a new high-end Android smartphone, which will seek to topple Apple and its iPhone. The new phone will be created by Motorola and in the current phase it carries the code name X phone and is expected to be launched sometime in 2013. Google and Motorola will apparently build this phone with many of the characteristics that have so far remained unseen in hardware and software of existing smart phones. However, currently there are no further details about what that will be specifically. Google's main intent is to get this handset to stand out among others, which means it should have some unique capabilities. Current rumors going around are that it will have a bendable screen and software solutions that have not yet appeared on the Android platform. In any case, this does not surprise us at all (if true of course), since Google bought Motorola last year, everyone has been waiting for something like this, a superphone from Google that could challenge Apple and perhaps even more Android competitors like Samsung, Sony and HTC. Given that Google has fired 4000 Motorola employees and agreed to sell off the TV set-top box department, it could be said that the restructuring after the acquisition is complete and now nothing stands in the way of putting them in concrete production. [Ed – Apple already has serious competition from Samsung and it looks like it will gain even more directly from Google. Right now the Samsung Galaxy S III is still listed as the bestselling Smartphone in the world and their Note II is also doing much better than many expected. In the meantime Apple’s sales are staying consistent instead of growing as they would like. There have also been recent hits to Apple’s share prices that we do not think Apple will ever truly recover from. This means that having another serious competitor out in the market will impact Apple even more. Maybe this will inspire Apple to go back to the table and actually invent something new instead of simply trying to push other people’s designs and technology through the US Patent Office and then suing everyone. Of course, we also wonder if this new Google phone will be AMR based or if they will parter with Intel for another x86 based phone. The latter would certainly give them capabilities that we usually do not see in Smartphones...]</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357062965176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:56:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357065908434-37</Id><Title>SAMSUNG Exynos5 SOC beat Intel by 60% using ARM A-15 ..</Title><Msg>Even if we were to account for Intel's latest 32nm Atom variants, it's clear that Samsung's Exynos 5 Dual and, by extension, ARM's latest Cortex-A15 CPU designs offer superior performance, with an even greater gap in GPU numbers. Intel is at long-last expected to release a completely new Atom architecture next-year, which will be going-up against quad-core variants of ARM's Cortex-A15. With ARM revealing that in 2014, a 64-bit architecture offering three-fold performance, scalable down to 14nm will be available, Intel is likely to run into some serious competition, which we suspect will see the two firms swapping performance crowns fairly often, though, there's still a chance for domination on either-side, we won't know until we see just how capable Intel's new architecture is, next year.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1357065908434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 13:45:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357066662966-38</Id><Topic><Title>SAMSUNG Exynos5 SOC beat Intel by 60% using ARM A-15 ..</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1357065908434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 13:45:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dude, you haven't been reading latest info have you? It appears, for smartphones, Intel is scrapping Medfield and will be introducing Merrifield (Atom) on 22nm this year! (2013) Leaked results for the Merrifield scored 31,612 for the Antutu benchmark. Leaked results for Samsung's Exynos 5250 dual-core (A15) is 14,185 for the Antutu benchmark Here are the 2 links (curtesy of ruiperara) to prove my point: slashgearDOTcom/intel-redhookbay-benchmarks-surface-show-dual-core-merrifield-processor-29262496/ antutuDOTcom/view.shtml?id=2718 As for 2014 and 64-bit architecture, well Intel will have all their cores and mobile SoC on 14nm process by then. Arm will be facing Intel's core SoC for the first time in the same power envelop! Imagine a lowly arm soc against Intel's Core SoC (Broadwell).</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357066662966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 13:57:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357070911585-39</Id><Title>So Apple says good enough computers will sell.</Title><Msg>What's wrong with this argument? This article says it well. It's from the "Apple: Don't follow the herd" article. [The 'Obvious' Catalyst Is Obvious In particular, I would like to direct your attention to the following line from the article: The coming launch of an iPad 5 and a new iPad mini will also help drive Apple's stock back up, Smith said. Wait just a minute! Are you telling me that in a world where tablets are going to replace the traditional PC because tablets have become 'good enough', people will actually keep buying the latest-and-greatest iPads for a premium to their older brothers? What is really different about this upcoming iPad 5? The iPad 3 got a 'retina' display, the iPad 4 added a faster processor, so what's the iPad 5 going to bring users? Yet another faster processor? If Wall Street really thought that additional processing power was anything close to important in today's 'good enough' computing environment, chip giant Intel (INTC) would not be trading at less than 9x earnings. There's maybe one more "kicker" with the iPad Mini when we see the obvious move to a 'retina' display and attendant faster processor, but after that, what will drive a refresh cycle? Current PCs and tablets are 'good enough', right? To me, the 'good enough' factor means that mix will shift towards the older, discounted products which keep on getting 'better enough'. ] I think that the good enough argument works only on very new form factor products. In time, everything goes back to best performing products that will obviously require best performance chips which will allow the latest and greatest capabilites in mobile gadgets. Wether it's a smartphone, tablet/hybrid, or even a smartwatch. And it goes without saying performance improvements will allow much better capabilities in desktops as well which will be able to interact more realistically with the user as Intel chips get better.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357070911585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 15:08:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357072308355-40</Id><Topic><Title>So Apple says good enough computers will sell.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357070911585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 15:08:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of us use Bic pens, drive Ford or Chevys, eat at fast foods ? why ? because we have to allocate what money we have. We want the cheapest that gets the job done. The hi performance folks are a tiny bit of the market. 10 years ago when computers were really slow, if you built a faster computer the world came running. Now they are all pretty fast, a lot of people only want what they need now. The market has changed. I bought my Iphone for how well it worked, not how fast it was. My only real gripe is I wish the networks were faster...stll!</Msg><Username>repklikint</Username><Timestamp>1357072308355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 15:31:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357074684664-41</Id><Topic><Title>SAMSUNG Exynos5 SOC beat Intel by 60% using ARM A-15 ..</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1357065908434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 13:45:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly. And when is someone going to be able to manufacture this 14 nano version of ARMH architecture, Never!!!!! Or at least not at an economic cost!!!!!!</Msg><Username>redwood1205</Username><Timestamp>1357074684664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 16:11:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357076309515-42</Id><Topic><Title>SAMSUNG Exynos5 SOC beat Intel by 60% using ARM A-15 ..</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1357065908434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 13:45:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can always count on the shills to find 2-3 month old news and to misinterpret it. The fact that SingIdiot had to go back two months to find something with which to bash Intel tells you all you need to know. Sing is just another of the shills who doesn't know better than to poop where he eats as he continues to try to do damage to the US economy...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357076309515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 16:38:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357076536906-43</Id><Title>Are Futures up 3%?</Title><Msg>??? Intel opens around 21.20?</Msg><Username>jakk_wagon</Username><Timestamp>1357076536906</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 16:42:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357076568465-44</Id><Title>Not About the Set-top Box</Title><Msg>It's not about the set-top box - it's about the content. If Intel can line up the content then it won't just be successful in this area, it will be wildly successful. That's what is so exciting about this development. The demand for a la carte TV delivery is incredibly huge. It will be a tremendous coup for whoever corrals the content for the first time. There are millions and millions waiting...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357076568465</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 16:42:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357076997305-45</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, did you read HP article?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357023409612</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 01:56:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It says that HP may dispose of units that don't meet targets. Which units do you suppose are at risk? I find it hard to believe that it will be the personal system and printing group. They just recently combined them to reduce costs to allow for increased profit margin. So I wonder which ones. What do you think?" [HP was most successful when it was run by engineers. They had a good idea what they were about then. Now not so much. I confess I'm not really much of a fan of Meg. I can't imagine they would do anything with the printing aspect of the business. It's a cash cow. A lot of potential but still not much leadership...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357076997305</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 16:49:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357077032222-46</Id><Title>Where's Ashraf Eassa? Does he have an apology for his AMD PUMP</Title><Msg>?????? They'll let any hack on Seeking Alpha.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357077032222</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 16:50:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357077223552-47</Id><Title>OBAMA HAS TO PRESENT A BUDGET TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE. NO MORE SPENDING.</Title><Msg>Obama is spending and spending. He has no budget and does not intend do have the budget. We, the people, have to demand the budget.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1357077223552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 16:53:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357077407216-48</Id><Topic><Title>Where's Ashraf Eassa? Does he have an apology for his AMD PUMP</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357077032222</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 16:50:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has Pumpwad Weaver apologized for having pumped Smelltel at $29, Buttwipe?</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1357077407216</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 16:56:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357077608506-49</Id><Topic><Title>A few words about yesterdays Outperform by Wells Fargo.</Title><Username>donnapinkwater</Username><Timestamp>1357051587088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 09:46:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"In his case i would do the opposite :-)" [This post is from someone shilling for TipRanks, just like Dnenni used to shill for his site. A three page message ID which means there is some hidden agenda...] [Who needs an analyst to tell them about Intel these days? Just look at what a disaster ARM has on its hands with 20nm planar and how incredibly long it will be before they can move to volume production on FinFET. ARMs fabrication is collapsing while Intel's is getting stronger and stronger. You don't have to be smarter than a 5th grader to see how this is going to end. Just smarter than a Chump Street analyst...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357077608506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 17:00:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357077878362-50</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA HAS TO PRESENT A BUDGET TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE. NO MORE SPENDING.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1357077223552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 16:53:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obama is spending and spending. He has no budget and does not intend do have the budget. We, the people, have to demand the budget." [Remind me of the last Republican president who didn't spend like a drunken sailor? It was Dwight Eisenhower. Republican hypocrisy on spending is beyond belief...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357077878362</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 17:04:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357079763530-51</Id><Title>"AMD fate will likely be decided in the next few months..."</Title><Msg>If all went according to the last year’s plans, 2013 would have seen the entry of AMD ‘Steamroller’ core in at least two parts relevant to the PC – ‘Kaveri’ and ‘Kabini’, the successors to the Piledriver based APU and PC CPU chips. The SOS signals emanating from AMD right now, as well as the associated media buzz, hint that there is high chance that these parts might never see the light of the day. What is going on? As we covered in detail two months ago, AMD fate will likely be decided in the next few months. Whether it is some sort of sale or ownership transformation to be managed by Morgan Stanley, or an internally-driven, we hope, massive company rehash to get it out of the doldrums, don’t expect much activity from AMD, especially its CPU division, in the early 2013. This leaves the PC CPU field now completely open to Intel. From vr-zone</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357079763530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 17:36:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357080318220-52</Id><Title>Fiscal deal being opposed now, might not happen</Title><Msg>Obama won't/can't stop spending. He wants to take your money away so he can spend and you can't. He'll take money out of your wallet and then spend it right in front of you.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357080318220</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 17:45:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357080495409-53</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA HAS TO PRESENT A BUDGET TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE. NO MORE SPENDING.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1357077223552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 16:53:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republican hypocrisy on spending is beyond belief...] _____________________________________ You call Republicans Hypocrites, but when Obama says he's gonna cut the debt in half in his first term and almost doubles it instead, you look the other way. Lazy losers like you are why the U.S. is a catastrophe. F'n loser.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357080495409</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 17:48:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357080927941-54</Id><Title>ARM: Help Wanted with 20nm Planar</Title><Msg>Help wanted All of this complexity also translates to a need for additional engineering talent, Abercrombie said. “The designs are bigger, there’s more complexity not just with double patterning but with all the other various rules. You just look at the number of rules in the design rule deck. It continues to increase almost exponentially from node to node to node. It gets more complex; there’s more to account for. You’re doing more layouts that are harder layouts.” What this boils down to is that semiconductor companies must hire additional skilled engineers, as well as purchase additional CAD tools. “Not only do they need more tools, but they need a tool that now can do double patterning or pattern matching or all of these other things. They need to run on more CPUs because the designs are so huge that you just need more CPU power to crunch it.” [Of course Intel has already gotten past all of these problems at both 22nm and 14nm...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357080927941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 17:55:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357081521228-55</Id><Topic><Title>ARM: Help Wanted with 20nm Planar</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357080927941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 17:55:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Signoff definitely is getting more intense as you think of the next nodes because there’s more complexity, more checks to be done because of not just one mask, now two masks, three masks and too many interactions and therefore the critical problem is the predictability of the yield. That what really becomes key.”"</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357081521228</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 18:05:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357082401765-56</Id><Title>Looks like no deal..We open down 1000 points on Wed.</Title><Msg>Greece has a brighter future than this country..</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357082401765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 18:20:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357082633716-57</Id><Title>Were all counting on the House to stand up and get the big spending cuts , That the USA really needs</Title><Msg>Were all counting on the House to stand up and get the big spending cuts , That the USA really needs</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1357082633716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 18:23:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357082921584-58</Id><Title>Intel and Apple</Title><Msg>[Now this is pretty interesting. This article says Intel is going to need all of its massive capacity but would be able to absorb Apple's needs in 2014/2015...] The time for Intel to purchase equipment for new 14nm production capacity is 2013. Intel has four 22nm fabs online. Our opinion is that Intel has already purchased sufficient equipment for 22nm production, particularly in light of delays in construction of the Ireland fab. CLSA Asia-Pacific Markets's Srini Pajjuri offered up a think-piece on the question of whether Intel will offer chip manufacturing services in its foundries to Apple (AAPL), a subject of ongoing speculation. However, the main issue, as he sees it, is a lack of excess manufacturing capacity until 2015 at the earliest: "Assuming Intel and Apple both agree on ARM (ARMH), we estimate that Apple would need a total of 85k wafer starts per month on 22nm in 2014. Our analysis shows that Intel's own CPUs will need 58% of its 22nm capacity in 2014 even if we assume that half of Intel's units are on 14nm. That leaves 39k 22nm wafers for others. Clearly that won't be enough though Apple could start using Intel for some of its volume. Intel should have its 2 new 14nm fabs fully ramped by late 2014, and we estimate that Intel will need 87% of the 14nm capacity in 2015. However, Intel will still have five 22nm fabs and converting two of them to 14nm should be enough to address most of the Apple volume." From Robert Castellano in a post about Applied Materials</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357082921584</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 18:28:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357083022647-59</Id><Topic><Title>Were all counting on the House to stand up and get the big spending cuts , That the USA really needs</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1357082633716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 18:23:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are much more likely to be able to count on the House to prevent any deal from being made...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357083022647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 18:30:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357083414352-60</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal deal being opposed now, might not happen</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357080318220</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 17:45:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just deal making wrangling, no worries. Market may take a swoon , again no real worries.</Msg><Username>repklikint</Username><Timestamp>1357083414352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 18:36:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357083551291-61</Id><Title>Funny Exchange</Title><Msg>[This is a funny exchange. Starts out with the Intel fan Mike chastising the ARM-biased author for writing fiction... ] 19 Comments Mike Bryant | July 26, 2012 8:57 AM | Reply I see you're entering for the Booker Prize this year. David Manners replied to comment from Mike Bryant | July 26, 2012 9:15 AM | Reply I knew, when I wrote it, that I'd get a snotty remark from you, Mike, so: if your Intel pals are so good at mobile SOCs why haven't they made one on their 22nm finfet process? Mike Bryant | July 26, 2012 9:45 AM | Reply They are. David Manners replied to comment from Mike Bryant | July 26, 2012 10:18 AM | Reply And their non-appearance on the market is due to their inferior performance characteristics? Lousy yield? Uncompetitive cost? Mike Bryant | July 26, 2012 11:21 AM | Reply You know full well it's about three quarter way through design, which is a lot further on than any designs using TSMC's 20nm non-finfet process, let alone the promised finfet process. Performance will be a huge improvement over Medfield and Cortex A9 designs, and Intel's yield will be as good as ever. Cost will be whatever Intel decide to charge for it. David Manners replied to comment from Mike Bryant | July 26, 2012 11:32 AM | Reply Well if Intel's 22nm mobile SOC is not even designed yet, then Warren is absolutely correct in saying Intel's current commercial mobile SOCs are on 32nm. Moreover, if it's not even designed yet, the 'huge' performance improvement is problematic. Furthermore Intel's yields have always been reported to be lower than anyone else's because Intel cares less about production cost than anyone else because it enjoys monopoly pricing. While, in the mobile SOC industry, which is not a monopoly industry, Intel won't get away with charging whatever it wants for it. Mike Bryant | July 26, 2012 11:53 AM | Reply Not at all. I never disputed that the current Medfield product is on 32nm and accept this lags just behind current 28nm TSMC fabbed products. However your article was on future products - you mention TSMC 20nm and Finfets, ARMv8 and other things still a long way off whereas Intel's 22nm SoC is aimed for full release next April. The fact this uses existing fab processes takes the risk out of it - Intel's tick-tock approach - and so it will be very surprising if this slips. Intel's rumoured yield figures - they never report them - are dominated by huge PC processor cores. The much smaller Atom processors will have yields better than industry norms simply because Intel makes more wafers than anyone else and so can optimise yield for a single process. AMD has tried to compete at this level and always failed on cost. There will however be a huge step forward for TSMC at 20nm when they stop offering lots of different processes as they too will gain the experience of optimising a single process using data from all of their customer's wafers. And as I said, cost will be whatever Intel decide to charge for it. They can always afford to undercut anyone else should they choose to do as we have always argued having in-house production will always be cheaper than using foundries and you have reported and generally agreed with this thesis. David Manners replied to comment from Mike Bryant | July 26, 2012 11:58 AM | Reply Oh well we were talking at cross-purposes. I was stuck in the here and now. As for the future: never forget the semiconductor industry's Golden Rule: 'When Intel steps outside its monopoly it always screws up'. Mike Bryant | July 26, 2012 12:05 PM | Reply Well ARM and Qualcomm had better not rest on their laurels or it will be an Intel monopoly :-) Whilst Qualcomm is frantically looking for the best way forward the messages out of ARM, and sometimes TSMC as well, are far too complacent for my liking. And the biggest mistake was deciding to produce the 20nm planar process as this will delay TSMC getting the finfet process needed to compete with Intel to market.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357083551291</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 18:39:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357083844299-62</Id><Title>House Republicans Said to Plan Two Options on U.S. Budget Bill</Title><Msg>[House Republicans will approve the Senate bill as it currently exists or will get the blame for the fiscal cliff...] House Speaker John Boehner offered fellow Republicans two options on budget legislation, including allowing a vote on a Senate-passed bill if party members don’t show they have a majority vote to amend it with spending cuts, two leadership aides said. The speaker told members they can either amend the Senate- passed bill with spending cuts if 218 of them commit to support it, or vote on the Senate measure, the aides said. That number is a majority of the 435-member House. Boehner cautioned members during a private caucus today that there is a risk in amending the bill with spending cuts and sending it back to Senate, the aides said. A Democratic leadership aide said on condition of anonymity that the Democratic-controlled Senate won’t take up an amended bill. “No comment,” said Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid when asked if his chamber would consider any changes by House Republicans to the bipartisan Senate bill. “They have to do what they think they have to do -- I’ve already done what I’ve done,” Reid, a Nevada Democrat, said in a brief interview. He added, “My senators have gone home.” Congress is trying to undo $600 billion in automatic tax increases and spending cuts that take effect starting today. The Senate passed its plan on an 89-8 vote early this morning.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357083844299</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 18:44:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357085400475-63</Id><Topic><Title>Intel TV will fail miserably if they still intend on spying on people</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357061898252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:38:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just can't see them competing in this area in any shape, way or form. My bet on Intel is the growth in the cloud and maybe a bit in the mobile and just being down so much. Maybe Apple or Sammy takes more Intel inside. I think they will drop this idea pretty quick. I wish they would just give the share holders the money instead of throwing it on consumer end products. What the hell do I know though.</Msg><Username>repklikint</Username><Timestamp>1357085400475</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 19:10:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357085778371-64</Id><Topic><Title>House Republicans Said to Plan Two Options on U.S. Budget Bill</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357083844299</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 18:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and the media will try to blame the GOP, and it will work for a while........but the ultimate price will be paid by Obama and Biden when they go down as the worst duo in the history of the organized world. F'n idiot.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357085778371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 19:16:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357086666749-65</Id><Title>Intel's push into WEB TV hits delays (yahoo news)</Title><Msg>Stupid idea, Intel.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357086666749</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 19:31:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357086693804-66</Id><Title>intel and applied materials</Title><Msg>is it advisable to hold investments in intel and applied materials for long term?</Msg><Username>kleinmanstephen</Username><Timestamp>1357086693804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 19:31:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357086746266-67</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's push into WEB TV hits delays (yahoo news)</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357086666749</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 19:31:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bet it never happens. One person familiar with Intel's thinking on Monday predicted it would launch its offering by mid-2013. Another person said a service might not arrive until as late as the fourth quarter, citing delays in reaching content-licensing agreements with entertainment companies that own major TV channels.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357086746266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 19:32:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357086997146-68</Id><Topic><Title>House Republicans Said to Plan Two Options on U.S. Budget Bill</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357083844299</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 18:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Senate should have put lower NASCAR ticket prices in the bill. That would guarantee passage.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1357086997146</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 19:36:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357087008642-69</Id><Title>Looks like Fiscal deal will pass: We move up 1000 points tomorrow</Title><Msg>All sources point to the bill passing tonite. Repubs are wisely backing down. INTC will test $23.02 before earnings.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357087008642</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 19:36:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357088447293-70</Id><Title>intc and applied materials</Title><Msg>is it advisable to have investments in intel and applied materials for long term?</Msg><Username>kleinmanstephen</Username><Timestamp>1357088447293</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 20:00:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357089439981-71</Id><Topic><Title>Intel TV will fail miserably if they still intend on spying on people</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357061898252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:38:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the Intel TV idea is worth a try. There's a huge upside for Intel if it works out. 1) If it works out, then later Intel can incorporate the set-top box chipset into EVERY PC...think about that, you can watch TV anywhere there's an internet connection. That would be cool. 2) and if the above happens it will drive data center requirements thru the roof. Watching TV is as ubiquitous as the internet! (They need to get Cisco on board with this idea)</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357089439981</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 20:17:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357089687040-72</Id><Topic><Title>Intel TV will fail miserably if they still intend on spying on people</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357061898252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:38:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>actually I doesn't have to be a PC ...but any internet connected device...smartphones, tablets or laptops, desktop computer, or any connected TVs.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357089687040</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 20:21:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357089866328-73</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's push into WEB TV hits delays (yahoo news)</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357086666749</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 19:31:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't have access to the WSJ to read the document but if you use Google to search for the title: Intel's push into WEB TV hits delays the second Google match is a link to the online WSJ online site that gave me access to the full article written by DON CLARK And CHRISTOPHER S. STEWART.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1357089866328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 20:24:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357090198983-74</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's push into WEB TV hits delays (yahoo news)</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357086666749</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 19:31:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They got 1 content provider on board, which is significant. Intel also has the right guy leading this effort to make the deals for content. Its just a matter of time before this becomes reality. Consumers are no longer willing to pay cable companies a ransom fee for channels they will never use.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357090198983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 20:29:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357090210974-75</Id><Topic><Title>intel and applied materials</Title><Username>kleinmanstephen</Username><Timestamp>1357086693804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 19:31:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel for sure. I'd be careful of Applied Materials because of the ARM foundries serious fabrication issues and the cyclical nature of their business.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357090210974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 20:30:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357090322379-76</Id><Topic><Title>Intel TV will fail miserably if they still intend on spying on people</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357061898252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:38:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will probably be opt-in idiot.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357090322379</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 20:32:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357090576792-77</Id><Topic><Title>Intel TV will fail miserably if they still intend on spying on people</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357061898252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 12:38:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes that would make more sense. I don't think Intel would force the facial sensing on consumers. If it is an option then some people might want it, especially if say, with this option you get the option to fast-forward the commercials :).</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357090576792</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 20:36:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357090899771-78</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's push into WEB TV hits delays (yahoo news)</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357086666749</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 19:31:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel has pitched media companies on a plan to create a "virtual cable operator," which would offer U.S. TV channels nationwide over the Internet in a bundle similar to subscriptions sold by cable- and satellite-TV operators, people familiar with the effort said previously. The company, besides expertise in chips for set-top boxes, has expertise in server technology that could help serve up video programming and other content. But Intel has so far reached at least one content deal, one of the people familiar with Intel's plans said, without identifying the partner." [This is all about lining up the content providers. And they already have one. The first is usually the hardest. A virtual cable provider. That's the concept and it's a very powerful one. If they line up the content it will happen and happen big. The set-top box is a much smaller problem. Everyone want's a la carte TV. Everyone. Entertainment companies will follow the money. It's a way for them to cut the cable companies out of the picture. I'd expect the rest to jump on as well. But delays are not surprising in the least...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357090899771</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 20:41:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357090995664-79</Id><Title>Department of Welfare in Pennsylvania says a single mom with two kids......</Title><Msg>is better off taking a job making 29k than one taking 69k. Why? Because of ABSURD OBAMA ENTITLEMENTS. It's just unreal.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357090995664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 20:43:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357091211015-80</Id><Title>Looks Like</Title><Msg>the House is going to vote on the Senate bill tonite. This should be interesting. The reason it might pass is because so many Republicans voted for it in the Senate...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357091211015</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 20:46:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357091880102-81</Id><Topic><Title>Looks Like</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357091211015</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 20:46:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will pass &amp; by a wide margin. The only no votes will be the teabaggers &amp; repubs who are on their way out of Congress.</Msg><Username>back_bay_professor</Username><Timestamp>1357091880102</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 20:58:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357092329907-82</Id><Topic><Title>Time to get rid of....</Title><Username>bkapito</Username><Timestamp>1356988087759</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 16:08:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Greg, INTC 12/31/11 $ 24.52. INTC 12/31/12 $ 20.62. If you're happy with a stock whose price goes down 15 PERCENT in a year, you are the idiot.</Msg><Username>bkapito</Username><Timestamp>1357092329907</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:05:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357092873723-83</Id><Topic><Title>Were all counting on the House to stand up and get the big spending cuts , That the USA really needs</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1357082633716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 18:23:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they don't get the spending cuts, The House should vote no. They were sent to the House to cut spending and this bill has no spending cuts ( How is this a balanced plan)</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1357092873723</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:14:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357093131708-84</Id><Topic><Title>SAMSUNG Exynos5 SOC beat Intel by 60% using ARM A-15 ..</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1357065908434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 13:45:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ZOMBIE $UCKED BRAINS....LOL $19 REVISIT AND THAN BREAKDOWN IN 2013 NEXT LOL</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1357093131708</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:18:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357093245302-85</Id><Topic><Title>SAMSUNG Exynos5 SOC beat Intel by 60% using ARM A-15 ..</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1357065908434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 13:45:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BSC Selects Samsung Exynos Processor Over Nvidia Tegra [11/19/2012 10:10 PM] by Anton Shilov The Mont-Blanc European project has selected the Samsung Exynos platform as the building block for powering its first integrated low power high performance computing (HPC) prototype. Previously, the Mont-Blanc project was co-developed by Barcelona Supercomputing Center and Nvidia Corp., but it looks like the latter is no longer a part of the project. The aim of Mont-Blanc project is to design a new type of computer architecture capable of setting future global HPC standards, built from today’s energy efficient solutions used in embedded and mobile devices. The Samsung Exynos 5250 is built on 32nm low-power HKMG (high-K netal gate) technology, and features two 1.70GHz ARM Cortex-A15 architecture cores plus an integrated ARM Mali-T604 GPU for increased performance density and energy efficiency. It has been featured and market proven in consumer and mobile devices such as Samsung Chromebook and Google’s Nexus 10. This will be the first use of an embedded mobile SoC in HPC, which enables the Mont-Blanc project to explore the challenges and benefits of deeply integrated energy-efficient processors and GPU accelerators, compared to traditional homogeneous multicore systems, and heterogeneous CPU + external GPU architectures. "The Exynos 5 Dual packs the most powerful ARM processors with a programmable GPU in a low-power mobile device that would normally be in someone’s pocket and running on a battery. Its performance density, energy efficiency, and low market price make it an extraordinary building block for prototyping a new generation of HPC systems," said Alex Ramirez, coordinator of the Mont-Blanc project. During the first year of activities, Mont-Blanc has focused on deploying successfully an HPC system software stack and full-scale scientific applications on ARM platforms, proving that ARM-based architectures are feasible alternatives for HPC. Now the efforts gear towards integration of the Exynos platform on a HPC solution, and software exploitation of the embedded GPU. "Previously, the Mont-Blanc project was co-developed by Barcelona Supercomputing Center and Nvidia Corp., but it looks like the latter is no longer a part of the project." { CLINK ! .... Clink clink clink bink bink } There goes another big tegra order -- Kicked to the curb. Google it yourself, boys : Barcelona Supercomputing Center Selects Samsung Exynos Processor for Supercomputer.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1357093245302</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:20:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357093291555-86</Id><Topic><Title>Time to get rid of....</Title><Username>bkapito</Username><Timestamp>1356988087759</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 16:08:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>duhhhhhh.... I murmur under my breath..."idiot"</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1357093291555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:21:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357093372849-87</Id><Topic><Title>intc and applied materials</Title><Username>kleinmanstephen</Username><Timestamp>1357088447293</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 20:00:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we answer your stupid question all the time but you just keep on re-posting. Yes..and No Now get lost.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1357093372849</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:22:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357093711527-88</Id><Title>Eric Cantor = 1000 points down on DoW</Title><Msg>which would you prefer...Eric Cantor and Dow ay down, or no Eric Cantor and Dow way up? duhhhhhhhh.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1357093711527</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:28:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357094009499-89</Id><Topic><Title>Time to get rid of....</Title><Username>bkapito</Username><Timestamp>1356988087759</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 16:08:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"INTC 12/31/11 $ 24.52. INTC 12/31/12 $ 20.62. If you're happy with a stock whose price goes down 15 PERCENT in a year, you are the idiot." [So, all of your stocks go up every single year? List please...] [PS. There's a difference between a stock that goes down and a stock that is manipulated down by the same idiots who think ARM is worth 74 times earnings...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357094009499</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:33:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357094783600-90</Id><Topic><Title>Time to get rid of....</Title><Username>bkapito</Username><Timestamp>1356988087759</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 16:08:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thought you were gonna say .... "the GOP"</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1357094783600</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:46:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357095372896-91</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Cantor = 1000 points down on DoW</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1357093711527</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:28:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ stop bothering people with your 2 yrs old comments.get a life</Msg><Username>kleinmanstephen</Username><Timestamp>1357095372896</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:56:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357095655185-92</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Cantor = 1000 points down on DoW</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1357093711527</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:28:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i think they want you at the ge board. get lost!!!!</Msg><Username>kleinmanstephen</Username><Timestamp>1357095655185</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 22:00:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357095899455-93</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Cantor = 1000 points down on DoW</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1357093711527</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:28:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cantor got a whole 9 congressman to vote no, FAIL!! Fiscal cliff = avoided</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1357095899455</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 22:04:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357098093851-94</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's push into WEB TV hits delays (yahoo news)</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357086666749</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 19:31:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, this could be very big for Intel. The entertainment companies would be crazy to not go along with this concept. If it works out, potentially all internet connected devices (smartphones, tablets, PCs) will be able to view TV channels. This would be huge advertisement money. Intel would be able to profit by licensing their set-top box chipset to every SoC maker out there, including arm-base SoCs...this is big.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357098093851</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 22:41:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357098531467-95</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Cantor = 1000 points down on DoW</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1357093711527</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:28:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ahh..are you talking about the Senate vote? The House hasn't voted. And Cantor is in the House....do you know the difference between the Senate and the House? Did you ever take a Constitution test? Can you find China on a map?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1357098531467</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 22:48:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357098568325-96</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Cantor = 1000 points down on DoW</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1357093711527</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:28:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're stinkin up the place...go take a course on basic TP.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1357098568325</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 22:49:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357099343588-97</Id><Title>house approved deal!</Title><Msg>cnn blog</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357099343588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:02:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357099460238-98</Id><Title>Deal passed, official, Obama can keep spending</Title><Msg>you go girls.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357099460238</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:04:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357099538667-99</Id><Title>The bill passed the house</Title><Msg>Just in...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357099538667</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:05:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357099579789-100</Id><Title>Paul Ryan &amp; John Boehner both vote for tax increases</Title><Msg>Repub. leadership is a total mess. Teabaggers have destroyed the party for at least a decade. No leadership skills whatsoever.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357099579789</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:06:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357099749701-101</Id><Title>Nice start to 2013</Title><Msg>Intel's year</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357099749701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:09:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357099753638-102</Id><Topic><Title>The bill passed the house</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357099538667</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:05:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Several Democrats even voted NO. I wonder if you'll get QE 12 next year like you've been begging for?</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357099753638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:09:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357099987819-103</Id><Topic><Title>The bill passed the house</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357099538667</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:05:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boehner &amp; Ryan both voted 'yes'. Repub leadership is a total mess, thanks largely to a minority teabagger group who has no leadership skills.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357099987819</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:13:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357100106619-104</Id><Topic><Title>The bill passed the house</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357099538667</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:05:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boehner should have taken the grand deal in 2011. Now, everyone is suffering, especially the economy.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357100106619</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:15:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357100368174-105</Id><Title>$$$ will pour into dividend stocks in 2013</Title><Msg>Huge relief - very little tax increase. INTC to $35 in 2013 according to my model.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357100368174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:19:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357101406988-106</Id><Topic><Title>$$$ will pour into dividend stocks in 2013</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357100368174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:19:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it a 5 percent increase no matter what tax bracket you are in or does it stay at 15 percent for the middle class?</Msg><Username>jakk_wagon</Username><Timestamp>1357101406988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:36:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357101504250-107</Id><Topic><Title>Deal passed, official, Obama can keep spending</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1357099460238</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:04:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As long as the duly elected representatives of the people authorize it!! Don't forget that in a couple months the enemies of the Obama-tin-tyrant can take away his check book!!! You know, that debt ceiling brinksmanship!!! Don't worry, there is still time for those who hate him to take him down!!! They can't make him a one-term president but I am sure they can limit him to TWO TERMS!!! PLEASE, PLEASE don't feel bad!!! America will survive both Obama and your hate.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1357101504250</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:38:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357101908083-108</Id><Topic><Title>$$$ will pour into dividend stocks in 2013</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357100368174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:19:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Capital gains/dividends move up to 20% ONLY for the $400K/$450K income earners. The market was factoring in a much higher rate for dividends, even being taxed as normal income. Huge relief.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357101908083</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:45:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357101972455-109</Id><Topic><Title>$$$ will pour into dividend stocks in 2013</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357100368174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:19:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Capital gains rates for high-income households return to Clinton-era levels: The capital gains rate would return to what it was under President Clinton, 20 percent. Counting the 3.8 percent surcharge from the Affordable Care Act, dividends and capital gains would be taxed at a rate of 23.8 percent for high-income households. These tax rates would apply to singles above $400,000 and couples above $450,000. politicoDOTcom/politico44/2013/01/white-house-declares-a-victory-153090.html politicoDOTcom/story/2013/01/fiscal-cliff-bill-full-text-85644.html?hp=t7_7 politicoDOTcom/story/2013/01/senate-clears-fiscal-cliff-deal-89-8-85640.html?hp=t1_7 thehillDOTcom/homenews/senate/275101-senate-fiscal-cliff-deal-in-trouble-in-house</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357101972455</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:46:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357102077263-110</Id><Topic><Title>$$$ will pour into dividend stocks in 2013</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357100368174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:19:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey!!!! I bet the futures are down big. Isn't the rule to Buy the rumor, Sell on the news!!!</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1357102077263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:47:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357102287562-111</Id><Topic><Title>The bill passed the house</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357099538667</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:05:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neither is running for president in 2016 like Rand Paul and Rubio. If you are running for Republican nomination, you had to vote against it. The 257-167 vote came after a day of high drama on Capitol Hill, during which conservative House lawmakers voiced serious concern about the Senate bill’s lack of spending cuts. Rank-and-file Republicans initially predicted they would tinker with the package, raising the possibility the Senate would abandon it and nothing would get done before the new congressional class is seated Thursday. But House leaders soon learned they did not have a majority behind any spending-cut plan, and allowed the straight vote. More Democrats supported the bill than Republicans.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1357102287562</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:51:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357102644317-112</Id><Topic><Title>$$$ will pour into dividend stocks in 2013</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357100368174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:19:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Asia up big &amp; Europe futures turned up after the vote. Who knows, but I'm guessing we get a relief rally especially since its January &amp; $$ has to be put to work somewhere.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357102644317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:57:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>