<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-09"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360386103095-1</Id><Topic><Title>"GloFo's 14XM Fabrication Really Seems Like A Cheat"</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360382532331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 23:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The race is for LP. XM makes sense as its an incremental step and it gets them in the temporal ballpark of Intel's accelerated 14nm LP rollout at the end of 2014." [What kind of bs is "temporal ballpark"? It doesn't get them in the ball park at all. It will produce a poor economics half-step that is too little, too late. A half-step two years behind Intel and then only if things go perfectly. How did things go for TSMC with 28nm? Would you say perfectly? LOL Don't expect 20nm or the half-step to 14nm to go perfectly. What evidence shows at this point is that each ARM node jump ramps slower and slower. Intel is already ramping FinFet like a champ. The ARM foundries have no chance of doing the same. You need to add a couple of years to all of the ARM camp projections... ] "At the end of the day, what matters is how much power the transistors are drawing and what speed you can switch them at. If they can get half-way in bridging the performance gap between 20 nm planar and 14nm FinFET, that should be good enough to make them competitive." [Yeah, if it wasn't going to be two years late. ARM if they are exceedingly lucky will move a half-step to 14nm while Intel is moving a full step to 10nm. The gap is going to get bigger, not smaller. It's just basic math. ARM is moving slower and in half-steps. The fabrication fade is in full swing...] "It's a half step in the right direction and a good parry to Intel's acceleration. If they can pull this off which seems likely, they'll be competitive." [TSMCs experience at 28nm says it's unlikely. Glofo's experience at 32/28nm says it's unlikely. What are you basing likely on other than wishful thinking? The ARM foundry track record disputes your conjecture...] "The big advantage of the foundries is they don't need the huge margins on processor ASPs that Intel needs to maintain status quo." [No, the ARM foundries don't HAVE the huge margins that Intel has and this makes them less competitive. Intel gets “paid twice” for its products, since it both designs and builds. If you have less margin then you have less to give away. You can't be as flexible on pricing. There is no advantage for the foundries here - the advantage is all Intel's...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360386103095</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 00:01:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360386847973-2</Id><Topic><Title>"GloFo's 14XM Fabrication Really Seems Like A Cheat"</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360382532331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 23:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Temporal means related to time. Temporal ballpark means around the same time. Intel's accelerated their process roll-out at 14nm so GloFo needs to match.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360386847973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 00:14:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360387557905-3</Id><Title>Misleading ARM FinFET Claimis</Title><Msg>From Ashraf Eassa: Applied Micro: Recent Developments Fuel Heavy Skepticism Excerpt: "Also, it's kind of interesting that Applied Micro is misleading investors by claiming FinFETs will be coming out in 2014 from the foundries. I remind everybody that this is likely a 2016 event, based on the fact that Taiwan Semiconductor believes that its 20nm planar node (i.e. non-FinFET) is coming in 2014 (probably late if the timing of the 20nm node is similar to that of the 28nm node): And enough discussions have taken place with enough customers with large requirements to lead us to believe that in both its first and second year of production, in both the first and second year production of 20 SoC and that first year will be next year, 2014. The second year will be a year after that, 2015. It is extremely saddening to see Mr. Gopi mislead investors in this way. Finally, it is foolish to assume that Applied Micro, with its very limited experience at actually designing general purpose micro-architectures, can out-design Intel. Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) hasn't been able to come close in nearly 10 years (after briefly catching Intel off guard in 2003), so it stands to reason that a threatened Intel is unlikely to cede the design prowess to Applied Micro, a company whose "Titan" CPU design (which also had suspiciously amazing specifications and even got to tape-out) went down in flames. Where Are The Design Wins? It was widely speculated that Applied Micro would announce a design win with Facebook at the OpenCompute conference, and that Facebook "wants to go all ARM." Well, no, that didn't happen. Applied Micro contributed a few reference designs to the OpenCompute project, and Frank Frankovsky from Facebook congratulated Applied Micro for getting some silicon out. However, that was it. No design wins, just a PR in which Mr. Frankovsky said that Facebook was excited to be able to test the X-Gene (among other SoCs). While I'm sure that Applied Micro will get some design wins, I remain skeptical that the product is actually any good and will be the panacea that so many who believe in the "ARM In Servers" party line expect." *** [So, we have the ARM world being probably two years off in their projections of when their half-step to 14nm will arrive. In the meantime, TSMC really needs to have volume production at 20nm by June of this year in order to lock up a big deal with Apple. It will never happen. It will be another year before it happens if then. This leaves Apple hanging and the door wide open for Intel to start locking up some new and very big deals to use up all of that huge state-of-the-art capacity that only they have. There is only one conclusion here and it's that ARMs fading fabrication is starting to snowball on them. FinFET will prove to be a disruptive technology that will totally change the competitive landscape, leaving Intel in complete control while ARM tries desperately not to become the AMD of mobility...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360387557905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 00:25:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360387633396-4</Id><Topic><Title>Question on Options - Deep ITM</Title><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1360383117010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 23:11:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just looked at the options and you are correct about the ask prices. TIME VALUE: If you look at the SPREAD of the bid/ask of the two year $13 strikes. 2014 $13 Call: $8.00/$8.05 2015 $13 Call: $8.00/$8.10 The BID and ASK SIZE indicates there are 100-200 contracts at each one. I would not be surprised to see the B/A SIZE vaporize after a couple contracts if you put a close LIMIT. With Intel price at $21, the $13 calls are $8 ITM. $29 PUT contracts are $8 ITM. $29 strike does not exist but the deeper $30 strikes exist. 2014 $30 Put:$9.60/$9.70 2015 $30 Put: $10.55/$10/65 There is a $0.95 difference in the Put contracts .... and guess what: The dividend for 1 year is now $0.90. For stocks with high yield, sell the puts and buy the calls. "why the heck would anybody buy a Jan 2014 options in the first place?" You are staring at the effect of dividend arbitraging on option pricing. The option market maker is encouraging transactions via pricing. I am REALLY surprised that you can buy the 2015 for a TOTAL of a 10 cent premium.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360387633396</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 00:27:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360387824092-5</Id><Topic><Title>"GloFo's 14XM Fabrication Really Seems Like A Cheat"</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360382532331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 23:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Temporal means related to time. Temporal ballpark means around the same time. Intel's accelerated their process roll-out at 14nm so GloFo needs to match." [Yeah, GloFo needs to match but won't be within two years. You did all you could to muddy the waters with your "temporal" bs and pronouncements of likelihood. Matching Intel on this is a complete fantasy. You should be ashamed for suggesting it's anything else...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360387824092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 00:30:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360388500694-6</Id><Title>Harris Associates’ Top Stock Picks for 2013 Include Intel</Title><Msg>There are a number of ways to use quarterly 13F filings from major investors such as hedge funds in order to improve the investment process. One way is be aggregating these filings and using them to devise large-scale investing strategies. For example, we have found that imitating the most popular small cap stocks among hedge funds can be profitable; in our August newsletter, we listed the most popular names in this category and on average these stocks outperformed the S&amp;P 500 by 18 percentage points between September and January (read more about our hedge fund strategies). We also like to review individual 13Fs, treating them as recommendations from fund managers. If our brief overview of the stock sounds appealing, then an investor can go on to do further research. Read on for our thoughts on Harris Associates’ five largest holdings by market value as of the end of December 2012: Harris’s top pick was Mastercard Inc (NYSE:MA), reporting a position of 2.6 million shares in the credit card company. The fund also liked Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC), with almost 59 million shares in its portfolio according to the 13F. By MATT DOIRON in Hedge Funds</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360388500694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 00:41:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360388882041-7</Id><Topic><Title>"GloFo's 14XM Fabrication Really Seems Like A Cheat"</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360382532331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 23:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both have set aggressive schedules and are therefore equally likely to make or break it. Don't think Intel's famed engineering process excellence is going to help them much. What you're looking at is an equal struggle for progress at low power and its a four horse race at least if we don't count IBM.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360388882041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 00:48:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360390691448-8</Id><Topic><Title>"GloFo's 14XM Fabrication Really Seems Like A Cheat"</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360382532331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 23:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The race is for LP. XM makes sense as its an incremental step and it gets them in the temporal ballpark of Intel's accelerated 14nm LP rollout at the end of 2014. Gloflo just announced FDSOI - planar they don't seem to know which side is up and which side is down. The big advantage of the foundries is they don't need the huge margins on processor ASPs that Intel needs to maintain status quo. Probably one of the most stupid posts - foundries are OK with low margins but Intel not</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360390691448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 01:18:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360396204776-9</Id><Title>SURE IS STRANGE HOW THE INTEL MB IS NOTHING THE AMD BOARD..</Title><Msg>AMD bashing haters are now RE posting THREE THOUSAND times bashing one AMD poster NON-STOP!!!!! THREE THOUSAND times in 7 days! I wonder why this is NOT happening here, is someone PAYING posters at the AMD MB to FLOOD the board into a circus of nothing but a "BASHING FORUM"??????????????????????????????????????????????????????????????? Has anyone ever seen what a complete garbage MB AMD now is?????????????????</Msg><Username>inteldontplayfair</Username><Timestamp>1360396204776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 02:50:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360396377026-10</Id><Topic><Title>SURE IS STRANGE HOW THE INTEL MB IS NOTHING THE AMD BOARD..</Title><Username>inteldontplayfair</Username><Timestamp>1360396204776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 02:50:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This board is NOTHING like the AMD board is.....is someone paying the bashers there???????????????????????????????????????</Msg><Username>inteldontplayfair</Username><Timestamp>1360396377026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 02:52:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360397112571-11</Id><Topic><Title>Misleading ARM FinFET Claimis</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360387557905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 00:25:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft's Surface is a mess/failure becuase Intel's chip is a power hungry mess! 4 hours is a joke! ARM tables are getting up to 10 hours battery life-ARM is doing much better! Ashraf is now a full on intel fanboy, expect full intel bias from him, it's pretty obvious.</Msg><Username>inteldontplayfair</Username><Timestamp>1360397112571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 03:05:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360397402976-12</Id><Topic><Title>Misleading ARM FinFET Claimis</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360387557905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 00:25:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next you will be saying Apple going with ARM is the AMD of mobility.....I think Apple is laughing at Intel right about now.</Msg><Username>inteldontplayfair</Username><Timestamp>1360397402976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 03:10:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360407109353-13</Id><Topic><Title>Important Report About INTC!</Title><Username>riveraandres435</Username><Timestamp>1360257318814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:15:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank u for this report.</Msg><Username>john.white982</Username><Timestamp>1360407109353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 05:51:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360412120131-14</Id><Topic><Title>Question on Options - Deep ITM</Title><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1360383117010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 23:11:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for responding alex. This is not the first instance that for a year( 2014 vs 2015) the diff in premium is small. Even the other day ( I dont have data) I observed the same. If the markets correct I was planning to buy deep ITM call options and am keeping a close eye on the prices. It looks like I can buy 2015 call options by paying a 5 to 10 cent premium over 2014 calls. Another question: If I can buy $13 strike intel by paying $8.xx somthing for a Jan 2015 calls and a person like me who beleives that intel will bounce back in late 2013...... a) why would you buy the stock instead buy these calls?( I understand there is a small time value I am paying - a risk I am willing to take considering the fact that less capital needed). b) If I dont excersise my options I dont get dividends. I am aware of that.( I am willing to skip one or two dividends - again the logic being I am deploying less cash and looking for capital gains/ markets will reward the R&amp;D efforts of intel at some point - which is what I am trying to capture) what am I missing here alex?</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1360412120131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 07:15:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360415612877-15</Id><Topic><Title>Important Report About INTC!</Title><Username>riveraandres435</Username><Timestamp>1360257318814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:15:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Call it what it is...spam...obviously we have few respondents who all give kudos to the original post. this is,to be kind,not very clever.</Msg><Username>doorstepman</Username><Timestamp>1360415612877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 08:13:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360416719459-16</Id><Topic><Title>Misleading ARM FinFET Claimis</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360387557905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 00:25:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the same Asfraf who's 'big plans" for Intel in 2013 are for the stock price to get to 23 or 24.......what a joke! He's a daytrader. Never seen so many desperate fools in one place. Waliisweaver and Ashraf lead the parade. Intle's fine long term, but #$%$ daytraders like the ones on this board, analysts, etc. have RUINED the markets.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1360416719459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 08:31:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360421091362-17</Id><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro - 128GB version sold out on Microsoft Store, Best Buy, and Staples - Can't even place orders</Title><Msg>This is an article on the storage available for users after installing Windows 8...how it is a confusing calculation. But it includes datapoints on customer demand for Surface Pro...and it is good! ============================ As of this morning, a few hours after the Surface Pro went on sale, Microsoft’s web site shows the 128 GB model as out of stock. Would-be buyers can’t even place an order. By contrast, the 64 GB model is available for immediate shipment. The situation is similar at Microsoft's retail partners, where the 128 GB models were out of stock everywhere I looked. Best Buy isn't taking orders from its website, but Staples is. They can ship a 64 GB model immediately, but you can't place an order for a 128 GB device. wwwDOTzdnetDOTcom/microsoft-officially-and-confusingly-discloses-surface-pro-storage-figures-7000011078/</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1360421091362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 09:44:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360421192093-18</Id><Topic><Title>How hard is it for intel to start another architecture?</Title><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1360287315801</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:35:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Might want to take a look at LWLG. A Fortune 100 microelectronics company (Intel?) has been testing their electro-optic polymer for some time now. The company is holding a conference call at 4:00 on Friday to update investors and field questions. Do your own DD of course.</Msg><Username>sixshotlimit</Username><Timestamp>1360421192093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 09:46:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360422433791-19</Id><Topic><Title>Implementing Solution .</Title><Username>elinorsnellerqiufjag5618</Username><Timestamp>1303909221000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2011-04-27 09:00:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are amazing.</Msg><Username>mcrichard54</Username><Timestamp>1360422433791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 10:07:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360424920949-20</Id><Topic><Title>Strong second half for INTEL</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1360383432247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 23:17:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"sanddollars" and "bacbacker" are Wallis aliases. The guy just NEVER STOPS! When he gets no responses to his messages, he responds to his own message with one of his aliases. KRAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAZEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE!!! HI-HO WEAVERINO!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360424920949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 10:48:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360425164920-21</Id><Title>IBM annouces it has leaped ahead of Intel in processor technology</Title><Msg>Update: IBM and AMD first at 22 nm, challenge Intel’s manufacturing lead Posted August 19, 2008 - 09:50 by Wolfgang Gruener Yorktown Heights (NY) – IBM and its chip development partners made a stunning announcement today, apparently beating Intel in the successful production of the first functional 22 nm SRAM cell. 22 nm processors are still three years out in the future, but IBM’s news is a good sign that chip manufacturer will be able to easily scale to this new level by the end of 2011. It appears that, for the first time in several decades, Intel may have to put some extra time into its research and development efforts to make sure it can keep its manufacturing lead at 22 nm and beyond. But then, Intel has a different opinion what this announcement really means. SRAM chips are typically the first semiconductor devices to test a new manufacturing process as a precursor to actual microprocessors. The devices developed and manufactured by AMD, Freescale, IBM STMicroelectronics, Toshiba and the College of Nanoscale Science and Engineering (CNSE) were built in a traditional six-transistor design on a 300 mm wafer and had a memory cell size of just 0.1 μm2, which compares to Intel’s 45 nm SRAM cell size (the test chip that was used for today’s 45 nm processors) of 0.346 μm2. A 22 nm chip is two generations out in the future and AMD even has to catch up with Intel’s 45 nm. Intel presented the first 32 nm SRAM cell wafer in September of last year and in fact is not expected to show 22 nm SRAM cells for at least another year, while first 32 nm CPU prototypes could be shown at IDF this week. IBM said that it is on track with its 32 nm process and promises that it will use a “leading 32 nm high-K metal gate technology that no other company or consortium can match.” IBM did not provide further details to substantiate this claim, however, Intel has been using its high-K metal gate technology since the introduction of the 45 nm Penryn processors in late 2007. While we are far from actual 22 nm and 32 nm products, it is clear that IBM and its partners are turning up the heat on Intel. For the first time in decades, there could actually be an interesting race towards a new production node. Update August 19, 10:50 am EDT: Intel spokesman Nick Knupffer provided us with Intel's view on this announcement. Not surprisingly, Intel has a different opinion: "Indeed, this is the smallest SRAM cell that has been demonstrated, but producing a single cell is merely an exercise in lithography scaling. The announcement admits that they only have demonstrated a 22 nm SRAM 'cell', not a 22 nm SRAM 'array' of any given density. A single SRAM cell has 6 transistors in it. Intel's 32 nm SRAM array, which we announced back in September, has 290 million cells or bits, and a total of 1.9 billion transistors. IBM has yet to report a large working 32 nm SRAM array as Intel did last September. Intel's 32 nm technology will use our 2nd generation of high-k + metal gate transistors." HISTORY HAS A WAY OF REPEATING ITSELF ONLY THIS TIME ARM=AMD . tgdailyDOTcom/hardware-features/38941-update-ibm-and-amd-first-at-22-nm-challenge-intel%E2%80%99s-manufacturing-lead#ZvB9j5G1x7SAVc8o.99</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1360425164920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 10:52:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360428175416-22</Id><Title>Put down some cash down on Intel and you will thank we pumpers.</Title><Msg>Why? Superior fabs. Trigate chips shrunk to 14nm then 10nm. New CEO makes the deals. Hey--that Tick Tock stuff really worked. Do you really understand--non-believers, how incredible the Intel manufacturing advantage is becoming as we go to 10 billion dollar fabs? You will. I for one would be shocked if Intel did not blow past 40 this year. I will enjoy reading long posts from Wally and even from you shorts for now but once Intel goes up to 40, there will start to be 5 or more posts per minute and then we get like the Apple board where all we get is NOISE! Intel, like Nazareth, has risen from the dead, thirteen years stuck in Dead stock Purgatory buried and left for dead. NO Investment money from Big institutions will increase their money in Intel until AFTER, the Intel rebirth becomes reality in the way of contracts and massive Net Income growth. They have all been burned for 13 years with Intel. How much in the way of net income will it take to kick Intel to the 77 where it was in 2000? I would bet it will take 4. 5 billion in a quarterly net income along with steady growth for each quarter to follow. What--you shortys and non-believers are laughing now? Phones and tablets will wipe that laugh off your face and the start is sooner than you could know. I will make a few predictions that put things in perspective. Nokia used to be the King of phones. before then was Motorola. Now we have Samsung and Apple but how on earth can they possibly hold this lead when they are being attacked by Chines companies, Motorola again, as well as a dozen companies more? Intel will get into the top end smart phones and it does not care who wins. It will sell to Nokia, Apple or Samsung if they want. it will sell to anyone because it is Intel and that is what it does. Hey shorts here---I know you will jump in long soon so there we are. Intel is more like the Russian army of the 1940s now. I mean it has taken a long time to get going But now that it has, it will start to run over all in its way swallowing up agreements from phone companies and tablet makers by the dozens. Name calling here is done by the Noise makers. Ignore them and --- watch the shocking growth to come from Intel.</Msg><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1360428175416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 11:42:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360432737352-23</Id><Topic><Title>Misleading ARM FinFET Claimis</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360387557905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 00:25:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly my point! Well said...att4glte!</Msg><Username>inteldontplayfair</Username><Timestamp>1360432737352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 12:58:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360433477069-24</Id><Topic><Title>Misleading ARM FinFET Claimis</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360387557905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 00:25:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Playfair, Did you use the last bump in AMD's price to get out of your long position before it heads to $1.00?</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1360433477069</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 13:11:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360436078885-25</Id><Topic><Title>Misleading ARM FinFET Claimis</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360387557905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 00:25:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone who thinks that MSFT created two products for the same audience and are targeted for the same market don't understand what MSFT was doing or they are intentionally spreading disinformation. Did you know that the Pro was targeted at MACbook Air and not the iPad? GizMag ... "In selling the Surface Pro, Microsoft’s marketing team has a big challenge. The new tablet is essentially an Ultrabook in a tablet’s body. But most customers are going to look at it and think “iPad competitor.” We already compared Surface Pro to the iPad, but perhaps a more appropriate comparison is to the MacBook Air. Let’s see how their specs – and other features – compare." and .... "Surface Pro has the higher-capacity battery, but actual uptimes may be similar. Both likely last about four to five hours with a medium to heavy workload. Though Surface Pro’s battery life is perfectly respectable for an Ultrabook, customers see it as a tablet. Four hours for a tablet is abysmal. Again, Redmond’s marketers have their hands full." from GizMag.... Microsoft Surface Pro vs. MacBook Air By Will Shanklin February 9, 2013 gizmagDOTcom/macbook-air-vs-microsoft-surface-pro-specs-comparison/26175/</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360436078885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 13:54:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360447119772-26</Id><Title>More on ARM Foundry Challenges</Title><Msg>Fabless companies have to accept a slow ramp-up of wafer volumes because of the IP qualification and parametric yield challenges.  Design teams will need to be manufacturing-aware and have in depth understanding of the process variables that have to be included as part of design disciplines. There will be the need for collaboration between fabless company and foundry on understanding the process variations.  Fabless companies cannot assume that their designs will give high yields based on their legacy interfaces that are in place with foundries. There is the need to anticipate potential yield problems and address them at the design implementation phase, and DFM factors have to be carefully analyzed.  Fabless companies will need to build stronger process and product engineering and DFM expertise. It means a extra cost of 50-100M USD per year. gsaglobalDOTorg/events/2012/1107/docs/slft2012_wei.pdf</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360447119772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 16:58:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360447558677-27</Id><Title>Endangered Species: The ARM Foundry</Title><Msg>At 90nm there were 19 ARM foundries. At 16/14nm there will be three. That number could drop to one (Samsung). Regardless the trend is incontrovertible. The fabless model is broken. There is no other reason for a decline from 19 to 3. Well, except Intel. The ARM Bubble continues its descent into the land of sharp objects. The broken fabless model is just one...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360447558677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 17:05:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360447976271-28</Id><Topic><Title>More on ARM Foundry Challenges</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360447119772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 16:58:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Foundry’s Support Capability Lowers From a slide at: gsaglobalDOTorg/events/2012/1107/docs/slft2012_wei.pdf [The number of designs that the ARM foundries can support at each node is dropping. At 65nm it was 65 to 80, at 40nm, it was 40 to 50, at 28nm, it was 20 to 30, at 20nm, it will be 12-16 and at 14nm it will be 5 to 8. Just another way the ARM foundries are putting themselves out of business...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360447976271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 17:12:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360448300181-29</Id><Topic><Title>More on ARM Foundry Challenges</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360447119772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 16:58:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dropping ARM Foundry Investments Fewer fabless start-ups Even fewer rising stars Large fabs acquiring small ones Dropping number of deals and investments 93 fabless Series A Semiconductor Fundings in 2000, 42 in 2004, and 3 in 2012. [Pretty sure James Covello hasn't seen these numbers/graph...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360448300181</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 17:18:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360448643702-30</Id><Topic><Title>More on ARM Foundry Challenges</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360447119772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 16:58:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New Relationship Between Fabless and Foundry Because of extremely high cost in process technology and SoC development, the relationship between fabless company and foundry become sensitive.  Foundries will select their customers very carefully, and the criteria for acceptance will involve financial returns as well as technical capabilities. In addition, foundries will need a vehicle for ramping volumes of wafers rapidly in new generation of process technologies.  There is also the complementary factor that, with the increasing cost of implementing SoC designs at most advanced technology node, only a small number of fabless companies can involve.  Whenever the partnership between a fabless company and foundry established, it would not be easy to change, as the change means high cost that should be paid by both parties.  At 20nm and 14nm, the foundry business model will probably be slightly changed. An IDM-like collaboration between fabless companies and foundries will be expected. [For anyone having trouble interpreting this, let me help. This means all of the fabless ARM shops are in trouble, big and small. They face fewer choices, less control, bigger delays, worse economics and rising costs. And they won't have FinFET for years. The ARM Bubble descent into the land of sharp objects just picked up speed...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360448643702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 17:24:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360449171601-31</Id><Topic><Title>More on ARM Foundry Challenges</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360447119772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 16:58:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only a few high-end chip makers today can even afford the exorbitant cost of NEXT-GENERATION RESEARCH AND DESIGN, much less the fabs to build them. R. Colin Johnson, “IBM Fellow: Moore’s Law Defunct,” EE Times, 4/07/09 [With Intel cranking out new fabs every 2 years based on its huge R&amp;D budget, they are in the catbird seat. The ARM foundries because of the broken fabless model are hamstrung with a failed approach, dropping players and inferior technology. The end game is upon us...] And now back to the slideshow: Comments on Fabless Culture Traditional culture is not tolerant enough to allow failure. Because innovation is too risky, “Me Too” has widely adopted not only in products development but also in business model. The result is that products from different companies are homogenized and price war is everywhere.  Most fabless companies are still under the control of founders which are in general the technical experts so that they “Prefer to being a chicken head rather than being the tail of phoenix” (Chinese proverb). Merge and acquisition are extremely difficult.  Local government does not want the companies they have supported to close door. They try their best to help these “dwarfs” , even if some of them already become “plant men”.  Venture capital does not take venture. The reason behind is that most venture capital comes from government. They undertake a responsibility to maintain the value of “State Asset”.  There are not enough real entrepreneurs. Entrepreneurship becomes a big (problem?)</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360449171601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 17:32:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360455322531-32</Id><Title>Is ARM's A15 a complete failure. No one seems to be using it other</Title><Msg>than tegra4 which has no designs, and Exynos5 which is used in some Samsung tablets. The A15 is a power hog and runs slow. Qualcomm and Apple have their own designs, they don't use A15.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360455322531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 19:15:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360459295262-33</Id><Title>Wow, the might Intel now parrying with low budget upstart ARMH.</Title><Msg>Karma is an itch-bay. Next, they will start picking apart the Raspberry Pi design as, "flawed." What a joke.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1360459295262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 20:21:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360459366498-34</Id><Topic><Title>Is ARM's A15 a complete failure. No one seems to be using it other</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360455322531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 19:15:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Atoms are much much hotter and have low resolution support, but I would buy intc at this $21 because intc still has some cash.</Msg><Username>batmantran</Username><Timestamp>1360459366498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 20:22:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360459587622-35</Id><Topic><Title>Put down some cash down on Intel and you will thank we pumpers.</Title><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1360428175416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 11:42:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intc is paying its employees too much (most of my friends went there)! Their employees would take intc earning down and smart phones are (still behind a real tricorder) saturated.</Msg><Username>batmantran</Username><Timestamp>1360459587622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 20:26:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360460502492-36</Id><Topic><Title>Put down some cash down on Intel and you will thank we pumpers.</Title><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1360428175416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 11:42:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is Intel going to get into the tier #1 smart phones? The SEC is well aware of the InDell bribery scam that went on for twenty years. InDell has to make a superior product and mend relationships with OEMs. Right now, their products are marginal and they have no top tier design wins. Last I heard, Atom had 15 subtractive decode bridges inside and was slower than frozen sloths.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1360460502492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 20:41:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360462824977-37</Id><Title>Micro-Server shipsments to triple this year</Title><Msg>Shipments of Micro-Servers to Triple This Year – Researchers. Mobile and Cloud Computing to Skyrocket Micro-Server Sales [02/08/2013 03:35 PM] by Anton Shilov Driven by booming demand for new data center services for mobile platforms and cloud computing, shipments of micro servers are expected to more than triple this year, according to a report from IHS iSuppli. Other high-growth segments of the server market are cloud servers, blade servers and virtualization servers. Shipments this year of micro servers are forecast to reach 291 000 units, up 230% from 88 000 units in 2012. Shipments of micro servers commenced in 2011 with just 19 000 units. However, shipments by the end of 2016 will rise to some 1.2 million units. The penetration of micro servers compared to total server shipments amounted to a negligible 0.2% in 2011. But by 2016, the machines will claim a penetration rate of more than 10% – a stunning fiftyfold jump. Micro servers are general-purpose computers, housing single or multiple low-power microprocessors and usually consuming less than 45W in a single motherboard. The machines employ shared infrastructure such as power, cooling and cabling with other similar devices, allowing for an extremely dense configuration when micro servers are cascaded together. “With cloud computing and data centers in high demand in order to serve more smartphones, tablets and mobile PCs online, specific aspects of server design are becoming increasingly important, including maintenance, expandability, energy efficiency and low cost. Such factors are among the advantages delivered by micro servers compared to higher-end machines like mainframes, supercomputers and enterprise servers – all of which emphasize performance and reliability instead,” said Peter Lin, senior analyst for compute platforms at IHS. The compound annual growth rate for micro servers from 2011 to 2016 stands at a remarkable 130% - higher than that of the entire server market by a factor of 26. Shipments will rise by double- and even triple-digit percentages for each year during the period. Cui Bono? Given the dazzling outlook for micro servers, makers with strong product portfolios of the machines will be well-positioned during the next five years – as will their component suppliers and contract manufacturers. A slew of hardware providers are in line to reap benefits, including microprocessor vendors like Intel, ARM and AMD; server original equipment manufacturers such as Dell and Hewlett-Packard; and server original development manufacturers including Taiwanese firms Quanta Computer and Wistron. Among software providers, the list of potential beneficiaries from the micro server boom extends to Microsoft, Red Hat, Citrix and Oracle. For the group of application or service providers that offer micro servers to the public, entities like Amazon, eBay, Google and Yahoo are foremost. Intel first unveiled the micro server concept and reference design in 2009, ostensibly to block rival ARM from entering the field. ARM, the leader for many years in the mobile world with smartphone and tablet chips, has been just as eager to enter the server arena – dominated by x86 chip architecture from the likes of Intel and a third chip player, AMD. ARM faces an uphill battle, as the majority of server software is written for x86 architecture. Shifting from x86 to ARM will also be difficult for legacy products. ARM, however, is gaining greater support from software and OS vendors, which could potentially put pressure on Intel in the coming years, IHS believes.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1360462824977</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 21:20:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360464053403-38</Id><Title>First Impressions: Microsoft Surface Pro</Title><Msg>Microsoft’s Surface Pro launched today, and I’ve spent the last 24 hours evaluating their sophomore PC hardware effort with mostly positive observations. What follows are my initial impressions of the Surface Pro, with a detailed review coming down the pipe within a week. Surface Pro ≠ Tablets First, one important guideline to keep in mind: I won’t be comparing the Surface Pro to the iPad, because the Surface Pro defies characterization as a tablet. Anyone slapping the same label on these devices is doing you a disservice. The Surface Pro runs a full desktop OS, has the internals of an ultrabook, and resulting benchmarks put all tablets to shame. My review unit shipped with the Surface Edition of Microsoft’s Wedge Touch Mouse (an accessory I’ve become enamored with), the 128GB Surface Pro, and both versions of the iconic snap-on keyboards. Having only used the Touch Cover on the Surface RT, it needs to be said that the Type Cover is in a league of its own. The physical keys have a subtle inward curve, and while the amount of travel is minimal, it’s a joy to type on. I instantly adapted from my full-sized ergonomic keyboard and am punching this article up in Word without any slowdown or errors. I would be comfortable using it for my daily writing duties at Forbes, and it’s a no-brainer for productivity on the road. If you purchase the Surface Pro, don’t leave without the Type Cover. Display, Graphics…and Gaming? The Surface Pro’s 1920×1080 display is stunning and a noticeable upgrade from Surface RT’s 1366×768 resolution. As with RT, this is a best-in-class panel with pure whites and vibrant, realistic color. I plugged in an Xbox 360 Wireless Receiver, installed Steam, and enjoyed Portal 2 Beyond productivity, the Surface Pro has another distinguishing trait which separates it from the tablet market: gaming chops. Not just Angry Birds or Jetpack Joyride, but AAA core titles like Portal 2 and XCOM: Enemy Unknown. Portal 2 ran surprisingly well using these settings and a 1920x1080 resolution I installed and played both on my Surface Pro and was pleasantly surprised with the results. Portal 2 ran smoothly at 1920×1080 with medium shaders and high texture detail (see image, right). XCOM performed equally well at 1920×1080. (At a reader’s request, I’ll also test StarCraft II and Diablo 3 for my final review.) With Intel’s HD Graphics 4000, an Intel Core i5, and 4GB of RAM, the early verdict is that a Steam install wouldn’t be out of line. Hardcore gamers need not apply, but casual or “mid-core” gamers should dive in. Improved Audio Compared to Surface RT, the Pro’s audio capabilities have undergone a dramatic increase in quality. Music is louder, crisper, and has a shade more bass response. The speakers are in the same general location as the RT, but notice in the picture below how the top half of the Pro has venting slots. Not only are the drivers slightly larger, but I suspect the design also improves the acoustics. Rest assured you’ll be able to enjoy podcasts, Hulu Plus or Xbox Music from a distance without straining to hear. Battery Life Observations The Surface Pro’s battery ran down during the roughly 3 hour process of writing this first impressions piece. This included 30 minutes of gaming, 15 minutes of music streaming, and constant web activity. Auto-brightness was on, and I kept Outlook and MetroTwit running in the background. This is by no means conclusive testing, but in terms of anecdotal observation, battery life may be a concern. I’m confident that enabling battery-saving features, reducing brightness, and not putting the Surface Pro through “review-style” paces will result in 4 to 5 hours of battery life. Apparently all this horsepower doesn’t come without some sacrifice. Since this is all about first impressions, I’ll say I’m enthusiastic about the Surface Pro in its role as an ultrabook and productivity machine. During the next week, I’ll rigorously test its tablet incarnation, run it through some benchmarks, and give you a more detailed analysis of battery life, gaming performance, digitizer pen, wedge mouse, and general usability. For those not willing to wait for the full review – perhaps those of you holding out for Surface Pro over the RT – I seriously doubt you’ll be disappointed with this hardware. From Forbes</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360464053403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 21:40:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360464942437-39</Id><Topic><Title>First Impressions: Microsoft Surface Pro</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360464053403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 21:40:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surface Pro reviews are definitive that the Pro is vastly superior to the RT ARM version of the product. Also nice are comments saying it shouldn't be compared to a tablet because it blows tablets away: "The Surface Pro runs a full desktop OS, has the internals of an ultrabook, and resulting benchmarks put all tablets to shame." So, we can expect Intel-based tablets that will meet or exceed the form factor and batter life standards of all ARM products but whose superior performance will distinguish them. Probably by the end of the year. The Surface Pro is extensive evidence of Intel's traction in mobility and if Apple doesn't quickly jump on the bandwagon, they can expect to be condemned to the second tier of technological prowess. Intel is at last ready to take significant tablet market share by making tablets competitive with desktops in performance. Those critics who said that nobody wants a tablet with desktop performance are being shown the error of their ways. Even though the Surface Pro still has a ways to go, it is solid progress and a demonstration of demand. Improvements will have quickly in rapid-fire sequence given the power of the Intel fabrication roadmap. "The Surface Pro puts all tablets to shame." The ARM Bubble continues its descent into the land of sharp objects. Surface Pro is yet another...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360464942437</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 21:55:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360467261605-40</Id><Topic><Title>Question on Options - Deep ITM</Title><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1360383117010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 23:11:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the vix also matters....</Msg><Username>anthonyspetrino</Username><Timestamp>1360467261605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 22:34:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360468799033-41</Id><Topic><Title>First Impressions: Microsoft Surface Pro</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360464053403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 21:40:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Judging from the luke-warm response to its major product launches, it appears that Microsoft is no longer able to drum up excitement over its new stuff. This fact doesn't seem to go un-noticed by the analysts and it doesn't bode well for Intel's future as a PC chip supplier.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360468799033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 22:59:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360471051221-42</Id><Topic><Title>Micro-Server shipsments to triple this year</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1360462824977</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 21:20:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too bad</Msg><Username>optermoron</Username><Timestamp>1360471051221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 23:37:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360471435838-43</Id><Topic><Title>Question on Options - Deep ITM</Title><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1360383117010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 23:11:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A zero premium call option is a perfect proxy for the stock. When you decide to hold the option through an ex-dividend, the dividend condition you described goes into effect. Options are cash only. Not marginable. Probably not an issue. anthonyspetrino pointed out the VIX. The VIX is directly related to the size of the premium. Low VIX means low premium. High VIX means high premium. Low VIX means complacent market that is vulnerable to drops. The call options will not drop as fast as the stock but will track the stock up 1 for 1. There is nothing else that I can see. Good find.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360471435838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 23:43:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360471698212-44</Id><Topic><Title>First Impressions: Microsoft Surface Pro</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360464053403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 21:40:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Judging from the luke-warm response to its major product launches, it appears that Microsoft is no longer able to drum up excitement over its new stuff. This fact doesn't seem to go un-noticed by the analysts and it doesn't bode well for Intel's future as a PC chip supplier." [As usual you did no research before posting. The response to Surface Pro has been much better than expected after the dismal showing of the ARM RT device. And clearly you have no response to any of the posts I made on the substantial decline of the fabless foundry model as it begins its fade to black. But, hey - you earned your usual ten cents for posting unsupported, content-free drivel. Life is good, right? As far as the analysts go, who cares? They haven't demonstrated any ability other than to collaborate in manipulation. Furthermore, the greatly improved response to Surface Pro over the RT does bode well for Intel's future as a PC chip supplier. ARM as a PC chip supplier is toast. They didn't even make it out of the gate. Of course, it's Saturday night and you prolly have better things to do than to try and prevent the further descent of the ARM Bubble into the land of sharp objects...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360471698212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 23:48:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>