<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363235796631-1</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE will incorporate ALL upcoming smartphones with Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363201680264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 15:08:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>aladiesright, What makes you believe that the ARMH chips offer a better value? Remember, guys like Qualcomm and Nvidia need to pay both foundry margin to TSMC as well as royalties to ARMH. Not attacking you -- would be very interested in a legitimate response. Thanks!</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363235796631</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 00:36:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363236115692-2</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE will incorporate ALL upcoming smartphones with Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363201680264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 15:08:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In exchange for paying foundries and ARM licensing, they have significantly lower R&amp;D costs and don't have to invest in their own fabs. The barrier to entry is therefore a lot lower. That's why there are 3 or 4 big ARM licensees that Intel is going up against alone.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1363236115692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 00:41:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363236862551-3</Id><Topic><Title>Looking Good !</Title><Username>hankg1030</Username><Timestamp>1362486818570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 07:33:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHAT ! ARE U KIDDING? I'D SAY MORE LIKE $50</Msg><Username>copenhugen</Username><Timestamp>1363236862551</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 00:54:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363242069236-4</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE will incorporate ALL upcoming smartphones with Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363201680264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 15:08:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In exchange for paying foundries and ARM licensing, they have significantly lower R&amp;D costs and don't have to invest in their own fabs. You're about 10 years behind the curve.... Money for nothing and chicks for free... Perhaps you can spin ALTR dumping TSMC and going with Intel into something positive...would not surprise me. You ARM suckers just don't understand the manufacturing aspect, You always get what you pay for - there is no such thing as a free lunch, That's why both AAPL and QCOM unsuccessfully offered $ 1 billion to TSMC Qualcom spent $ 2.025 billion or 21% of sales on R%D TSMC spent $ 1.156 billion or 8% of sales on R&amp;D September 6, 2012 - Spending on R&amp;D by semiconductor companies worldwide is expected to grow 10% in 2012 to a record $53.4 billion, as companies all across the ecosystem try to keep up with more complex IC designs and new process technologies, according to data from IC Insights. Total chip sales are only expected to increase 3% in 2012 to $321.4B, says the analyst firm (others aren't so optimistic anymore), meaning R&amp;D as a percentage of sales will rise to 16.2% -- right around the 15%-17% where it's hovered for the better part of the past decade. R&amp;D/sales had been 10%-12% of revenues in the early 1990s, and just 7%-8% of sales in the late 1970s-early 1980s, the firm notes. Chip companies across the ecosphere (integrated device manufacturers [IDMs], fabless suppliers, and foundries) are seeing their development costs rise due to more complex IC designs and new process technologies, currently on 300mm wafers but with 450mm now in progress &amp; due later this decade.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363242069236</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 02:21:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363245492958-5</Id><Title>Pat Gelsinger - very carefully chosen words</Title><Msg>“I’m flattered, of course, to be considered for running such a great company as Intel,” Gelsinger said. “But I’m happy in my role at VMware and hope to be doing it for many years to come.” To me, these words do not rule out possibility of him becoming next CEO. The fact that he did not flat out dismissed it is indication that the possibility exists....</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363245492958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 03:18:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363247045133-6</Id><Topic><Title>Pat Gelsinger - very carefully chosen words</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363245492958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 03:18:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is an out of favor company at the moment. Whoever comes in needs to change that. Not an easy task for such an old and massive company. There's a lot of inertia working against you.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1363247045133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 03:44:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363248650196-7</Id><Topic><Title>I think Intel Web TV service will be a huge hit</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363147636844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 00:07:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would Intel want to have its chips in a DVD player? Yes, Intel can try to get its chips inside "Smart" TVs, but they have already tried that with the Google TV. Google TV failed (and so will Samsung "Smart" TV) because for its price, it did not offer anything radically useful. Consumers are smart, they are not going spend $3000 on a "Smart" TV, which only offers some awkward gesture and voice controls that are harder to use than the remote control. And they do not want to surf the web on a TV either, they can do this more comfortably using a phone, tablet or PC. The TV is used for 3 things - watching Live TV, watching movies, and playing games. That's it. The trick is to offer those 3 services in the most enjoyable experience for the consumer. The only way to do this is to build a platform and slowly add more and more features around it. It's all about the having a platform. PCs have Windows/MaC OS/Linux/Chrome as their platforms. Smartphones and tablets have iOS and Android. TV needs platform(s) too. Right now, the platforms for the TV are fragmented and missing for key component. Xbox, Nintendo and Playstation platforms exist for games. Netflix, Apple TV, Hulu, Amazon Prime and Youtube exists for movies. But guess what? nobody has anything for Live TV. This is the key. The cable operators control the Live TV. You can only get access to Live TV thru the cable box. Live TV does not go thru IP (internet) so cannot be shared over home network. Apple and Google couldn't take their TV products to the next level because they could not create a seamless and integrated experience with their movie platforms. The cable operators would not work with them (to make the products better) because they feared loosing the market to them. This is where Intel's Web TV service comes in. Intel is going to take control of the content. They will provide that missing link by putting Live TV thru IP. Intel's Web TV service is going to allow platforms to be built ... with INTEL INSIDE.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363248650196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 04:10:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363249094420-8</Id><Topic><Title>Pat Gelsinger - very carefully chosen words</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363245492958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 03:18:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be joking....</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363249094420</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 04:18:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363256418397-9</Id><Topic><Title>Pat Gelsinger - very carefully chosen words</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363245492958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 03:18:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gelsinger also took a public, negative swipe at ARM which sounds like he was already in CEO mode. "So when VMware CEO Pat Gelsinger reportedly said he's "skeptical" that ARM would be a big server chip player, shares fell more than 3% to 41.11. The stock closed below its 50-day moving average for the first time since early September, a warning flag for sucessful investors."</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363256418397</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 06:20:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363258182340-10</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell release date ahead of Computex?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363209075387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:11:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have been speculating on this board that Intel may pull a surprise early launch. Intel never said it was the beginning of June but that has been the rumor. The timetable doesn't make sense against all the other information I am getting. Intel has an order to things and they generally take a certain amount of time to complete each step. Seems by my estimates they should release late April early May.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363258182340</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 06:49:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363262316343-11</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell release date ahead of Computex?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363209075387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:11:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wwwDOTpcauthorityDOTcomDOTau/News/335598,intels-upcoming-z87-chipset-has-an-annoying-usb-3-bugDOTaspx ukDOThardwareDOTinfo/news/33716/usb-30-problems-for-intels-haswell</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1363262316343</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 07:58:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363263045897-12</Id><Title>We sure don't have much altitude</Title><Msg>if a major market correction comes, it could be bad.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363263045897</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 08:10:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363264260751-13</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell release date ahead of Computex?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363209075387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:11:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, that kinda sux. but it's just annoying. it isn't apollo 13 or anything like that.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363264260751</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 08:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363264571113-14</Id><Title>How long to fix Haswell USB 3 glitch?</Title><Msg>A year? I don't think Intel should intro a dysfunctional chip. Do you?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363264571113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 08:36:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363265999967-15</Id><Topic><Title>Pat Gelsinger - very carefully chosen words</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363245492958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 03:18:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly, that was a carefully chosen response that expresses his happiness for his current job, but he did not preclude taking the Intel CEO role if it were offered.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1363265999967</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 08:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363266795940-16</Id><Title>Nothing but RED for ARMH since GETANID61 popped off</Title><Msg>FUNNY STUFF!</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363266795940</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:13:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363267159749-17</Id><Title>BCCI-- SET TO BURST ON UPGRADE TO THE NASDAQ--FACTS</Title><Msg>HUGE UPSIDE!</Msg><Username>large.blocks</Username><Timestamp>1363267159749</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:19:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363267203743-18</Id><Topic><Title>Importan info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>seanlacroix518</Username><Timestamp>1363042083166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 18:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks a lot</Msg><Username>whitlockjohn510</Username><Timestamp>1363267203743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:20:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363267316210-19</Id><Title>Unimportant info about INTC future!!!</Title><Msg>Isn't it great?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363267316210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:21:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363267345332-20</Id><Topic><Title>Unimportant info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363267316210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:21:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>love it! Made my day!</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363267345332</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:22:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363267359412-21</Id><Topic><Title>Unimportant info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363267316210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:21:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great..I'm writing my Mom about it now!</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363267359412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:22:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363267389196-22</Id><Topic><Title>Nothing but RED for ARMH since GETANID61 popped off</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363266795940</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:13:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah..tooooofunny</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363267389196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363267470129-23</Id><Topic><Title>How long to fix Haswell USB 3 glitch?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363264571113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 08:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you read the links I provided (Yahoo would not let me post excerpts for some reason) a new chipset stepping will be made available in July. If you keep your external flash drives fully awake all the time, if you even have any that is, there is no problem ;-). Seriously though it's a harmless bug if you know about it beforehand and adjust your work methods accordingly to account for it e.g. regularly save of external flash documents etc.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1363267470129</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:24:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363267816286-24</Id><Topic><Title>We sure don't have much altitude</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363263045897</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 08:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if a major market correction comes, stock prices will drop. If you are not properly invested for your risk tolerance, it WILL be bad. That is sort of what the market is about.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363267816286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:30:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363267962493-25</Id><Title>Can Intel make mobile chips for Apple? Article:</Title><Msg>There is still much speculation as to who might win Apple, Inc.'s (NASDAQ: AAPL : 428.33, -0.02) mobile processor business for 2014. Intel Corporation (NASDAQ: INTC : 21.65, 0.01) might be the front runner for manufacturing Apple's next-generation mobile chips (tentatively called A7) after it got a high volume foundry customer in Altera Corporation (NASDAQ: ALTR : 34.975, -0.065). Since Intel already makes chips for MacBooks, it won't be difficult for Apple to shift its mobile chips supply to Intel. Intel, whose chips power about 80 percent of PCs, is trying to diversify from its core business and sharpened its focus on foundry business, which has been in the back burner as Intel predominantly made its own chips rather than making them for others. Moreover, the consumer shift from PC to tablets and smartphones have resulted in weak demand for PC, which is Intel's forte. With Altera deal in place, Intel may be eyeing Apple, which is one of the largest semiconductor consumer. Intel is highly regarded for its manufacturing capabilities and its technology advantage should help the chip giant make gains in foundry services and perhaps more significantly in mobile devices. Moreover, Altera deal in itself is a validation of Intel's manufacturing advantage. As Intel has publicly stated it has yet to commit material capex to its foundry business, any mobile products sold to Apple would need to be a standard product or customized variant thereof. "As Intel's business model preference is to get paid for both process and architecture, we believe an arrangement with Apple near-term and even longer-term may be based on Intel selling offshoots of its base mobile platforms," UBS analyst Stephen Chin said in a client note.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363267962493</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:32:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363268073308-26</Id><Topic><Title>We sure don't have much altitude</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363263045897</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 08:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's worse when you bought something that's only up a few percent, rather than something that's up 30-40%. Down is always down. I'm probably 10-15 years your senior and I have experienced a number of market "corrections" over the years. It's a bit like sailing the high seas.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363268073308</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363268174182-27</Id><Title>No big movers this AM...this is a computer driven market.</Title><Msg>Scary...I think a storm is heading our way.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363268174182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:36:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363268288645-28</Id><Topic><Title>Can Intel make mobile chips for Apple? Article:</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363267962493</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:32:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Although, there is one hiccup. Apple designs its mobile chips via technology licensed from ARM Holdings, a key rival to Intel's x86 architecture. While, ARM-based chips are found in almost every mobile device, Intel's own technology has lagged behind mobile chips. If Intel manages to convince Apple to deploy x86 architecture on Apple chips, then it would be a killer deal for the semiconductor giant. For Apple, it is high time to diversify its supply chain from Samsung, which is the lone supplier of microprocessors used in the iPhone and the iPad. But, the Korean technology giant has become Apple's biggest competitor in both smartphone and tablet categories. In addition, both technology giants are fighting out in courts alleging of patent infringement against each other. Korea's Samsung is expected to widen its lead over Apple in global smartphone sales this year. Samsung is estimated to capture 33 percent share of the 2013 smartphone market while Apple will hold 21 percent, according to research firm Strategy Analytics. With Samsung's smartphone sales growing at a rapid pace, Samsung may prioritize the supply of its own parts over Apple's in case of supply shortage. In this scenario, it would be wise enough for Apple to move its mobile chips manufacturing away from Samsung, and Intel would be a perfect replacement. Also, the high demand for Apple's devices makes it a must to have additional suppliers. Pressure on the existing supply chain would be higher given Apple's expansion in China and India and rumors of a cheaper iPhone. So, having an additional supplier gives more choices for Apple and mitigates the risk of not meeting the demand. If Intel wins Apple's chip business, it could be a significant revenue boost as analysts expect Apple to ship 180 million iPhones and 110 million iPads in 2014. In fiscal 2012, Apple sold 125 million iPhones and 58.3 million iPads.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363268288645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:38:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363269249200-29</Id><Topic><Title>We sure don't have much altitude</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363263045897</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 08:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's worse when you bought something that's only up a few percent, rather than something that's up 30-40%" Blanket statements are always wrong. "I'm probably 10-15 years your senior and I have experienced a number of market "corrections" over the years." Must have been very painful for you. You must be positioned very defensively with so little time left.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363269249200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:54:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363269312119-30</Id><Topic><Title>I think Intel Web TV service will be a huge hit</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363147636844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 00:07:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Citing all the reasons why Intel failed to make x86 the defacto standard in Smart TV's and consumer electronics does not make the case why its Web TV concept would be successful. If Intel had had a Clovertrail plus at the time TV and DVD makers were designing their products maybe Intel could have got the design-win instead of ARM and be in the hundreds of millions TV's and DVD players instead of ARM. Intel failed at the time because they simply lacked a product that could compete against ARM's offering, just like they lacked a product that could compete against ARM for smartphones. The reality is virtually every TV and DVD player sold today will come equipped as a "smart" device because its in the vendors interest to do so. Soon every appliance a consumer buys will be smart down to their washer and dryer. The company making the chip inside the TV, the DVD player and the Internet of Things will have by far the best opportunity to extend and grow their ecosystem to serve the customer. That could be Intel or ARM's ecosystem. It is dumb for Intel to walk away from this reality simply because they failed with the consumer electronics companies before. Now as for live TV, you state the cable companies control live TV. They absolutely do and they will continue to control live TV even IF Intel's Web TV arrives. Nothing Intel can do will change that short of buying the cable co's. Cable companies already stream video programming via IP to consumers and they already can deliver media to PC's and tablets. Further, the cable companies have an inherent advantage in delivering all IP-based media because they are also providers of the broadband Internet service to the consumers. Cable companies are allowed to charge consumers for the amount of monthly Internet service they use but they don't have to impose the same fee delivering the same service the consumer buys from the cable company. Hence cable companies will always have the advantage.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1363269312119</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:55:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363269453073-31</Id><Topic><Title>No big movers this AM...this is a computer driven market.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363268174182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:36:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reminds me of Halloween stories by the fire light. Don't forget "low volume". That means it is reallllllllllllllllly bad stuff coming.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363269453073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:57:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363269720699-32</Id><Topic><Title>Flumoxed' aliases</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1352671230820</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:00:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Add Galbaimperator to the list. This idiot changes his mind on Intel 6 times a day." ____________ Talk about nailing it.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1363269720699</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363269879434-33</Id><Title>Flumoxed Aliases</Title><Msg>atlantasap galbaimperator miltonusa hothectors amdmonkey amdroadkill On and On and ON...........changes his mind on Intel 6 times a day. Claims to know "important" Intel info that will move the price one minute, the next minute he's ready to run for the door. Complete buffoon.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1363269879434</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:04:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363270623390-34</Id><Title>TSMC to tape out Apple A7 processor in March</Title><Msg>Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSMC) is expected to tape out Apple's A7 processor on a 20nm process in March and then move the chip into risk production in May-June, which will pave the way for commercial shipments in the first quarter of 2014, according to industry sources. TSMC declined to comment on market report. TSMC is expanding production facilities at 14-fab at the Tainan Science Park with a total investment at the park of NT$500 billion (US$16.87 billion), said the sources, adding that TSMC will utilize 14-fab to manufacture the A7 chips for Apple. Meanwhile, TSMC has set a capex budget of US$9 billion for 2013, up from US$8.3 billion spent in the previous year. About 90% out of the capex for 2013 will be used to ramp up TSMC's 28nm capacity</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363270623390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:17:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363270906833-35</Id><Title>Mkt heavily Shorted</Title><Msg>This mkt is so heavily shorted that the Bulls just keep squeezing the shorts on any rhyme or reason. If the newly elected Pope farts the mkts will probably run up another 100pts and the S&amp;P might crack 1600. This mkt is soooo extended that when the rubberband breaks heaven help us all. The trend is up but everything seemed to have been baked into the price and I see a very strong resistance at 1565.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1363270906833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:21:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363271075301-36</Id><Topic><Title>REDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDD!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1363198571899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 14:16:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>upppppppppppppppppp</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1363271075301</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:24:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363271398091-37</Id><Topic><Title>Importan info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>seanlacroix518</Username><Timestamp>1363042083166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 18:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice</Msg><Username>lawrenceholcomb554</Username><Timestamp>1363271398091</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:29:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363271459555-38</Id><Topic><Title>Mkt heavily Shorted</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1363270906833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:21:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What about a tax holiday for companies repatriating overseas profits?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363271459555</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:30:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363271857864-39</Id><Topic><Title>Mkt heavily Shorted</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1363270906833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:21:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi Alex, The last time congress gave a tax exemption to the corporations to repatriate their monies the corps got the tax break but did not expand here in the US and did not hire anyone. That's why congress is hesitant. Besides with Obamacare the corps feel safer to hire and do business overseas than in the US.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1363271857864</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:37:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363271988480-40</Id><Topic><Title>Secret INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>timothy.maldonaldo</Username><Timestamp>1363184916481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report! thank you shareholder</Msg><Username>joanne.brewsky</Username><Timestamp>1363271988480</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363272041330-41</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to tape out Apple A7 processor in March</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363270623390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:17:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If this report is true, then Apple is in big trouble. I think Apple signs with Intel soon.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363272041330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:40:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363272183124-42</Id><Title>DOW 14.6 - 14.8</Title><Msg>before it starts a pullback. I don't think it will cross 15k as per my technicals.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1363272183124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:43:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363272295482-43</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to tape out Apple A7 processor in March</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363270623390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:17:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Apple is in big trouble." You just made that up... "Apple signs with Intel soon" TSMC to tape out Apple A7 processor in March</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363272295482</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:44:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363272466014-44</Id><Topic><Title>I think Intel Web TV service will be a huge hit</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363147636844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 00:07:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, the internet of things is coming. But each connected device will need to be part of a PLATFORM. This is the big fight right now. Apple, Google and Microsoft are all pushing their platforms. The fight starts with the TV then will expand to the rest. Intel's job is to make sure they can support all platforms..and they do....their other job is to make sure their chips are superior in performance, power and price...and they have that too.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363272466014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:47:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363272521340-45</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to tape out Apple A7 processor in March</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363270623390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:17:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>haha..."tape out"?! .... means nothing.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363272521340</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:48:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363272589353-46</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to tape out Apple A7 processor in March</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363270623390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:17:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>weak...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363272589353</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:49:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363272697872-47</Id><Title>Calxeda’s first ARM server is a serious threat to x86 server domination</Title><Msg>Fifteen months ago, a CPU developer named Calxeda made waves when it announced a joint effort with HP to develop dense ARM servers that would challenge x86 supremacy in the server market. The company promised that it could leverage the low power consumption of ARM products to build clusters of Cortex-A9 SoCs inside a rackmounted chassis. Anandtech’s Johan De Gelas (a name old-timers will recognize from Aces Hardware) has benchmarked and written the first review of a Calxeda-based system, the Boston Viridis. This system contains six EnergyCards, totaling 24 CPUs (96 Cortex-A9 cores) clocked at 1.4GHz. Anandtech ran the system through a range of synthetic and real-world application tests and compared its single- and quad-threaded performance to both Atom and Xeon-based solutions. The results are sure to make Intel sit up and take notice. The ECX-1000 processor at the heart of the Viridis lags even Atom in some metrics, like bandwidth utilization (Atom is ridiculously slow compared to Xeon processors, just to put that in perspective). Its per-thread performance in integer workloads, however, is quite competitive with Intel’s in-order architecture. While it never matches the Xeon-based products in terms of single-threaded performance per clock, the synthetic tests show the ECX-1000 is an excellent product. The real-world tests are stunning. Not only does Calxeda’s array of “wimpy” cores outperform Xeon processors in web server tests, it beats them in both raw performance and performance-per-watt. De Gelas writes that “the Calxeda’s ECX-1000 server node is revolutionary technology.” After seeing the performance figures, I agree. There’s a place for ARM products in the datacenter. This also makes AMD’s long-term bet on an ARM server solution look like a good idea.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363272697872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363272752362-48</Id><Title>Getanid's been pumping TSMC "taping out" for 2 years</Title><Msg>Looks at his post history. Never seen such a blowhard.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363272752362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:52:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363272759535-49</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to tape out Apple A7 processor in March</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363270623390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:17:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you really read this article? Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSMC) is expected to tape out Apple's A7 processor on a 20nm process in March and then move the chip into risk production in May-June, which will pave the way for commercial shipments in the first quarter of 2014 Expected and produce in 2014. TSMC is expanding production facilities at 14-fab at the Tainan Science Park with a total investment at the park of NT$500 billion (US$16.87 billion), Lot more than CAPEX allocated for 2013 .Meanwhile, TSMC has set a capex budget of US$9 billion for 2013, up from US$8.3 billion spent in the previous year. About 90% out of the capex for 2013 will be used to ramp up TSMC's 28nm capacity Oh they are going to spend 90% of 2013 CAPEX for 28nm production. I haven't herd BS like this since Nixon said "Let me say this about that"</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1363272759535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:52:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363272822284-50</Id><Topic><Title>Unimportant info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363267316210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:21:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks a million!</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363272822284</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363273104398-51</Id><Title>Well Known INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Msg>This is dynamite!</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363273104398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:58:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363273432949-52</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to tape out Apple A7 processor in March</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363270623390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:17:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, then tell it like it is... what are the numbers... ??</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363273432949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 11:03:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363273687464-53</Id><Topic><Title>Pat Gelsinger - very carefully chosen words</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363245492958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 03:18:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This pig is such an underperforming POS, it's going to take a cure for cancer to get it to $23..Nice stock for 90 year old widows..</Msg><Username>pentomic</Username><Timestamp>1363273687464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 11:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363274519521-54</Id><Topic><Title>REDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDD!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1363198571899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 14:16:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you get my package? Bet you did and gobbled it down. You probably even licked the bowel and are now stuffed. Right?</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363274519521</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 11:21:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363274873802-55</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to tape out Apple A7 processor in March</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363270623390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:17:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's your article, not mine, you tell me! All I know is they say 9B for 2013 CAPEX and 90% is committed to 28nm in 2013. They also say they are going to spend an additional 16.87 B on 20nm for production in 2014. Seems they are double spending, kinda like congress. Only congress can get away with it by printing money, TSM can't.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1363274873802</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 11:27:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363274981511-56</Id><Topic><Title>I think Intel Web TV service will be a huge hit</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363147636844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 00:07:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes and the TV and DVD are already established platforms that consumers will always buy. Current TV's and Blu-Ray players will ultimately be replaced by new versions that support 4K resolutions so those devices aren't going away. The Intel Web TV is not a neccessary device because the consumer can already get all the live TV and streaming the Web TV promises to do. The only real innovation Web TV offers is the potential add revenue from spying on its cusomers but that's also its most objectionable feature.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1363274981511</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 11:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363275495804-57</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to tape out Apple A7 processor in March</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363270623390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:17:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's your article, not mine" Not my article... GEESH !! just posted it.. "All I know is they say 9B for 2013 CAPEX and 90% is committed to 28nm in 2013. " Yes, that's what's been stated... "They also say they are going to spend an additional 16.87 B on 20nm for production in 2014. Seems they are double spending" I was hearing thru the grapevine that Apple bought an entire site at 20nm... Could add some credibility to that... but then again, the $16B was from DIGITIMES... :)</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363275495804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 11:38:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363275751004-58</Id><Title>Army back up, Intel back down, what ya gonna do ?</Title><Msg>Oh well, maybe tomorrow things get better for this stock and worse for Army. Can things go much worse. ? The competition has the right mix of performance and price. Intel now has too much cost in their chips IMHO. The world of chips has changed IMHO. Hi Wally.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1363275751004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 11:42:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363275783743-59</Id><Topic><Title>Getanid's been pumping TSMC "taping out" for 2 years</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363272752362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:52:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Getanid's been taping out his 4 inch #$%$ since 2011. True story.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363275783743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 11:43:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363275885943-60</Id><Topic><Title>I think Intel Web TV service will be a huge hit</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363147636844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 00:07:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to be preoccupied with a bigbrother scenario,IIMO it's simply not the case,since one can turn off the camera if they want,it's about a unique quality customized viewing experiance, Anyway at the very least give this potential big revenue maker a chance.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1363275885943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 11:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363276271238-61</Id><Topic><Title>I think Intel Web TV service will be a huge hit</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363147636844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 00:07:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>flushing money down the terrlet they are.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1363276271238</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 11:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363276433322-62</Id><Title>Getanid feels important talking about "Taping out"</Title><Msg>Maybe he should just TAP out. Getanid61 by norcalnative_2•Feb 28, 2012 11:26 AM. getanid61•Feb 28, 2012 10:23 PM . So then either Tegra 4 was taped out before Dec 2011 or customers don't have any samples(yet)...</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363276433322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 11:53:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363276501389-63</Id><Topic><Title>Secret INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>timothy.maldonaldo</Username><Timestamp>1363184916481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for sharing</Msg><Username>ywilliam63sh</Username><Timestamp>1363276501389</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 11:55:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363276586442-64</Id><Topic><Title>I think Intel Web TV service will be a huge hit</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363147636844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 00:07:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To big of a potential $$$$$ maker to ignore,nothing ventured nothing gained I say.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1363276586442</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 11:56:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363277239113-65</Id><Topic><Title>Army back up, Intel back down, what ya gonna do ?</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1363275751004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 11:42:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARMH is still below its 50 DMA. This will only get worse as the 50 DMA keeps creeping up. Notice how the stock rebounded a bit but failed to break back through this critical resistance level? Volume was very heavy on the break, but volumes are now very light. This is a sucker's rally in ARMH.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363277239113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 12:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363278422365-66</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to tape out Apple A7 processor in March</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363270623390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:17:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What would be amazing is if anyone thought this was good news for ARM. Beginning production in 2014 means no volume production until at least 2015. So maybe if all goes really well they will have 20nm production in 2015 and if things continue to go really well they may have the half-step to FinFET in 2017. In the meantime all their CapEx is going into 28nm in 2013 so they can put their 28nm up against Intel's 14nm. More proof that it's game over in the fabrication wars...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363278422365</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 12:27:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363278541981-67</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to tape out Apple A7 processor in March</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363270623390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:17:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I was hearing thru the grapevine that Apple bought an entire site at 20nm..." What, Semiaccurate?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363278541981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 12:29:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363278806083-68</Id><Topic><Title>Well Known INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363273104398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:58:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great post!</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363278806083</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 12:33:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363278828723-69</Id><Topic><Title>Unimportant info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363267316210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:21:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>keep it coming!</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363278828723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 12:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363279946469-70</Id><Title>Yahoo MB became 80% spammers</Title><Msg>I'm checking my charts on google now, too bad they don't have MBs.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1363279946469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 12:52:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363280146102-71</Id><Topic><Title>Calxeda’s first ARM server is a serious threat to x86 server domination</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363272697872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:51:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uneducated BS. Who in their right mind compares a 24 socket server with a 2 socket server which is less than half the price ?! I know Johan (and Charlie Demerjian) from the Aceshardware days and respect his work but he slipped up here. The correct comparison would have been against a 4 socket Romley server which is what it was designed for or against greater nodes of 2-way LV Xeons. A 4 socket Romley would have easily beat this Boston 24 node A9 server on performance, performance/watt and with the right hardware configuration, price.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1363280146102</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 12:55:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363280338125-72</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to tape out Apple A7 processor in March</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363270623390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:17:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"About 90% out of the capex for 2013 will be used to ramp up TSMC's 28nm capacity". It thought they were past "ramping up" 28nm production.?.?</Msg><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1363280338125</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 12:58:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363280980413-73</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to tape out Apple A7 processor in March</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363270623390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:17:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could add some credibility to that... but then again, the $16B was from DIGITIMES... :) Neither one of you seem to be able to read ... total investment will add up to $16 billion. 20nm will be marginal with respect to cost/performance improvement. CSCO is a large customer of TSMC - Intel will grab some of that business (the most lucrative) and portion of TSMC growth will be redirected to Intel. What appears to be small for Intel is NOT small for TSMC. The real problem for TSMC is 16nm FF (see ALTR decision)</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363280980413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 13:09:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363281334132-74</Id><Topic><Title>Secret INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>timothy.maldonaldo</Username><Timestamp>1363184916481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>walkeradrian14</Username><Timestamp>1363281334132</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 13:15:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363281642983-75</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo MB became 80% spammers</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1363279946469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 12:52:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To bad Yhoo has allowed it to get so far out of hand,one ID/person system IMO is one way to defeat it.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1363281642983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 13:20:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363281663219-76</Id><Topic><Title>Importan info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>seanlacroix518</Username><Timestamp>1363042083166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 18:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fantastic job</Msg><Username>leath_david</Username><Timestamp>1363281663219</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 13:21:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363281822021-77</Id><Topic><Title>Pat Gelsinger - very carefully chosen words</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363245492958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 03:18:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gunslinger did not say no, he said HELL NO !</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1363281822021</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 13:23:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363282242585-78</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo MB became 80% spammers</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1363279946469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 12:52:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yahoo is idiocy for not insisting on one ID/person.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363282242585</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 13:30:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363283065182-79</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo MB became 80% spammers</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1363279946469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 12:52:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google used to, when the stopped I switched here, but havent been very happy with Yahoofinance page/message board lately</Msg><Username>akrinn</Username><Timestamp>1363283065182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 13:44:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363283402109-80</Id><Topic><Title>Calxeda’s first ARM server is a serious threat to x86 server domination</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363272697872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:51:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looking at the big picture, there now exists competition for Intel in servers. That's bound to drive down ASPs and ARM based startups like Boston don't need much to survive in a race to the bottom. As startups, they don't have market capitalization to worry about like the old established Intel.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1363283402109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 13:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363283761561-81</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo MB became 80% spammers</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1363279946469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 12:52:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And I suppose you only have one i.d., doooooooooooshnozzle.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1363283761561</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 13:56:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363284017046-82</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo MB became 80% spammers</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1363279946469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 12:52:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How hypocritical, seeing that the ULTIMATE form of spam is you pumping Facebook to 100 then selling at 27 when nobody was looking. #$%$.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363284017046</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 14:00:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363284098786-83</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo MB became 80% spammers</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1363279946469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 12:52:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess the only way to change it is to complain to Yhoo,I know they care about public opinion,when they shut down the other forums on April 1st unforunately more sewage will migrate here IMO.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1363284098786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 14:01:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363284965926-84</Id><Topic><Title>Calxeda’s first ARM server is a serious threat to x86 server domination</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363272697872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:51:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Looking at the big picture, there now exists competition for Intel in servers. That's bound to drive down ASPs and ARM based startups like Boston don't need much to survive in a race to the bottom. As startups, they don't have market capitalization to worry about like the old established Intel." [Let's see - who am I going to believe? You or EMC who says ARM has no potential for significant penetration of the server market. EMC or the guy who has never heard of ZDNet? EMC or the guy who says people don't need serious computing capabilities? EMC or the guy who thinks everyone's computing needs can be met by an iPad? EMC or the guy who continuously posts up the most ludicrous arguments with no support whatsoever? I know it will come as a surprised to you, just like the drop in ARM's stock price, but I'm going to have to go with EMC on this one. ARM's server efforts are a joke...] [And saying that startups don't need to worry about capital belongs on your impressive list of the stupidest things said in technology and business. Intel doesn't have to worry about capital - they have plenty and it comes from profits. Startups don't have plenty because they must borrow since they don't have profits...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363284965926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 14:16:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363285054637-85</Id><Topic><Title>Calxeda’s first ARM server is a serious threat to x86 server domination</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363272697872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:51:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Looking at the big picture, there now exists competition for Intel in servers. ' It's always existed and it is still more potent than this A9 toy. Power, Sparc, IBM System Z, even AMD. You can easily configure and build a Xeon system to beat this Boston on any metric you want. This toy will have zero effect on Intel's server a.s.p just like ARM phone and tablet chips have had zero effect on Core a.s.p contrary to popular misbelief that it would. CPU is also only about 5-10% server cost so it is not Intel that would engage in any price cutting if it was ever needed but the x86 server makers themselves.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1363285054637</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 14:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363286447085-86</Id><Topic><Title>Calxeda’s first ARM server is a serious threat to x86 server domination</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363272697872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:51:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As startups, they don't have market capitalization to worry about like the old established Intel." This guy is out to lunch!</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363286447085</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 14:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363286651228-87</Id><Title>The Mobile Business In A (Large) Nutshell</Title><Msg>"If Intel goes it alone, and is successful, it means that Qualcomm's (and others) Application Processor business will decline precipitously. It means that Apple will have no choice but to use Intel designed x86 based application processors or they will not be competitive in the market. It also means that Samsung will have to abandon their in-house designs and use the Intel devices or they will not be competitive in the market. It will also mean that the ARMH stock price will return to $10." From Russ Fischer</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363286651228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 14:44:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363286848076-88</Id><Title>Nice to See</Title><Msg>Nice to see ARM consolidate a bit - in preparation for the drop below $40...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363286848076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 14:47:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363286892208-89</Id><Topic><Title>Pat Gelsinger - very carefully chosen words</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363245492958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 03:18:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nuff, you should become Intel's new CEO since you're so brilliant. You could run the company and give directions via the Yahoo message board. That way if something went wrong, you could claim that you had no stake in it, you were just a spectator (like now). Everyone would see you as being very credible and ethical :)</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363286892208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 14:48:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363287724362-90</Id><Topic><Title>Well Known INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363273104398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:58:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great!</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363287724362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:02:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363287728124-91</Id><Title>Shouldn't we be back at $24 by now? Seriously.....</Title><Msg>Gotta be hedgies and banks or some other unknown force.........I am not selling......why would anyone else be selling.......we are at new highs......#$%$?????</Msg><Username>waltertobley2000</Username><Timestamp>1363287728124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:02:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363287745573-92</Id><Topic><Title>Unimportant info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363267316210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:21:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fantastic!</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363287745573</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:02:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363287768829-93</Id><Topic><Title>Well Known INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363273104398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:58:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's so great!</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363287768829</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363287830552-94</Id><Topic><Title>Shouldn't we be back at $24 by now? Seriously.....</Title><Username>waltertobley2000</Username><Timestamp>1363287728124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:02:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree...this is like watching paint dry...and sometimes, depending upon what you paint over, it never dries.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363287830552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:03:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363287898076-95</Id><Topic><Title>Shouldn't we be back at $24 by now? Seriously.....</Title><Username>waltertobley2000</Username><Timestamp>1363287728124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:02:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Possibly people are waiting for the silent period so they know there won't be a warning...well, that's Monday...so maybe INTC up then...who knows?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363287898076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:04:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363288081321-96</Id><Topic><Title>Secret INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>timothy.maldonaldo</Username><Timestamp>1363184916481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome report !!</Msg><Username>richardhernandez960</Username><Timestamp>1363288081321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:08:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363288249593-97</Id><Topic><Title>Well Known INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363273104398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:58:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow..that's great well known info!</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363288249593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:10:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363288820001-98</Id><Topic><Title>Secret INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>timothy.maldonaldo</Username><Timestamp>1363184916481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you !</Msg><Username>gregorymoore964</Username><Timestamp>1363288820001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:20:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363289528956-99</Id><Title>ARMH UP INTC DOWN</Title><Msg>So what's new, lemmings?</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1363289528956</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:32:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363289937126-100</Id><Topic><Title>Well Known INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363273104398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:58:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes yes yes</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363289937126</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:38:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363290618490-101</Id><Title>How Does Websters Spell TURD- I-N-T-E-L</Title><Msg>I just looked it up.. Not only is it spelled this way, but there is a picture of Paul Otellini right there in the dictionary... WHOOOOOOOOOOO,,, They even have a scratch &amp; Sniff... Whoooooooooooeeeeeeeeee,, that thing really smells bad..... Just like this company and it's stock.....</Msg><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363290618490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:50:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363290789781-102</Id><Title>Looks like some idiot tried his best to take it down but</Title><Msg>failed. what an idiot he must be.</Msg><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1363290789781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:53:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363291151651-103</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>linkosarah</Username><Timestamp>1362149300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:48:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just subscribed. I am hoping for the best.</Msg><Username>lovelinesslou</Username><Timestamp>1363291151651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:59:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363291799806-104</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like some idiot tried his best to take it down but</Title><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1363290789781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel probably bought his shares</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363291799806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:09:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363291949451-105</Id><Title>18? Just two bucks higher than GS</Title><Msg>Intel Rating Reiterated by Sanford C. Bernstein (INTC) March 14th, 2013 - 0 comments - Filed Under - by Patrick Bannon Intel (NASDAQ: INTC)‘s stock had its “underperform” rating restated by equities researchers at Sanford C. Bernstein in a report issued on Thursday. They currently have a $18.00 target price on the stock. Intel traded down 0.35% on Thursday, hitting $21.5799. Intel has a 52-week low of $19.23 and a 52-week high of $29.27. The stock’s 50-day moving average is currently $21.12. The company has a market cap of $106.7 billion and a price-to-earnings ratio of 10.17. Intel last released its earnings data on Thursday, January 17th. The company reported $0.48 earnings per share for the quarter, beating the analysts’ consensus estimate of $0.45 by $0.03. The company had revenue of $13.50 million for the quarter, compared to the consensus estimate of $13.76 billion. During the same quarter last year, the company posted $0.64 earnings per share. Intel’s revenue was down 3.0% compared to the same quarter last year. Analysts expect that Intel will post $1.94 EPS for the current fiscal year. A number of other firms have also recently commented on INTC. Analysts at Goldman Sachs reiterated a “sell” rating on shares of Intel in a research note to investors on Friday, March 8th. They now have a $16.00 price target on the stock. Separately, analysts at TheStreet reiterated a “buy” rating on shares of Intel in a research note to investors on Thursday, March 7th. Finally, analysts at Robert W. Baird reiterated an “outperform” rating on shares of Intel in a research note to investors on Monday, March 4th. They now have a $26.00 price target on the stock. Sixteen equities research analysts have rated the stock with a buy rating, two have assigned an overweight rating, twenty-seven have assigned a hold rating, two have issued an underweight rating, and four have given a sell rating to the stock. Intel currently has an average rating of “hold” and an average price target of $22.92. Intel Corporation designs and manufactures integrated digital technology platforms. A platform consists of a microprocessor and chipset.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1363291949451</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:12:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363292279151-106</Id><Title>INTC to suffer in 2nd Half</Title><Msg>Wall St. Cheat Sheet.... whiskey tango foxtrot. when will this ever end?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363292279151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:17:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363292323624-107</Id><Topic><Title>Secret INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>timothy.maldonaldo</Username><Timestamp>1363184916481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report !</Msg><Username>coral.elliot</Username><Timestamp>1363292323624</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:18:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363292611886-108</Id><Title>INTC investors not participating in the rally</Title><Msg>unless, holding fixed is participating.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363292611886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:23:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363293949776-109</Id><Topic><Title>Well Known INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363273104398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:58:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHISKEY, TANGO, FOXTROT (Classic Fluxmoxed alias now used by Galba Imperator) is wrong with you? You find this to be humorous? You really are off your rocker. Wow. I feel sorry for you so will leave you alone.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1363293949776</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:45:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363293979826-110</Id><Topic><Title>How Does Websters Spell TURD- I-N-T-E-L</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363290618490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I looked it up too, but only found a picture of DanaLucy with yours and all of the other fake IDs. You could rotate the picture of DanaLucy in 3-D so it's possible to see where the backbone is missing. Toooooo Funnnny</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363293979826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:46:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363294190464-111</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like some idiot tried his best to take it down but</Title><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1363290789781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually he is really a she. Joann was the one wielding the Ax today. She is a know nothing analyst who has sort of bounced around brokerage firms. Another Phd economist who doesn't know squat about technology or engineering.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363294190464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:49:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363294257303-112</Id><Title>Just for Fun</Title><Msg>Run a one-month ARM verses Intel comparison. See that big gap that started opening on March 5th? It's gonna get bigger...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363294257303</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:50:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363294302266-113</Id><Title>Where's the Paul.Otelini poster?</Title><Msg>Get out here and show us that fancy Math of yours on how Intel will get to 3.00 EPS, raving skumbag. By Mark Lawson | More Articles March 14, 2013 Page 3 of 3 Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC): Current price $21.55 The chip analyst JoAnne Feeney at Longbow Research reported that her conversations with vendors of components for personal computers imply to her that the second half is shaping up worse than expected, and might cause problems for PC-related names like Intel, Advanced Micro Devices, Nvidia, and Intersil Corporation. Feeney maintains Neutrals on all four names, commenting that “contacts now see desktop units down 5 to 10 percent for the year vs. our forecast for INTC DT segment to be down 4 percent year-over-year in 2013. Look for a slow Haswell ramp as last year’s inventory build, following a surprisingly weak second half, leads the industry to stick with the safer Ivy Bridge platform (socket compatible with Sandy Bridge, unlike Haswell) and for Haswell to make up less than 50 percent of desktop CPU shipments even in the fourth quarter.”</Msg><Username>foxnewzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363294302266</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:51:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363294356450-114</Id><Title>Some comments couple days ago from ASML</Title><Msg>I actually believe Intel is extending its lead - no difference or very little in printing 14nm CPUs or SoCs. Though ALTR commited to TSMC 20nm (probably as much as 18 months ago) Apple will do the same - just too much at stake for Apple taking a chance. Intel chip analysts will be the last one to figure it out The more you start to look into the details where an eagle is it looks like when you go to a 14-nanometer logic design, which they will call 10 or 11 or 9 in terms of nomenclature they (TSM, Glofo, Samsung - my comment)) also call 20-nanometer 16 and 14 and it’s one big mess in terms of how do you call it. But if you look at it in terms of lithography point of view, 14-nanometer lines which is the next generation. It comes after 20 is awfully, awfully difficult in double-patterning left below multiple-patterning and if at all you are able to do it, you are imposing yourself a lot of design restrictions, limitations and also at significant higher cost.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363294356450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363294471800-115</Id><Title>Just for Fun</Title><Msg>Lets look at Intel's chart since Wallisweaver called it a strong buy 1 year ago.</Msg><Username>foxnewzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363294471800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:54:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363294868453-116</Id><Topic><Title>INTC to suffer in 2nd Half</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363292279151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The idiot has it backwards. So, so first half. Blockbuster 2nd half.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363294868453</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:01:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363295007006-117</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH UP INTC DOWN</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1363289528956</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It got half of its loses back from yesterday. That is progress.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363295007006</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:03:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363295077436-118</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like some idiot tried his best to take it down but</Title><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1363290789781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, she said, "Look for a slow Haswell ramp as last year’s inventory build, following a surprisingly weak second half, leads the industry to stick with the safer Ivy Bridge platform (socket compatible with Sandy Bridge, unlike Haswell) and for Haswell to make up less than 50 percent of desktop CPU shipments even in the fourth quarter." Except there wasn't an inventory build. As recently reported there was a very significant inventory drop. How can an analyst miss this kind of thing? Unless they make things up as they go like khitchdee. And does Intel care if they continue to sell the cash cow Ivy Bridge processors? If there is any logic or research in her findings, it didn't get published. And Intel finished flat any way. James Covello better get on the horn and make some more calls to his peeps (perps?) in the Intel Manipulation Committee. I heard they are calling an emergency meeting to "discuss why things just aren't going as planned" and to open up a couple of new orifices on the DanaLucy team. Well, it's really just DanaLucy and his band of merry imaginary fake ID investors...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363295077436</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:04:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363295232081-119</Id><Topic><Title>Just for Fun</Title><Username>foxnewzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363294471800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:54:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Inte's down 30 percent since then. Meanwhile ARMH is up 100% since then and Wally says to look at ARMH chart. You can fix crazy. You can't even dress it up.</Msg><Username>foxnewzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363295232081</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:07:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363295314116-120</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like some idiot tried his best to take it down but</Title><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1363290789781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She sort of gets things backwards and I just don't understand why people pay attention to her. She said awhile back. "AMD's growth prospects look better then Intel." Well we can see where her type of logic can lead you.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363295314116</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:08:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363295382291-121</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like some idiot tried his best to take it down but</Title><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1363290789781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, she said, "Look for a slow Haswell ramp as last year’s inventory build, following a surprisingly weak second half, leads the industry to stick with the safer Ivy Bridge platform (socket compatible with Sandy Bridge, unlike Haswell) and for Haswell to make up less than 50 percent of desktop CPU shipments even in the fourth quarter." The way I see it : Intel reduced inventory of "legacy parts" and build inventory for Haswell</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363295382291</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:09:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363295387649-122</Id><Title>Galba Imperator (Flumoxed) and all his aliases walk into a bar....</Title><Msg>..........Whiskey Tango Foxtrot happens next?</Msg><Username>foxnewzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363295387649</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:09:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363295391880-123</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH UP INTC DOWN</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1363289528956</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It (ARM) got half of its loses back from yesterday. That is progress." [Yeah, that or consolidation in preparation for lower lows and lower highs. After 9 days of moving down it only makes sense for the stock to pause for a moment. Let's watch and see what happens now. A continuation of the downward spiral is more likely...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363295391880</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:09:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363295441533-124</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH UP INTC DOWN</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1363289528956</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARMH's up 100% since last year, Intel's down 30%. LOL @ your sour grapes. Just pathetic.</Msg><Username>foxnewzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363295441533</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:10:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363295527766-125</Id><Topic><Title>Galba Imperator (Flumoxed) and all his aliases walk into a bar....</Title><Username>foxnewzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363295387649</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:09:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got rid of flumoxed. I only have one alias at a time. How bout you Lucy? you have to be quite the idiot to take Foxnews as your moniker.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363295527766</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:12:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363295646329-126</Id><Topic><Title>Just for Fun</Title><Username>foxnewzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363294471800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:54:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DanaLucy always capable of finding a stat to manipulate. But Intel is not down 30 percent in the last month and ARM is not up 100 percent. Just go look at the monthly comparison (Intel is widening the stock performance gap over ARM). And put DL DumbAzzz on ignore with his new fake ID...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363295646329</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:14:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363295729743-127</Id><Topic><Title>Well Known INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363273104398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:58:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, another example of the Liberal sense of humor. Could you IMAGINE having to hang out with this Galba Imperator DOLT?</Msg><Username>foxnewzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363295729743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:15:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363296260129-128</Id><Topic><Title>Well Known INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363273104398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:58:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone must have opened the lid on a garbage can full of 3 week old meat, and all of these stinkin' flies have shown up. , all one guy of course, foxnews = intel_dividend = lucy.....</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363296260129</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:24:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363296305239-129</Id><Topic><Title>Unimportant info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363267316210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 09:21:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wonderful stuff.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363296305239</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:25:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363296559444-130</Id><Title>Big battery breakthrough for Intel ?</Title><Msg>Intel to launch 4th generation core processor in India with focus on battery Charanjit Ahuja : Chandigarh, Thu Mar 14 2013, 22:09 hrs Intel Technololgy India Private Limited will launch its 4th generation Intel core processor in the middle of this year in India. A unique feature of the fourth generation processor would be that it would run on as little as 10W battery and would represent a major leap in battery life.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363296559444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:29:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363296864907-131</Id><Topic><Title>Shouldn't we be back at $24 by now? Seriously.....</Title><Username>waltertobley2000</Username><Timestamp>1363287728124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:02:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Honestly, there is no catalyst for the stock near term. That is ok. I am happy to buy now and wait to collect. I am still getting my divy. I have been saying this is a second half story for this stock. If you are looking for an explosion higher, look for another stock.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363296864907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363297348648-132</Id><Title>Digitimes is confirming TSM 20nm process is in trouble, and won't be ready</Title><Msg>for initial production until mid 2014, and volume production in 2015. If everything goes well. WOW!! Apple has huge volumes, TSM can't satisfy them. Intel is the only choice for apple.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363297348648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363297617705-133</Id><Topic><Title>Secret INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>timothy.maldonaldo</Username><Timestamp>1363184916481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good report ;)</Msg><Username>dannycarter53</Username><Timestamp>1363297617705</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:46:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363298033698-134</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes is confirming TSM 20nm process is in trouble, and won't be ready</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363297348648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is an interesting article. It states intel will get 10% of A7 orders. Perhaps, TSMCs slow ramp up is the reason.?. Josephine Lien, Taipei; Jackie Chang, DIGITIMES [Tuesday 12 March 2013] Foundry service providers Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSMC) and Samsung Electronics are reportedly competing for Apple's A7 processor orders. Rumors regarding the possibility of Intel obtaining the orders have also spread. According to institutional investors, Intel may obtain 10% of Apple's A7 processor orders. The patent lawsuits between Samsung and Apple have been heating up, causing the latter to reduce its reliance on the former. Apple has been shifting orders of DRAM, mobile RAM chips and panels away from Samsung. Samsung used to be the sole OEM firm for Apple's processors, but the latter has now begun to issue orders to other firms. TSMC has been said to become the second largest supplier for Apple's A7 processors and production is reportedly to begin in 2014. But recent rumors have spread that Intel may also receive Apple's orders. According to institutional investors, Samsung is likely to receive 50% of the A7 processor orders, TSMC 40%, and Intel 10%. In the past, Apple's processor orders were unattractive because of low profit margins and Samsung was the only cooperating firm. In addition, at the time Samsung's smartphones were no threat to Apple's iPhone. But Samsung has since become the biggest smartphone vendor in the world.</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1363298033698</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:53:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363298350887-135</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes is confirming TSM 20nm process is in trouble, and won't be ready</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363297348648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>digitimes is a lot of B.S.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363298350887</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:59:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363298528506-136</Id><Topic><Title>Importan info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>seanlacroix518</Username><Timestamp>1363042083166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 18:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome</Msg><Username>roberthawkins100</Username><Timestamp>1363298528506</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:02:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363298869455-137</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes is confirming TSM 20nm process is in trouble, and won't be ready</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363297348648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>uhhhhh, you just quoted an article from Digitimes in your original post. So are you saying that your original post is B.S. or that you are dumber than a box of rocks........or both?</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363298869455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:07:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363298996776-138</Id><Title>If TSMC is spending 90% of CapEx this year on 28nm, they won't have 20nm</Title><Msg>volume production next year. They have to fund their 20nm this year to have volume in 2014. Intel is funding 14nm CapEx this year, to have volume next year. Like I've been telling you all this for a long, TSMC's 20nm is in trouble. Apple has no choice but to go with Intel.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363298996776</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:09:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363299144910-139</Id><Title>Xolo launces speedy phone with long battery life</Title><Msg>Xolo launches Intel-powered smartphone at Rs 19,999 : Panjim, Thu Mar 14 2013, 21:47 hrs Xolo today announced the launch of its new Android smartphone 'Xolo 1000' powered by Intel's atom processor at a price of Rs 19,999 apiece. "Xolo 1000 has 2 gigahertz Intel atom processor which can process at least two applications simultaneously like a phone with dual core processor. We have tested this phone against top models of international brands and have found it to be the fastest," Xolo Business Head Sunil Raina said here. He claimed that during the test Xolo 1000 showed two times high processing speed in linpack test which is done to validate browsing speed. Xolo 1000 will be available on e-commerce portals from March 20 and at retail stores from March 21. "Xolo 1000 loaded web pages with more speed compared to others. Nearest competitor loaded web page in 922 millisecond and Xolo loaded same pages at in 917 millisecond," Raina added. The phone has 4.7 inch screen, 8Gb internal memory, 8 megapixel rear and 1.3 megapixel front camera. Xolo's co-founder and Director Vishal Sehgal said that Xolo 1000 battery back supports talk time of up to 9.5 hours both on 2G and 3G networks. "The battery will last after 38 hours if a person runs only music on it. An user can run high definition video on it for 6 hours," Sehgal said. Xolo is first in Asia and second globally, after Motorola in Europe to launch smartphone built on this 2ghz Intel chipset.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363299144910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:12:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363299414869-140</Id><Topic><Title>Xolo launces speedy phone with long battery life</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363299144910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:12:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's an Android phone. Intel is getting bashed hard because greedy people want to get in at 19 again.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363299414869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:16:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363299499619-141</Id><Title>Intel Android based phones. HUGE</Title><Msg>What's TSMC taping out ? lmao</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363299499619</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:18:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363299836151-142</Id><Title>Intel releases Android Dual bootable on Windows 8</Title><Msg>Dual Bootable Android 4.2.2 Released By Intel By Edwin Kee on 03/12/2013 23:14 PDT Dual Bootable Android 4.2.2 Released By Intel would be the name on your lips, assuming you have been on the lookout to find a way to enjoy the Android platform on your desktop or your notebook, and have given it a go with pre-alpha builds of software which tend to carry a whole lot of bugs with them. Well, Intel, has just rolled out an Intel-optimized build of Android 4.2.2 Jelly Bean which is now capable of dual booting alongside Windows 8 as an operating system, now how about that? One must stress, however, that the recently introduced build of Android 4.2.2 Jelly Bean was specially rolled out for developers and for folks who think that they fall under the “most enthusiastic of enthusiasts” category. It is not all fun and games, but there is a bunch of new options to consider, as the new code has been built on the Linux 3.8 kernel, and sports a new interactive installer, with of course, the aforementioned ability to dual-boot on a Windows 8 system. Can you smell a spanking new update for the Motorola RAZR i in the works already?</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363299836151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:23:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363300522868-143</Id><Title>New Windows-powered tablets threaten iPad's enterprise dominance, claims analyst</Title><Msg>zdnetDOTcom/new-windows-powered-tablets-threaten-ipads-enterprise-dominance-claims-analyst-7000012624</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1363300522868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:35:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363300906775-144</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes is confirming TSM 20nm process is in trouble, and won't be ready</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363297348648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's an interesting response :-)</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1363300906775</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:41:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363301322103-145</Id><Title>A lot of people think PC/Desktop sales are still imploding</Title><Msg>This is the basis of the downgrades,and "sell" s from the analysts. Does anyone have any quality info about this? My ignore list is really long, and I expect it will get longer tonight, but I think we need some independent confirmation that the 2nd half is either going to be a disaster or otherwise.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363301322103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:48:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363301534101-146</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes is confirming TSM 20nm process is in trouble, and won't be ready</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363297348648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is an interesting article. It states intel will get 10% of A7 orders. Perhaps, TSMCs slow ramp up is the reason.?. Intel = TriGate TSMC = planar The article makes not much sense</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363301534101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:52:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363301874995-147</Id><Topic><Title>Secret INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>timothy.maldonaldo</Username><Timestamp>1363184916481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks !</Msg><Username>isabelle.cervantes</Username><Timestamp>1363301874995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:57:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363304344181-148</Id><Topic><Title>New Windows-powered tablets threaten iPad's enterprise dominance, claims analyst</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1363300522868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:35:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I concur with that and it's about time.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1363304344181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 19:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363304719268-149</Id><Topic><Title>New Windows-powered tablets threaten iPad's enterprise dominance, claims analyst</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1363300522868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:35:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The new breed of enterprise tablets provides the same comprehensive PC enterprise features deployed and already in use by enterprises," the report explains. "While the iPad provides many new features, enterprise must evaluate, deploy, train IT and purchase new tools. Domain Join and Active Directory are not supported on the iPad." Moorhead lists a number of advantages that Windows-powered tablets have over the iPad, at the top of which is backward compatibility. The Windows-powered hardware listed is compatible with over a million peripherals, while the selection of add-ons on offer for the iPad is limited. Another factor working against the iPad is price. Both the Latitude 10 and the ThinkPad Tablet 2 come in cheaper than a 64GB Wi-Fi-only iPad 4. "Enterprises will not pay more to acquire the new breed of Windows tablets," explains Moorhead, "and when factoring in additional new management tools, iPads cost more." So what should enterprises do? The report recommends that enterprises that are piloting or already deploying iPads to take a look at the latest enterprise tablet offerings from HP, Dell and Lenovo, and incorporate those new options into their decision-making process.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363304719268</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 19:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363304796028-150</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes is confirming TSM 20nm process is in trouble, and won't be ready</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363297348648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It seems a bit of a stretch for TSM to claim they are going to do 14nm next year when they can't even ramp 20nm till 2015. I think TSM is in pure panic mode. If Intel opens up as chip maker to all the chip designers out there like ALTR then TSM is really are going to begin to lose a lot of business.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363304796028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 19:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363304880517-151</Id><Topic><Title>New Windows-powered tablets threaten iPad's enterprise dominance, claims analyst</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1363300522868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:35:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An iPad will never exist on my network.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363304880517</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 19:48:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363305047907-152</Id><Topic><Title>Big battery breakthrough for Intel ?</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363296559444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Officially it is 8-10 watts but I am hearing a "tuned" one can make do with #$%$</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363305047907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 19:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363305059485-153</Id><Topic><Title>Shouldn't we be back at $24 by now? Seriously.....</Title><Username>waltertobley2000</Username><Timestamp>1363287728124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:02:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Honestly, there is no catalyst for the stock near term." [So, you're saying that if another big deal were announced, it wouldn't be a catalyst? I guess I don't understand the logic behind that. Sure, you can say that we don't know that there will be another big deal but we already have some evidence there will be. One of the guys at Intel said a major mobility player was coming on board. And we think the Cisco deal has already been made. And there are a lot of other possibilities out there. Bottom line is that one of these shoes could drop and it could be exactly what we need to generate a short squeeze and to pop the ARM bubble...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363305059485</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 19:50:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363305293044-154</Id><Topic><Title>Shouldn't we be back at $24 by now? Seriously.....</Title><Username>waltertobley2000</Username><Timestamp>1363287728124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:02:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are not enough shares short to squeeze and I just don't see a big deal near term that would drive the stock higher. I doubt a big Apple deal will happen that that is about the only thing that will move the needle significantly. Of course I would love to be wrong but I just don't see anything happening.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363305293044</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 19:54:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363305841916-155</Id><Topic><Title>A lot of people think PC/Desktop sales are still imploding</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363301322103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:48:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are one of if not THE worst posters on this board...........for you to talk about your ignore list is absolutely laughable. What a fool.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363305841916</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 20:04:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363305882951-156</Id><Topic><Title>A lot of people think PC/Desktop sales are still imploding</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363301322103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:48:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think this is just a repetive mantra that Analysts spout when they want to steer you away from Intel. Two observations that I have is yes PC sales growth isn't what it was and the other thing is business purchases slowed because of the recession. I think that it is a little hard to separate the two out and analysts tend to merge the two numbers to paint an overly negative view of PC sales. My reasoning for buying Intel and MSFT is that people are just way too gloomy about the health of the PC market.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363305882951</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 20:04:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363306235389-157</Id><Title>Here's a thought for you deep thinkers on this board. If TSMC can't do 20nm</Title><Msg>for another 2 years in volume, will that mean ARM is a goner in mobile?</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363306235389</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 20:10:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363306506416-158</Id><Title>Samsung's S4 looks like S3.. with a lot of features that nobody will use.</Title><Msg>Samsung will have to sell these for $49.99 with 2 year contract.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363306506416</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 20:15:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363306823385-159</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes is confirming TSM 20nm process is in trouble, and won't be ready</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363297348648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is there another DIGI Article? This morning a DIgitimes article said comercial production first quarter 2014.</Msg><Username>redwood1205</Username><Timestamp>1363306823385</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 20:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363307103087-160</Id><Topic><Title>A lot of people think PC/Desktop sales are still imploding</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363301322103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:48:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It just got longer...my ignore list...and it also helps me ignore the odor of you.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363307103087</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 20:25:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363307259544-161</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes is confirming TSM 20nm process is in trouble, and won't be ready</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363297348648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC can't have VOLUME 20nm production in 2014, if they don't INVEST in 20nm this year. Morris Chang told Analysts (This is from the horses mouth) that most of their investments this year will be on 28nm. End of Story... DIGITIMES or not.. Digitimes is sometimes right, but they are wrong a lot of the time. Just like most of the internet web sites like Seeking Alpha and Motley fool.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363307259544</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 20:27:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363307761265-162</Id><Title>Wall St Analysts are SLOW.. They'll figure out TSMC's 20nm in another 6 months.</Title><Msg>Meantime they are all busy figuring out $3B in extra revenues in 2016 from Intel's new foundry business.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363307761265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 20:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363308062334-163</Id><Topic><Title>Here's a thought for you deep thinkers on this board. If TSMC can't do 20nm</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363306235389</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 20:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"for another 2 years in volume, will that mean ARM is a goner in mobile?" [Not a goner but certainly they will give up very significant market share. It has already been concluded that they will be at 28nm for a very, very long time. With Intel going up two process nodes, the switch is on (as demonstrated by the Altera deal) and will accelerate - just as the air coming out of the ARM bubble will accelerate. The amazing thing is that Intel will actually have the capacity to take this huge market share from ARM. As far as ARM's future goes, I would guess 3-5 years before ARM becomes the new AMD...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363308062334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 20:41:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363308686632-164</Id><Topic><Title>Digitimes is confirming TSM 20nm process is in trouble, and won't be ready</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363297348648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To actively compete, TSMC really needs 20nm by June. Of course, that's not happening and it will likely be 18 months before they have volume production. Obviously with them spending all their CapEx this year on expansion of 28nm, they really aren't going to be making much progress on 20nm. The impact of not having 20nm by June means that Intel will start booking contracts from those TSMC can't help. At some point it will snowball and the route will be on...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363308686632</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 20:51:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363308974600-165</Id><Topic><Title>Shouldn't we be back at $24 by now? Seriously.....</Title><Username>waltertobley2000</Username><Timestamp>1363287728124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:02:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, I certainly wouldn't ignore the potential impact of accumulated deals. Several nice ones on top of Acronix, Altera and maybe Cisco might break the camel's back of Wall Street stupidity. The appearance of a significant and sustained move to Intel's manufacturing would be just as good as a single gigantic deal. I continue to believe that the tipping point is upon us and it's just a matter of when in the next 9-12 months it will happen...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363308974600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 20:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363309253842-166</Id><Topic><Title>A lot of people think PC/Desktop sales are still imploding</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363301322103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:48:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A guy who starts threads saying "I think Intel and the market are about to drop big" or "I know some BIG Intel news but I can't tell you!" acting like he's important. Idiot liberal gay clown.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363309253842</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:00:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363309893810-167</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC to tape out Apple A7 processor in March</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363270623390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:17:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's not what DigiTimes says. Not even close.</Msg><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1363309893810</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363309940258-168</Id><Title>More and More Intel Smartphone Announcements</Title><Msg>1.) The Lava Xolo X1000 today 2.) The Lenovo IdeaPhone K900 this week 3.) The ZTE announcement that all future smartphones will be with Intel Inside 4.) Intel's first Philippine smartphone launch - Acer Liquid C1 Intel Philippines country manager Ricky Banaag holds up the Acer Liquid C1 smartphone, featuring the company's new Atom Z2420 processor, at a press conference March 13. The Acer Liquid C1 is touted as the first Intel-based smartphone to be launched in the Philippines. The Atom Z2420 represents Intel's major foray into mobile phone processors, after decades of leadership in the computer processor market. Although no specific pricing has yet been announced, Banaag said that the new processor is specifically designed for affordable mobile platforms in emerging markets. "(The Philippines is) the fastest-growing smartphone market in Asia," Banaag said, citing third-party statistics.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363309940258</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:12:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363309962629-169</Id><Topic><Title>Calxeda’s first ARM server is a serious threat to x86 server domination</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363272697872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:51:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who's gonna buy an ARM Server when they can't get reliable and consistent chips for said servers???? TSMC is going down and taking ARM's future with it.</Msg><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1363309962629</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363310068063-170</Id><Title>VMware boss AGAIN laughs at the ARM server revolution</Title><Msg>There will be no revolution.</Msg><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1363310068063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:14:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363310118722-171</Id><Topic><Title>More and More Intel Smartphone Announcements</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363309940258</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:12:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't wait for khitchdee and the rest of the shills to say that Intel doing business in the "the fastest-growing smartphone market in Asia (the Philippines) is irrelevant...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363310118722</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:15:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363310184076-172</Id><Title>Altera and Intel teaming up for 14nm changed the world</Title><Msg>Instant validation. Altera just announced to the entire world that Intel is the way to go, Only a complete idiot can't see what's coming: More and much bigger FAB deals for Intel.</Msg><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1363310184076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:16:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363310241661-173</Id><Topic><Title>Altera and Intel teaming up for 14nm changed the world</Title><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1363310184076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:16:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who fabs snapdragons for samsung? samsung?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363310241661</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363310261795-174</Id><Topic><Title>More and More Intel Smartphone Announcements</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363309940258</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:12:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes - the announcements have been good news. BTW - does anyone know what Intel's current market penetration is? I know it is low - but that's okay as long as it's growing...</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1363310261795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:17:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363310326789-175</Id><Topic><Title>A lot of people think PC/Desktop sales are still imploding</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363301322103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:48:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ahhhhh...so you're attlte #$%$-4-brains. It figures...fart bag.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363310326789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:18:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363310380086-176</Id><Title>getanid16 = attlte</Title><Msg>same jerk..I only one on ignore..get em both on perma-nore now.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363310380086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:19:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363310441272-177</Id><Topic><Title>Big battery breakthrough for Intel ?</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363296559444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 17:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>still sinkin up the place, eh attlte?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363310441272</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:20:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363310649669-178</Id><Topic><Title>getanid16 = attlte</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363310380086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:19:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think its att4glte..something like that, posing as getanid16...how infantile is that?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363310649669</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:24:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363310976533-179</Id><Topic><Title>Altera and Intel teaming up for 14nm changed the world</Title><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1363310184076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:16:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huh?</Msg><Username>ukcats1970</Username><Timestamp>1363310976533</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363311117227-180</Id><Topic><Title>Altera and Intel teaming up for 14nm changed the world</Title><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1363310184076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:16:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who dresses and feeds you?</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363311117227</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:31:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363311227666-181</Id><Topic><Title>getanid16 = attlte</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363310380086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:19:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You ruin this board yet act like you are some sort of "big player" here. Get in a Bingo league or something.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363311227666</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363311434262-182</Id><Title>Lenovo Yoga's are flying off the shelves</Title><Msg>Check it</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363311434262</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:37:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363311546201-183</Id><Topic><Title>getanid16 = attlte</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363310380086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:19:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, getanid16 is not the raving lunatic att4glte.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363311546201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:39:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363311592029-184</Id><Topic><Title>Altera and Intel teaming up for 14nm changed the world</Title><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1363310184076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:16:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363311592029</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:39:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363311689936-185</Id><Topic><Title>getanid16 = attlte</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363310380086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:19:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you have some serious personality and emotional issues. You seem very easily rattled by others, especially when you think they have a liberal political bent. I think you were a sissy on the school grounds and got bullied a lot. I think your father was an alcoholic, and your mother sat in silence as he abused her and you and your siblings. I think you have a mediocre intellect and think there's strength in rancid right-wing baloneyism. You are Foxnewsss, and att4glte, and probably a lot of other racoon meat eating id's. Go foxtrot your silly self.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363311689936</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363311762587-186</Id><Topic><Title>Altera and Intel teaming up for 14nm changed the world</Title><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1363310184076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:16:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ergo, wouldn't it be QCOM that wants Intel to fab for it?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363311762587</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:42:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363311794104-187</Id><Topic><Title>Altera and Intel teaming up for 14nm changed the world</Title><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1363310184076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:16:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your wife after our nooners.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363311794104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:43:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363311813120-188</Id><Topic><Title>getanid16 = attlte</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363310380086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:19:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Parents don't drink, mom's never had a sip. They've been married over half a century. Best parents ever. You sound like a delusional, lonely old liberal skumbag.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363311813120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:43:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363311825734-189</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo Yoga's are flying off the shelves</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363311434262</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:37:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>twit.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363311825734</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:43:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363311943279-190</Id><Topic><Title>getanid16 = attlte</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363310380086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:19:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical response from a very troubled family member..denial.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363311943279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:45:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363312022386-191</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo Yoga's are flying off the shelves</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363311434262</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:37:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, I see once again you've claimed to put someone on ignore yet it was just a Liberal lying. When a liberal's mouth is moving, they are lying. You are a worthless hot mess, so on Ignore YOU go. Watch and learn how to ignore someone/do what you say you are going to do.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363312022386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:47:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363312090481-192</Id><Topic><Title>getanid16 = attlte</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363310380086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:19:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>att4glte may be Mr. Hyde, while getanid61 is definitely the same one , but not as smart as Dr. Jeckyll.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363312090481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363312715625-193</Id><Topic><Title>Calxeda’s first ARM server is a serious threat to x86 server domination</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363272697872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:51:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel circled Single digits stock inn 2014</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1363312715625</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:58:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363314483620-194</Id><Topic><Title>Calxeda’s first ARM server is a serious threat to x86 server domination</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363272697872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:51:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nitwit</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1363314483620</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 22:28:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363314666314-195</Id><Topic><Title>More and More Intel Smartphone Announcements</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363309940258</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:12:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>khitchee = singelton same guy</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1363314666314</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 22:31:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363315484514-196</Id><Topic><Title>More and More Intel Smartphone Announcements</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363309940258</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 21:12:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's pretty cool ... all small markets and all overpriced models. Thanks for introducing us to companies and markets that no one has ever heard of. (People, here's what is happening in real life: Lenovo has to do an Intel phone or their allocation for other Intel chips will get cut off forever. It's called payola.)</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1363315484514</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 22:44:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363316151667-197</Id><Topic><Title>Wall St Analysts are SLOW.. They'll figure out TSMC's 20nm in another 6 months.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363307761265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 20:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Meantime they are all busy figuring out $3B in extra revenues in 2016 from Intel's new foundry business" Not sure if number is accurate - anyway let's rephrase and figure out what $3 B of lost business would mean to TSMC - it's HUGE because it's all leading/bleeding edge. Well Fargo analyst got it somewhat right - Intel is capturing some of TSMC leading edge business and it might influence TSMC spending behavior going forward. What goes on in TSMC mind? ALTR jumped ship... who could be next? TSMC needs to deliver ROI Should we (TSMC) reduce capex ? The ALTR move has caused a lot of rethinking (within TSMC) - WS analysts are "dumb" because they look (shortterm) at $ and cent</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363316151667</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 22:55:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363316690801-198</Id><Topic><Title>How Does Websters Spell TURD- I-N-T-E-L</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363290618490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is Dana Lucy you friggin idiot.. I use my real name to post you fool.... Intel has been a turd for 14 years and should be flushed down the toilet with the rest of the dung... Speaking of which, I need to go and take a Wallisweaver..... I will flush twice when I am done...Cuz you are really stinky.</Msg><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363316690801</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 23:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363316824407-199</Id><Topic><Title>How Does Websters Spell TURD- I-N-T-E-L</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363290618490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get the F off this board you GD Troll!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1363316824407</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 23:07:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363317882512-200</Id><Topic><Title>How Does Websters Spell TURD- I-N-T-E-L</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363290618490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmmm. Well, you make the same silly 10 and 14 year arguments that DL does (although the stock has moved up by $2.50 since November). You do the same name calling instead of presenting support for your positions that DL does. You have the same kind of repressed anger and hostility that DL does. And you have the same kind of adolescent potty mouth that DL does. So, it doesn't really matter if you are DL or not because you are still the same kind of rage-fueled wingnut. There is a set of people posting on this board who all appear to be very similar or may in fact just be one or perhaps two individuals. More than anything else they exhibit a constant stream of bile and venom coupled with an inability to demonstrate enough knowledge and expertise to ever build any credibility. You can completely confirm these opinions by unleashing another round of adolescent name calling. Go ahead. I'm already starting to laugh at your inability to control yourself...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363317882512</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 23:24:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363318884566-201</Id><Topic><Title>Intel releases Android Dual bootable on Windows 8</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363299836151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:23:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a very useful feature for people that buy Core or Atom based tablets. Also want Ubuntu Touch and Tizen!</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1363318884566</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 23:41:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>