<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369027030391-1</Id><Title>things are looking pretty good technicaly</Title><Msg>after three and a half weeks of consolidation I think this will start a new leg-up to 26 -28</Msg><Username>jake_718</Username><Timestamp>1369027030391</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 01:17:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369027487512-2</Id><Topic><Title>INTC should go down again next week if the market starts correcting.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369002456006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:27:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC didnt jump up like a lot of other stocks. I dont think anything is going to hold intel back for this next 30 days. Haswel comes out in about 2 weeks too. I expect $26 in next 30 days (and I dont own INTC)</Msg><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1369027487512</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 01:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369027576149-3</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will see 24 + before 18</Title><Username>itakebackrnyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368979855680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 12:10:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL..i would go as far as to say it will see 26 before 22.</Msg><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1369027576149</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 01:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369027721397-4</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will see 24 + before 18</Title><Username>itakebackrnyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368979855680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 12:10:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes I can trust you but not with my money</Msg><Username>jake_718</Username><Timestamp>1369027721397</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 01:28:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369028223844-5</Id><Topic><Title>Intel will see 24 + before 18</Title><Username>itakebackrnyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368979855680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 12:10:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not even a bad news can keep this monster down now after 13 years of building momentum .I really see a monster move is coming.</Msg><Username>jake_718</Username><Timestamp>1369028223844</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 01:37:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369031488646-6</Id><Topic><Title>A Samsung-Intel axis...now that's global domination.</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368987180572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 14:13:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey Benito aka Duce - you stupid fick</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1369031488646</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 02:31:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369032448500-7</Id><Title>will amd u</Title><Msg>goofed up: shorting NVDA shorting AMD (at the wrong time) went long Gold ( he once posted on Goldman Sachs board) he's a looser</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1369032448500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 02:47:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369035148000-8</Id><Title>Apple has no choice but to ...</Title><Msg>... use Haswell for the iPad. Nothing ARM designed will now compete with Haswell. Also, it's an easy switch. iOS and ALL iPad Apps already work on x86 processsors. That's because every iOS App developer develops their Apps on an Intel processor based iMac running Xcode. Easy Peasy. App developers won't even know the switch happened. It was most certainly designed that way. Apple wouldn't bet their crown jewels on a one-trick pony like ARM. Samsung can't stay with ARM either. I'm not sure as I haven't done any Android development but I think Android Apps are also developed on x86. To think of it, there is no such thing as an ARM based development platform. Let me know if I'm wrong. All iPhone Apps are also developed on Intel processors. Same situation. We'll see Apple iPhones switching to Silvermont same time next year, or sooner! Sorry ARM.</Msg><Username>butexcuseme</Username><Timestamp>1369035148000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 03:32:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369037759716-9</Id><Topic><Title>INTC should go down again next week if the market starts correcting.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369002456006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:27:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go down like you do in the cab with the man?</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1369037759716</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 04:15:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369037829957-10</Id><Topic><Title>will amd u</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1369032448500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 02:47:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Folowed you?</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1369037829957</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 04:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369037939679-11</Id><Topic><Title>Ashraf breaks the Intel-Samsung Galaxy win story</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368975428539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 10:57:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf broke like the wind. I'll believe it when I see it. Releasing one demo with Intel inside does not make a trend.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1369037939679</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 04:18:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369051545436-12</Id><Title>Looks to be another down day for this laggard</Title><Msg>Check out VNQ Costco SBUX Green Mountain CVS Makes lots of money</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369051545436</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369053651062-13</Id><Title>Lenovo K900 on Geekbench</Title><Msg>For those interested in the scores. browserDOTprimatelabsDOTcom/geekbench2/1970892</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1369053651062</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369053979365-14</Id><Title>Lenovo K900 Released In China, Going Global In Summer</Title><Msg>The Lenovo K900 smartphone was first unveiled at CES 2013 and it quite surprisingly smoked every other competitor. This due to the fact that it is powered by Intel’s next generation Clover Trail+ smartphone processor. The Lenovo K900 has now gone on sale in China, despite that it is not known for sure when it will come stateside, the company says international launch in unspecified markets is due this summer. Lenovo K900 certainly packs a mean punch, touting a 2GHz dualcore Atom Z2580 processor, Gorilla Glass 2 full HD 1080p 5.5-inch display, 13 megapixel camera and Android 4.2 Jelly Bean. Despite having all this on-board, the K900 us just 6.9 millimeters and weighs just 162 grams. In China this smartphone is now retailing for RMB 3,299 which is roughly $530. There’s no word as yet from the company on international pricing or availability. The smartphone has a stainless steel frame with the unibody chassis providing the slim and sleek look. Lenovo believes that its new smartphone is the perfect choice for high-end smartphone buyers. It certainly touts internal hardware that would give many smartphones currently available in the market a run for their money. From ubergizmo</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369053979365</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:46:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369054007854-15</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K900 Released In China, Going Global In Summer</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369053979365</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:46:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The Lenovo K900 smartphone was first unveiled at CES 2013 and it quite surprisingly smoked every other competitor."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369054007854</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:46:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369054186444-16</Id><Title>World's first 8-inch Windows 8 tablet Acer W3 appears on official website</Title><Msg>Looks like Windows 8 will soon be gracing displays smaller than 10 inches. Earlier this month, Acer's 8.1-inch tablet running Windows 8 appeared on Amazon, increasing speculation that devices competing with the iPad mini and Nexus 7 will soon be out in various markets. Of course, that Amazon listing disappeared as soon as it came and then Denis Kutnikov, of Acer Russia said that such a tablet would be announced on June 4th at Computex. However, it looks like Acer could not keep the secret till the event and now the tablet has shown up on the company's own website as the Acer W3. The Acer W3 features an 8.1-inch WXGA (1280 x 768) display and is powered by an Intel Clover Trail Atom Z2760 processor. In addition to 2GB of RAM, buyers have the option of going for either the 32GB or the 64GB internal storage versions. From IBNLive</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369054186444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:49:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369054858719-17</Id><Topic><Title>Hindsight is 20-20. There was no way to know that Iphone would be</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369002817915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:33:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's great Intel is becoming well positioned for mobile today, but why make excuses for what was clearly very poor business judgment regarding the cellphone/pre-smartphone market that was well known to be growing faster than the PC market at the time Then after seeing the early success of the iPhone why did it take six more years for Intel's management to finally produce a CPU/SoC product that was competitive to ARM offerings? Further, I would fault Intel's management for failing on another pivotal opportunity in mobile. After seeing Apple's success with it's proprietary mobile iOS it was clear there would be an alternative mobile OS that would become the standard for all mobile devices not made by Apple. Why didn't Intel see this opportunity earlier and take the lead to create the free Linux-based mobile OS and mobile software ecosystem instead of waiting for a search-engine company to do it? By the time MeeGo was launched as a "Me Too" effort the battle to be the dominant mobile OS was already over. And during this period why did Intel spend so many billions on WiMAX and Clearwire that were entirely wasted investments in the mobile carrier business that didn't leverage Intel's core business and didn't make Intel any more competitive against ARM? During that same period Intel's accomplishments against AMD were impressive and deserve recognition. But It is near impossible to understate the dysfunction that prevailed within Intel's executive ranks with respect to mobile. What is inconceivable is how the board stood by and allowed this to continue for so long.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369054858719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369055284159-18</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K900 on Geekbench</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1369053651062</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:40:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am trying to find the quote but I thought that I heard that Geekbench is heavy on FP denormal operations which the Intel CPU handles but the ARM CPU performs a flush to zero. Did you see that article? If that is true, it impacts the ability to compare the results. I tried to see what options they used to compile Geekbench with and could not. The compile time options make a pretty big difference. Have you seen the compile time options documented anywhere? thanks</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369055284159</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:08:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369055386879-19</Id><Topic><Title>Hindsight is 20-20. There was no way to know that Iphone would be</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369002817915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:33:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"During that same period Intel's accomplishments against AMD were impressive and deserve recognition." [I don't mind anyone pointing out the mistakes that were made. At the same time one should give credit where credit is due. To limit the good things that happened to that one line above is grossly unfair. FinFET happened and it's the most important advancement in semiconductor history. And the roadmap that is in place now is quite good and gives mobility the priority it deserves. There is little use in dwelling on mistakes that have been substantially corrected. The rewards of FinFET are now coming to fruition. Let's move on...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369055386879</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:09:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369055740615-20</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K900 on Geekbench</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1369053651062</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:40:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>investorshubDOTadvfnDOTcom/boards/read_msg.aspx?message_id=88008447</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1369055740615</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:15:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369056350714-21</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K900 on Geekbench</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1369053651062</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:40:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In summary, Geekbench sux and is irrelevant. I am going to go into my darkened room for 3 days and 3 nights and flog myself at sunrise and sunset.</Msg><Username>thebluereddork</Username><Timestamp>1369056350714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:25:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369056700429-22</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K900 on Geekbench</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1369053651062</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:40:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No idea if that FP denormal operations comment if valid or not. You can exclude those two FPU results (Sharpen Image and blur Image) when you manually look at the results. Some other Atom cores don't seem to have that FP problem though. Had a quick google for the options as I thought I had seen them before but couldn't find any.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1369056700429</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:31:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369057512309-23</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K900 on Geekbench</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1369053651062</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:40:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. This is what I was thinking of. I know there are some good things about Geekbench (cross platform numbers) but I know there are some really bad things in Geekbench. The workloads they base their micro benchmarks on are strange and non-representative.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369057512309</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369058205006-24</Id><Title>oh where is that 3 to 5 percent pop on the Sammy tab rumor ??</Title><Msg>you guys got jokes.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369058205006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369058358215-25</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K900 on Geekbench</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1369053651062</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:40:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know the integer code is reasonably representative (just from the algo's they have chosen), I can't really comment about the float versions though as I don't really know anything about the algos that they use. The high FP scores for the ARM cores do correlate with other 'real' benchmark suites such as phoronix.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1369058358215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:59:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369058569781-26</Id><Topic><Title>A Samsung-Intel axis...now that's global domination.</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368987180572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 14:13:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel will be selling x86 chips to Apple too for use in iPads. Good for Intel and Apple. Certainly good for owners of both INTC and AAPL like me.</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1369058569781</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:02:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369058869698-27</Id><Topic><Title>Apple has no choice but to ...</Title><Username>butexcuseme</Username><Timestamp>1369035148000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 03:32:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I feel confident that Apple has already been working in secret with Intel on doing exactly that for, at least, a couple of years. Intel has its own "Apple Group" that works separately on Apple products and have to keep what they are working on a secret even from others at Intel. Apple will not be left behind by any means, but of course, this is HUGE for Intel if the Samsung rumor is true as well as the iPad win that I expect is also true. Intel could soon be providing the processors for about 70% or more of all tablets between Samsung and Apple. Or at least, full-sized tablets at first.</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1369058869698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:07:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369059690469-28</Id><Topic><Title>Hindsight is 20-20. There was no way to know that Iphone would be</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369002817915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:33:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There was no intent to minimize Intel's accomplishments, but the accomplishments along with what the Core architecture did to AMD are visible and common knowledge, while the missed opportunities are not. The main purpose of calling attention to management performance (which includes missed opportunities) is to avoid repeating the mistakes of the past. It appears Intel's management today has a focused strategy to compete in mobile, although some of the experiments in the media industry remain questionable and deserve closer board scrutiny.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369059690469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:21:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369059809191-29</Id><Topic><Title>oh where is that 3 to 5 percent pop on the Sammy tab rumor ??</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369058205006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>explain that model that takes you there.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369059809191</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:23:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369059981703-30</Id><Title>PUSH TOWARDS $28 COMING</Title><Msg>Consolidation going on. With release of haswell, this thing is going to parabolic. $40 by end of year</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369059981703</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369060144487-31</Id><Title>SAMSUNG GOING INTEL FOR THEIR GALAXY TAB 3, APPLE WILL BE NEXT</Title><Msg>Watch for iphones and ipad announcement with intel inside. Apple has not really no choice. Either go with intel or be at a competitive disadvantage.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369060144487</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:29:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060639362-32</Id><Topic><Title>SAMSUNG GOING INTEL FOR THEIR GALAXY TAB 3, APPLE WILL BE NEXT</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369060144487</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:29:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh brother what utter nonsense.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369060639362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369061054534-33</Id><Topic><Title>SAMSUNG GOING INTEL FOR THEIR GALAXY TAB 3, APPLE WILL BE NEXT</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369060144487</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:29:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MERRIFIELD Dual core (1W) at same performance use 2.4x less power than competition. At same power, performs 1.6x the speed of competition. BAY TRAIL Intel's quad core beauties either giving twice the performance at the same power level or 4.3x less power at the same performance From AE's article</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369061054534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:44:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369061290700-34</Id><Title>HASWELL, SILVERMONT, INTEL TV, 14NM ALL COMING THIS YEAR</Title><Msg>Iwatch, google/motorola x phone, samsung products, apple products, all intel inside too much momentum to stop this thing from going to $40 and above</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369061290700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369061330659-35</Id><Topic><Title>HASWELL, SILVERMONT, INTEL TV, 14NM ALL COMING THIS YEAR</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369061290700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cisco $3 billion / year fab deal...too much! $40 by end of year</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369061330659</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:48:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369061584646-36</Id><Title>RECORD BREAKING REVENUE DESERVES RECORD BREAKING STOCK PRICE</Title><Msg>RECORD $54 BILLION THIS YEAR (WITH MARGIN OVER 60%). Q3 and Q4 should produce near $15 Billion each with margins well over 60% (these will record quarters in Intel)</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369061584646</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:53:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369062582383-37</Id><Topic><Title>oh where is that 3 to 5 percent pop on the Sammy tab rumor ??</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369058205006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ok u r up .6 cents now. Maybe u meant 3 to 5 cents.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369062582383</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:09:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369062743923-38</Id><Title>INTC: LOWER ASP, MORE COMPETITION, HIGHER COSTS, LOWER STOCK PRICE IS DESERVED.</Title><Msg>HEY THIS CAPS STUFF IS KINDA FUN.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369062743923</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:12:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369062809488-39</Id><Topic><Title>oh where is that 3 to 5 percent pop on the Sammy tab rumor ??</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369058205006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you fool. look for a 15% pop in the next 4 weeks with haswell launch and subsequent Haswell product intros</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369062809488</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:13:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369062894180-40</Id><Topic><Title>Looks to be another down day for this laggard</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369051545436</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While INTC lags, SBUX hits another all time high and VNQ hits another 52 week high. By the way, both pay divs too.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369062894180</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:14:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369062925871-41</Id><Topic><Title>INTC: LOWER ASP, MORE COMPETITION, HIGHER COSTS, LOWER STOCK PRICE IS DESERVED.</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369062743923</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:12:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MY RECOMMENDATION TO YOU BUDDY: Cover now before you fall victim to the greatest bull run in Intel's history. $40 and above.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369062925871</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:15:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369063277993-42</Id><Topic><Title>INTC: LOWER ASP, MORE COMPETITION, HIGHER COSTS, LOWER STOCK PRICE IS DESERVED.</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369062743923</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:12:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You might be right.... but i gotta go where the story leads. Good luck.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369063277993</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:21:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369063358009-43</Id><Topic><Title>oh where is that 3 to 5 percent pop on the Sammy tab rumor ??</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369058205006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i PITY DA FOOL</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369063358009</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:22:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369063659591-44</Id><Title>Headed for the red zone real soon</Title><Msg>Can't sustain 24.25 - the high of the day</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369063659591</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:27:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369064071421-45</Id><Topic><Title>I Admit It</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368765797183</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 00:43:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO POP ON SAMMY RUMOR , GEE I WONDER WHY ....</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369064071421</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369064432742-46</Id><Title>Arnold says: Game Over, Intel has won!</Title><Msg>Arnold Frisch, recently retired Chip Design Engineer from Intel on Seeking Alpha. ............. It's the laws of physics that controls the winner in the processor race for mobile applications, and Intel has already won this race. Anyone who disagrees is in denial, has some ulterior motive, or is just dense. What all this means is that whoever builds phones or a tablets using Intel processors can make them run faster and run longer on a given battery than by using an ARM (or AMD) processor. This argument cuts off the other arguments about market share, design wins, better architecture and other objections by the Intel opponents. Market share is a measure of the past. What was, not what is. What is, is that the 22nm finFET is a better transistor and it makes for a better processor. If you want the best processor in your next phone/tablet/mobility_device, it had better be an Intel processor.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1369064432742</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369064509232-47</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement</Title><Username>royr44</Username><Timestamp>1369059272660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:14:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is what i exactly need at the moment</Msg><Username>sweatstephanie12</Username><Timestamp>1369064509232</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:41:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369064681205-48</Id><Topic><Title>Arnold says: Game Over, Intel has won!</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1369064432742</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARNOLD COULD NOT BE MORE WRONG. STAY TUNED.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369064681205</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369064905203-49</Id><Topic><Title>Arnold says: Game Over, Intel has won!</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1369064432742</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quote: Arnold could not be more wrong. Stay tuned. ================== Wow, terrific rebuttal !!</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1369064905203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:48:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369065047636-50</Id><Topic><Title>Arnold says: Game Over, Intel has won!</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1369064432742</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Following arnulds and wallys logic methodologeee. Danka</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369065047636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369065291145-51</Id><Topic><Title>Arnold says: Game Over, Intel has won!</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1369064432742</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, I am still waiting for RT to take over the world like you last predicted.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1369065291145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:54:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369065590360-52</Id><Topic><Title>Headed for the red zone real soon</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369063659591</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:27:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>F you. Please consider taking a swan dive off a high rise. Make everyone happy.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369065590360</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369066245595-53</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement</Title><Username>royr44</Username><Timestamp>1369059272660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:14:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>schuleinz95</Username><Timestamp>1369066245595</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:10:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369066284285-54</Id><Topic><Title>Looks to be another down day for this laggard</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369051545436</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hate to hurt your feelings Nuff, but you have to be one of the worst investors ever . Those are all stocks that a loser would pick.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369066284285</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:11:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369066350438-55</Id><Topic><Title>Headed for the red zone real soon</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369063659591</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:27:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a sad pitiful stock ..losers on board wally is the head bozo and loss leader</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369066350438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:12:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369066689532-56</Id><Title>INTC is poor. This is exactly why.</Title><Msg>Simply put I needed to present this website with absolutely everyone... This newsletter has a newsletter with extensive research of up and coming small cap stocks. shortDOTie/qki5va</Msg><Username>richardbostic83</Username><Timestamp>1369066689532</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369067438375-57</Id><Title>Can someone quantify new income from smartphones/tablets</Title><Msg>I have seen quite a bit of messaging about how the new Intel chips will revive the company's growth. I see a huge market potential for growth, but don't have the expertise to quantify this, If Intel gains 10, 25 or 50 percent of the market, what does this say for revenues, and more importantly, profits. With a current PE of only 12, I would think that INTC is well underpriced, even if growth in smartphones/tablets is small.</Msg><Username>bobs1016</Username><Timestamp>1369067438375</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:30:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369068002448-58</Id><Topic><Title>INTC beaten by CSCO</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368820313047</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 15:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TODAY IT WAS OVER 10k IN June 25 CALLS.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369068002448</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:40:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369068240689-59</Id><Topic><Title>INTC beaten by CSCO</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368820313047</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 15:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC HAS BECOME AN "OPTIONS" TOY. , at least until some catalyst comes along.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369068240689</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369069707585-60</Id><Topic><Title>Hindsight is 20-20. There was no way to know that Iphone would be</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369002817915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:33:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Wallis, Are you long Intel? I am. Most shareholders in this POS for millions are none too happy with Paley old boy for having passed on an exclusive deal with Apple which would have given Intel the Ipad and Iphone and the huge revenue that would have come with it. Simply saying it was a mistake and that is that is hardly looking at things in a rational way.l Yeah sure--Hitler made a mistake in attacking Russia and other than that he did fine. Stupid right? Pauley old boy was fired. He shocked the world with his announcement to leave early and likely he was FIRED! If the clown had said the truth about how he passes on Apple with this deal, he would have been fired years ago. The stock is 24 when it would be north of 100 had the idiot done the Apple deal. You can forgive him but he is forever on the sheet list of most Intel longs.</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1369069707585</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369069992242-61</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement</Title><Username>royr44</Username><Timestamp>1369059272660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:14:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be waiting for more great news to come.</Msg><Username>zairacabral99</Username><Timestamp>1369069992242</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:13:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369070549326-62</Id><Topic><Title>Headed for the red zone real soon</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369063659591</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:27:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like I predicted. RED</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369070549326</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:22:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369070741567-63</Id><Topic><Title>Can someone quantify new income from smartphones/tablets</Title><Username>bobs1016</Username><Timestamp>1369067438375</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:30:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gartner. Worldwide smartphone sales totaled 210 million units in the first quarter of 2013, up 42.9 percent from the first quarter of 2012. So over 800 million sold in a year. Way to go Paul O for missing this for so long. Idiot. Glad they fired your dumb assswteroid.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1369070741567</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:25:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369070772319-64</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement</Title><Username>royr44</Username><Timestamp>1369059272660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:14:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is 100% Bull****</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1369070772319</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:26:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369071183999-65</Id><Topic><Title>oh where is that 3 to 5 percent pop on the Sammy tab rumor ??</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369058205006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MUST BE LATER TODAY.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369071183999</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:33:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369071927198-66</Id><Topic><Title>INTC beaten by CSCO</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368820313047</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 15:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see 18K 25 July Call volume and 11K June 25 Call volume today</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369071927198</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:45:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369072032769-67</Id><Topic><Title>oh where is that 3 to 5 percent pop on the Sammy tab rumor ??</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369058205006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was "backbay bst" from his "model". He should show us his model. I hope it isn't Play Doh!</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369072032769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:47:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369072228524-68</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement</Title><Username>royr44</Username><Timestamp>1369059272660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:14:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you shared this to us.</Msg><Username>mmilkey92</Username><Timestamp>1369072228524</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:50:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369072876151-69</Id><Title>Stagnation just before a large correction</Title><Msg>Look at the tell signs on both the NASDAQ/NYSE. What is happening is stagnation in the major indices. This happens when the large derivative players are shifting their positions. They are now moving money and are going to bet against both markets. In the past this is when large corrections take place (over 10 percent). The large derivative players are the ones that run the indices. For example look at Warren Buffet; he is a heavy derivative player that has, over the last five years, substantially decreased his position in stocks and gone the derivative route. Smart, rich player. Derivative are an easy way to hide money.......so large losses can be covered up. The SEC does not understand this and they cannot track this. The result is no regulation. It will only take one major, dishonest derivative player to send our financial systems into ruin.</Msg><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1369072876151</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:01:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369074663406-70</Id><Topic><Title>INTC beaten by CSCO</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368820313047</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 15:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep. I see them too. Sounds like you think their might be something to my theory. I was watching the June $25 CALLs earlier when they were both buying and selling the June if you assumed that the SIZE of the BID/ASK quantities tells if they are buying or selling. I have nothing to say that it is "on purpose" with any particular goal of pushing the price higher or lower. There are times of the year when the FAILS TO DELIVER (naked shorts) make sense as a DIVIDEND ARBITRAGE since the premium is so low and nearly 100% on the PUT. There is a chance that this is simply a PERPETUAL dividend arbitrage where they accumulate a position during the quarter so they can take advantage of it. It does seem to throttle more on the UP side than the DOWN side.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369074663406</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:31:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369076747119-71</Id><Topic><Title>Can someone quantify new income from smartphones/tablets</Title><Username>bobs1016</Username><Timestamp>1369067438375</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:30:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Worldwide smartphone sales totaled 210 million units in the first quarter of 2013, up 42.9 percent from the first quarter of 2012. So over 800 million sold in a year. Way to go Paul O for missing this for so long. Idiot. Glad they fired your dumb assswteroid." [If you hadn't missed the Apple iPad/iPhone significance as well, then you would have had so much money that you wouldn't be here doing your Monday morning quarterback routine. Way to go for holding others to a standard you don't meet...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369076747119</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:05:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369076747578-72</Id><Topic><Title>INTC beaten by CSCO</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368820313047</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 15:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buying or writing? Because if writing, they're going to expire worthless, like they always do.</Msg><Username>angstromatic</Username><Timestamp>1369076747578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:05:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369076854795-73</Id><Topic><Title>Can someone quantify new income from smartphones/tablets</Title><Username>bobs1016</Username><Timestamp>1369067438375</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:30:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You hit the nail on the head: the profits are what is difficult, not revenue.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1369076854795</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:07:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369077059796-74</Id><Topic><Title>Hindsight is 20-20. There was no way to know that Iphone would be</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369002817915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:33:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Pauley old boy was fired. He shocked the world with his announcement to leave early and likely he was FIRED!" [Please explain what good your sour grapes routine is doing. You've known for years about this. You should have sold and moved on to companies with CEO's who don't make mistakes. Now quit your belly-aching. It makes you look like a girlyboy... ]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369077059796</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:10:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369077068669-75</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement</Title><Username>royr44</Username><Timestamp>1369059272660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:14:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fantastic. I will check it out.</Msg><Username>michael.clermont33</Username><Timestamp>1369077068669</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:11:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369077583837-76</Id><Title>Risk for Shorts just went Way Up</Title><Msg>Apple Testing 1.5-Inch OLED Displays For Its Rumored Smart Watch? A couple of reports today are suggesting that Apple is advancing its development and production of the rumored smart watch. The reports come from the Taiwanese newspaper Economic Times. The first report claims that Apple has started testing 1.5-inch OLED displays from RITEK subsidiary TiRdisplay. According to the report, RITEK’s joint partnership with RitFast will also supply the touch sensor technology that will be used for the watch. This report reflects earlier rumors about Apple’s plans for RiTdisplay’s 1.5-inch displays and Intel being involved in the project. Today’s report also mentions that Apple had originally wanted to use a 1.8-inch display in the smart watch. That size proved to be too large, however, so the company decided on a smaller 1.5-inch display. The second report talked about the smart watch industry as a whole. According to “market rumors,” Foxconn has already received orders for Apple’s smart watch, but only with small volume orders around 1,000 units for small-scale production trial. The Apple smart watch rumor really picked up speed in December after reports that Apple and Intel were working together to produce it surfaced. Other rumors have suggested that Apple has experimented with curved glass designs for the smart watch’s display. Other than that, the rumor mill has been relatively quiet the last couple of months concerning the Apple smart watch. At the beginning of March, reports claimed that the rumored device could launch this year. From Macgasm</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369077583837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:19:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369077662467-77</Id><Title>Get Wealthy from Where INTC is Investing</Title><Msg>INTC is investing into the OTT video space and Concurent (CCUR) could be the #1 most undervalued video delivery tech stock on the NASDAQ with the largest upside potential for the next 2-3 weeks. CCUR is currently $7 per share with an extremely low enterprise value of just $38.9mm. CCUR is the world's #1 video on demand (VOD) software solutions provider with a 30% global VOD market share and reach of 50mm pay-TV subscriber VOD households across 4 continents! A huge new VOD spending boom is beginning in 2013 as cable TV companies invest big time to grow their concurrent VOD stream capacity to support rapidly growing demand for VOD TV shows and movies on all screens! CCUR's new MediaHawk CDN platform allows pay-TV service providers to integrate classic VOD with new IP CDNs to double VOD content catalog sizes while deploying additional VOD delivery to iOS and Android mobile devices! CCUR's #1 revenue generating VOD client from 1999 through now has been Time Warner Cable (TWC) - the #2 largest pay-TV operator in the U.S.! CCUR's MediaHawk just started powering TWC's new VOD delivery to their recently launched iOS and Android apps! CCUR also powers TWC's very popular "start over" and "look back" services, which CCUR won an Emmy Award for! CCUR is rapidly growing throughout Europe and Asia, and just signed Virgin Media - the #1 cable TV operator in the UK! Virgin could add greatly to CCUR's 4Q numbers! CCUR's GAAP EPS ramped up in its most recent quarters from $0.02, to $0.04, to $0.08, and to $0.11 - while its main rival Seachange (SEAC) has been posting record GAAP EPS losses! CCUR is more profitable today than ever before in history, yet its enterprise value is only 0.61X revenue vs. its average enterprise value/revenue ratio from 2004 through 2007 of 3 and its rival SEAC currently being valued with an enterprise value/revenue ratio of 1.69 and an enterprise value/cash flow ratio of 15.28 - two ratios that would currently value CCUR at $14.76 and $15 respectively!</Msg><Username>ttvhbn42</Username><Timestamp>1369077662467</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:21:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369078062289-78</Id><Title>Intel holds the key to a successful $200 PC: IHS</Title><Msg>Can PC OEMs put together an ultrathin, touch-screen PC that will both appeal to consumers and come in at just $200? Analysts believe so, but chipmaker Intel holds the key to success. And that key is almost older than dirt – cut prices. "A price point that low seems far-fetched considering the mobile PC prices of today, with Ultrabooks and other ultrathins going as high as $1,000 or more," said Craig Stice, senior principal analyst for compute platforms at IHS. "However, the small laptops known as netbooks saw their prices reach down into the $200 range at the height of their popularity a few years ago, and a cost analysis of netbooks shows how such a low level of pricing can be used to support a no-frills type of ultrathin PC." Stice arrives at this conclusion by examining the major components of a netbook on a third-quarter 2013 timeline, and pricing them out at $207.82. "Hitting this kind of price point is not impossible for the PC industry, already a cutthroat market accustomed to razor-thin margins," wrote Stice on a statement to ZDNet. "Such a possibility was stated by outgoing Intel CEO Paul Otellini, who during Intel’s first-quarter earnings call in April made the bold prediction that touch-enabled, ultrathin Intel-based notebooks using non-core processors could be available by the end of this year." Crunching the numbers, Stice found that Intel can control up to 33 percent of the total bill-of-materials cost for a PC just through the CPU and motherboard, and that a price break on these components would allow OEMs to drive down prices, which, in turn, would be further pushed down through competition. While netbooks floundered because of their limited computing power, which in turn made them more suite to content consumption than creation, IHS believes that Intel's Bay trail hardware should give the PC market a "much-needed shot in the arm" and could ignite a new mobile PC market revolution. From ZDNet</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369078062289</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:27:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369080407614-79</Id><Title>Want to see one of casper's friends? He is in the daily DOW chart.</Title><Msg>His name is spooky.</Msg><Username>loser_insight</Username><Timestamp>1369080407614</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:06:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369080415387-80</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement</Title><Username>royr44</Username><Timestamp>1369059272660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:14:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm subscribed. Cool</Msg><Username>oreeric45</Username><Timestamp>1369080415387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:06:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369082759096-81</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement</Title><Username>royr44</Username><Timestamp>1369059272660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:14:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just joined.</Msg><Username>v.stacey93</Username><Timestamp>1369082759096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:45:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369082820630-82</Id><Title>I don't own any INTC stock, but the "blunder" announcement might actually be a strategic move, imo...</Title><Msg>While it appears that Otellini is merely admitting a "major blunder," what he may also be doing is reminding Apple about the direction Jobs wanted to originally go with the iPhone, in hopes they might take that into account with iPhone's future. That ship might have already sailed, but it can't hurt to try to get the gears turning at Apple, just in case.</Msg><Username>rora1494</Username><Timestamp>1369082820630</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:47:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369087153196-83</Id><Title>Gawdammit the stock is up 4c. Mr Weaver must have pumped less today.</Title><Msg>The more he pumps, the lower it goes.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369087153196</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:59:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369087239291-84</Id><Title>Did anybody read the Samsung vs TSMC Barron's piece</Title><Msg>Competition is HEATING up - if Apple thinks long term the only answer is Intel Not sure if this is true though - " In contrast, we believe Samsung’s 14FF node would deliver a scaling benefit in the 10-15% range compared to Samsung’s 20nm node. We note an area scaling benefit would translate into lower manufacturing costs on Samsung’s 14FF node compared to TSMC’s 16FF node." Jefferies &amp; Co.’s Sundeep Bajikar this morning reiterates a Buy rating on shares of Samsung Electronics (005930KS), and a ₩2,100,000 price target, writing that the company’s chip manufacturing effort going forward will have a lower costs than those of Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing (TSM), based on recent presentations by Taiwan Semi and by Intel (INTC). Bajikar cites a presentation by TSM at an event called “ARM Techcon” last year, and argues there is a cost benefit that Samsung will have in moving to smaller transistors that Taiwan Semi won’t have: According to TSMC CTO’s presentation, and consistent with TSMC CEO’s comments on TSMC’s Q1 earnings call, TSMC’s 16FF (16nm FinFET) node would not deliver a chip area scaling benefit compared to its 20nm node. In contrast, we believe Samsung’s 14FF node would deliver a scaling benefit in the 10-15% range compared to Samsung’s 20nm node. We note an area scaling benefit would translate into lower manufacturing costs on Samsung’s 14FF node compared to TSMC’s 16FF node. Our checks indicate Samsung is focusing its investments on delivering a broadly available 14FF alternative for TSMC’s largest customers like Qualcomm and Nvidia. Bajikar thinks both Samsung and Intel are pulling ahead of Taiwan Semi in leading process technology, and he offers an info-graphic to represent that (click for larger image):</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1369087239291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:00:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369087457648-85</Id><Topic><Title>INTC beaten by CSCO</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368820313047</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 15:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My theory is that they will be writing lots of call options when the Intel share price has moved up and the act of large quantity writing will pressure the share price back down. When the share price goes down, they seem to close out some of the position. A $25 June Call will expire and not result in shares being assigned only if Intel finishes below $25. We will have to wait until the expiration day to see if they finish in the money. It is very hard to tell who is writing and who is holding. It is even harder to tell if the activity is part of a combo activity: straddle, strangle, vertical, horizontal, condor, butterfly, .... neutral, volatility, bullish, bearish, .... It is impossible to tell if "expiring worthless" was the goal and was really a success. Last Friday, there were 30,000 call options assigned and 20,000 put contracts. That is hardly "like they always do".</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369087457648</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369087774399-86</Id><Topic><Title>Did anybody read the Samsung vs TSMC Barron's piece</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1369087239291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's easy to see both GloFo and TSMC dropping out the state-of-the-art fabrication race as the latest flawed fabless model casualties. And I will not believe any of the ARM world will be capable of FinFET until I see products being sold - just like Intel. That time is a very longs way off...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369087774399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:09:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369088945853-87</Id><Topic><Title>Gawdammit the stock is up 4c. Mr Weaver must have pumped less today.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369087153196</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mother ephing b@stard. You don't know jack c$it. Where's the daily Nuff baloney: lower margins, lower revenue, lower earnings, no growth, too much competition, possible div. cut, and insider selling? Ad nauseum.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369088945853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:29:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369095874595-88</Id><Title>Rumor: Apple testing 1.5" OLED displays for wearable 'iWatch'</Title><Msg>Development of Apple's rumored smart watch is allegedly gaining momentum, as a pair of new reports claim the company is testing 1.5-inch OLED screens for a wrist-worn device, and that Foxconn has been contracted to build a trial batch. The latest rumors on Apple's so-called "iWatch" were highlighted on Mon by Macotakara. The publication spotted pair of reports from Taiwan's Economic Daily News. In the first report, the publication claims that Apple is testing organic light emitting diode displays for its anticipated smart watch. The company allegedly tested 1.8-inch panels, but felt they were too big, prompting development to go smaller with 1.5-inch displays. According to the report, Apple is exploring 1.5-inch OLED touchscreens manufactured by RiTdisplay of Taiwan that use one-glass-solution touch sensors. This would allow the display component to be as thin as possible for the wearable accessory. It should be noted that rumors for years have claimed that Apple is interested in OLED displays, but to date the company has never used the display technology in any of its devices. OLED screens could, however, be an optimal choice for wearable technology because of their low power consumption levels. In a second report, the Daily News claims that Foxconn, Apple's longtime manufacturing partner, has already received orders for an "iWatch." However, the initial production run is said to be for no more than 1,000 units, as Foxconn is allegedly running a "small-scale trial production." With "iWatch" rumors heating up, one survey from last month found that 19 percent of consumers are interested in buying such a device from Apple. That exceeds pre-announcement interest in both the iPad and Intel-based Mac hardware. Rumors of an Apple smart watch began growing earlier this year, when a number of reports claimed that the company is developing a wearable wrist accessory. One such report claimed that the company has a 100-person team working on the project. appleinsider</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369095874595</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:24:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369096348557-89</Id><Title>Structural Change In The Mobile Processor Marketplace: Intel Wins; ARM, AMD Lose</Title><Msg>This is my first article for Seeking Alpha. I am very recently retired from an Intel (INTC) position as chip design engineer with more than 30 years of varied experience in a wide swath of technologies and companies, and I have been a part of at least six startups. I have 27 US patents to my name. Arnold Frisch</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369096348557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:32:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369096502946-90</Id><Topic><Title>Structural Change In The Mobile Processor Marketplace: Intel Wins; ARM, AMD Lose</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369096348557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:32:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Part III Without further ado, I can state with certainty that the new mobile oriented processors coming from Intel later this year will capture the processor space for the leading smartphones and tablets. There are two fundamental, related, reasons for this: These processors are faster than anything that ARM/TSMC (or AMD) can offer at the same level of power consumption. Their power consumption at the same level of performance is much less than anything ARM/TSMC (or AMD) can offer. You have heard all this before, but many of you don't believe this and are still arguing that moving to 28 nanometer or 20nm (still planar) will save ARM from the Intel bomb. Well, that's just wrong! Read on! These two statements, above, are corollaries to laws of physics relating to silicon FET-based integrated circuits. In current technologies - 32 nanometer and smaller - constructed in a planar (TSMC) fashion, the predominant use of energy occurs as a result of leakage in inactive FETs. The FETs leak because they are running at low voltage, and in order to do that, they must have low threshold voltages. When you construct a FET with low threshold voltage in a planar technology, you can't completely turn it off. So it leaks. When you construct a FET for the same use in a 3D or "finFET" technology, the gate (the valve that controls the flow of charge carriers) has much more effective control and is more nearly able to completely extinguish the leakage current in the inactive FETs. Voila, the battery charge lasts longer. And because the gate length is shorter, the FET uses less energy for each transition from one state to another. So you can squeeze more transitions from a given amount of stored energy in the battery, i.e. it runs faster.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369096502946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:35:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369096582431-91</Id><Topic><Title>Structural Change In The Mobile Processor Marketplace: Intel Wins; ARM, AMD Lose</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369096348557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:32:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Part III It's the laws of physics that controls the winner in the processor race for mobile applications, and Intel has already won this race. Anyone who disagrees is in denial, has some ulterior motive, or is just dense. What all this means is that whoever builds phones or tablets using Intel processors can make them run faster and run longer on a given battery than by using an ARM (or AMD) processor. This argument cuts off the other arguments about market share, design wins, better architecture and other objections by the Intel opponents. Market share is a measure of the past. What was, not what is. What is, is that the 22nm finFET is a better transistor and it makes for a better processor. If you want the best processor in your next phone/tablet/mobility_device, it had better be an Intel processor. Architecture is an abstract thing; the "goodness" of an architecture can only be measured by objective effects. How quickly can I do something? How long will the battery charge last? Intel wins again, by actual comparison in Motorola phones! I have given you the facts that support my statement that Intel has already won this race. If any of you want to continue to argue about this, please supply the facts that support your argument. I don't argue with people I don't know unless I know the facts that they are trying to use to support their arguments. Now, the impact of this win: It's clear that Intel will rapidly gain market share pitting phones with Intel inside against phones with ARM or AMD inside. As I have stated elsewhere, this is a case where word of mouth will sell Intel-based phones and tablets. Whoever buys one will be delighted and tell their friend about the long battery life and the great performance - and their friends and their friend's friends will go out and buy "Intel inside."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369096582431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:36:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369096717743-92</Id><Topic><Title>Structural Change In The Mobile Processor Marketplace: Intel Wins; ARM, AMD Lose</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369096348557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:32:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At last someone who worked for Intel but didn't get fired weighs in...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369096717743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:38:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369096810885-93</Id><Topic><Title>Structural Change In The Mobile Processor Marketplace: Intel Wins; ARM, AMD Lose</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369096348557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:32:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You have heard all this before, but many of you don't believe this and are still arguing that moving to 28 nanometer or 20nm (still planar) will save ARM from the Intel bomb. Well, that's just wrong! Read on!"</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369096810885</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:40:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369096938555-94</Id><Topic><Title>Structural Change In The Mobile Processor Marketplace: Intel Wins; ARM, AMD Lose</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369096348557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:32:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's the laws of physics that controls the winner in the processor race for mobile applications, and Intel has already won this race. Anyone who disagrees is in denial, has some ulterior motive, or is just dense." [I like this new guy! He tells it like it is and has the expertise to back it up...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369096938555</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:42:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369098151005-95</Id><Topic><Title>Stagnation just before a large correction</Title><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1369072876151</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey, kid, go do your homework.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1369098151005</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 21:02:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369100675932-96</Id><Title>INTC may give a warning next week</Title><Msg>It cannot be good if all computer manufactures are not good.</Msg><Username>gh0613</Username><Timestamp>1369100675932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 21:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369101084673-97</Id><Topic><Title>INTC may give a warning next week</Title><Username>gh0613</Username><Timestamp>1369100675932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 21:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The week before Haswell introduction? Three weeks before new PHI introduction? Bay Trail Introductions ?? Don't be SILLY!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369101084673</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 21:51:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369102644243-98</Id><Title>Samsung is looking forward to stack their memory dies over Atom</Title><Msg>ARM is garbage. You will see this coming after the Galaxy Tab 3.</Msg><Username>pc_addicte</Username><Timestamp>1369102644243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:17:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369103034582-99</Id><Title>ZOMBIE RETAIL: SEE WHAT ARMH Soc Has done to INTEL: Monopoly:London Calling: Did Allwinner outsell Intel, Qualcomm? ARM Inside.</Title><Msg>ZOMBIE RETAIL: SEE WHAT ARMH Soc Has done to INTEL: Monopoly:London Calling: Did Allwinner outsell Intel, Qualcomm? ARM Inside. London Calling: Did Allwinner outsell Intel, Qualcomm? ARM Inside. EE Times London Calling: Did Allwinner outsell Intel, Qualcomm? Peter Clarke 5/8/2013 11:07 AM EDT (ARM Inside) It may seem strange but Chinese chip vendor Allwinner Technologies Co. Ltd. (Zhuhai, China) probably sold more application processors for tablet computers in 2012 than Intel and Qualcomm put together. The numbers for annual sales of smartphones and tablet computers are growing fast and we think we know who the winners are: the likes of Apple, Samsung, Nvidia, Qualcomm and so on, right? But Strategy Analytics is reporting an interesting snippet from its market research; that in 2012 Chinese vendors grabbed 20 percent volume share of the tablet application processor market between them. That's in a market that by value grew 83 percent year-on-year to reach $2.7 billion, the firm reckons. So even if those Chinese vendors were selling at the low-end of the pricing spectrum this is not chicken feed. Sravann Kundojjala, senior analyst with Strategy Analytics, pointed out that the Chinese vendors are selling dual-core ARM chips at $4 or $5 and quad-cores at $8 or $9, less than half what Nvidia is selling its equivalent chips for and so probably the Chinese vendors, while significant in volume, do not yet have 10 percent of the market by value. Strategy Analytics reckons Apple had about 48 percent revenue share of the tablet processor market in 2012, although clearly their devices are captive in the iPad. Nvidia, Texas Instruments, Samsung and Qualcomm made up Strategy Analytics' top-five ranking of vendors. Strategy Analytics reckons Nvidia led the non-iPad tablet market with 27 percent revenue share in 2012 having scored high-profile design wins in the Google Nexus 7 and the Microsoft Surface RT. So who are these Chinese tablet processor vendors? Strategy Analytics would like you buy a $6,999 report to find out their take on it. The Chinese are coming But we can try and guess who might be on Strategy Analytics' list. It probably includes: Allwinner Technology, Rockchip, Amlogic, Infotmic, Ingenic, Hi-Silicon, NuFront. It may include Via Technologies Inc. – a long time vendor of x86 chips and more recently of ARM processors – although Via is based in Taipei, Taiwan, and so may or may not have been included in the Chinese category. Hi-Silicon, which is effectively part of Huawei, may have won business with its parent, although it is equally possible that such captive sales could have been missed. Ingenic is MIPS licensee with a reputation for being one company that has figured out to make most Android apps run smoothly on MIPS. Nufront is one of our less likely contenders. In fact we reckon that the first three names on our list – Allwinner, Rockchip and Amlogic – are probably responsible for more than half the Chinese supply of tablet processors in 2012. Allwinner clearly has the lion's share, according to supply chain checks made by my colleague Junko Yoshida; maybe nearly half the supply of Chinese tablet processors on its own. This would make it responsible for nearly 10 percent of the global supply by volume. The rest of the Chinese suppliers are part of a long list of much smaller suppliers. Interestingly in the previous year Rockchip was in a similar Chinese market-leading situation. The market changes and swings happen very fast in China. Even more interesting is that Allwinner is therefore likely to have outsold Intel and Qualcomm put together. Strategy Analytics reckons Intel and Qualcomm missed the tablet processor boat in 2012 and captured less than 5 percent volume share in the tablet applications processor market. Stuart Robinson, director of the Strategy Analytics' handset component service, said that any success for these two in tablets will depend on Microsoft and whether its Windows tablet operating system can gain market acceptance. Things can change rapidly in a fast-growing market but we suggest keeping an eye on Allwinner and its smaller competitors, Intel and Qualcomm.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369103034582</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:23:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369103329392-100</Id><Title>biggest pyramid scheme ever these markets</Title><Msg>Never seen so many people being sucked in and told to buy by brokers at these ridiculous levels. Just trying to keep it going last ones in lose it all. ONe world wide scheme trying to make everything grear if all markets go up. Trying to fool the world that everything is great because all markets are recovering. Just like the tooth fairy.</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1369103329392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369103607239-101</Id><Topic><Title>ZOMBIE RETAIL: SEE WHAT ARMH Soc Has done to INTEL: Monopoly:London Calling: Did Allwinner outsell Intel, Qualcomm? ARM Inside.</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369103034582</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:23:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be sure to put this stuff on the QCOM, NVDA, AMD, Samsung, AAPL, and all the other boards. It is much worse for them especially QCOM since they are already selling below cost. .</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369103607239</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:33:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369104676124-102</Id><Topic><Title>Risk for Shorts just went Way Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369077583837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:19:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ditto</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1369104676124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:51:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369106107840-103</Id><Topic><Title>ZOMBIE RETAIL: SEE WHAT ARMH Soc Has done to INTEL: Monopoly:London Calling: Did Allwinner outsell Intel, Qualcomm? ARM Inside.</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369103034582</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:23:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTEL has to do the same and revenue/margin hell as I am warning I sold Intel for 15 years Intel management is now screwing up Slapping Debt on Balance sheet and buy backs also depleting cash DIVIDEND will vanish in few years watch out............ All nations want have jobs at home and what are they going to do? USE Domestic commodities and imports fall off the cliff USA zombies........watch when you fake jobs vanish vs Real jobs already shipped off shore</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369106107840</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369106573863-104</Id><Topic><Title>ZOMBIE RETAIL: SEE WHAT ARMH Soc Has done to INTEL: Monopoly:London Calling: Did Allwinner outsell Intel, Qualcomm? ARM Inside.</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369103034582</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:23:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Home GPUs AMD Continues Assembling Dream Team: Sean Pelletier from NVIDIA Tech Marketing to Join Last year AMD was hemorrhaging talent. While we don't have a good indication of the extent of the talent exodus, Qualcomm seemed to benefit quite a bit from the tough times that had fallen on AMD. AMD PR mounted the beginnings of a turnaround with the announcement that Jim Keller, former K8 architect and chip-head at Apple had rejoined the company. Then came John Gustafson and last month, we got word that Raja Koduri rejoined as well - also after a multi-year stint at Apple. Today I just got word from a couple of very accurate and trusted sources that my old friend Sean Pelletier will be joining AMD as well. Sean will abandon his role as Senior Technical Marketing Manager at NVIDIA to assume a similar role at AMD, initially focusing on GPUs. Reporting on individual hires doesn't actually tell you a lot about talent within a company, but it can give insight into whether or not a company is viable. Not too long ago, leaving Apple, NVIDIA or pretty much any other tech company to join AMD sounded like a career death sentence. The fact that smart folks from all paths are considering AMD as an option for long term employment tells us a lot about how things have changed.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369106573863</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:22:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369107214550-105</Id><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Msg>1.) We know that Intel is going to be two process nodes up on ARM as Intel's 14nm will be in volume production long before ARM's 20nm. This means ARM's 28nm will have to compete with Intel's 14nm FinFET. No comparison. Airmont will be the ARM-Slayer. 2.) We know that the economics of ARM foundries is going to decline steadily. See the article "Intel will win in foundry wars" for the details. Also Intel will be first to 450mm wafers by a long shot. And ARM foundries are taking longer to reach the same yield level with each drop in die size. Intel continues to enjoy improved economics at each node due to superior technology, fabrication and manufacturing. 3.) We know that Intel has a roadmap chocked full of consistent improvements. We will see a plethora of new product announcements all year long. We will see a ton of new Haswell products available immediately after the formal announcement on June 3rd. 4.) We know that we will see more big Intel foundry deals. 5.) We know that Intel is doubling tablet sales each quarter and that the ARM RT is toast. 6.) We know that 2014 will be the year of the Intel Smartphone as 14nm technology will combine with Intel's newly integrated LTE solution to finally offer superior products across the board. 7.) We know that ARM is the most over-valued stock since the dotcom era. With a P/E of 83 and Intel coming on fast there is no way they can grow earnings at a rate to justify that valuation. 8.) We know that with the exception of the blueredmonk that there is no ARM fanboi on this board capable of engaging in a discussion of technology with any semblance of credibility. 9.) We know that new form factors are re-energizing the computer business. We know that only Intel has the ecosystem to provide complete solutions across all of computing and mobility. 10.) And we know that the second half of the year will be much better than the first half with particular excitement brewing for back-to-school and the holiday period.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369107214550</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:33:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369107837268-106</Id><Title>Samsung To Use Intel Atom Processor In Its New 10” Tablet</Title><Msg>Google it. Yahoo won't let me post it...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369107837268</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:43:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369108005464-107</Id><Title>The iWatch is coming! The iWatch is coming!</Title><Msg>[Shorts be afraid - be very afraid...] The Apple iWatch rumor mill has rumbled to life yet again, with one report that Apple is sampling 1.5-inch OLED displays for the li'l fellow, and a second that long-time iKit assembler Foxconn has received orders for a test batch of the "wearable computing" device. From the register</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369108005464</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>