<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367813076006-1</Id><Topic><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you buy a convertible, you're not sure whether you want a laptop or a tablet. Same applies to the manufacturer. IMHO convertibles are a rather stupid idea.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367813076006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 00:04:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367813088827-2</Id><Title>Shills Started Late Tonight</Title><Msg>But still managed to get in 42 content-free posts thanks to the hardest working one man shill show in the business. Well, they are prolly really nervous about tomorrow and the rest of the year for that matter. I hear that the analyst's trophy wives are throwing things in boxes. So much for the big vacation after the Q1 earnings call. They barely have enough money now for drugs, booze and #$%$...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367813088827</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 00:04:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367813321723-3</Id><Topic><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If you buy a convertible, you're not sure whether you want a laptop or a tablet. Same applies to the manufacturer. IMHO convertibles are a rather stupid idea." [Your opinion isn't humble enough or your wouldn't offer it. You thought RT was going to be a rousing success. You think an iPad is all the computing power anyone would ever need. Listening to someone with your limited computer knowledge is a rather stupid idea. Mark your post as the 43rd content-free shill post of the night...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367813321723</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 00:08:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367814247329-4</Id><Topic><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NAW, Apple is going to ditch X86, and gonna concentrate on iOS, developing tablets into fully fledged PC's. Apple using it's own ARM architecture, is going to convince its multitude of Apple graphics software users that all you need is a tablet. After all can't an iPad do everything? Apple, What a joke! A year late to the party in Touch notebooks, possibly two years late to the party with Tablet-PC's. Apply is facing a hiding to nothing. Which ever cannibalise their own market. - Bring out MacTouch, eats into their own iPad sales. - Bring out iPad convertible, cuts into their own MacBook sales, already being decimated by Win8-touch Ultrabooks. BTW, will be a total suicide for Apple, (see WinRT if you have doubts). - Bring out MacBook Touch, convertible, totally kills their own iPad sales. Irrespective of Apple's claims, they simply have failed to bring to market; 1. A fully functional PC in a Tablet form factor. 2. A Fully functional Notebook (or desktop) PC with Touch capability. 3. A Fully functional convertible PC come tablet device. Apple will be ONE whole year behind the windows crowd, so much for Apple being innovative. yes iPod, iPhone, MacAir, iPad were truly innovative at the time. Hey but that was like 3 years ago. No real innovation since Jobs died!</Msg><Username>gooddigger</Username><Timestamp>1367814247329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 00:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367820806806-5</Id><Title>Wallis, regarding Ottelini's comments on Sprint.</Title><Msg>What do you think of this? I myself have noticed that AT&amp;T and Verizon are moving like a snail to upgrade their systems, and Intel CEO is absolutely right about allowing some fire to be lit under the butts of AT&amp;T and Verizon. I also hope Google makes a big move too, sooner rather than later, in the internet service provider space. Here's what was said: "Paul Otellini is favoring Softbank Corp (OTCMKTS:SFTBF) (TYO:9984) over DISH Network Corp (NASDAQ:DISH) for the takeover of Sprint Nextel Corporation (NYSE:S) according to Reuters. The CEO of Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) has written a letter to Federal Communications Commission (FCC) Chairman Julius Genachowski in which he said that he is backing SoftBank, which is a wireless carrier based in Japan. There have been talks held between Sprint Nextel Corporation (NYSE:S) and Softbank Corp (OTCMKTS:SFTBF) (TYO:9984) since last October over the $20 billion offer. The deal was almost finalized but to everyone’s surprise Dish offered $25.5 billion to acquire Sprint. The deal will be concluded by July if Sprint accepts the offer of SoftBank. Otellini in his letter to FCC wrote that the idea of SoftBank building the third largest US wireless network was very enticing, and the intensity of competition should increase in the wireless carrier competition. “We need this competition in the wireless space as the ATT/Verizon model is not giving that to consumers at this time,” Otellini said. There was no further word from Otellini as to why he favors SoftBank over DISH Network Corp (NASDAQ:DISH). According to a spokesperson of Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC), SoftBank is a business partner of Intel and thus Otellini’s favor is natural. He further said that, after the deal, SoftBank would emerge as the third competitor in the market, and the ultimate benefit will be for the consumers. He went on to say that SoftBank is largely seen as a market disruptor, which will also be beneficial."</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367820806806</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 02:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367821129692-6</Id><Title>Four great articles over the weekend from Seeking Alpha.</Title><Msg>1. Intel: Sivermont - The ARM Killer 2. Intel And Microsoft Speed Up Windows RT's Death. 3. Intel: A Must-Read History Lesson. 4. Intel Will Regain Lead With Processors Beyond 22 Nanometer. Every one of these articles alot better and certainly more informative than anything James Covello from Goldman Sachs has said about Intel.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367821129692</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 02:18:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367825715320-7</Id><Topic><Title>Always remember to take SOME PROFITS after you stock has run up over 25% INTC is up from low $19's to over $24 , It is time to take some.</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367808892334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:54:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I set a limit order on Friday noon and the bounce never happened so I'm not selling for less than that but not willing to do a long term limit order. INTC looks set to go otside market conditions which could drag all techs down because they have been on a roll lately.</Msg><Username>charles_neff</Username><Timestamp>1367825715320</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 03:35:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367828944835-8</Id><Topic><Title>Four great articles over the weekend from Seeking Alpha.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367821129692</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 02:18:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks, Paul Ottelini. BTW, never noticed it before, but your subtle variant on "Otellini" is interesting. Anyway, glad you liked the articles...more coming soon.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367828944835</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 04:29:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367832024925-9</Id><Topic><Title>MacBook Air Probably Becomes A Convertible</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367800006552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A pure touch UI doesn't work within a windowed GUI. MS has had a 'touch' UI and a tablet form factor for the best part of decade but it just never worked. Fingers are just too large for UI components in a traditional pointer based environment. That said, touch as an additive UI to traditional windows does work. I use the touch UI on my ultra-book when in desktop mode to scroll etc, but it could never be a replacement for the track pad/external mouse. Perhaps Apple will add touch UI to it's laptops, but it'll keep iOS for 'real' tablets where no pointer is possible. Whether iOS supports x86 is another question:) From a raw CPU performance perspective I think you are under estimating Apples Swift and over estimating Haswell performance for the given thermal profile of a tablet. I would still expect Apples Swift to have a better cost/performance profile than Haswell which then flows into a cheaper BOM. Finally, I'm not sure if people are that sensible. Roll forward a year or two, how many people would still buy (todays) iPad over a much more power windows 8 convertible? Brand, sheep, etc.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367832024925</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 05:20:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367835659753-10</Id><Topic><Title>This stock is going to the MOON!</Title><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1363965968442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:26:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My advice is to short this stock. Everybody will make a lot of money.</Msg><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1367835659753</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 06:20:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367843327372-11</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL DOWNGRADED $2 PRICE TARGET PC MARKET COLLAPSING</Title><Username>nasdaqczar2</Username><Timestamp>1365692696048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>intel has a #$%$ business now it looks pathetic it should see single digits soon pc died so did this company eom</Msg><Username>goldmansuxtrader</Username><Timestamp>1367843327372</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 08:28:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367844996099-12</Id><Topic><Title>May and June Intel Catalysts</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367645980626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 01:39:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ditto</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367844996099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 08:56:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367845233405-13</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to announce they are going to us AMD chips, Lower priced chips will help Apple margins</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367808213700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:43:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Using AMD chips would also help Apple sell fewer Macbooks... as every other PC manufacturer has found.</Msg><Username>mrekrek1</Username><Timestamp>1367845233405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:00:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367845718534-14</Id><Title>RBC Capital Upgrades Intel (INTC) to Outperform Raises Target To $29</Title><Msg>due to "traction in mobile".</Msg><Username>keiretsunikkei</Username><Timestamp>1367845718534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:08:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367845830759-15</Id><Topic><Title>Apple to announce they are going to us AMD chips, Lower priced chips will help Apple margins</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367808213700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:43:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol. AMD is the last thing Apple needs right now.</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367845830759</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:10:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367846347862-16</Id><Topic><Title>RBC Capital Upgrades Intel (INTC) to Outperform Raises Target To $29</Title><Username>keiretsunikkei</Username><Timestamp>1367845718534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:08:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RBC Capital upgraded microchip maker Intel Corporation (INTC) on Monday, as the analysts believe the company should see increased traction of its ultra-mobile platform. Also, the analysts believe the negative PC sentiment as reach an all-time bottom. As such, ITNC was upgraded from “Sector Perform” to “Outperform.” Furthermore, the analysts see shares reaching $29, up from the previous target of $24.This new target suggests a 21% upside to Friday’s closing price of $23.96. “We do believe that due to the roll-off of start-up costs and bonus back of inventories, gross margins can move higher with limited revenue growth in 2HCY13. As a result, our gross margin assumption for 2013 of 60.7% is higher vs. Street at 59.2%,’ said RBC Capital analyst Doug Freedman. “Traction in mobile is upcoming, as the magnitude of design wins may be surprising to investors. We feel that even ahead of a more compelling leading-edge 14nm line-up in 2014, Intel is today receiving a lot of interest from OEMs. There has been feedback from our handset ecosystem checks suggesting that Intel’s 2014 ultra-mobile platform may be their best yet. This is especially encouraging given that the expectation on Intel.s success in ultra-mobile is very low,” added Freedman. Intel shares were up 22 cents, or +0.92%, during pre-market trading on Monday. The stock is up +16.2% year-to-date. The Bottom Line Shares of Intel Corporation (INTC) have a dividend yield of 3.76% based on Friday’s closing price of $23.96 and the company’s annualized dividend payout of 90 cents per share.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367846347862</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:19:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367846861599-17</Id><Topic><Title>INTC forecasting lower revenue, lower earnings and lower margins than last years Q out look is not good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367805190945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD for their MAC lines? ( warning .... sarcasm ahead ) Cool. Apple can kill the screen (save tons of $$$) and make the MAC a game console. Apple could get out of the PC business before the unit volumes become negative and they are required to take back old MAC units.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367846861599</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367847005355-18</Id><Topic><Title>REMEMBER APPLE/INTEL DEAL IN MAY AFTER MICRON PURCHASE OF ELPIDA IS COMPLETED</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1365725511465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:11:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$40 end of year</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367847005355</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:30:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367847178659-19</Id><Topic><Title>MONDAY, MAY 06, DADI WILL DETAIL SILVERMONT AND BAY TRAIL</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367417712236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:15:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TWO BIG EVENTS TODAY. Lenovo K900 release in China and Silvermont announcement at 9AM PT</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367847178659</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:32:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367847508365-20</Id><Topic><Title>RBC Capital Upgrades Intel (INTC) to Outperform Raises Target To $29</Title><Username>keiretsunikkei</Username><Timestamp>1367845718534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:08:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367847508365</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:38:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367847936949-21</Id><Title>Where's Marcopubio A.K.A. I takebackmyapology</Title><Msg>Now what?</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1367847936949</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:45:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367848043238-22</Id><Title>GOING MUCH HIGHER, $24 SHOULD BE SOLID SUPPORT NOW</Title><Msg>$40 by end of year</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367848043238</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:47:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367848069207-23</Id><Topic><Title>Where's Marcopubio A.K.A. I takebackmyapology</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1367847936949</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:45:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who in H cares...........</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1367848069207</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367848280659-24</Id><Title>Better money to be made in other equities</Title><Msg>INTC is a mature company stuck in a rut for a decade. Buy it if you want income. However if you want growth + income try VNQ (or other REITs). As long as interest rates stay down REITs will fly. The Feds have now turned their attention to bolstering the commercial properties throughout the US. Just ask any commercial real estate agent or land developer.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367848280659</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:51:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367848328183-25</Id><Topic><Title>RBC Capital Upgrades Intel (INTC) to Outperform Raises Target To $29</Title><Username>keiretsunikkei</Username><Timestamp>1367845718534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:08:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is incredibly significant because this is the first of what will be many singing the CORRECT tune on Intel's roadmap and what they REALLY have going on. Great writeup !</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367848328183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367848374345-26</Id><Topic><Title>RBC Capital Upgrades Intel (INTC) to Outperform Raises Target To $29</Title><Username>keiretsunikkei</Username><Timestamp>1367845718534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:08:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they better try again. of course as you all have noted many times, anaylsts suck.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1367848374345</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:52:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367848457784-27</Id><Topic><Title>RBC Capital Upgrades Intel (INTC) to Outperform Raises Target To $29</Title><Username>keiretsunikkei</Username><Timestamp>1367845718534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:08:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sour grapes/bitter beer face. Poor whiny baby.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367848457784</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:54:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367848522650-28</Id><Title>Most Rapidly Growing EPS, Undiscovered with Huge Upside!</Title><Msg>This undiscovered stock has EPS that is growing as a tremendous rate quarter after quarter: Concurrent (CCUR), currently trading for $7.75 per share with 8.75mm o/s, a market cap of $67.84mm, with $22.37mm in cash and no debt, and an enterprise value of only $45.47mm for an insanely low multiple of 0.72x its trailing revenues of $63.23mm. CCUR's operating margins have been absolutely exploding quarter-to-quarter: from 1.3% in 4Q2012, to 2.7% in 1Q2013, to 5.3% in 2Q2013, and 7.3% in 3Q2013. CCUR's GAAP EPS has been rapidly rising quarter-to-quarter: from $0.02 in 4Q2012, to $0.04 in 1Q2013, to $0.08 in 2Q2013, and $0.11 in 3Q2013! CCUR over the past decade captured the world's #1 video on demand (VOD) technology market share in the cable TV industry with a global reach of 50 million cable TV VOD households! CCUR is now rapidly capturing a major share of the new booming multi-screen content delivery network (CDN) market. The two largest U.S. cable TV companies Comcast and Time Warner Cable (TWC) both recently deployed their own CDNs to support multi-screen video delivery to IP connected devices! CCUR's IP CDN solutions were selected by TWC to power multi-screen video delivery through their CDN, allowing their 12 million subscribers to watch VOD and live-TV on their tablets, smartphones, and other IP connected devices, from any location!</Msg><Username>ttvhbn42</Username><Timestamp>1367848522650</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:55:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367848818224-29</Id><Title>Always remember to take some profits in all your stocks before there all gone. Profits go away very fast</Title><Msg>Always remember to take some profits in all your stocks before there all gone. Profits go away very fast</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367848818224</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:00:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367849009493-30</Id><Title>COVER NOW, HEADFAKE</Title><Msg>GOING MUCH HIGHER</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367849009493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:03:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367849774313-31</Id><Title>Upgrade worth 5 pennies</Title><Msg>INTC is bad money. It doesn't rally on big market days and can't do #$%$ when it gets an upgrade.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367849774313</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367849876574-32</Id><Topic><Title>RBC Capital Upgrades Intel (INTC) to Outperform Raises Target To $29</Title><Username>keiretsunikkei</Username><Timestamp>1367845718534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:08:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While they upgrade, they sell their shares to the lemmings. This upgrade is worth 4 pennies so far.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367849876574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:17:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367849996442-33</Id><Topic><Title>This stock is going to the MOON!</Title><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1363965968442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:26:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time to short this stock. I will cover at $21.63.</Msg><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1367849996442</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:19:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367850071057-34</Id><Title>Pathetic stock performance</Title><Msg>the past 3 trading days. With any kind of market correction this sinks fast.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367850071057</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367850572193-35</Id><Topic><Title>Always remember to take some profits in all your stocks before there all gone. Profits go away very fast</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367848818224</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:00:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FYI, "there" [sic] should be "they're", the contraction of "they are" Profits go away very fast in either the up/down direction if you find yourself on the wrong side. Your losses must be piling up. When Intel was $21, you were CONVINCED that Intel would test the $19.23 price. That may happen but has not yet. When Intel was $21, you forecast that Intel would drop below the $19.23. Possibly. You twist truisms to make your sell, sell, sell message to base your spam. Your advice may apply to some but not all.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367850572193</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:29:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367850696546-36</Id><Title>Asus CEO Very Optimistic About Windows Tablets</Title><Msg>He believes Intel based W8 tablets will be available under $300.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367850696546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:31:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367850841498-37</Id><Topic><Title>Pathetic stock performance</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367850071057</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:21:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Work it Nuff! you POS! Uh Oh, INTC going up - better increase your comments! Hurry! LOL!</Msg><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367850841498</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:34:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367851016294-38</Id><Topic><Title>Pathetic stock performance</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367850071057</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:21:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the past year, your opinion would have been correct. Intel still has a BETA of less than 1 and the DJI has been struggling through 15k. There was call option selling at JUN and JUL $25 strike and May bull spread buying activity. All this would tend to drive the share price toward $24. INTC will probably stay pretty close to $24 until noon when the webcast starts.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367851016294</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:36:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367851137934-39</Id><Title>Smart Glasses will replace Cell service - Vuzi breaking out - last chance to buy</Title><Msg>The future is on your doorstep</Msg><Username>whattime0000</Username><Timestamp>1367851137934</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:38:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367851149079-40</Id><Topic><Title>Pathetic stock performance</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367850071057</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:21:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HAHAHAHA...more pumping!!!! It's always something is coming. In fact, it has been a decade of it.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367851149079</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:39:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367851528439-41</Id><Title>You would be better buying defensive stocks</Title><Msg>Try Starbucks, Green Mountain, CVS and Costco. They actually have a business plan unlike the hype coming from Intel.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367851528439</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:45:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367851631907-42</Id><Topic><Title>You would be better buying defensive stocks</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367851528439</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:45:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What about facebook and Cisco? You lost big on these.</Msg><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367851631907</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:47:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367851664700-43</Id><Title>TODAY'S UPGRADE WILL BE ONE OF MANY</Title><Msg>EVEN ANALysts ARE GETTING BEHIND INTC NOW</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367851664700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:47:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367851847333-44</Id><Topic><Title>Pathetic stock performance</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367850071057</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:21:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmm. "Pumping"??? I said that I expect the INTC price to stay UNCHANGED at or near $24 in a bright green market. How do you classify that as PUMPING? Just because I am not dramatic share price change in either direction does not make me a pumper. Intel has a BETA below 1 and it has that IMO because of the damping effect of option trading. Just because I am not a flaming sell, sell, sell parrot does not make me a pumper. Just because I am not a flaming buy, buy, buy parrot does not make me a basher. I certainly do not offer one-size-fits-all investment advice.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367851847333</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367851853477-45</Id><Topic><Title>You would be better buying defensive stocks</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367851528439</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:45:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never promoted any that cr@p.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367851853477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:50:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367852124139-46</Id><Topic><Title>You would be better buying defensive stocks</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367851528439</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:45:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which defensive stocks to you know that have potential to double its revenue in 2 years. Smartphones, 7" tablets, Fab'ing, TV, wearable devices (iWatch)....these are all brand new markets for Intel, with their extending process lead, Intel will take major shares in these markets in the next 2 years. Intel should be viewed as a growth stock. $40 by end of year.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367852124139</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:55:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367852297877-47</Id><Topic><Title>TODAY'S UPGRADE WILL BE ONE OF MANY</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367851664700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:47:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have not heard of these guys but .... Topeka Capital Initiates Coverage on Intel Corporation at Buy, Announces $28.00 PT May 06, 2013 10:21 AM</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367852297877</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:58:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367852711392-48</Id><Topic><Title>Asus CEO Very Optimistic About Windows Tablets</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367850696546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:31:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's several established players at that price point. Selling will be difficult.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367852711392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:05:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367853165940-49</Id><Topic><Title>Asus CEO Very Optimistic About Windows Tablets</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367850696546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:31:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let me quote someone from last week: "If it wasn't for nonsense, you would make no sense at all". 'Splain to me how AAPL will sell $400-600 iPads when there are $300 devices that do much more.</Msg><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1367853165940</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367853274706-50</Id><Topic><Title>Asus CEO Very Optimistic About Windows Tablets</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367850696546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:31:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You f*k*e*n annoying s*h***I**t. Windows 8 tablets will sell like crazy. You get the flexibility and mobility of the small form factor but all the power and software of Windows 8. Windows 8 tablets will be great BYOD</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367853274706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367853531730-51</Id><Topic><Title>Asus CEO Very Optimistic About Windows Tablets</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367850696546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:31:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ask any Win8 tablet vendor what's cool about them -- you can do so much on them. What they don't get is that's not what people are looking for in a tablet.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367853531730</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:18:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367853612809-52</Id><Topic><Title>You would be better buying defensive stocks</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367851528439</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:45:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Potential" - that says it all!</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367853612809</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:20:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367853640038-53</Id><Title>WOW they still can't stop a flash crash, they can only slow it down some</Title><Msg>WOW they still can't stop a flash crash, they can only slow it down some</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367853640038</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:20:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367853729299-54</Id><Topic><Title>WOW they still can't stop a flash crash, they can only slow it down some</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367853640038</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:20:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its been 3 years and they still can't stop a flash crash</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367853729299</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367853768492-55</Id><Topic><Title>MONDAY, MAY 06, DADI WILL DETAIL SILVERMONT AND BAY TRAIL</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367417712236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:15:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$40 by end of year</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367853768492</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:22:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367854264939-56</Id><Title>So this is what an upgrade gets you</Title><Msg>All the good news has already been factored into the price. You can't keep this price propped up by fluff.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367854264939</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:31:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367854302207-57</Id><Title>SILVERMONT EVENT - HALF HOUR AWAY</Title><Msg>THE PRESS WILL BE ALL OVER IT. EXPECT A POP.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367854302207</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367854314292-58</Id><Topic><Title>WOW they still can't stop a flash crash, they can only slow it down some</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367853640038</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:20:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They can stop it but there is no will. The players who need to participate are making revenue and profits by propagating the model. The ultimate culprit is high frequency trading. Hedge funds and investment banks are now paying the NYSE to be close to the source to get the HFT edge. They rent space in their room where all the machines have the same length net cable to equalize the response time. Their algorithms all back off trading when network response is slow. The big, aggressive sell order back in 2010 cause the network response to slow and all the HFT machines backed off. All that would be needed would be to put a minimum transaction time on orders at say 1 millisecond and flash crashes would disappear. The answer is easy but those who would lose their edge have very good lobbyists.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367854314292</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:31:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367854326585-59</Id><Title>Its not a upgrade its a pump and dump and everyone knows it</Title><Msg>Its not a upgrade its a pump and dump and everyone knows it</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367854326585</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:32:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367854417326-60</Id><Topic><Title>Its not a upgrade its a pump and dump and everyone knows it</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367854326585</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:32:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't think so, even your beloved covello will be forced to upgrade intel</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367854417326</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:33:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367854420204-61</Id><Title>Remeber INTC is already up over 25% and now it time to take some profits</Title><Msg>Remeber INTC is already up over 25% and now it time to take some profits</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367854420204</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:33:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367854475624-62</Id><Topic><Title>Remeber INTC is already up over 25% and now it time to take some profits</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367854420204</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:33:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel going to $40 by end of year fool. Too many deals and products coming out to stop this train</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367854475624</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367854775293-63</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K900 Smartphone confirmed, May 6th in China</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1366832924136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 15:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good info</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367854775293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:39:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367854798341-64</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 meets 8-inch tablet</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366901363690</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:49:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 on small tablets will sell like crazy</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367854798341</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:39:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367854820507-65</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC / GF combined capex = $14 billion!!!</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1366905798569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:03:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel price point going lower while arms going higher</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367854820507</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:40:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367854831424-66</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Smith on Bay Trail</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366865645518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:54:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good info</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367854831424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:40:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367854876169-67</Id><Topic><Title>Asus ME302C tablet with full HD display, Intel Clover Trail+ spotted</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366994491111</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 12:41:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even intel's budget SOC is killing arms very best, Clovertrail+ beats them, Merrifield will destroy</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367854876169</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367854885676-68</Id><Topic><Title>Large Mobile Customer may be AMAZON!</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1366987240381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$40</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367854885676</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:41:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367854889181-69</Id><Title>PRICE TARGET 35!!</Title><Msg>GET YOURS</Msg><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1367854889181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367854900177-70</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell, Intel’s most power efficient mainstream processor</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1366996618887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 13:16:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>coming on June 3</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367854900177</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367854915831-71</Id><Title>INTC is now on the road to dominate the Mobile Market as it did in the PC Market</Title><Msg>All the other competitors can only make their product at TSMC, and TSMC will always be behind INTC in the size of the Semi it can produce. ARMH is finished</Msg><Username>seriouslynot</Username><Timestamp>1367854915831</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:41:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367854992309-72</Id><Topic><Title>Intel north Cape promises 10 hour battery life in Tablet mode</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1366927166600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:59:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>form factors like north cape, surface pro, Lenovo helix, and now Asus R7...these are examples of PC evolving. Don't forget Windows 8 on 7" tablets too. And intel will make move into US phone market with Merrifield with integrated LTE 4G</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367854992309</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855011250-73</Id><Topic><Title>$200 Android Powered Notebooks With Intel CPU Confirmed</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1366984238529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 09:50:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shorts = fried</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367855011250</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:43:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855037354-74</Id><Topic><Title>Bravo Ashraf: INTC: The King is Back</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367180371747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 16:19:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cover now shorts, silvermont only minutes away</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367855037354</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:43:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855066611-75</Id><Topic><Title>WARNING TO SHORTS: COVER YOUR A**S**S</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367333882361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:58:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cover now, 15 minutes to silvermont announcemnt</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367855066611</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:44:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855090737-76</Id><Topic><Title>APPLE/INTEL DEAL WILL GET THIS OVER $30 OVERNIGHT, GET OUT NOW SHORTS</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367334258452</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 11:04:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>overnight fools</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367855090737</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:44:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855149818-77</Id><Topic><Title>PRICE TARGET 35!!</Title><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1367854889181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:41:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aren't you going to mention that we can wait another decade before seing that price.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367855149818</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:45:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855211315-78</Id><Topic><Title>Intel XOLO X500 (based on low-end Intel Lexington Z2420) scores similar to premium Samsung Galaxy, HTC One, and Sony Experia phones</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365769812557</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 08:30:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lexington, Intel's budget SoC killing snapdragon 600 LOL</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367855211315</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:46:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367855229297-79</Id><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Msg>I have been waiting 2 years for this. Time to see what this new Atom uArch can do.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855261654-80</Id><Topic><Title>Asus Fonepad (based on Intel Lexington Z2420) Now Available in South East Asia</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365772392431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 09:13:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lexington making a killing in developing countries</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367855261654</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855306885-81</Id><Topic><Title>Asus CEO Very Optimistic About Windows Tablets</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367850696546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:31:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The benefit of the tablet is mobility but what good is mobility if it means having to sacrifice the type of work or entertainment one can do when using it? As much as I can appreciate Android it doesn't come close to delivering the range of apps and utilities available under a professional 64 bit Windows 8. The beauty of Intel tablets is not having to make the difficult choice between Windows OR Android, and not having to choose between the apps one has to give up because with Intel tablets Android comes from free provided one has a little more storage to hold the boot image.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367855306885</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:48:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855362465-82</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE Geek (Atom Z2580 Clovertrail+) smartphone is smoking fast, spanks the top ARM SoCs</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365680605869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 07:43:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel will dominate smartphones and all computing devices</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367855362465</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855426203-83</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SILVERMONT!!!!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367855426203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855455045-84</Id><Topic><Title>PRICE TARGET 35!!</Title><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1367854889181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:41:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$40 BONEHEAD!!!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367855455045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:50:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855474526-85</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SILVERMONT!!!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367855474526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855577021-86</Id><Topic><Title>Asus CEO Very Optimistic About Windows Tablets</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367850696546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:31:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100% AGREE</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367855577021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367855581511-87</Id><Title>WOW just non Stop pumping Looks like INTC is really going to fall this time. Take some Profits</Title><Msg>WOW just non Stop pumping Looks like INTC is really going to fall this time. Take some Profits</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367855581511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:53:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855612142-88</Id><Topic><Title>WOW just non Stop pumping Looks like INTC is really going to fall this time. Take some Profits</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367855581511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:53:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>COVER NOW JA*CK***#$%$*S***S**</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367855612142</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:53:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855640050-89</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SILVERMONT!!!!!!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367855640050</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855646249-90</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE Geek (Atom Z2580 Clovertrail+) smartphone is smoking fast, spanks the top ARM SoCs</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365680605869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 07:43:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Prove it. *wink* *wink* (oops, got a run in my nylons)</Msg><Username>thebluereddork</Username><Timestamp>1367855646249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:54:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855702073-91</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>intcDOTcom/eventdetail.cfm?eventid=129393 in 5 mins time</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367855702073</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:55:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855750671-92</Id><Topic><Title>WOW just non Stop pumping Looks like INTC is really going to fall this time. Take some Profits</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367855581511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:53:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many times do I have to till you that I am not short and its just time to take some profits after INTC has run up 25%</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367855750671</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:55:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367855860002-93</Id><Title>ARM Reminds Me of Subprime</Title><Msg>There is that same total disconnect of the ARM stock price with anything having to do with reality. This morning I watched as the ARM stock price bounced up and down like crazy with one change of about 50 cents (moving down) happening instantaneously. This has to be one of the most manipulated stocks in years and years. I can't help but watch with the same feeling that one gets watching a train wreck in slow motion. It can't last but it just goes on and on. Just like subprime...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367855860002</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:57:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855963638-94</Id><Topic><Title>WOW just non Stop pumping Looks like INTC is really going to fall this time. Take some Profits</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367855581511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:53:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How many times do I have to till you that I am not short and its just time to take some profits after INTC has run up 25%" [If you think we will ever believe your coinboy character, Dana, then you are totally out of your mind...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367855963638</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:59:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367856439992-95</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Reminds Me of Subprime</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367855860002</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:57:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM's home exchange is closed so it's usual for the price to be more volatile.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367856439992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367856689888-96</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OoOE confirmed.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367856689888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:11:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367856901668-97</Id><Title>// GALE // DRRX // DARA //</Title><Msg>German index additions. High growth</Msg><Username>acad_at80centswasa_pos</Username><Timestamp>1367856901668</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:15:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367856956462-98</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>8 cores in micro-server.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367856956462</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367857054563-99</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dadi putting the stock market TV show guys to shame. Good for him.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367857054563</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367857114470-100</Id><Title>Bla Bla Bla, would take 2 Minutes, power, performance diagram</Title><Msg>what microcephaluses working for INTC</Msg><Username>webdesignmed</Username><Timestamp>1367857114470</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:18:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367857160238-101</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Reminds Me of Subprime</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367855860002</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:57:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Waldo, INTC gets upgraded and the price goes down, leaving you with zero cap gains in almost 3 years. hate armh, raise some cash and short it, you keep bashing it all day long and you're only underwater since the liftoff to new highs from way down there right under 40.00</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1367857160238</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:19:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367857593946-102</Id><Title>Can someone explain the $24 resistance?!</Title><Msg>This stock was doing great, but has met incredibly strong resistance at $24 for several days now. What the heck gives? Why can't it break through? Meanwhile AMD is just zooming up when their profits on the console chips will be a joke.</Msg><Username>scaredinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1367857593946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:26:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367857643992-103</Id><Topic><Title>// GALE // DRRX // DARA //</Title><Username>acad_at80centswasa_pos</Username><Timestamp>1367856901668</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:15:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>new momentum signals in 2 of those. ty</Msg><Username>chips_nano08</Username><Timestamp>1367857643992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:27:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367858416934-104</Id><Topic><Title>Can someone explain the $24 resistance?!</Title><Username>scaredinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1367857593946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:26:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry and be scared like Nuff. He's afraid of his own shadow. The stock is consolidating and will soon rise way above 24.</Msg><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367858416934</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:40:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367858675854-105</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Reminds Me of Subprime</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367855860002</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:57:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Poor Waldo, INTC gets upgraded and the price goes down, leaving you with zero cap gains in almost 3 years. hate armh, raise some cash and short it, you keep bashing it all day long and you're only underwater since the liftoff to new highs from way down there right under 40.00" [Dana, do you ever have a day where you don't wash down your breakfast with a couple of big mugs of bile and venom?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367858675854</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367858970177-106</Id><Topic><Title>WOW just non Stop pumping Looks like INTC is really going to fall this time. Take some Profits</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367855581511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:53:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you feel the need to take profits, do so. You need not announce your intentions. Selling is a personal thing. For some, this may be a buying opportunity. Don't think people see you as their financial advisor/expert :)</Msg><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367858970177</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:49:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367859163194-107</Id><Title>I hope there is a transcript of this presentation</Title><Msg>Having trouble catching every word because of accents. Also, the presentation is fairly technical. When engineers give a talk, they want to include all the information. When marketing people give a presentation, they know to hit one or two main points again and again. Hopefully, Ashraf and Russ Fisher will be commenting on this presentation. ARM will probably answer Silvermont with Huge.Big.Little and their stock will go up another $10 bucks.</Msg><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1367859163194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:52:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367859324688-108</Id><Topic><Title>I hope there is a transcript of this presentation</Title><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1367859163194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:52:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>big.LITTLE is a distaster. An inelegant hack to mask a foolish design target at the wrong process node. Silvermont appears to be elegance incarnate.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367859324688</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:55:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367859564955-109</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>Friday's bullish momentum is likely to carry the stock market in the near term, suggesting more near term upside. However, stocks are short term overbought. It won't be surprising to see them consolidate around the record levels for a few sessions. Technically, the indicators of the major indexes are still lagging the price movements and the S&amp;P 500 has gone nearly six months without a 5% correction. I would not chase this rally. With that said, any downside is likely to be limited. consider using options trades, such as put selling, to gain some upside exposure. Now in regards to INTC - with RBC Capital having upgraded INTC and raised its PT to 29 from 24 and the stock hasn't done much indicates we will be seeing a lower entry point. Just be patient.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1367859564955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:59:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367859654796-110</Id><Title>LOL!</Title><Msg>The Intel guy just called big.LITTLE an ABOMINATION!!!! LOL</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367859654796</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367860257898-111</Id><Title>Silvermont vs competition (ARM)</Title><Msg>2.0x The Performance/ 4.3x The lower Power</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367860257898</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:10:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367860594782-112</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont vs competition (ARM)</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367860257898</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unreal, and now ARM won't be able to blow smoke up the butts of OEM's. I mean are we going to see Intel back near all time highs in 2-5 years? Sure seems possible if not 40+ at a MINIMUM.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367860594782</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367860629653-113</Id><Topic><Title>LOL!</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367859654796</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow big little a distaster. man u are cluless and dummer. than what i thought. like i told u there is room for every one in the space. dip #$%$.</Msg><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367860629653</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367861403656-114</Id><Topic><Title>LOL!</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367859654796</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, it is a disaster.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367861403656</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:30:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367861471565-115</Id><Title>ARM is done</Title><Msg>Seriously. Did you guys SEE the performance/watt improvements? Holy cow!</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367861471565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:31:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367861479591-116</Id><Topic><Title>I hope there is a transcript of this presentation</Title><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1367859163194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:52:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have archived the presentation and you can listen again with stop and replay controls.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367861479591</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:31:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367861585233-117</Id><Topic><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1367859564955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:59:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RBC Capital is not a reliable indicator at all for INTC. I wouldn't be so sure.</Msg><Username>davidhughes252</Username><Timestamp>1367861585233</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:33:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367861707135-118</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is done</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367861471565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is that all u got crybaby.disaster is the intel stock price for the last ten years idiot.</Msg><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367861707135</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:35:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367861711133-119</Id><Topic><Title>I hope there is a transcript of this presentation</Title><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1367859163194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:52:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it under investor information or where on their website? Thx.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367861711133</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:35:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367861775956-120</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is done</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367861471565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed. Like I've be saying for a long while now, it's not a question of if, but rather simply a question of when. And I believe 'when' starts now. Cheers, GS</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1367861775956</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:36:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367861778019-121</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is done</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367861471565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's one of the most futile attempts to scare anyone that I've ever seen. "BOO!" would have worked better.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367861778019</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367861915441-122</Id><Topic><Title>Can someone explain the $24 resistance?!</Title><Username>scaredinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1367857593946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:26:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is a "value" stock and you have investors (pension funds, arbitragers, ...) who sell covered calls for extra income. Selling calls or buying puts encourages the option market maker to short Intel. I don't know if this is being done to simply for the extra income or to control the Intel price but when Intel trades in a narrow channel, there seems to be extra option activity and look for 10k contract strike points.. 10k May $24 23k May $25 9k June $25</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367861915441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:38:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367861977396-123</Id><Title>Interesting Read - Link here</Title><Msg>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2013-05-05/the-oil-and-gold-booms-are-over.html</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1367861977396</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:39:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367862028757-124</Id><Topic><Title>Can someone explain the $24 resistance?!</Title><Username>scaredinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1367857593946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:26:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alexander, if I had 20k shares of Intel, for instance, and I planned on holding them for a long time.......are you saying there's a way to guarantee more income than just the Dividend? How risky is it?</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367862028757</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367862133198-125</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>50% more ipc than Saltwell (aka Medfield/Clover Trail) means Apple A6/ARM A15 class ipc. The fused instructions show the advantage of CISC x86 as this is still only a 2-way issue architecture unlike the 3-way opposition. Lower mis-prediction penalty than Saltwell. Double the performance of Saltwell implies 33% more clockspeed i.e. max of 2.7 GHz. All at lower power than A15/A6/S800. Internal FSB also now gone, aids memory latency. Dual-core module can be connected with point to point interconnects (QPI ?) like having a 2-way/4-way server on a chip. Silvermont fits nicely above Clovertrail/Medfield in performance meaning the latter can still be continued to be sold on depreciated 32nm wafers on lower end devices in future. I would say all in all the ARM vendors are in a spot of bother later this year ;-). More details .... anandtechDOTcom/show/6936/intels-silvermont-architecture-revealed-getting-serious-about-mobile</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367862133198</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:42:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367862282424-126</Id><Topic><Title>I hope there is a transcript of this presentation</Title><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1367859163194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:52:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I used the same EVENTS link as the LIVE presentation and it started playing again.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367862282424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367862423268-127</Id><Title>Khitchdee</Title><Msg>Hate it or love it, Intel's on top.......and we're gonna shine, Homie, till our heart stop.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367862423268</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:47:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367862637252-128</Id><Title>Silvermont offers three times the performance and is as much as five times more power- efficient</Title><Msg>Housing Crash Fades as Defaults Fall to 2007 LevelsQ Sharma: The Oil and Gold Booms Are OverQ 2:32 Why the Dow Jones Average Is Actually MeaninglessQ Begum Losing Legs Is Bangladesh Women’s Faustian BargainQ 1:50 Warren Buffett vs. Bill Gross: Who's Winning?Q How Gore Got Romney-Rich With $200M After DefeatQ Housing Crash Fades as Defaults Fall to 2007 LevelsQ Sharma: The Oil and Gold Booms Are OverQ 2:32 Why the Dow Jones Average Is Actually MeaninglessQ Begum Losing Legs Is Bangladesh Women’s Faustian BargainQ 1:50 Warren Buffett vs. Bill Gross: Who's Winning?Q How Gore Got Romney-Rich With $200M After DefeatQ Intel Revamps Atom Chip Design to Outfit Tablets, Small Laptops By Ian King - May 6, 2013 11:35 AM CT Facebook Share Tweet LinkedIn Google +1 0 COMMENTS Print QUEUE Q Intel Corp. (INTC), seeking to harness rising demand for tablets, redesigned one of its marquee chips to better cater to thin and light computing devices by providing more power while using less battery life. The new design for the Atom chip is called Silvermont and Intel has sent samples to customers, Executive Vice President Dadi Perlmutter said at a briefing at the company’s Santa Clara, California, headquarters today. Silvermont offers three times the performance and is as much as five times more power- efficient than its predecessor, he said. The design will also be the basis of chips aimed at everything from mobile phones to low-end servers, Perlmutter said.</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367862637252</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367862821041-129</Id><Topic><Title>// GALE // DRRX // DARA //</Title><Username>acad_at80centswasa_pos</Username><Timestamp>1367856901668</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:15:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC, 23.90</Msg><Username>taroilsands</Username><Timestamp>1367862821041</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:53:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367862958418-130</Id><Title>Just a few more days until the third annual celebration of ...</Title><Msg>Wallis Weaver Day!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! President Barry Obama has declared May 21 Wallis Weaver Day, a national day of remembrance: "In six months those who bought Intel at 24 will look just fine." Wallis Weaver, May 21, 2010</Msg><Username>muxuhmillyanprob</Username><Timestamp>1367862958418</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:55:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367862971263-131</Id><Title>AnandTech; Silvermont delivers 2010 11-inch MacBook Air performance</Title><Msg>"On single threaded performance, you should expect a 2.4GHz Silvermont to perform like a 1.2GHz Penryn. To put it in perspective of actual systems, we’re talking about around the level of performance of an 11-inch Core 2 Duo MacBook Air from 2010. Keep in mind, I’m talking about single threaded performance here. In heavily threaded applications, a quad-core Silvermont should be able to bat even further up the Penryn line. Intel is able to do all of this with only a 2-wide machine (lower IPC, but much higher frequency thanks to 22nm). There’s no doubt in my mind that a Baytrail Android tablet will deliver amazing performance, the real unknown is whether or not a Baytrail Windows 8 detachable/convertible will be fast enough to deliver a good enough legacy Windows experience. I suspect it’ll take Airmont before we really get there by my standards, but it’ll be close this round for sure. What’ll really be interesting to see is how Silvermont fares in smartphones. Max clock speeds should be lower than what’s possible in a tablet, but not by all that much thanks to good power management. When viewed in that light, I don’t know that there’s a more exciting mobile architecture announced at this point. The ability to deliver 2010 11-inch MacBook Air performance in a phone is insane." anandtechDOTcom/show/6936/intels-silvermont-architecture-revealed-getting-serious-about-mobile/6</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1367862971263</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:56:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367862981190-132</Id><Topic><Title>LOL!</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367859654796</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>big.little is a disaster at 28nm because trying to fit four A15 cores in a phone just does not work. Basically what they have done to make this work is overclock the lower performance A7 quad-core up to 1.6 GHz and then under-clocked the higher performance quad-core A15 to 1.2 GHz to take over the work at the high end which is probably equivalent to say having 2.0-2.2 GHz on the quad-core A7. It would have been just more power efficient to have made this just a highly-clocked quad-core A7 in the first place and saved yourself all that leakage on the pointless A15s, Nvidia are doing this with the quad-core 2.3 GHz Tegra4i which uses A9s. This is what happens when you have amateurs (like Samsung) trying to do processor chips, you don't know what you are going to get until it comes out of the oven as they obviously have not thought this through properly beforehand. If you going to use A15 on a phone you should only 1-2 cores although you can do 4 on a tablet.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367862981190</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367863254263-133</Id><Title>Are INTC shares pinned to $24 in honor of ...</Title><Msg>Wallis Weaver Day (May 10th in case you've forgotten).</Msg><Username>muxuhmillyanprob</Username><Timestamp>1367863254263</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367863394315-134</Id><Topic><Title>Are INTC shares pinned to $24 in honor of ...</Title><Username>muxuhmillyanprob</Username><Timestamp>1367863254263</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sour grapes. Poor loser with a zillion aliases chasing an anonymou poster on the internet. The joke is deeply upon you.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367863394315</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367863435270-135</Id><Topic><Title>LOL!</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367859654796</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i guess idiots like you that are intc pumpers can live with the stock. looks like no big deal to investers. stock down. arm up. dip #$%$.</Msg><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367863435270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:03:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367863662224-136</Id><Title>Intel New 64-bit Itanium to change the way big tin gets things done</Title><Msg>DOOOH!</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1367863662224</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:07:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367863750442-137</Id><Topic><Title>AnandTech; Silvermont delivers 2010 11-inch MacBook Air performance</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1367862971263</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:56:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Garbage vaporware.</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1367863750442</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:09:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367863813998-138</Id><Title>Intel PR firm stands to make a fortune this year</Title><Msg>They are going to be busy spinning this trash.</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1367863813998</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:10:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367863967940-139</Id><Topic><Title>Can someone explain the $24 resistance?!</Title><Username>scaredinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1367857593946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:26:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My theory: for the option market maker yes. For real people, no guarantees but .... As an individual investor, it is possible to sell call options for the purpose of increasing income and it is possible to sell put options to get shares at a lower than market price. I would recommend that one understand how options work before deciding to take action and only act if they think it makes sense for them. IMO, I personally do this for 1/2 my position and just hold the other half because I want to have a position. I sell at the money calls for a couple months our and then either roll them out or let them be assigned. If assigned, I sell put options to buy them back at a discount. I have Level 4 option trading status so I don't have to put up cash for the puts I write. The broker places a cash hold on the cash that would be needed to margin the shares is they were put to me. The option market maker has predictable trading patterns and he can be encouraged to trade in a particular way. Big players can encourage him to short or buy Intel share by the option orders they place. I think this is why Intel Beta is so low.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367863967940</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367864319228-140</Id><Topic><Title>LOL!</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367859654796</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'looks like no big deal to investers' It will be within a year when it kills ARM A15 sales stone dead. You can stick a fork in it in, it's done. Silvermont is better performing at lower power. p.s. I knew it would take a pause at $24 until the 50 DMA caught up and said so at $23.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367864319228</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:18:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367864333637-141</Id><Topic><Title>Can someone explain the $24 resistance?!</Title><Username>scaredinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1367857593946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:26:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's all about May 10. Yes, it's WALLIS WEAVER DAY! STILL $24 after THREE YEARS!</Msg><Username>muxuhmillyanprob</Username><Timestamp>1367864333637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:18:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367864375096-142</Id><Title>INTC needs more pumping from vinnie</Title><Msg>Monday run up has just about come and gone and INTC still lags after three strong days in the market.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367864375096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:19:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367864679597-143</Id><Topic><Title>INTC needs more pumping from vinnie</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367864375096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:19:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That moron Vinnie is never right..2 upgrades, Silvermont, endless pumps and the pig reacts like a fart in the wind..Can't hold $23.90..</Msg><Username>pentomic</Username><Timestamp>1367864679597</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:24:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367864761446-144</Id><Topic><Title>LOL!</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367859654796</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. The A7 is clocked at 1.2 and the A15 is clocked at 1.6 (in the International S4) and 1.8 in the Korean version.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367864761446</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367864827044-145</Id><Topic><Title>LOL!</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367859654796</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't it overheat and have</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367864827044</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:27:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367864863411-146</Id><Topic><Title>INTC needs more pumping from vinnie</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367864375096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:19:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you care? Thought you sold. You t^w^a^t^</Msg><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367864863411</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367865151885-147</Id><Title>Sinking....</Title><Msg>or is that stinking? Wall Street blows off INTC and the price already reflects any good news.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367865151885</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:32:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367865306578-148</Id><Title>All the upgrades !!</Title><Msg>and its red !!!! LOL!!!!LOL!!!! to heavy to lift first she needs to go on diet</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1367865306578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:35:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367865346273-149</Id><Topic><Title>I hope there is a transcript of this presentation</Title><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1367859163194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:52:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My article is submitted.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367865346273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:35:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367865467024-150</Id><Topic><Title>All the upgrades !!</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1367865306578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:35:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She's on a diet - A steady diet of eating Sh-t</Msg><Username>pentomic</Username><Timestamp>1367865467024</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:37:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367865637083-151</Id><Topic><Title>Can someone explain the $24 resistance?!</Title><Username>scaredinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1367857593946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:26:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at least he tried to make some money with the armh put, but it seems he hates to take a profit on anything chip related. I was impressed with the timing of the purchase of the ARMH put , disappointed in the failure to take a profit before the breakout.. as for intc, one thing seems certain, Waldo will pump, pump, pump no mater what the price does.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1367865637083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367865697469-152</Id><Title>After the 25% run up in INTC everyone knows its time to take some profits, Don't fall for the upgade pump and dump</Title><Msg>After the 25% run up in INTC everyone knows its time to take some profits, Don't fall for the upgade pump and dump</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367865697469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:41:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367866074581-153</Id><Topic><Title>AnandTech; Silvermont delivers 2010 11-inch MacBook Air performance</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1367862971263</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:56:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Baytrail is delivering Penryn 2010 era Core 2 Duo class performance on single threads there's little question it will run W8 just fine. I have W8 running on a 2006 Kentsfield era Core 2 Quad for testing and it works super. It would be insane to carry around a tablet faster than that. What's remarkable is that that is Intel's low-end offering. Those that want top-of-the-line performance will go for a Haswell tablet.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367866074581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:47:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367866099135-154</Id><Topic><Title>All the upgrades !!</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1367865306578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:35:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>she need some good sh#t medicine She looks bloated</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1367866099135</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:48:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367866257348-155</Id><Topic><Title>I hope there is a transcript of this presentation</Title><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1367859163194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:52:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks! And thanks for the option info. I don't think I'll dive into it as I'd rather do other things than study options. Take care.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367866257348</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:50:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367866263675-156</Id><Topic><Title>AnandTech; Silvermont delivers 2010 11-inch MacBook Air performance</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1367862971263</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:56:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The ability to deliver 2010 11-inch MacBook Air performance in a phone is insane". Are you stupid?</Msg><Username>scaredinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1367866263675</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:51:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367866687882-157</Id><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Msg>ARM is now 40 cents off the high of the day. Looks like word is getting out and even making it through the ARM investor cloud of indifference to reality. It appears that there is some effort being made to keep Intel down. But the news in the pipeline is just too powerful and voluminous. It's gonna break out big time sometime between now and the Haswell release on June 3rd. I'm thinking much sooner rather than later...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367866687882</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:58:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367866949529-158</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367866687882</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:58:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you do realize, the INTC technicals are worse, nah, that would be against the pump, pump, pump INTC agenda</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1367866949529</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:02:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367866996466-159</Id><Title>Where Are AMD’s Z-60 Tablets?</Title><Msg>From Charlie at SemiAccurate Here's an excerpt: "The outlook for AMD’s current tablet offerings, as few and as rare as they may be, is grim. The only light at the end of this tunnel is AMD’s upcoming Temesh SoC which will hopefully get AMD’s power consumption numbers under control and boost their GPU performance up to a reasonable level. But of course Intel isn’t standing still. Since the launch of AMD’s Brazos chip back in late 2010, Intel has completely refreshed its roadmap and put together a very aggressive plan to make Atom into both a viable tablet and phone processor." 2013: Year of the Intel Tablet 2014: Year of the Intel Smartphone</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367866996466</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:03:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367867162593-160</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367866687882</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:58:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"you do realize, the INTC technicals are worse, nah, that would be against the pump, pump, pump INTC agenda" [Intel has a great roadmap, a pipeline full of exciting new products and 14nm FinFET just six months out. ARM has none of those. I don't hear you citing any of ARM's positives. There aren't any. Today's announcements are a perfect example...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367867162593</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:06:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367867392109-161</Id><Title>Intel unveils low-power SoC architecture: Silvermont</Title><Msg>[The press is just starting to arrive. It will be copious...] Intel has some ambitions plans in mind with the introduction of Silvermont, the next generation of the tech giant's microarchitecture platform. The San Jose-based corporation is particularly emphasizing the lower power consumption rates attached to Silvermont. See also: Intel Iris could be a real threat to AMD and Nvidia Intel touts that the 22-nanometer System-on-a-Chip platform offers three times more performance for five times less power than the current Atom core generation. Some of the key enhancements include power sharing between GPUs and SoC IPs along with being able to manage burst frequency based on thermal, electrical, and power delivery constraints. With a multi-core system fabric supporting to eight cores, Intel boasts that this SoC offers more scalability across its range of product and market segments. Specifically, Intel cited intelligent systems, datacenters, Ultrabooks, and mobile devices (both smartphones and tablets). Thus, the chip maker could be hoping to use Silvermont to strengthen its mobile strategy, which has somewhat fallen to the sidelines. Silvermont is scheduled to be the first in a family of cores that will be refreshed every year for the next few years. From ZDNet</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367867392109</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:09:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367867824475-162</Id><Title>Looks like everyone is tired of the INTC good old boy system, Were they hand out free shares to the insiders and all they do is sell them</Title><Msg>Looks like everyone is tired of the INTC good old boy system, Were they hand out free shares to the insiders and all they do is sell them, Stock is down and the insiders are the only ones making money</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367867824475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:17:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367868153653-163</Id><Title>ARMH who?</Title><Msg>People will be asking this time next year</Msg><Username>seriouslynot</Username><Timestamp>1367868153653</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:22:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367868359488-164</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like everyone is tired of the INTC good old boy system, Were they hand out free shares to the insiders and all they do is sell them</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367867824475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel buys back more shares than it hands out to employees so no dilution is taking place, in fact outstanding shares are decreasing. Share compensation is a recognized way of motivating employees and is not harmful to other shareholders if the company buys the shares it dishes out which Intel does with interest. ARM does not buy back its employee shares which is not a problem now in fantasy bubble land but when the stock eventually collapses the extra dilution will hurt everyone then. The realignment with reality will be brutal when it happens, just one dodgy quarterly results and ARMH will lose 10+% overnight with more to follow.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367868359488</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:25:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367868430837-165</Id><Topic><Title>Intel unveils low-power SoC architecture: Silvermont</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367867392109</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:09:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are we down $0.08? If we had been up $0.50 I would have said "disappointment. a mere peut" But this?</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367868430837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:27:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367869465859-166</Id><Topic><Title>Intel unveils low-power SoC architecture: Silvermont</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367867392109</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:09:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice to see the bubblethat was in AMD did not continue through today.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1367869465859</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:44:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367869557953-167</Id><Title>Ashraf, fix your blog</Title><Msg>SA put you into a redirect loop. Browsers won't load it.</Msg><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367869557953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:45:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367869609268-168</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like everyone is tired of the INTC good old boy system, Were they hand out free shares to the insiders and all they do is sell them</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367867824475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then why has the stock not go any were in 13 years?</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367869609268</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:46:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367869744947-169</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH who?</Title><Username>seriouslynot</Username><Timestamp>1367868153653</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:22:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARMH is the new AMD. A competitor of limited resources and fractious self-interference that continually falls behind because it can't keep up in manufacturing efficiency, and design failures just exacerbate that. One thing ARM lacks that AMD has always had: sociopathic CEOs who care more about gaming their compensation packages than delivering growth and dividends to their investors. AMD is over $6 billion in the hole after 40 years in business. It's a loser ditch-digger that has learned to sling mud instead of getting the job done.</Msg><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367869744947</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:49:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367869751187-170</Id><Topic><Title>Ashraf, fix your blog</Title><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367869557953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>worked fine for me.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367869751187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367869913986-171</Id><Title>Light volume.</Title><Msg>Talked up INTC big time this past week, up at the club. Even gave a little speech on silvermont at the "Cognac and Old Clocks" after dinner session. Mayor was there. Rod and Bloy each bought a boatload. I will be the laughing stock for touting this stock. We should have stuck with thoroughbreds and Rolls'.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367869913986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:51:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367869988754-172</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like everyone is tired of the INTC good old boy system, Were they hand out free shares to the insiders and all they do is sell them</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367867824475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Saturated markets. A business designed for technological revolution had to become an obsolete-and-replace business. It survives because it's the best at making the things. And now it will survive because it is the best at repurposing its resources, and it can coordinate its efforts strategically. 20 competing ARM licensees can't do that. They just try to tart-up the latest ARM core, which itself has to be built to fit all their business models.</Msg><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367869988754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:53:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367870134428-173</Id><Topic><Title>Ashraf, fix your blog</Title><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367869557953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>can't post comments, however.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367870134428</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:55:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367870169350-174</Id><Topic><Title>Ashraf, fix your blog</Title><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367869557953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Firefox and Opera didn't load it correctly, but Google Chrome did.</Msg><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1367870169350</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:56:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367870328271-175</Id><Topic><Title>Can someone explain the $24 resistance?!</Title><Username>scaredinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1367857593946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:26:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THREE MORE YEARS!!!! THREE MORE YEARS!!!! May 10, 2010: Wallis Weaver!!!!!!!!!!!!! 24 BUCKEROONIES!!!!!!</Msg><Username>muxuhmillyanprob</Username><Timestamp>1367870328271</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:58:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367870341442-176</Id><Topic><Title>Ashraf, fix your blog</Title><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367869557953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yourbestfriendintheworld, What problem are you experiencing? I'll contact SA to have them look into it. Thanks!</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367870341442</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:59:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367870383915-177</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like everyone is tired of the INTC good old boy system, Were they hand out free shares to the insiders and all they do is sell them</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367867824475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Plus the dumping of INSIDER shares over and over again</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367870383915</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:59:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367870459384-178</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like everyone is tired of the INTC good old boy system, Were they hand out free shares to the insiders and all they do is sell them</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367867824475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's actually been as low as 12 and as high as 33 so that's not exactly nowhere ;-). Money could have made either side of these swings. Once the market clearly sees that Intel's TAM is not just defined by the traditional PC market and revenue/profit start increasing again, it will break free of this previous 33 peak. http://finance.yahoo.com/q/bc?s=INTC&amp;t=my&amp;l=off&amp;z=l&amp;q=l&amp;c=</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367870459384</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:00:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367870573053-179</Id><Topic><Title>Ashraf, fix your blog</Title><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367869557953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Firefox loaded it correctly for me.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367870573053</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:02:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367870631977-180</Id><Topic><Title>Ashraf, fix your blog</Title><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367869557953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i discovered the problem while using Chrome ...but now it loads. i am omnipotent.</Msg><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367870631977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:03:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367870847410-181</Id><Topic><Title>Ashraf, fix your blog</Title><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367869557953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>holy #$%$. a quick skim shows that it says that Intel has chips that are 1.6 times as fast as ARM chips while using 42% as much power. That's a better than 3X improvement in performance/power. And AMD just bet the farm on an ARM future.</Msg><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367870847410</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:07:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367870861775-182</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like everyone is tired of the INTC good old boy system, Were they hand out free shares to the insiders and all they do is sell them</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367867824475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the long run it will not go any were , just like MSFT the insider stock sales pound the stocks back down on any money up, I bet that you can buy MSFT under 28 by OCT</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367870861775</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:07:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367870955215-183</Id><Topic><Title>Ashraf, fix your blog</Title><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367869557953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Worked for me. The PowerPoint slides looked great too. FWIW was using IE10.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367870955215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:09:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367871106540-184</Id><Topic><Title>Ashraf, fix your blog</Title><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367869557953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ybf, I agree. AMD's ARM bet seems misguided. They're cutting R&amp;D, but expanding product offerings? does this even make sense? lol</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367871106540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367871182260-185</Id><Title>Mr Weaver and his multiple personalities pumping Silvermont and INTC is down.</Title><Msg>Once that crazy dude Weaver stops posting, this stock will go up.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1367871182260</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:13:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367871232557-186</Id><Title>Lenovo k900: Rumor has it the 5.5-incher will look to take the whole Asian continent by storm</Title><Msg>Lenovo K900 Goes on Sale in China, P780 with Massive Battery to Follow Soon Adrian Diaconescu | May 6, 2013 | 0 Comments Well, look who’s getting serious about leaving a mark in the global smartphone world! It’s Lenovo, one of the world’s leading PC vendors, a company that until recently seemed like it couldn’t care less about mobile phones. By far Lenovo’s most exciting handheld for some time to come is going to be the IdeaPhone K900, first unveiled back in January and finally up for grabs in China starting today. The K900 is not just an extremely sexy slab of silicon, with a stunning metal chassis and uber-thin profile, but it’s also the zippiest Intel-powered phone to date, so there’s been a lot of media attention focused on it. Available in “The Middle Kingdom” for 3,299 Yuan ($530), the K900 is expected to roll out on a wider scale beginning next week. Rumor has it the 5.5-incher will look to take the whole Asian continent by storm, but unfortunately there’s no official word on a Western launch yet. Why unfortunately? Simple, because Lenovo’s crown jewel has everything it takes to be a serious Galaxy S4, HTC One or LG Optimus G Pro contender. Besides the awesome design and the incredible 6.9 mm thickness, the K900 comes with a Full HD IPS screen, an explosive dual-core 2 GHz Atom CPU, Android 4.2 Jelly Bean, a 13 MP camera and 2 GB of RAM. The 16 GB of on-board storage might not sound too hot, but there’s microSD support, so this thing still allows you more wiggle room than, say, the HTC One. And what can we say about that (Chinese) price other than it makes for an extremely lucrative all-around deal? But besides the K900, Lenovo has a few other aces up its sleeve. Like the P780. Aggressively promoted in China with the help of NBA star Kobe Bryant, this is almost certainly going to be an Asian-exclusive device. Which is a terrible shame, even though the P780 is no powerhouse. Still officially undetailed, the phone looks like a mid-ranger on paper fro</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367871232557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:13:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367871419264-187</Id><Title>What happened to...</Title><Msg>vinnie_bag_of_dogs_nuts? Haven't heard from you since the Silvermont announcement.</Msg><Username>intoodeep99</Username><Timestamp>1367871419264</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:16:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367871706985-188</Id><Topic><Title>What happened to...</Title><Username>intoodeep99</Username><Timestamp>1367871419264</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:16:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats one of Mr Weaver's other personalities.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1367871706985</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:21:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367871916888-189</Id><Title>James Covello / Romit Shah are awfully quiet</Title><Msg>unreal</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367871916888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:25:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367872061034-190</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo k900: Rumor has it the 5.5-incher will look to take the whole Asian continent by storm</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367871232557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:13:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The K900 is currently being advertised on the front page of the China region Lenovo webpage.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367872061034</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367873001354-191</Id><Topic><Title>James Covello / Romit Shah are awfully quiet</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367871916888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:25:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they still have a sell rating. price target still @ 18</Msg><Username>philip_914</Username><Timestamp>1367873001354</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:43:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367873685293-192</Id><Topic><Title>James Covello / Romit Shah are awfully quiet</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367871916888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:25:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both have commented negatively about any public Intel news. They would reiterate their rating before and then afterward would say "no change" after Intel news. Neither of them issued a statement since January. For them, just keeping quiet is a big change.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367873685293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:54:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367873878915-193</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like everyone is tired of the INTC good old boy system, Were they hand out free shares to the insiders and all they do is sell them</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367867824475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel pays its employees in stock options. Insider selling means nothing.</Msg><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367873878915</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:57:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367874351209-194</Id><Topic><Title>Ashraf, fix your blog</Title><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367869557953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD rarely makes sense. It has the foresight and memory of a goldfish. It got into gaming consoles right when gaming consoles started losing their grip on performance superiority and market dominance. It got into ARM because it had nowhere else to go after x86 imploded, but it's pretty clear they didn't see _this_ coming. Neither did I. I bought my ARMH shares exactly 6 months ago, and closed them out today for about a 40% gain. Once Intel has you outgunned, it's time to hang 'em up. I doubled up on an AMD Put position. Time to look carefully at adding INTC.</Msg><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367874351209</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 17:05:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367874974351-195</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like everyone is tired of the INTC good old boy system, Were they hand out free shares to the insiders and all they do is sell them</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367867824475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM insiders dumped heavily at $38-40; heads of CPU and GPU division disposed of the entirety of their stakes. Intel's chief product officer holds 400k shares of Intel. He exercises options but rarely sells. Hmm..</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367874974351</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 17:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367876364412-196</Id><Topic><Title>Light volume.</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367869913986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's alright, old #$%$. You can sell out in the morning and move to the Canaries. And don't worry about your reputation. Nobody talks about what's forgotten.</Msg><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367876364412</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 17:39:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367877198168-197</Id><Topic><Title>Light volume.</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367869913986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huh?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367877198168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 17:53:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367878550173-198</Id><Title>Intel News Starting to Ramp Up</Title><Msg>Intel's new mobile chip to boast up to 8 processor cores CNET That said, the typical tablet using the "Bay Trail" chip -- the version of Silvermont aimed at tablets and hybrids -- will likely use two or four cores. One of the key changes to Atom is a higher-performance out-of-order design, just like Intel's ... Intel's new Atom chips peak on performance, power consumption ARNnet Intel expects the new architecture, code-named Silvermont, to be in smartphones, tablets, PCs and servers starting this year. Atom chips code-named Bay Trail will appear in tablets this holiday season. They will support the Android and Microsoft ... Intel unveils low-power Silvermont chip design for 'teraflops to milliwatts' VentureBeat Perlmutter said Intel's mission is to create chips from “teraflops to milliwatts,” meaning from supercomputing performance levels to the most power-efficient devices. Early samples of new chips, code-named Bay Trail and Avoton, are generating good ... Intel revamps Atom chips Reuters Silvermont will be the basis for Intel's 22-nanometer Bay Trail tablet chips due out later this year and Intel says it will more than double the performance of its current tablet chips. It will also be used in Intel's upcoming Merrifield smartphone ... Intel Details Atom "Silvermont" Architecture Maximum PC "Early sampling of our 22nm SoCs, including 'Bay Trail' and 'Avoton' is already garnering positive feedback from our customers. Going forward, we will accelerate future generations of this low-power microarchitecture on a yearly cadence." This is the ... Mac Pro Could adopt Intel's Newly Announced 22nm Xeon Patently Apple Earlier today, Intel announced a number of new systems coming to market later this year. They touched on Silvermont, Bay Trail, Haswell and Xeon processors shifting to 22nm technology. The latter will provide Apple's Mac Pro users with a nice power ...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367878550173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 18:15:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367878857308-199</Id><Title>Ashraf: Intel Drops An Atomic Bomb On ARM's 'Abomination'</Title><Msg>Excerpt: ARM's soon-to-be-retired CEO had a tendency to go on about how Intel would never be a leader in power efficiency. This may still be true in the micro-controller space where Cortex M-series chips reign, but it's certainly not true in the phone space and above. Intel's engineer at the presentation boldly referred to "big.LITTLE" as an "abomination" and pointed out that not only could Intel's Silvermont reach higher performance levels at lower power consumption, but Intel could also scale down to lower power levels at the lower performance levels: All of this also comes without the need to have extra, wasteful cores on the die, or complex software routines to switch between the "big" and the "LITTLE" cores. This is elegance incarnate, and it is clear that both Intel and Qualcomm -- the big dogs in this space -- don't buy into "big.LITTLE" style designs for very good reason. It's a hack. ARM apparently severely underestimated Intel, and it is likely that a lot of the "hype" that ARM was magical and insurmountable in the low power processor space will fade to black as Silvermont shines brightly during the second half of 2013. It will be interesting to see how ARM's share price reacts to this potentially huge shift in the low power landscape. [LOL. Check out the entire article...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367878857308</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 18:20:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367879801874-200</Id><Title>So after losing the power consuption race, what else does ARMH have?</Title><Msg>Exactly, Nothing They are done and done</Msg><Username>seriouslynot</Username><Timestamp>1367879801874</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 18:36:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367882338216-201</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like everyone is tired of the INTC good old boy system, Were they hand out free shares to the insiders and all they do is sell them</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367867824475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then, they weren't very bright were they given the move to new heights above 48.00? will your QLGC get another bounce given it's fall from the heights back down to earth, the flip side of an overbght stock, once was, now not. and seems you have way too many chip related stocks, tsk, tsk.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1367882338216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 19:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367883146261-202</Id><Topic><Title>So after losing the power consuption race, what else does ARMH have?</Title><Username>seriouslynot</Username><Timestamp>1367879801874</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 18:36:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, they may still have Intel. Intel is ARM's biggest licensee. Intel doesn't make ARM cores, but it does use ARM low-power tech. What it's proved with Silvermont is that it does it better than any ARM-core maker, and delivers it with a core that kicks ARM to the curb. So ARM will be able to sit back and collect fat royalties from Intel. But all of the ARM chip makers are going to find themselves losing business to Intel's new products. So ARM's other sources of royalties are going to dry up. Leaving them with little other than the royalties from Intel. ARM's revenues are headed down, due to this. That's why I sold my ARMH as soon as I got the clue. I may start shorting ARMH once the market shows some cognizance. Not yet, though. The market can be slow to grok technological tectonics, and I want to stay out of the way of accidental overshoot.</Msg><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367883146261</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 19:32:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367883875196-203</Id><Title>Intel's baseband inside Galaxy S4 (Exynos Octa)</Title><Msg>EETimes eetimesDOTcom/design/power-management-design/4412874/Teardown--Samsung-Galaxy-S4 Teardown: Samsung Galaxy S4 Allan Yogasingam 4/26/2013 2:35 PM EDT "When we open the I9500 model, the most surprising discovery is that of Intel’s mobile communication components earning design wins for the baseband and corresponding transceiver. This Galaxy S4 uses Intel’s PMB9820 baseband processor, which we surmise is from their X-GOLD 636 reference design. This baseband is optimized for EDGE, WCDMA and HSDPA/HSUPA bands. The transceiver IC is the PMB5745, which we believe is their SMARTi UE3 RF transceiver. This is the first major design win we’ve seen for Intel since they lost their lucrative sockets in the Apple iPhone to Qualcomm. However, it should be noted that the Qualcomm does have the design wins in the GT-I9505 model, which will be readily available in the US and Canada."</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1367883875196</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 19:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367886122496-204</Id><Topic><Title>So after losing the power consuption race, what else does ARMH have?</Title><Username>seriouslynot</Username><Timestamp>1367879801874</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 18:36:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YBF, Intel is indeed a big ARM licensee, but the technology in the new Atom is *not* ARM based in the slightest - it's all home grown, 0% license fees to ARM tech. Where Intel uses ARM tech is actually in the modem, where some of the VERY cheap low power cores are used for very dumb tasks (i.e not even the heart of the modem). Every chip sale that Intel takes from Qualcomm, Nvidia, MediaTek, etc. is a royalty completely drying up for ARM. That's why while people think ARM has this "perfect" business model, it is really highly dependent on nobody gaining share in the high value smartphone/tab space (~10% of the unit volume for ARM, with 35% of the revenue). With Intel in this race, not just in phones/tabs but in routers/switches with the "Rangeley" SoC, ARM's royalties do indeed slow. The only saving grace is that the super low power stuff - i.e. not computing, just dumb microcontrollers from the likes of Atmel, etc. - is moving more towards ARM. Hope this helps.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367886122496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 20:22:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367891132620-205</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo k900: Rumor has it the 5.5-incher will look to take the whole Asian continent by storm</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367871232557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:13:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It sure is! Man, that phone is the best looking one I've ever seen. Isn't that Kobe Bryant holding the phone? lenovoDOTcom, click on China region.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367891132620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367891179974-206</Id><Title>Anyone..has splained why its down?</Title><Msg>Ashrraff? The Beaver? Why down? You guys have hyped..and I mean HYPED this thing. So why down?</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367891179974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:46:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367891363283-207</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone..has splained why its down?</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367891179974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:46:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're such a loser. Wasn't that you at Target today, looking all Flumoxed in the tampon section?</Msg><Username>galba_tamponerator</Username><Timestamp>1367891363283</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:49:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367891786950-208</Id><Title>INTC is up over 25% its time to take some profits, Before there gone again</Title><Msg>INTC is up over 25% its time to take some profits, Before there gone again</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367891786950</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:56:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367891970574-209</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is up over 25% its time to take some profits, Before there gone again</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367891786950</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:56:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do so at your own peril.</Msg><Username>kip_castle</Username><Timestamp>1367891970574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:59:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367891977977-210</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo k900: Rumor has it the 5.5-incher will look to take the whole Asian continent by storm</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367871232557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:13:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Chinese love Kobe Bryant. This phone is going to sell like crazy.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367891977977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:59:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367892076915-211</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is up over 25% its time to take some profits, Before there gone again</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367891786950</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:56:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly kip. Intel is way undervalued right now. You would be crazy to sell or short at this price. Wait until $40.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367892076915</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 22:01:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367892801699-212</Id><Title>HARDWARE MAKERS HAVE CHOICE BUT TO USE INTEL INSIDE</Title><Msg>from Ashraf's article: "Intel's dual core Silvermont-based chips apparently lay waste to the competition's quad core processors in smartphone power envelopes (1W). At the same performance, Intel uses on average 2.4x less power, and at the same power, two Silvermont cores are 1.6x the speed of the competition. This is not something that can be understated. This is much more dramatic of an advantage -- if true -- than Intel had on Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) when it finally put an end to AMD's leadership in the PC market. In tablets, the picture looks even better for Intel and worse for the ARM guys, with Intel's quad core beauties either giving twice the performance at the same power level or 4.3x less power at the same performance"</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367892801699</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 22:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367893759224-213</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone..has splained why its down?</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367891179974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:46:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Warum ist die Banane krumm?" It translates as "Why are bananas bent" or, literally "Why is the banana bent?" t's usually a counterquestion to a rhetorical or otherwise unanswerable question. The approximate meaning is "There is no answer - why did you ask?"</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367893759224</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 22:29:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367894001626-214</Id><Topic><Title>So after losing the power consuption race, what else does ARMH have?</Title><Username>seriouslynot</Username><Timestamp>1367879801874</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 18:36:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's even better. ARM is screwed and I am out of ARMH entirely.</Msg><Username>yourbestfriendintheworld</Username><Timestamp>1367894001626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 22:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367894016399-215</Id><Title>Other than Samsung's Exynos, there are no A15 chips around. Tegra4 got</Title><Msg>delayed.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1367894016399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 22:33:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367894239023-216</Id><Title>THE STREET DOESN'T GET IT YET!</Title><Msg>I have to say I don't think Dadi did a very good job of delivering the message today. ANALysts have ADHD, I doubt they were able to pay attention to whole presentation. It will take a day or two for the data to sink in.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367894239023</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 22:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367895514572-217</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Technical details of Silvermont realworldtechDOTcom/silvermont/ p.s. Only 200K Surfaces sold in 2013Q1 ! dailytechDOTcom/Amid+Abysmal+Sales+ARM+Chipmaker+Qualcomm+Has+Windows+RTs+Back/article31487.htm</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367895514572</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 22:58:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367895870884-218</Id><Topic><Title>THE STREET DOESN'T GET IT YET!</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367894239023</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 22:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His English could do with working on as he was not easily heard or understood. The Chief Architect was clearer though and gave all the answers I wanted to hear. The detailed articles by Anandtech/RWT filled in the details. Silvermont was actually better than I thought, I was expecting 30-40% better ipc which is the usual OoO advantage but they worked efficiently on the design too. It's also lower power than I thought it would be. It's going to create a new premium mobile experience that customers are just not used to, could be seismic ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367895870884</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 23:04:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367896212081-219</Id><Topic><Title>Other than Samsung's Exynos, there are no A15 chips around. Tegra4 got</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1367894016399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 22:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TI's mobile head honcho now at NVDA ... did TI find a buyer for their OMAP A15? Renesas still for sale (another A15 contender) .... Mediatek betting big time putting A15 into phones....</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367896212081</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 23:10:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367898213233-220</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Silvermont Analysis Intel claims that the core and system level microarchitectural improvements will yield 50% higher IPC for Silvermont versus the previous generation. Comparing the two microarchitectures in Figure 7, that is a highly plausible claim as out-of-order scheduling alone should be worth 30% and perhaps 5-10% for better branch prediction. Additionally, the 22nm process technology has reduced Vmin by around 100mV, and increased clock frequencies by roughly 20-30%. In total, this paints a very attractive picture for Silvermont. In the more abstract realm of CPU to CPU comparisons, Intel indicated that Silvermont is a much faster design than the Cortex A7 or the A15 at any given power level; the goal is to avoid any complicated and high latency software-driven power management and rely on firmware-based management and power gating. As a design point, this is a good choice and follows in the steps of Apple’s Swift or Qualcomm’s Krait, which are undeniably successful CPU cores. Even if Intel’s projections are modestly optimistic, Silvermont should conclusively dispel the myth that the x86 instruction set is a barrier to power efficient microarchitecture. If Intel’s claims hold true, the Silvermont microarchitecture might be even more efficient than some ARM cores when normalized for Intel’s advantage in process technology. That seems an unlikely and counter-intuitive outcome, but could be explained by Intel’s larger teams and superb physical design. Products based on Silvermont will launch in the latter half of 2013. Ironically, Merrifield will probably be the first 64-bit smartphone SoC, a milestone for a company that has traditionally lagged in this area. Merrifield should be very competitive for Android phones; if Intel also delivers a discrete LTE modem, it will inject competition into a market where Qualcomm has been unchallenged for quite some time. 3</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367898213233</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 23:43:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367898341970-221</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel’s progress in tablets will accelerate with updated CPU cores, graphics, and SoC fabric. Windows tablets will be a particularly strong point, since Valleyview uses a variant of the Ivy Bridge GPU which is far better from a DirectX and OpenGL standpoint than pretty much every alternative. The Avoton server chip is already sampling to OEMs and should also be quite interesting. In conclusion, the 22nm Silvermont CPU is a tremendous step forward, particularly in mobile devices. It is a thoroughly modern microarchitecture that is both higher performance and more efficient than the previous Saltwell core. The new core and updated SoC fabric and should put Intel on an even technical footing with mobile competitors such as Qualcomm, Nvidia, and Samsung, and perhaps even grant a significant advantage. Before the year is out, real performance and power measurements that demonstrate the impact of Silvermont will be available.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367898341970</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 23:45:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367898848125-222</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Silvermont should be banned ... on the grounds of something that good just has to be illegal !! LOL</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367898848125</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 23:54:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>