<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-09"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368072133651-1</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's next generation A7 processor to be produced by Intel?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368065033282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:03:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you imagine if this news drops in the next week? I can see the stock broker on the phone with his client "I'm telling you, ARMH is going through the roof. It's picking up steam over $50 a share and going to $100 by the end of the month." Then the news hits, and ARMH drops $15 a share in seconds. "I'll have to call you back."</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1368072133651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 00:02:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368072480601-2</Id><Title>Still More to Come</Title><Msg>May 6: Intel to announce Silvermont - Buzz should last all year May 6: Lenovo K900 release in China *** May 10: Lenovo K900 in India May 15-17; Google I/O Developers Conference - Buzz depends on announcements. Good potential. May 16: Intel's Annual Stockholder Meeting May 22-24: Tizen Developer Conference June 3: Intel to release Haswell - Buzz should last all year June 4: Computex - Buzz depends on announcements. Good potential June 10-14: Apple's WWDC - Macs about to get a major upgrade thanks to Intel’s (NASDAQ:INTC) new “Iris” graphics processors? June 26-28: Microsoft's Build Developer Conference - Rumors of next Surface Pro announcement 2013: Year of the Intel Tablet 2014: Year of the Intel Smartphone</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368072480601</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 00:08:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368072671864-3</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget about Tizen</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368068372699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:59:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What Intel really needs to do is figure a way to develop its own version of Unix. One that is optimized for X86. One that gains acceptance in the corporate world and would scare Microsoft back into the reality of not forcing new product introductions like Windows 8 down everybody's throats. They screw up and we had to suffer?</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1368072671864</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 00:11:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368073912531-4</Id><Topic><Title>Requirements to be an ARM Investor</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368063548961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:39:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My dad worked for this company back in the 90s that sold rack space for radios on mountain tops. Their main customers were police, fire, and pagers. One day the owner woke up and realized that pagers were on the way out, so he quickly sold the company for fat profits to a Boston investment group. Their stock was worth pennies when my dad left. He left in the 90's and, well, can you even buy a pager plan today? They have empty racks on mountains all over the country. The stock closed today at $82 a share! I feel like asking the average investor if they know anything about this company. They probably know only what's on the website. Twenty years from now ARMH can be worth $100 a share. They will have fancy statistics "we sold over 20 trillion processors" and can give a song and dance about all the tens of thousands of design wins they have. Suckers will never stop buying this stock. And of course they will always tout the secret "Intel killer" processor which is coming out in a couple of years. . What i am saying is that story you hear today will be the story you hear 20 years from now, regardless how many times it's proven false.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1368073912531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 00:31:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368074310640-5</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's next generation A7 processor to be produced by Intel?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368065033282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:03:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>intel_fanboy, You seem like a level-headed, smart individual. Please post here more.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368074310640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 00:38:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368074355216-6</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's next generation A7 processor to be produced by Intel?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368065033282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:03:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bacbacker, Unlikely. While Intel would be more than happy to get all of the iOS apps to work on X86 (not as hard as you'd think, actually), it seems like it would cost too much and be too risky this round.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368074355216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 00:39:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368074465058-7</Id><Topic><Title>Still More to Come</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368072480601</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 00:08:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2013: Year of the Intel Tablet. You got that right! Already up to a great start with 3 million Windows 8 OS sales with 90% being Intel based. This will only build quarter after quarter with a huge boost in Q4 Holiday sales thanks to Baytrail availability. 2014: Year of the Intel SMARTphone. Currently, the only selling point left for Qualcomm is the LTE capability. Intel will have huge announcements geared towards Intel LTE smartphone during 2014 MWC, leaving Qualcomm and other smartphone chip makers with no competitive advantage at all. In fact, Intel's great performance and battery efficiency will leave all competitors in the dust. It will be all up to the phone makers if they want the best in class chips by Intel to allow for some advanced capabilities and cool features or settle for slightly cheaper scrappy chips based on ARM architecture. So it seems that 2014 indeed will be the year of the Intel smartphone.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1368074465058</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 00:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368081101308-8</Id><Topic><Title>Khitchdee, your days are numbered. Getanid61 and Warren East slid out the back door</Title><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368064879431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:01:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anandtech lost its creed as an unbiased evaluator. Nothing stopping Intel from stumble. Slow decay next decade</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1368081101308</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 02:31:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368087725163-9</Id><Topic><Title>Requirements to be an ARM Investor</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368063548961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:39:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent story. Mind sharing the name of the company? The simple fact is that stock prices don't satisfy the laws of physics.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368087725163</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 04:22:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368097655763-10</Id><Title>When it comes to bribes and monopolistic behavior Intel is #1</Title><Msg>Too bad for them the world moved right past their fraud. Even Paul knows the gig is up. Intel is nothing but a hedge fund at this point.</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1368097655763</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 07:07:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368098969734-11</Id><Topic><Title>ashraf the idiot</Title><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367931417750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My pals amcc are getting ready to a make there move idiot but again your to stupid, to realize it second half of the year thats were we start eating intels lunch. Keep shorting amcc.due your job which is pumping intel. Look at arm you missed the boat. Idiot</Msg><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1368098969734</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 07:29:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368099140257-12</Id><Topic><Title>Khitchdee, your days are numbered. Getanid61 and Warren East slid out the back door</Title><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368064879431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:01:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Slow decay next decade" ________________ khitchdee • Jan 30, 2013 11:09 PM Flag Don't worry, once the 14nm low power ramp happens towards the end of 2014 on Intel's accelerated schedule, it will light a fire under Apple and Samsung and force them to consider a switch to Intel chips. That should boost the stock price and in a few years, all the extra fab capacity that Intel has commisioned will start getting used to build smartphone chips, and the revenue will corresponding go up to far exceed Qualcomm</Msg><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368099140257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 07:32:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368101759818-13</Id><Topic><Title>The Truth about ARM</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368023974537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'm old? and you'll not be around here if you EVER get married and you were 61 when you said that. That was 2 years ago or so. OLD GOAT ! grumpy? no. I just speak the truth about INTC and you blow about how great it is when it is = to a CD a few years back. "$3 eps" - another WW dream. Rather they are shrinking or there would be an addition to these real soon. 40% of $3 would be $1.20 and a 30 cent div. So much for a yearly increase. 5/11/11 dividend raised .1812 to .21 5/7/12 dividend raised .21 to .225</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1368101759818</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 08:15:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368102176822-14</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the world does Intel have Fabs in Israel?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367793421451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:37:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel Israel also BTW designs some of the best processors and wifi solutions on this planet. Design teams in Oregon and Israel contribute each new processor generation in a ping pong pipeline. Where do you think Centrino came from, New Jersey? Haswell is an Oregon design, the next one will come from Israel.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1368102176822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 08:22:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368102330276-15</Id><Title>Lenovo K900 India launch delayed</Title><Msg>Lenovo K900 India launch has been pushed back to later this month, likely to May 20, NDTV Gadgets has learnt from its sources. We had earlier reported that the phablet was set to launch in India on May 10, but there have been fresh developments since.</Msg><Username>jnsnyu88</Username><Timestamp>1368102330276</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 08:25:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368103388742-16</Id><Title>100s of design wins</Title><Msg>What do Samsung, Apple, ZTE, Lenovo and Motorola have in common? They all make mobile phones. Through some surreptitious manoeuvring, Apple and Samsung hog a 100% of the profit in the market. I guess that leaves hundreds of design wins for Intel's game changing Silvermont from people not making profit. Wait, I forgot there's also the whole PC makers bandwagon that is going to make Windows tablets using this never before seen innovation.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1368103388742</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 08:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368104231754-17</Id><Title>ARM is Doomed</Title><Msg>There have been opinions offered today that ARM might somehow float above the fray with excessive valuations just about forever. It's not true. Here's why: The market always adjusts to economics. Always, always, always. Sure, the market can be incredibly stupid and it can take a long time. The phrase is that the market can stay stupid longer than you can stay solvent. So, one has to be careful. But it always happens and it will with ARM. Bottom line is that it's always about the bottom line. ARM has two very fundamental flaws in its economics that will lead to its doom. One: Fabrication. ARM's fabrication roapmap is exceeding flawed. It doesn't have FinFET and won't for years and years. This precludes it being competitive on an ongoing basis. Intel will go two process nodes up at the end of this year. Lack of competitiveness will erode profits and lead to a collapse of the stock price. Nothing ARM can do about it. Not enough time, money and technology to fix the fabrication problem. Two: The Fabless Model. This is the reason that the number of ARM foundries has dropped continuously and there are only a couple left. The fabless model doesn't provide technology (like FinFET) or money to build enough capacity. Lack of competitiveness will erode profits and lead to a collapse of the stock price. Nothing ARM can do about it. Not enough time, money and technology to fix the fabless model problem. There you have it. ARM is doomed. Two fundamental reasons why profit erosion will lead to collapse of the stock price. No question of if, just a question of when. So, watch the market stay stupid. But don't depend on it to last forever. It won't...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368104231754</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 08:57:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368104410958-18</Id><Topic><Title>The Truth about ARM</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368023974537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sorry I misspoke. You're old, tired, grumpy, grouchy AND confused...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368104410958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:00:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368104523626-19</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is Doomed</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368104231754</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 08:57:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel/ARM Roadmap Comparison ARM/Intel Roadmap Comparison Intel (All FinFET): 22nm: Haswell June 2013 14nm: Broadwell: End of 2013/Start of 2014 14nm: Skylake: 2015 10nm: Skymont: 2016 7nm: 2018 5nm: 2020 ARMH Planar 28nm: Production has been increasing but is still insufficient to meet market demand. Substantially all of the production is coming from TSMC, which is a significant bottleneck. 20nm: Volume production in 2014/2015. TSMC has promised to ramp 20nm faster than 28nm but this appears to be nothing more than rhetoric as 20nm will be yet another level of complexity when trends have show each successive ARM die shrink to ramp significantly slower than the previous. FinFET 14/16nm: ARM foundries will pursue a half-step to FinFET by making it half FinFET and half 20nm. This clearly illustrates their lack of confidence in bringing a full step online in a reasonable time frame. There are so many unknowns with the half-step process, that any prediction of volume production cannot be reliably made. Conclusions 1.) Intel will continue to have significant opportunities for high margin foundry work, as illustrated by the Altera deal. 2.) Intel's fabrication economics will continue to improve just as ARM's are degrading. ARMs 20nm planar and the half-step to FinFET both have inferior economics to the Intel nodes. 3.) Intel will reach 450mm wafer implementation well ahead of ARM, giving them significantly improved economic benefits. Intel's lead in fabrication and manufacturing is increasing in virtually every area.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368104523626</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:02:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368104729305-20</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is Doomed</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368104231754</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 08:57:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's just plain sad to watch you work around the clock to bash a stock that's gone up 100 percent since you started talking of it's demise. It's the most bizzarre and pathetic thing any message board has ever seen. Congrats, you made history.</Msg><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368104729305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:05:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368104801911-21</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is Doomed</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368104231754</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 08:57:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need rehab worse than Lindsay Lohan.</Msg><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368104801911</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:06:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368105099691-22</Id><Topic><Title>100s of design wins</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1368103388742</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 08:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love it!! In your world there is only Apple and Samsung. Motorola doesn't exist. All those little Asian jobbers that contract manufacture consumer electronics don't exist. You never for the life of you even acknowledge the phone carriers themselves. Intel can go to a T-Mobile and say "Hey, the iPhone is costing you $400 each, and the Samsung products range in the $300 to $500 range. How about this, we're going to make a private label phone for you from some small Asia contract manufacture and sell them to you at $175 each. Not only that but we have advertising money, just mention it's Intel powered and half your ad is paid for. " Of course in your world they will say "Oh no, consumers will never buy this. We can't tell our tens of thousands of salespeople to show this phone instead of the iPhone or Samsung Phones. That's all consumer know and will ever want." Yes, hundreds of design wins. Arm tried to move into Intel's world and didn't do so well. If you read the book "Inside Intel" you'll see exactly how aggressive Intel is when they move into a market. Intel is in the market to win market share, even without your permission.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1368105099691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:11:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368105195417-23</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is Doomed</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368104231754</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 08:57:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally is doomed to the land of mediocrity that matches his trading/investment sklls.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1368105195417</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:13:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368105305253-24</Id><Title>EXACTLY one year ago today, ARM was at 24 and Wally said it was finished</Title><Msg>It's up OVER 100 percent since then. Will Wally pay all the old ladies back that took his investment advice? You can't make up the insanity that consumes Wallisweaver. __________ wallisweaver•May 9, 2012 11:03 AMFlag Let me interpret this for anyone who doesn't pay a lot of attention to fabrication: The fabrication war is over. Intel has won and ARM has lost. Intel is the only company on the planet that can produce smaller die sizes at a profit. The economic implications of this are huge. This should be today's news and market mover instead of all this stupidity over Greece. And sooner or later it will. Definitely by earnings... Less</Msg><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368105305253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:15:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368105437453-25</Id><Topic><Title>100s of design wins</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1368103388742</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 08:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kitchdee bashes Intel when he's short and praises it when he's Long. He dances around the fire singing Hymns from the Devil, who he sold his soul to in the name of money.</Msg><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368105437453</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368106146518-26</Id><Topic><Title>EXACTLY one year ago today, ARM was at 24 and Wally said it was finished</Title><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368105305253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:15:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and INTC was higher then than it is now, working it's way down to 19.00 with Wally riding the merry go round</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1368106146518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:29:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368106148641-27</Id><Topic><Title>The Truth about ARM</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368023974537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Will try and nail this intra-quarter's peak and I think we could be close now at just under 50." 49.99 could be it but need confirmation in the days to come.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368106148641</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:29:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368106193329-28</Id><Topic><Title>EXACTLY one year ago today, ARM was at 24 and Wally said it was finished</Title><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368105305253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:15:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His arguments were, and still are sound in my view. But, as someone else pointed out recently, the market is not rational. I believe the market will ultimately get the "a ha" sooner or later, more likely later because there are borderline criminal, manipulative analysts looking to squeeze every penny out of keeping Intel down, and keeping ARMH up. The sea change in mobile uArchitecture is coming though, and once a few of the big name mobile players switch over to x86 the jig will be up for the current status quo. Patience,....</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1368106193329</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:29:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368106319653-29</Id><Topic><Title>EXACTLY one year ago today, ARM was at 24 and Wally said it was finished</Title><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368105305253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:15:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Patience. Oh, ok. You're supposed to take 103% losses and then be patient for future "gains." LMAO. I bet 96% of the posters here are strapped down to a permanent bed.</Msg><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368106319653</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368106729959-30</Id><Title>Next Up</Title><Msg>Haswell ARM is doomed...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368106729959</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:38:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368106905670-31</Id><Topic><Title>EXACTLY one year ago today, ARM was at 24 and Wally said it was finished</Title><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368105305253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:15:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe the problem that you are having is that you are attempting to be successful at day trading INTC and/or ARMH. In this case maybe you should take your investment money and head to a casino instead. Same investment strategy and you have a better shot at winning because casinos are currently better regulated than WS.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1368106905670</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:41:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368106934897-32</Id><Topic><Title>Next Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368106729959</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The worst poster on any message board always posts in the highest volume. You prove this very true.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1368106934897</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368107079654-33</Id><Topic><Title>EXACTLY one year ago today, ARM was at 24 and Wally said it was finished</Title><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368105305253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:15:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't daytrader. Only idiots (many on this board) do that. I'm very happy with my longterm long position in Intel and countless quarters of Dividends. But why do know-nothings have to run their mouths on these boards? I mean the guy's been wrong by over 100 percent and posts MULTIPLE threads per DAY about ARM as if he's some authoritarian. Are you telling me that's not insanity defined?</Msg><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368107079654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:44:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368107292545-34</Id><Topic><Title>EXACTLY one year ago today, ARM was at 24 and Wally said it was finished</Title><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368105305253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:15:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's clearly insane and would like nothing more than to take you with him. The choice is your...analyze him and go insane with him, or laugh in his face.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1368107292545</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:48:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368107484499-35</Id><Topic><Title>EXACTLY one year ago today, ARM was at 24 and Wally said it was finished</Title><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368105305253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:15:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally is one of the biggest idiots I have ever heard pumpin and pimpin and schillin. Remember when he use to cry to the SEC ? What a little crybaby. Obviously a mommas boy.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1368107484499</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:51:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368108123697-36</Id><Topic><Title>Next Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368106729959</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not sure what you mean by "doomed". I am pretty sure that there will always be some application where an ARM CPU makes sense and there is no merchant product that makes sense. I am pretty sure that ARMH as a company will be around for quite awhile too. Will the stock continue to behave like it has over the last couple months? No. The ARMH chart looks like a wonderful mirror image of the 2000 bubble. ARMH is a small company with 450m shares outstanding and a very small available float. Now there is a company where the insiders have sold!!! no liquidated their holdings. "DOOMED"? Company ... no Some late investors? They might not do as well as they expected.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368108123697</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:02:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368108146041-37</Id><Title>FOLKS, THIS THING IS GOING TO $40 THIS YEAR</Title><Msg>BUY NOW!!!!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368108146041</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368108206978-38</Id><Title>IT'S GOING TO FLY TODAY, MAYBE $25</Title><Msg>The word is getting around about silvermont. $40 by end of year</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368108206978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368108486367-39</Id><Title>Warning coming...</Title><Msg>then this pig drops.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368108486367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368108724278-40</Id><Topic><Title>EXACTLY one year ago today, ARM was at 24 and Wally said it was finished</Title><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368105305253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:15:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My apologies for accusing you of being a day trader. I am long also. There will be a shift over to x86, still firmly believe in that, (for many of the reasons that Mr. Weaver has stated). I also believe that the inflection point for this shift will be this year.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1368108724278</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:12:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368108814955-41</Id><Topic><Title>Next Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368106729959</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He says doomed because he is a stock basher that likes to wreak havoc......he's the mirror image of those that he detests. Sad that he is such a chump.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1368108814955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368108960808-42</Id><Topic><Title>Warning coming...</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368108486367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:08:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHY WOULD INTC WARN when they are about to have a record-breaking year dumbo?</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368108960808</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:16:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368109193681-43</Id><Title>Gud Morn Slackers</Title><Msg>hope yall have a fun day.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368109193681</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:19:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368109244878-44</Id><Title>Citi Research's Glen Yeung: Silvermont Better than ARM A15</Title><Msg>Citi Research's Glen Yeung: Better than ARM? "We suspect that Intel's Silvermont [micro-architecture] will provide better performance metrics than even ARM's vaunted Cortex A15...Expected to appear in tablets in [the second half 2013] and smartphones in [the first half 2014], Silvermont also has the distinction of being the first mobile chips (from any vendor) to benefit from tri-gate [3D] transistors...And like ARM's Cortex A15 core, Silvermont is a fully out-of-order architecture, a feature heretofore not present in Atom solutions...We view Silvermont as the basic building block for Intel's future mobile architectures." Intel chip gives new hope for Windows 8 tablets Analysts are encouraged by Intel's new Atom design. So future Windows Blue-based tablets powered by Intel's revamped mobile chips could provide a lift for Microsoft and its hardware partners. by Brooke Crothers May 8, 2013 5:07 PM PDT 38 CommentsFacebook36Twitter185Linked In11More Dell Latitude 10: Expect Windows Blue tablets -- packing quad-core Bay Trail processors -- that are as slim or slimmer than the Windows 8 variety. (Credit: Microsoft) Analysts are upbeat about Intel's new mobile chip design due later this year. That could mean a much-needed boost for Windows 8 tablets -- where many of those chips will land. Imagine this: an ultraslim, light tablet with roughly twice the performance of any Atom-based Windows 8 tablet on the market now. (And that's the full version of Windows, not Windows RT.) That could happen in the second half of this year. So think of Windows Blue (or Windows 8.1) products similar to Samsung's 0.38-inch thick ATIV Smart PC 500T Tablet or Dell's 0.4-inch thick Latitude 10 with new Intel quad-core "Bay Trail" processors based on the overhauled Atom micro-architecture. And smaller tablets, like Acer's rumored 8-inch tablet, should ultimately benefit too. That can only be seen as good news for Windows 8 tablets, which haven't exactly been taking the market by storm. Here'</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1368109244878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:20:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368109396668-45</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's next generation A7 processor to be produced by Intel?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368065033282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:03:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh this is a good find. Intel would produce A7 chips for Apple on the condition that Apple use Intel's chips in their upcoming products. It takes time for Apple to get iOS to work on x86, so they could first announce they will switch (similar to how they did in macs in 2005), and Intel can fab the arm processors in the meantime. In the meantime, they both work on getting iOS/(or new touch-base Mac OS) to work in x86. With release of Silvermont and its superiority, it's an obvious move for Apple.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368109396668</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:23:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368109597081-46</Id><Topic><Title>Warning coming...</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368108486367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:08:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DOW down, NASD down, INTC up. I guess we must have gotten a few more upgrades today.</Msg><Username>intoodeep99</Username><Timestamp>1368109597081</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:26:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368109615690-47</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's next generation A7 processor to be produced by Intel?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368065033282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:03:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It also explains why Raja Koduri left Apple</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368109615690</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:26:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368109724374-48</Id><Topic><Title>Next Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368106729959</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM the stock may be in for a pop, but really, ARM the company will keep chugging along fine...just will not encroach in Intel's high margin, high ASP traditional areas :)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368109724374</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:28:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368109772292-49</Id><Title>THE WORD IS SPREADING ABOUT SILVERMONT</Title><Msg>INTC TO $40 BY END OF YEAR!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368109772292</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:29:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368109875203-50</Id><Title>Intel's new chief says push into mobile technology will gather steam on his watch</Title><Msg>IAN KING – 09 MAY 2013 INTEL, the world's largest chipmaker and a major employer in Ireland, will appoint chief operating officer Brian Krzanich as chief executive officer next week, leaning on an insider to accelerate a shift toward mobile devices as the personal-computer age wanes. The former factory manager will become the sixth CEO in Intel's history at the annual shareholder meeting next Thursday, when Paul Otellini, (62) steps down as CEO and director. In opting for Mr Krzanich (52), Intel hewed to a tradition of hiring for the top job from within, backing a three-decade veteran who firmly grasps the complexities of making the chips that run more than 80pc of the world's PCs. Yet, as Intel lags behind Qualcomm in the production of semi-conductors for smartphones and tablets, the decision not to appoint an executive who has expertise in mobile technology carries risks. "A fresh set of eyes from an external candidate might have been a good move," said Cody Acree, an analyst at Williams Financial in Dallas. "Intel has to be ultra-successful in another large market or in a lot of markets to re-invigorate your growth." Mr Krzanich's main challenge will be jump-starting Intel's efforts to gain ground in the market for chips that run mobile devices. The PC industry, Intel's stronghold, is facing its second consecutive decline in annual sales this year while tablets and smartphones continue to surge. Intel has spent more than a decade and billions of dollars trying to gain a foothold in smartphones, yet chip</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1368109875203</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368110010601-51</Id><Topic><Title>Intel chip gives new hope for Windows 8 tablets</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368064057258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:47:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GREAT ARTICLE, MUST READ.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368110010601</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:33:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368110169600-52</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's next generation A7 processor to be produced by Intel?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368065033282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:03:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not true. The A7 is a TSMC 20nm part. This is common knowledge in Silicon Valley. The design has already taped out. My guess is that Apple will stick with TSMC for 16nm if 20nm goes well. Google: Apple Will NOT Manufacture SoCs at Intel and: TSMC Apple Rumors Debunked!</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110169600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:36:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368110278033-53</Id><Title>The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly</Title><Msg>Interesting article by a former Intel employee. Not that I agree with it but interesting perspective just the same. Google: The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly It was a generation ago when Intel, less than three years old, created the three fundamental building blocks of the compute era: the DRAM, the EPROM and the Microprocessor, an incredible feat of innovation by any measure. Manufacturing yield, not power or performance determined success of failure and in the first two decades.........</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110278033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368110291804-54</Id><Topic><Title>Gud Morn Slackers</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368109193681</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:19:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>right on brother</Msg><Username>beachfoley</Username><Timestamp>1368110291804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:38:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368110312797-55</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's next generation A7 processor to be produced by Intel?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368065033282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:03:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You away moron, you are laughing stock of semi industry</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368110312797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368110365701-56</Id><Topic><Title>Warning coming...</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368108486367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:08:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No - it is just making up for the big rally days when it did absolutely nothing. BTW it will probably end in the red today.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368110365701</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:39:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368110381605-57</Id><Topic><Title>The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110278033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go away moron, everyone is laughing at you. You are a joke</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368110381605</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:39:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368110507825-58</Id><Topic><Title>The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110278033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you see Anand or Ashraf coming on here to promote their articles? You idiot</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368110507825</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:41:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368110847908-59</Id><Topic><Title>Requirements to be an ARM Investor</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368063548961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:39:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>American Tower. It wouldn't surprise me if they are doing a song and dance to get the stock up then having the executives sell some of their shares and using the proceeds to fund the company. The only thing that is really good about what they do is that they own a lot of real estate. The bad news is that they have a declining client base. Unless of course some retro phase of pagers suddenly comes back into style.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1368110847908</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:47:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368111256324-60</Id><Topic><Title>The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110278033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>D. Nenni never worked at Intel. He wouldn't have been able to survive due to his "qualifications" which BTW he has put on display here before being laughed out of the place. I do agree, he is a joke and that everyone is laughing at him.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1368111256324</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:54:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368111278796-61</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'(just google overheating on any major phone and you'll see the same "complaints")' and what that tells you is that ARM vendors have been over-engineering their phones for some time and this is because they all using the same basic ISA and so are in an unnecessary ARMs race with each other meaning they have to try and outdo each other on specs rather than usable functionality. What phone application actually seriously requires a quad-core 2GHz processor ? At least Intel is breaking up this insane inbred monopoly cartel and providing the users with sane usable dual-core devices with sensible peak power limits.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368111278796</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:54:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368111325507-62</Id><Topic><Title>The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110278033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He does, apparently drive a nice sports car though :)</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1368111325507</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368111456949-63</Id><Topic><Title>The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110278033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't write it. Check First Amendment of the US Constitution and get back to me.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368111456949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:57:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368111566295-64</Id><Topic><Title>The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110278033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this the clown who claimed Samsungs 28 nm implementation of Gate first was causing a yield issue, despite it being the exact same gate stack as the 32 nm which has no issues at all?</Msg><Username>zisdead1</Username><Timestamp>1368111566295</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368111761281-65</Id><Topic><Title>The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110278033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Is this the clown who claimed Samsungs 28 nm implementation of Gate first was causing a yield issue, despite it being the exact same gate stack as the 32 nm which has no issues at all?" Samsung has yet to ship a 28nm part so.......... Google: Can Samsung Deliver As Promised?</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368111761281</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368111842479-66</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>major overheating is usually a failure of some sort...</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1368111842479</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:04:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368111867789-67</Id><Topic><Title>Next Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368106729959</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"ARM the stock may be in for a pop, but really, ARM the company will keep chugging along fine...just will not encroach in Intel's high margin, high ASP traditional areas :)" [Well, perhaps I should clarify a bit: ARM's incredibly, monstrously, dotcom era-high P/E ratio is doomed. And the stock price will collapse with it. The company should do just fine but at a much lower and realistic valuation - something around 10. It will have the low end of the market and that should still be a lot of business. They will settle into the AMD role quite well I think and maybe even find stability in that role. But their fabrication and fabless model problems aren't going to go away. They can't close the fabrication gap and no one is going to be funding new ARM foundry companies... ]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368111867789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:04:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368111950251-68</Id><Topic><Title>The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110278033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The First Amendment (Amendment I) to the United States Constitution prohibits the making of any law respecting an establishment of religion, impeding the free exercise of religion" semiwiki religious spam is legal for you to worship.</Msg><Username>dummy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1368111950251</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:05:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368111969855-69</Id><Topic><Title>Where are we headed, Marsavian?</Title><Username>wdblowfish</Username><Timestamp>1368033792056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:23:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Much too pessimistic, Marsavian. Once the Street gets the validation on Haswell and Bay Trail, which is beginning to happen now, the run up to $30 will be swift. I expect that to happen in the next 3 to 4 months. Let me tell you why I think so: As Otellini mentioned - each of the concerns/FUDs - Windows on ARM and Microserver have held the stock down to a smaller PE multiple. When these concerns go away, the PE multiple should get to 15 - that is how we will get to $30 pretty quickly. Any further climb will be steady based on quarterly financial results. Of course, there are some wildcards which can cause rapid appreciation in the stock price: (1) Apple adopting x86 for phones/tablets (2) Google/Motorola coming out with a very aggressive line of phones/tablets based on x86 (3) Big carriers coming out with their own label phones/tablets (4) Intel Media turning out to be a good play (Netflix-like valuation)</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1368111969855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:06:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368112114869-70</Id><Topic><Title>Warning coming...</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368108486367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:08:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"then this pig drops." [Dana, don't you ever get tired of the daily stupidity post? The daily "sky is falling" post? The daily doom and gloom post? You are the poster child for content and fact-free. You are the poster child for too ignorant to engage in rational discussion...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368112114869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:08:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368112210229-71</Id><Topic><Title>The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110278033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sunday's preaching comes from the book of Semiwiki on the topic of "Can Nenni Deliver at All and Why not ???? "</Msg><Username>dummy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1368112210229</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368112351171-72</Id><Topic><Title>The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110278033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't follow his advice to follow google to this "wonderful article". He is a blogger who gets paid by the number of clicks on these web pages. It's the same behavior that go him kicked off of the Yahoo Message Boards under the handle of D. Nenni. Pathetic, really....</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1368112351171</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368112402814-73</Id><Topic><Title>The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110278033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I didn't write it. Check First Amendment of the US Constitution and get back to me." [It's not the Constitution you are running a foul of, Nenni - it's Yahoo's posting policies. It's why you got booted previously. And if you keep up the self-promotion you might have it happen again...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368112402814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368113504029-74</Id><Topic><Title>The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110278033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Samsung has yet to ship a 28nm part" BS ! Every non-LTE i.e. international Galaxy S4 has a 28nm Exynos Octa in it and we know they have been shipped now because we posted user reviews about them. Also the iPad/iPhone5S refresh for this summer will have 28nm A6(X) chips in them. Why don't you go and post a retraction now ? I won't hold my breath because that would require integrity and honesty.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368113504029</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:31:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368113527444-75</Id><Topic><Title>Next Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368106729959</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed. This stock has gone exponential because a lot of the momo guys are panic buying the hell out of it. This stock is almost entirely disconnected from the underlying business, which should probably be priced more like a utility than anything else.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368113527444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:32:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368114309303-76</Id><Topic><Title>When it comes to bribes and monopolistic behavior Intel is #1</Title><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1368097655763</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 07:07:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nuff ....... permanently down on his luck, bitter, vengeful, broke. An old and hollow man, sitting in his rented duplex all day, with nothing to do except take pot shots at Intel and try to remember better times. Sad case.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1368114309303</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:45:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368114344715-77</Id><Topic><Title>The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110278033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung's 28nm may be in very short supply, but they are shipping.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368114344715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:45:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368114729246-78</Id><Title>Time for market crash</Title><Msg>We are so over valued and over priced on just buying not fundamentals to support it. I see a huge sell-off of 15% easily here. World wide even bigger.</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1368114729246</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:52:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368115466628-79</Id><Title>Intel has already won the next Mobile Chip Revolution, all we need is the design wins to make it clear to the rest of wallstreet</Title><Msg>This stock will be $100 in 4 to 5 years</Msg><Username>seriouslynot</Username><Timestamp>1368115466628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:04:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368115523076-80</Id><Topic><Title>Time for market crash</Title><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1368114729246</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:52:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've been preaching about a market crash since Feb. Trying to talk, not just a single stock down, but the entire global market. Sounds desperate (and insane). Foolishly but predictably loosing whatever you have left with your short positions.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1368115523076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368115705990-81</Id><Title>Acer CEO optimistic about Windows 8.1, claims Microsoft is back 'down to Earth'</Title><Msg>thevergeDOTcom/2013/5/9/4315028/acer-windows-8-changes-microsoft-back-down-to-earth While Microsoft executives have been hinting at the arrival of a Windows 8 update, codenamed Blue, two Acer execs have been voicing their approval of planned changes for the OS. Speaking to The Wall Street Journal, Acer president Jim Wong explained that Microsoft is making alterations "at a high percentage" rate thanks to OEM input. Arguing that the world is not going 100 percent touch in the next five years, he says "touch makes a lot of possibilities for PCs," but that "you need to take care of the rest of the world that doesn’t need touch" too. Windows chief Julie Larson-Green dropped big hints about changes for non-touch use of Microsoft's Windows 8 operating system recently. Speaking at the Wired Business Conference earlier this week she reiterated previous comments from Windows CFO Tami Reller that Windows 8.1 will include changes based on user feedback. Discussing the potential return of the Start button, Larson-Green said that "there has been meaningful discussion" within Microsoft. Windows 8.1 is expected to include a Start button and boot-to-desktop option. Acer CEO and chairman JT Wang is also optimistic about Microsoft's plans. "In the past we consider they [Microsoft] live in heaven," he said to The Wall Street Journal. "But now they go down to earth and they start to learn how people living on earth think." Wang's comments follow his outspoken views about Microsoft's Surface RT tablet ahead of its launch, asking the software maker to "think twice" about entering the hardware market. Microsoft's change of approach follows the departure of former Windows chief Steven Sinofsky in November. Sinofsky was known to aggressively maintain his control over the company's Windows division — making it difficult to execute internal collaboration and product changes.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368115705990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:08:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368115730796-82</Id><Title>Suitability of FinFET technology for low-power mixed-signal applications</Title><Msg>Suitability of FinFET technology for low-power mixed-signal applications Here's what I think Intel is expanding its foundry business beyond what was previously expected. IMO the new CEO will add a additional "third leg" beside CPU and SoC - some sort of Intel foundry business unit The MSCC deal was a hint - could not find any analysis on this deal. This looks far more profitable than chasing Apple Wireless applications require a low power technology that enables digital/analog/RF functions on the same chip. FinFET technology presents a competitive alternative to planar CMOS as it features good digital, analog and low-frequency noise performances. Also, very good matching performance is presented here for the first time. Moreover, FinFETs are shown to be attractive for low-power applications below 10 GHz. The suitability of Fin varactors is evaluated and tradeoffs are given. An inductorless oscillator with large tuning range (1-8.5 GHz) for low-power wideband applications is demonstrated for the first time</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368115730796</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368115940687-83</Id><Topic><Title>Acer CEO optimistic about Windows 8.1, claims Microsoft is back 'down to Earth'</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368115705990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:08:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>blogsDOTwsjDOTcom/digits/2013/05/09/pc-makers-hopeful-on-windows-8-changes/ ... a more immediate change is that Windows 8 devices are about to get much more price-competitive. The price premium of a Windows 8 tablet over an Android one is now at least $150. That gap could shrink to around $50 this year, putting sticker prices of Windows 8 tablets below $300, said Jerry Shen, chief executive of Taiwanese PC maker Asustek Computer Inc.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368115940687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:12:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368116731257-84</Id><Topic><Title>Time for market crash</Title><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1368114729246</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 11:52:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I remember when I caught you, Lucy_Nuff using this Kopach alias on the Oracle board after earnings last year. You got mad at me for "chasing you around the internet." I also remember you going bonkers that Oracle would drop from 25 to 22 and never recover.......It was back to 30 just weeks later. LOL@LUCY_NUFF.</Msg><Username>lucy_mutt</Username><Timestamp>1368116731257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:25:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368116804145-85</Id><Topic><Title>Where are we headed, Marsavian?</Title><Username>wdblowfish</Username><Timestamp>1368033792056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:23:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Accurate characterization of the situation. If one looks at ARMH's share price even after Intel's Haswell and Bay Trail Bay announcements it suggests the broader market simply doesn't yet believe any of ARMH's plans will be impacted. Despite what they heard they still believe ARMH will take a significant share of Intel's server and mainstream Window's business. And since they believe in the ARM dream with such conviction they certainly don't believe Intel is going to have much impact in ARMH's core tablet and smartphone business. What we are witnessing is a delayed reaction to the realization of what Intel's announcements actually means to mobile space. Intel has already laid the foundation for the stock to be well in excess of $30.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1368116804145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:26:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368116977056-86</Id><Topic><Title>Acer CEO optimistic about Windows 8.1, claims Microsoft is back 'down to Earth'</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368115705990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:08:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe for the 7" RT to effectively compete and establish any sort of market share they will need to come very close, or at current Nexxus level pricing. If they have a decent product they should just implement the original X-box marketing strategy of inundating the market with commercials along with effective pricing. The current crop of RT commercials are pretty lame by focusing on the snap-on keyboard, and not addressing the overall experience.</Msg><Username>chitownbarber25</Username><Timestamp>1368116977056</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:29:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368117069880-87</Id><Topic><Title>Acer CEO optimistic about Windows 8.1, claims Microsoft is back 'down to Earth'</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368115705990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:08:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DT is reporting that after cutting back DRAM production they are now facing a shortage situation which could eventually impact PC shipments .....</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368117069880</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:31:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368117318597-88</Id><Topic><Title>Suitability of FinFET technology for low-power mixed-signal applications</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368115730796</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Search Mixed Signal Design Engineer jobs and related careers at 4G LTE technology information site. Connect the dots....</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368117318597</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:35:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368117420415-89</Id><Topic><Title>Suitability of FinFET technology for low-power mixed-signal applications</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368115730796</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Search Mixed Signal Design Engineer jobs and related careers at 4G LTE technology information site. Connect the dots....</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368117420415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:37:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368118027709-90</Id><Title>crash time semis</Title><Msg>Long over due too far too fast just like markets . Just day trading games.</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1368118027709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:47:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368118077357-91</Id><Topic><Title>The Morphing of Intel's Monopoly</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1368110278033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clown ..lets not beat about the bush... your making a fool of yourself..... Now link me to one concrete piece of data that backs up your claim , that as explicitly stated by you..."Gate first on 28nm is causing a yield issue at samsung" ..... dont give me, "not shipping" ...#$%$. I dont care about that.. I want to call you out about your 28nm gate first yield issue ... so then maybe samsung if the choose can sue you for Defamation.</Msg><Username>zisdead1</Username><Timestamp>1368118077357</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:47:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368118135874-92</Id><Topic><Title>crash time semis</Title><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1368118027709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Lucy_nuff, they had a very respected portolio manager on TV a couple of days ago and they asked him what he liked and he said Technology, specifically Semiconductors. LOL @ lucille_nuff.</Msg><Username>lucy_mutt</Username><Timestamp>1368118135874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 12:48:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368118993805-93</Id><Topic><Title>Next Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368106729959</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Waldo still pounding the pe argument, which matters nada. and posting as certainties what are merely his opinions, which, as most know, are quite unreliable as predictors of future realities.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1368118993805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 13:03:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368119377002-94</Id><Topic><Title>Gud Morn Slackers</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1368109193681</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:19:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you out riding your Harley, wondering why you are a daytrader or did you just get tired of writing doom blogs?</Msg><Username>herbal_dud</Username><Timestamp>1368119377002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 13:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368119377494-95</Id><Topic><Title>Next Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368106729959</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are detested beyond comprehension and post in high volume. Certain there are people that read this board and wish you were 6ft under. How does it feel to be so despised?</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1368119377494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 13:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368120944112-96</Id><Topic><Title>Where are we headed, Marsavian?</Title><Username>wdblowfish</Username><Timestamp>1368033792056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:23:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a bit more nuanced than that I believe. Haswell and Bay Trail combined have to arrest the decline of Intel's traditional market before you make believers of the market and that might take a few quarterly results. It's not that some Analysts don't believe that Intel will make inroads into mobile, it's just that they don't believe that will offset what they perceive to be the decline of Intel's traditional market at the expense of mobile in general. Now I don't really believe Intel's traditional market is in secular decline, just in a temporary hardware/software/form factor transition pause before taking off again. However that is not a favored view unless your surname is Otellini but I think he will be proved right in the end. I was also being ultra-conservative with that early 2015 estimate as a worst case scenario as I feel 30+ might only take 12-15 months from here until say Broadwell/Airmont release. There is also a lot of historical resistance up to 30+ that needs overcoming that might take some time too.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368120944112</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 13:35:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368121470664-97</Id><Title>Brian Raise the divy. Nice way to launch</Title><Msg>your new career.</Msg><Username>a33stacybb</Username><Timestamp>1368121470664</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 13:44:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368121603554-98</Id><Topic><Title>Where are we headed, Marsavian?</Title><Username>wdblowfish</Username><Timestamp>1368033792056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:23:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC just chewed through $24.50 in seconds. I could see 300k to 400k shares publicly waiting to be sold and likely more in the shadows. Something happened to the volume at 1pm. Someone had a good lunch for INTC.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368121603554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 13:46:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368121853462-99</Id><Topic><Title>Warning coming...</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1368108486367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:08:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"BTW it will probably end in the red today." Still want to stick with that prediction, genius?</Msg><Username>intoodeep99</Username><Timestamp>1368121853462</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 13:50:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368122341981-100</Id><Topic><Title>Where are we headed, Marsavian?</Title><Username>wdblowfish</Username><Timestamp>1368033792056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:23:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" It's not that some Analysts don't believe that Intel will make inroads into mobile, it's just that they don't believe that will offset what they perceive to be the decline of Intel's traditional market at the expense of mobile in general. " Intel can certainly stimulate PC market with new exciting products and "hope for the best". However a far more proactive strategy is to expand Intel's foundry business without compromising its core business and it looks mixed signal could be a huge opportunity. After googling around it appears they (MS) also would like TriGate technology and Intel can give it to them. Give TSMC Apple's business ( with relatively low margin) and take TSMC high margin business like mixed signal , RF</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368122341981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 13:59:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368122664182-101</Id><Title>My greenest stock today</Title><Msg>Despite the defeatists: "market is doomed" (kopach) "ARMH is doomed" (Wallis) "everything is doomed" (backbayidiot) "nothing is proven" blueredmonk I'm thoroughly enjoying this green day of early spring.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368122664182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368124151260-102</Id><Topic><Title>Where are we headed, Marsavian?</Title><Username>wdblowfish</Username><Timestamp>1368033792056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:23:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed, the foundry business has real good growth potential as well as depriving TSMC and other foundries of much needed lucrative business. However it's not really going to contribute much in the short term, it will be like a rolling snowball that gathers more and more weight over time until it's an avalanche. By the time Intel has conquered mobile it will be more relevant and important to future revenue/profit growth but first Intel has to reignite the core PC business and become the premier SoC of choice in mobile. As it happens there are good noises coming from the PC OEMs in that regard ... digitimesDOTcom/news/a20130508PD224.html 'The PC industry is expected to return to a shipment ratio of 4:6 for the first and second halves of 2013, Acer president Jim Wong said at the company's investor conference on May 8. Consumer demand is expected to reach its first peak of 2013 in September for the back-to-school season, sources with upsteam suppliers said. The sources pointed out that the PC industry's strong second-half performance will benefit from vendors' weak inventory levels in the first half as most brand vendors have been digesting their inventories and should start placing orders to restock for the second half. In addition, Intel's Haswell platform's stronger performance and lower power consumption, compared to the existing platform, are expected to boost brand vendors' confidence in next-generation PC products. Furthermore, Microsoft's recognition of Windows 8's failures and plans to improve the operating system, are also helping PC brand vendors feel positive about the PC industry in the second half. In additional news, Acer has announced financial results for first quarter of 2013, with consolidated revenues of NT$91.97 billion (US$3.08 billion), operating income of NT$29 million (US$0.97 million), profit after tax (PAT) of NT$515 million (US$17.24 million), and EPS at NT$0.19.'</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1368124151260</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:29:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368124407678-103</Id><Topic><Title>Where are we headed, Marsavian?</Title><Username>wdblowfish</Username><Timestamp>1368033792056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:23:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel lumps their HPC business into the server group. The HPC market is projected for an 8% CAGR and end in 2020 at the $47b level. PHI is going to give Intel a big chunk of that growth, profit, margin, .... The HPC systems have a high silicon density and a high percentage of the system price.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368124407678</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:33:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368125315475-104</Id><Topic><Title>Where are we headed, Marsavian?</Title><Username>wdblowfish</Username><Timestamp>1368033792056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:23:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ARM camp has certainly popularized the "The PC is Dead" mentality because it works to supports their vision that desktops and labtops are on the decline and tablets &amp; smartphones are becoming the center of the computing universe. It is not surprising that the camp that promoted this vision supplied almost 100% of the parts for tablets and smartphones - and none of the former. Now everyone knows that there are things one can do with a desktop and large monitor that they just can't do on a tablet. Microsoft received this message very clearly with Windows 8 which is why they are having to change their Metro-only strategy and release a fix that restores much, if not all of the Windows desktop. The notion that the PC is dead is absurd. The better question is " In which form factor do you want your PC?" By what other name would one call a Core 2 Class performance device with a professional 64 bit Windows, dual-boot capability, HD display and high-speed interconnects and runs all legacy Windows apps? If size wasn't mentioned, one might think it was describing an All-In-One desktop, but we're talking about a handheld 8" slate. The larger investment community not only is having difficulty accepting the technical merit of Intel's advancements, they don't yet appreciate how Intel is about to absorb the tablet into the "PC world".</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1368125315475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:48:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368125561842-105</Id><Topic><Title>My greenest stock today</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368122664182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny, my best trade was long the SQQQ, played for a nice bounce and got one. Market needs to let some air out of the very overbght conditions</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1368125561842</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:52:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368125799898-106</Id><Topic><Title>My greenest stock today</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368122664182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spoke too soon.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368125799898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:56:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368125910986-107</Id><Topic><Title>My greenest stock today</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368122664182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leave it to Tampon boy to jinx it.</Msg><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368125910986</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:58:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368125937809-108</Id><Topic><Title>My greenest stock today</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368122664182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Despite the defeatists: "ARMH is doomed" (Wallis)" [I speak not of defeat but of victory. Intel's victory. Those who sully our efforts in the pursuit of victory and provide comfort to our enemies shall be called before the emperor's justice...] [Okay, that was a joke, in case you didn't get it...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368125937809</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:58:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368126066584-109</Id><Topic><Title>My greenest stock today</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368122664182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got it.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368126066584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:01:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368126319120-110</Id><Title>Wow, that was a strange dip</Title><Msg>Market dropped down and now is moving back up. Anyone know what happened?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368126319120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:05:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368126363902-111</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, that was a strange dip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368126319120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>80 hour work week, huh? you watch every tick every day and have no job. Gutless liar.</Msg><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368126363902</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368126430464-112</Id><Topic><Title>My greenest stock today</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368122664182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>admitttedly, a tough market to short, but the rsi levels on some of thes are extreme. markets need to work off the overbght conditions, even if perhaps only briefly</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1368126430464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:07:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368127808494-113</Id><Title>ACCUMMULATION HAPPENING...AFTER THAT, ANALYSTS WILL PUSH THIS HARD</Title><Msg>$40 EOY</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368127808494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:30:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368127857234-114</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, that was a strange dip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368126319120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be nice.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1368127857234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:30:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368127865929-115</Id><Topic><Title>ACCUMMULATION HAPPENING...AFTER THAT, ANALYSTS WILL PUSH THIS HARD</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368127808494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:30:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Covello will go extreme the other way! He will give $50 price target!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368127865929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:31:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368127953092-116</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, that was a strange dip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368126319120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree...maybe a mini-flash crash.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368127953092</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368128114429-117</Id><Title>SEe markets crashing just so over bought and over priced.</Title><Msg>Its all been Wall Street games and Bernanke playing games with rates. It will all back fire on him when everyone realizes they have been reeled in.FRee play money isnt free for ever.You have to pay up.</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1368128114429</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:35:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368128207934-118</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, that was a strange dip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368126319120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i dont know about the market but the strange dip was coinwacker</Msg><Username>dummy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1368128207934</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:36:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368128216518-119</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, that was a strange dip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368126319120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it was a simple program sell.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1368128216518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:36:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368128250859-120</Id><Topic><Title>SEe markets crashing just so over bought and over priced.</Title><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1368128114429</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:35:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DOW GOING TOWARDS 16,000 BY END OF YEAR FOOL</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1368128250859</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:37:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368128330078-121</Id><Topic><Title>SEe markets crashing just so over bought and over priced.</Title><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1368128114429</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:35:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh, the humanity !!! “Danger, Will Robinson! Danger!”</Msg><Username>dummy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1368128330078</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:38:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368129944053-122</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, that was a strange dip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368126319120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And we're supposed to trust his word when he says he doesn't use aliases.......LOL!</Msg><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1368129944053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 16:05:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368130087527-123</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, that was a strange dip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368126319120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's asy to work an 80 hour work week if self employed and living in the shop pumping intc all day. Not exactly billable hour rates all day.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1368130087527</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 16:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368130365853-124</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, that was a strange dip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368126319120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish Yhoo would chop nuffs ugly head off &amp; stuff it up his a,s-,s</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368130365853</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 16:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368130416907-125</Id><Topic><Title>My greenest stock today</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1368122664182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From 4/15 to 4/30, Intel was up from $21.18 to $23.73. During that time, there was a couple days of 100m shares trading. The short interest dropped by 2mil shares during those 11 trading days from 235m to 233m shares. It still looks like the short interest state is unchanged. 4/30/2013 233,212,213 71,694,120 3.252878 4/15/2013 235,467,126 41,270,640 5.705439</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368130416907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 16:13:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368136050823-126</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, that was a strange dip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368126319120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"it's asy to work an 80 hour work week if self employed and living in the shop pumping intc all day. Not exactly billable hour rates all day." [I bet I don't spend 10 percent of the time doing my posting that you spend stalking me, butkus. There's something seriously wrong and creepy about you...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368136050823</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 17:47:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368136114089-127</Id><Title>Haswell Countdown Continues</Title><Msg>Three weeks out...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368136114089</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 17:48:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368136737282-128</Id><Title>wallisweaver</Title><Msg>Keep up the good work you do here. I know you're criticized a lot for pointing out the ARM bubble, but it really is relevant as ARM's future success is predicated on Intel failure/market share loss. BTW, did you see RAX today? That's what I think ARM will be doing by the end of 2013.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368136737282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 17:58:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368137181844-129</Id><Topic><Title>Where are we headed, Marsavian?</Title><Username>wdblowfish</Username><Timestamp>1368033792056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:23:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>should it manage to close above 25.50 then it's all clear. short covering would take it to new highs</Msg><Username>jake_718</Username><Timestamp>1368137181844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 18:06:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368137719100-130</Id><Topic><Title>wallisweaver</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368136737282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 17:58:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf, I enjoy your articles and posts (actually I like Wallis' posts too), but I must say I can see a scenario in which INTC and ARMH are both successful long term. It seems to me there is enough future growth (especially in Asia) in smartphones, tabs, and servers, that both could prosper. On the other hand, and I think to your point, it seems the PE ratio for ARMH has gotten a bit ridiculous. They are priced for perfection. Another big growth driver could be IoT (internet of things) devices. The potential for IoT growth seems pretty staggering. Even though I am an INTC fanboy, I think ARM got the jump in this arena.</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1368137719100</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 18:15:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368138352095-131</Id><Topic><Title>wallisweaver</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368136737282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 17:58:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM isn't going away, but the nosebleed valuation probably will.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368138352095</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 18:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368138589472-132</Id><Title>How is that 18 price target Intel working out for you James C? Stupid is what stupid does.</Title><Msg>Shorting Intel now is stupid. You let your hate for the company get in the way of some easy money long. You will have to change your spew soon. When Intel hits 30, no way you can have an 18 price target without your boss shiiietting all over you. Oh well. It is not as if you or I know where any stock is going on any given day is it. The difference is that I do not lie and tell people that I do know.</Msg><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1368138589472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 18:29:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368138866710-133</Id><Topic><Title>wallisweaver</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368136737282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 17:58:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah - just checked again - PE is up to 82 now.. 82!!</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1368138866710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 18:34:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368138897595-134</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, that was a strange dip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368126319120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whats really creepy is the incessant pumping of INTC you've been doing non stop for years. I do believe Cramer has it right tonight, a frothy market in which ARMH is not alone, accompanied by the always pumped INTC.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1368138897595</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 18:34:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368139579268-135</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget about Tizen</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368068372699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:59:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very interesting, considering she was in on Tizen. Any chance Samsung is the big Mobile foundry customer?</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1368139579268</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 18:46:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368139770092-136</Id><Title>Ok one more time.. INTC will take a mkt</Title><Msg>They were slow on mobile. But intc is a gorrila. Saw them take wireless in the 90s when it was developed by hrs and the isil spin off. Intc reverse engineered it and soon isil had to sell the 802.11b tech which hrs enginerrs developed to cnxt . Same thing happened to authentec. Ahhh where did that go...? Intc is unstoppable. Remindes me me of ATT in the 80s before the gvt broke it out into the baby bells... Yes folks intc will dominate any mkt they choose to address watch and learn... Peace... The Capper.</Msg><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1368139770092</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 18:49:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368141143387-137</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget about Tizen</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368068372699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:59:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tizen is an interesting story, however I'm not sure how INTC profits from it much. It is supposedly shared with Samsung and others. It could hurt Google because it may be more marketable in Asia. But it will run on ARM processors as well. Phone makers may choose to use it but then implement it on an ARM platform... Do you all know if Intel would receive royalties/license fees?</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1368141143387</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 19:12:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368142289223-138</Id><Title>Intel aquires Aepona and Mashery</Title><Msg>Anyone know much about these companies?</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1368142289223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 19:31:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368144726202-139</Id><Topic><Title>How is that 18 price target Intel working out for you James C? Stupid is what stupid does.</Title><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1368138589472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 18:29:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Getting out of a target price that is too low is not a problem. One example is just to REITERATE the rating but release a higher target. One example would be Romit Shah from Nomura. 10/19/2011 target price is $18 and 12/13/2011 the target became $21 without any explanation. The raising of the target to $21 was done silently. streetinsiderDOTcom/rating_historyDOTphp?q=INTC&amp;firm=110</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368144726202</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:12:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368145745642-140</Id><Topic><Title>Intel aquires Aepona and Mashery</Title><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1368142289223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 19:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PATENT 20080209451 Methods for analyzing, limiting, and enhancing access to an internet API, web service, and data MASHER CLIP It is well-known that big tech companies are spending billions amassing patent portfolios and wielding them as competitive weapons against each other and their smaller challengers. What is new and different about Oracle’s lawsuit against Google is that it is not about whether someone can enforce a patent on a process or feature, like Amazon’s one-click patent or the many user interface patents Apple and others have been granted. Instead, Oracle is making a copyright claim on the APIs (Application Programming Interfaces) used to communicate with the Java programming language. Oracle has reiterated that the Java language itself is free and open source (as Sun declared it to be years ago). So the question of how Oracle can profit from the success of Android and the role of Java in that success now hinges on whether one can assert a copyright on an API. ....... The arguments boil down to whether it is possible to “own” the language that is being used (as Oracle and Larry Ellison want it to be), or only the words that have been written in that language (as has been the traditional interpretation of copyright law until this case – an interpretation that has paved the way for decades of innovation in software and applications). An API is a specification of the dialect that computer programs or their components use to exchange data with each other or with the hardware they are running on. One program uses an API to tell another program “ask for this, and you will get this in return.” APIs govern how an app running on your phone’s processor talks to the keyboard or the screen, or how the USA Today app on your iPad gets the updated headlines, story and pictures from the server. They are essential to the operation of any “cloud” implementation, MORE ...</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368145745642</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:29:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368145960923-141</Id><Topic><Title>How is that 18 price target Intel working out for you James C? Stupid is what stupid does.</Title><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1368138589472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 18:29:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The raising of the target to $21 was done silently." [But not without shame...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368145960923</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:32:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368146102210-142</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget about Tizen</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368068372699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:59:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't see that Intel would get any revenues out of it except on its own Tizen products. But it's a chance for Intel and Samsung people to hang out together and work together. Who knows what might come of it?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368146102210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:35:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368146373599-143</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, that was a strange dip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368126319120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So wdblawgrow, if someone really liked a football team and pumped them all the time, then you think it would be okay to follow them around in your car? Showing an appreciation for anything is no reason to be stalked. Your stalking is creepy. Cut it out...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368146373599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:39:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368146610617-144</Id><Topic><Title>wallisweaver</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368136737282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 17:58:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got the $46 puts for July. So far I'm down since I bought them when the stock was around $47 or so. I'm only losing a little though because the size is less than 2% of my investments. If it only drops down to below 70 PE, I should be fine by July. But I am aso thinking going a few more on the January 14 puts as the Baytrail release could create some fear to bring down their PE closer to reasonable levels that make sense. The whole investment though will still amount to 2% of my total holdings.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1368146610617</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:43:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368146614154-145</Id><Topic><Title>wallisweaver</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368136737282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 17:58:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you. Yes I saw the article: Overheated Expectations Send Rackspace Investors To The Torture Chamber Wonder if there is room in there for all of the excessively exuberant ARM investors?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368146614154</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:43:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368146816628-146</Id><Topic><Title>Intel aquires Aepona and Mashery</Title><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1368142289223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 19:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is an article on Aepona if you search for phrase: What’s the Difference between Aepona, Apigee, Twilio, and Voxeo? Aepona seems to be a network infrastructure company providing API for the cloud.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368146816628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:46:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368146958574-147</Id><Topic><Title>How is that 18 price target Intel working out for you James C? Stupid is what stupid does.</Title><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1368138589472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 18:29:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw no evidence of shame. It looked like Romit implemented his orchestrated bash against Intel. No evidence of shame at all.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1368146958574</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:49:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368147125248-148</Id><Topic><Title>wallisweaver</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368136737282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 17:58:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM is a good company with smart and dedicated employees. But it's not projected to do well - it's projected to do incredibly well beyond any comprehension.It's this valuation that I take exception to. Trying to get your mind around a P/E of over 80 is like trying to imagine what a billion dollars looks like. Actually it's like trying to imagine what 23 billion dollars looks like because that's their market cap. They need to be doubling earnings every year to deserve that kind of valuation. It's not going to happen...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368147125248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:52:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368147432841-149</Id><Topic><Title>How is that 18 price target Intel working out for you James C? Stupid is what stupid does.</Title><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1368138589472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 18:29:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I saw no evidence of shame. It looked like Romit implemented his orchestrated bash against Intel. No evidence of shame at all." [Nor should we expect to see any evidence of shame because this would be indicative of honor, integrity and accountability. I don't think the big Wall Street firms hire people with those characteristics. I think they hire people willing to do what is considered expedient no matter the ethics, morality or legality. For them it's all about the money, totally about the money and the end justifies the means. That's why they can advise one way and trade the other...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368147432841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368147741265-150</Id><Topic><Title>wallisweaver</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368136737282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 17:58:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel 14nm FinFET production and Airmont will send the ARM house of cards tumbling down. Should happen by January but by June 2014 absolute worst case. Of course, I think Haswell can do major damage as well. The sheer number of new product announcements during the remainder of 2013 should have a devastating effect...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368147741265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 21:02:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368148394053-151</Id><Title>Acer projects second-quarter sales of Windows 8 laptops and hybrids to be double that of first quarter, said JT Wang, Acer chairman and CEO</Title><Msg>Acer projects second-quarter sales of Windows 8 laptops and hybrids to be double that of first quarter, said JT Wang, Acer's chairman and CEO</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1368148394053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 21:13:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368152576711-152</Id><Title>Best of Romit Shaw - one from the vault</Title><Msg>About 2 years ago - around the time Apple decided to select TSMC for 20nm - oh well the times are a changing....Intel far better positioned nowadays to be Apple 's fab of choice @ 14nm.... correct me if I'am wrong but 4G LTE will be integrated into 14nm SoC - all componenbts not just CPU are benefitting from TriGate. Nomura Research’s chip analyst Romit Shah this morning offers an “open letter” to Intel (INTC) CEO Paul Otellini in which he suggests the company license ARM Holdings’s (ARMH) microprocessor instruction set, possibly buy Texas Instrument’s (TXN) “OMAP” chip line for mobile devices, and consider a $20 billion buyback authorization. Shah reiterates a Neutral rating on Intel shares and a $22 price target. Intel shares this morning are down 23 cents, or 1%, at $19.52. Despite healthy earnings growth, Shah observes, Intel’s shares trade at an all-time low valuation, at a 30% discount to the S&amp;P. Referring to the “mea culpa” letter by Cisco Systems (CSCO) John Chambers two weeks ago, Shah thinks Otellini faces a similar moment of truth. “Although Intel’s operational execution has been strong, we believe aspects of the company’s strategy in mobile computing (handsets and tablets) have not been,” writes Shah. “Mobile, in our opinion, represents the biggest opportunity for Intel to restore growth and valuation.” The total “mobile computing market” of smartphones and tablets — apparently, excluding laptops, notebooks — will be 1.5 times the size of the PC market next year, Shah estimates. Intel’s x86 instruction set won’t catch up with ARM’s chip designs — and, by implication, the implementations of ARM’s instruction set by Nvidia (NVDA), et al. — no matter how good Intel is at fab’ing chips.....</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368152576711</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 22:22:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368152856277-153</Id><Topic><Title>Best of Romit Shaw - one from the vault</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368152576711</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 22:22:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We believe dual-core ARM- based SoCs today are 30-40% more power efficient on average than Intel’s current Atom offering. While Intel should bridge the power gap by further integration (SoC approach vs. a multi-chip offering) and die-shrinks using advanced processes, we believe ARM is likely to stay ahead on performance per watt. Intel could also consider buying Nvidia, but at a price tag of $7.5 billion based just on enterprise value, probably a bit too much to swallow, not to mention regulatory issues over Nvidia’s graphics chip dominance. So, TI’s “core wireless business” — basically, the OMAP chip line — might be had for just $3 billion. OMAP generated roughly $600mn in revenue in 2010. In addition, TI has a solid list of customers that include Nokia, Motorola, Samsung and RIM. The company also has a full wireless connectivity portfolio that would be complementary. Based on a multiple of 2.5x, we believe TI’s core wireless business is worth $3bn. At a minimum, Shah writes, Intel should repair its relationship with Microsoft (MSFT), whose Windows Phone 7 operating system will be running Nokia (NOK) phones in future, in one form or another. Qualcomm (QCOM) is currently the clear leader to supply chips for Win Phone 7, and Shah thinks Intel needs to get back together with Microsoft. A rapprochement would have the added benefit, Shah believes, of setting up Intel better for the expected release of a version of Windows that will support ARM-based chips as well as x86 for the PC market. Last, Shah recommends Intel buy back shares big time: We believe a large share repurchase makes sense for several reasons: (1) Intel is generating less than 1% on its existing cash balance, (2) debt is cheap, (3) the company has posted 20 consecutive years of positive free cash flow, and (4) this would be materially accretive to EPS. A $20bn share repurchase consisting of $10bn in cash and $10bn in debt would boost our 2011 EPS estimate by $0.35, or 18%, to $2.30. The company’s balance sheet would weaken from $12bn in net cash to $8bn in net debt. That said, we estimate that Intel will generate north of $5bn in free cash flow in 2011 and 2012 after-dividend payments of $4-5bn and capital expenditures of $9bn.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368152856277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 22:27:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368153133481-154</Id><Title>Guss on "doubling down"</Title><Msg>and some "advise" to new CEO.... We continue to believe Intel needs to license ARMH and focus on becoming a direct-to-OEM foundry. Gus Richard, Piper Jaffray: Rates Intel shares Neutral. “Krzanich has been rumored to be the lead candidate for some time. We view the selection of Mr. Krzanich as the company staying the course and not a positive development. In the post PC era, the company needs to transform the company and culture to adapt to a changing landscape. We continue to believe Intel needs to license ARMH and focus on becoming a direct-to-OEM foundry. Promoting the COO is doubling down on the manufacturing roadmap and does not address the issues the company is facing. We believe the market will view this announcement as a disappointing development. Maintain Neutral.”</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368153133481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 22:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368153894543-155</Id><Topic><Title>Guss on "doubling down"</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368153133481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 22:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do these guys not know that Intel already licenses ARM and it one of the TOP 10 ARM vendors. I make no defense of the list which is actually 15 entries long, but even if it is just Nomura's opinion it is an interesting talking point. And it is what Nomura is telling potential investors in ARM Holdings plc in a 53-page note to clients that re-assesses Nomura's long-term view of ARM as a potential investment. Nomura attributes the customer ranking to "Bloomberg data as of Nov 3, 2011," without much further discussion, except to say that ARM's customer base is broad and the company is not dependent on just a few customers. Here's that Nomura/Bloomberg list in full, ranked by percentage contribution to ARM's revenue in 2010. Intel 7.0% TSMC 5.7% Samsung 5.7% TI 4.6% NEC 3.5% ST 3.5% ZTE 2.8% Broadcom 2.6% AMD 2.5% Infineon 2.4% Apple 2.1% Qualcomm 2.0% Fujitsu 1.9% UMC 1.9% Lenovo 1.8%</Msg><Username>rjs5</Username><Timestamp>1368153894543</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 22:44:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368154213307-156</Id><Topic><Title>Best of Romit Shaw - one from the vault</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368152576711</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 22:22:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMAP generated roughly $600mn in revenue in 2010. In addition, TI has a solid list of customers that include Nokia, Motorola, Samsung and RIM. The company also has a full wireless connectivity portfolio that would be complementary. Based on a multiple of 2.5x, we believe TI’s core wireless business is worth $3bn. It's it still for sale? What brilliant piece of advise...TI dumped it...LOL Did Renesas Mobile find a buyer? nope</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1368154213307</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 22:50:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368154681723-157</Id><Title>INTC $26 +</Title><Msg>INTC will hit $26 + next week!!!!!!</Msg><Username>sss150</Username><Timestamp>1368154681723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 22:58:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368156269058-158</Id><Topic><Title>wallisweaver</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1368136737282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 17:58:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would be happy to see near $40 by July of this year. I'll make some free money then to buy the Asus Taichi hybrid with dual screen with 256 GB SSD and Intel's i7 processor.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1368156269058</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 23:24:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>