<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-05"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360041124617-1</Id><Title>Intel Wants Windows Phone Engineers</Title><Msg>[Let's hope that shorts can hang in until the Mobile World Congress later this month and really get their heads handed to them in a basket. Lots of exciting announcements and news coming out. Intel's mobility traction is ramping up...] [Motorola X phone, slew of smartphones, tablets and Ultrabooks, the Windows Phone...] "Yup, Intel is set to make a splash at Mobile World Congress later this month with a slew of smartphones, tablets and Ultrabooks, and we have also seen how LinkedIn was used to help recruit folks to help out with the upcoming Motorola X phone. Well, LinkedIn is in the spotlight again now, as we have word that Intel has published a job opportunity on LinkedIn which is looking out for Windows Phone engineers. One can read into that however one wants to, but how about this – could Intel be looking into a mobile platform as part of their future investment? The job listed at LinkedIn specifically requested for those who are experts in the Windows Phone environment, and it would be interesting to see what else the future will bring. At this point in time, Windows Phone devices are powered mostly by ARM with Qualcomm as the exclusive chip provider, but two is definitely company from our perspective, and neither do I think that three’s a crowd. The job description’s opening pitch reads as such, “Windows Phone Engineers: Intel would like to talk to you. If you have Windows phone expertise, the Intel site in Redmond would like to talk to you.”"</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360041124617</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 00:12:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360045294556-2</Id><Title>OBAMA's 2013 recession has started, Q1 GDP will be negative caused by higher taxes, GOV cuts and Boeing not shipping Aircraft</Title><Msg>OBAMA's 2013 recession has started, Q1 GDP will be negative caused by higher taxes, GOV cuts and Boeing not shipping Aircraft</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360045294556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 01:21:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360046845892-3</Id><Title>Time to buy again!</Title><Msg>Intel will explode to the upside starting in second quarter. - Haswell will spur PC pent-up refresh cycle as corporation adopt Windows 8 - Gross margins will get back above 60% as there will be no more excess capacity charges (factories utilization will be back to normal) nor impact of higher factory startup costs. - More design wins for smartphones with CloverTraill+. Don't be surprise to see phones with CloverTrail+ with LTE 4G support hitting US markets this year! - PCs hybrids will continue to blur the lines between tablets and PCs and more and more people will opt for a PC hybrid as 'best of both world' value proposition takes hold. - Possible huge foundries deals with Cisco and/or Apple.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1360046845892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 01:47:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360047097691-4</Id><Title>CloverTrail+ with qualcomm baseband = Intel smartphone for US market</Title><Msg>Why can't phone makers use Intel CPU/GPU with qualcomm's 4G LTE? Also on the 4th quarter conference call, P.O stated: "In 2013, we'll also begin to deliver the industry's first 22-nanometer tablet and smartphone SoCs to OEMs. We are now shipping our single-mode data LTE baseband to customers and over the course of the year, we'll begin delivering multimode data and voice modems to customers, giving us a full complement of competitive technologies to grow our device business." So don't count out an Intel-based smartphone with 4G LTE support for US market this year!</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1360047097691</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 01:51:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360047385284-5</Id><Title>Haswell intro will be true Windows 8 launch</Title><Msg>Expect thinner, lighter and longer lasting battery life with Haswell products. Imagine a thinner, lighter version of the following products: Lenovo Yoga Lenovo Helix Asus Asus Transformer Book TX300 All with over 10 hours of battery life!</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1360047385284</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 01:56:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360050935141-6</Id><Topic><Title>Time to buy again!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1360046845892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 01:47:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pps target?</Msg><Username>orieljudy</Username><Timestamp>1360050935141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 02:55:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360063170578-7</Id><Topic><Title>CloverTrail+ with qualcomm baseband = Intel smartphone for US market</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1360047097691</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 01:51:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was my impression...I was shocked. I thought razr i in the US would be announced by now. Fact is, QCOM is an enemy of INTC, so your dream union won't happen. Are these legal issues?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360063170578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 06:19:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360063233763-8</Id><Topic><Title>Time to buy again!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1360046845892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 01:47:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$32 for starters, IMO.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360063233763</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 06:20:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360064803575-9</Id><Topic><Title>CloverTrail+ with qualcomm baseband = Intel smartphone for US market</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1360047097691</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 01:51:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC and QCOM are probably the real competitors (rather than INTC and ARMH). I think the Clovertrail + QCOM baseband will not happen because noone would devote engineering resources to build it. Intel will not build a reference platform. QCOM will not build a reference platform. The industry is taking the short cut to the PC model where there is a small group of ODM who put logos on reference platforms.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360064803575</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 06:46:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360067384709-10</Id><Title>Intel is officially irrelevant - Sell this garbage</Title><Msg>These chips are no longer needed. Low power is their future, but their offerings are not competitive. Slow unwinding of assets.</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1360067384709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:29:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360067416875-11</Id><Title>ARMH Earnings Report</Title><Msg>I am surprised ARMH is up in pre-market. Whether the growth reset is to 19% (revenues), 16% (Pre-tax earnings) or 10% (share price), this report does not point to a $45 share price. They would need 30% growth for years to justify this. Why is the share price increase so low? With INTC just starting to eat their lunch, I expect no growth after this year. Today would be a good day to increase a short position.</Msg><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1360067416875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:30:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360067574540-12</Id><Title>INTC is going to $15</Title><Msg>it's over for this behemoth of fraud and bribery.</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1360067574540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:32:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360068098451-13</Id><Title>Bid and Ask price</Title><Msg>Does the pre-market bid and ask price have the dividend reduction factored in? Or is that not reflected until the market opens at 9:30?</Msg><Username>pharmtimes</Username><Timestamp>1360068098451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:41:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360068479196-14</Id><Topic><Title>Bid and Ask price</Title><Username>pharmtimes</Username><Timestamp>1360068098451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:41:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Different tickers will reflect it at different times. Use the trade price plus the difference from the close. I think the close was $21.16 so a trade price of $21.16 - 22.5 = $20.92 = unchanged if my math is correct.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360068479196</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:47:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360069145072-15</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is going to $15</Title><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1360067574540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:32:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is it like to live down in an outhouse hole? Please enlighten us?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360069145072</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:59:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360069161738-16</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is going to $15</Title><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1360067574540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:32:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First in response to your name. Likely you lost the election and I do not give a horses rump about your crying about your pride. Quit your crying. Obama and the growing left won and you LOST Get over It. Now about Intel to 15. AMD is ROADKILL! Bet it is out of business sometime in the next few years and it is not Intel that killed it. Those phones killed it. Intel 15? Yes--if it utterly fails to counter attack and get into phones and tablets, it will go to 15 and lower. However, likely Intel will be in volume in phones and tablets in 2014 and by 2015 end, Intel could be approaching 50% market share in smart phones using its Intel chip. 40 and higher is far more likely that is 15 but go ahead and make your bet. You could be right. But please spare us your political crying. The GOP is slowly but surely becoming the party of the 30%. Rural older white people party is the GOP. It's base is all getting old and dropping dead.</Msg><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1360069161738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:59:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360069467793-17</Id><Topic><Title>Bid and Ask price</Title><Username>pharmtimes</Username><Timestamp>1360068098451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:41:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks, so using a very simplistic example: if you sell pre-market at $21.12 you lost 4 cents on the closing price of yesterday but picked up the 22.5 cent dividend? So essentially the stock is down this morning compared to its closing price.</Msg><Username>pharmtimes</Username><Timestamp>1360069467793</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 08:04:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360069818642-18</Id><Topic><Title>Bid and Ask price</Title><Username>pharmtimes</Username><Timestamp>1360068098451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:41:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the stock is actually up today about 18 cents in premarket as it has basically almost covered the entire dividend reduction from the ex-dividend date reduction.</Msg><Username>spyeman</Username><Timestamp>1360069818642</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 08:10:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360069873211-19</Id><Title>Asus Fonepad - 7" Android Tablet running on Intel Lexington - $265</Title><Msg>Seems like we can look forward to a crop of Android Tablets based on Intel SoCs at MWC... =================== ASUS FonePad 7-inch Tablet Leaked, Packs Intel CPU and Android Jelly Bean ASUS is one the first company in the world that developed a tablet member of the Nexus tribe. As you probably guessed, I am talking about the popular Nexus 7 unveiled last year in June, synchronized with the debut of Android 4.1 Jelly Bean. The Nexus 7 became such a huge success mostly because of its technical specs and price point, using the same recipe that helped Amazon Kindle fire climb to the top of the best-selling Android tablets in Q4 2011. It seems that ASUS has learned its lesson from the the collaboration with Google, and after the rumor mill hinted that the Taiwan-based company will bring two new affordable tablets at MWC 2013, MeMo Pad 7 and MeMo Pad 10, today we’ve found out about a new cheap ASUS tablet. Apparently, ASUS is readying a new 7-inch tablet, named Fonepad. Yes, the name is a bit confusing, especially that the Taiwanese company already has the Padfone and Padfone 2 smartphone-tablet combo in its portfolio. But let’s forget the name and have a look inside the alleged ASUS Fonepad. Surprisingly enough, it looks like it will be underpinned by an Intel Atom CPU, as leaked Postel Indonesia’s database suggests. The reports are also indicating that the affordable ASUS Fonepad will boast a 7-inch display with IPS technology and a resolution of 1,2800 x 800, and if the price is right it might be a rival worthy of Google’s… errr, ASUS’ Nexus 7. The technical specs sheet also includes 1 GB of RAM, 16 GB of internal storage, 3 megapixel camera on the back of the case, Android 4.1 Jelly Bean out of the box and all the connectivity features worthy of a modern tablet: 3G, WiFi, Bluetooth, and GPS. The price of the ASUS Fonepad also leaked, and it seems that the 7-inch tablet will cost as much as $265. Will it be worth it? We can’t know yet, especially because we have very little info about the Atom Z2420 Lexington chipset. So far, Intel has only provided its processors for terminals meant for the emergent markets, and, to be honest, most of them came with sub-par performance. After the Kindle Fire and Nexus 7 changed people’s perspective on the affordable 7-inch tablets, as both provided decent performance, thus the Intel Lexington platform underpinning the ASUS Fonepad must meet their expectations. Well, at least it will come with above-par battery life, as Intel has always cared about this aspect of their chips. The reports are also claiming that the ASUS Fonepad will also have calling facilities, making the tablet even more interesting. Do you think the Taiwan-based company will bring the ASUS Fonepad at Mobile World Congress 2013 event that debuts later next month? androidDOTgs/asus-fonepad/</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1360069873211</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 08:11:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360070658490-20</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>poisoninsara</Username><Timestamp>1359740614322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:43:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this article.</Msg><Username>meadowblemilia</Username><Timestamp>1360070658490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 08:24:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360071579378-21</Id><Title>Why is INTC getting crushed in pre-market today??</Title><Msg>Especially when future are due to open much higher. Paul O. needs to step down now - utter failure.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1360071579378</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 08:39:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360071946127-22</Id><Topic><Title>Why is INTC getting crushed in pre-market today??</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1360071579378</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 08:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's at 21.12, and that's after having the Dividend taken out.....so it's doing very well, not "getting crushed". You are NOT an Intel shareholder and what you derive humor from is shameful.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1360071946127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 08:45:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360072382178-23</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA's 2013 recession has started, Q1 GDP will be negative caused by higher taxes, GOV cuts and Boeing not shipping Aircraft</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360045294556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 01:21:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget to blame Bush, too.</Msg><Username>gaspasser17</Username><Timestamp>1360072382178</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 08:53:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360072990848-24</Id><Title>ARMH IS ON FIRE IN PRE-MARKET TRADING!</Title><Msg>HI-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360072990848</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:03:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360073325349-25</Id><Topic><Title>INTC holding up in market retreat</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360002427686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:27:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alex, in a different post you explained (can't seem to find the post but just the same ) the arbitraze with the ex-dividend play that some use in order to shave some pennis. imo, it's bad for the markets that some do that instead of having a solid strategy play, like playing volitilty, but it is what it is. Also was mentioned that if for example , there is a huge puts buying the OMM will have to hedge by shorting (500,000 shares against 5000 puts) Intel. What's not clear to me is how is it hedge since the OMM will have to pay the divinded ? unless we asume that he is doing naked short behind the scene.. hope my Q. make sense tnkx</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1360073325349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:08:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360073449312-26</Id><Title>Euro Zone Economy Showing Signs of Recovery, Optimism Builds</Title><Msg>The euro zone's embattled economy has turned a corner, according to a business survey on Tuesday that showed businesses are more optimistic about the future but highlighted a growing chasm between the region's economies. Markit's Eurozone Composite PMI, which gauges business activity across thousands of companies and is seen as good gauge of growth, rose in January to a 10-month high of 48.6 from 47.2 in December - an improvement on the preliminary reading of 48.2. While still signalling a contraction as the index has been below the 50 mark that signifies growth since February last year, it has risen consistently in the last three readings. Private industry makes up nearly two-thirds of the euro zone's economy and worryingly for policymakers, the data showed a widening chasm between Germany - Europe's largest economy - and France, the bloc's second biggest. "The euro zone is showing clear signs of healing, with the downturn easing sharply in January and the region moving closer to stabilization in the first quarter," said Chris Williamson, chief economist at Markit.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360073449312</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:10:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360073538529-27</Id><Title>Shorts Continue Giving It Back, Giving It Back</Title><Msg>Shorts missed another chance to cover yesterday. We're going to do this all year long...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360073538529</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:12:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360073616666-28</Id><Title>never see 21.50 today sucks</Title><Msg>sucks</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360073616666</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:13:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360073829594-29</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts Continue Giving It Back, Giving It Back</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360073538529</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:12:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Walldork- Which has been the better investment over the last 2 years, ARMH or INTC? I won't hold my breath while waiting for an honest response...... or any response for that matter,</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360073829594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:17:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360073840097-30</Id><Title>intel sucks lower now the price payed never see that price today 22.00 pray list sucks stock market</Title><Msg>sucks</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360073840097</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:17:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360074021904-31</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts Continue Giving It Back, Giving It Back</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360073538529</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:12:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, we can be pretty darn sure that Waldo didn't have the guts to short it despite his never ending armh bashing and intc pumping</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1360074021904</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:20:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360074177023-32</Id><Topic><Title>Asus Fonepad - 7" Android Tablet running on Intel Lexington - $265</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1360069873211</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 08:11:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finally, good to see Android Tablets based on Intel. Though a bit surprised it was based on the low-end Lexington. I had expected such Tablets to be based on the new dual-core Intel is launching at MWC. Sort of raises the expectation that there will be a whole slew of Tablets based on the entire Medfield range. That will be very cool, especially after the long wait we had to put up with!</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1360074177023</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:22:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360074512507-33</Id><Title>Intel Only Semiconscious at Minyanville09:18am EST</Title><Msg>Intel and Wallis the Pumper have something in common. TOOOOO FUNNNNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360074512507</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:28:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360074582251-34</Id><Topic><Title>Time to buy again!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1360046845892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 01:47:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm waiting till Friday, will probably get a little boost today, then drop wednesday, thursday and possibly friday... I'll buy more around 20.50 and then again around $20 if it goes that low...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1360074582251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:29:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360076068563-35</Id><Topic><Title>Time to buy again!</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1360046845892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 01:47:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Put "bacbacker" on the Wallis Alias List.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360076068563</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:54:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360076194219-36</Id><Topic><Title>INTC holding up in market retreat</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360002427686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:27:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your question makes perfect sense. Your confusion makes perfect sense too. Welcome to the club. 8-) Disclosure: I have no special knowledge other than what I have read in public documents (SEC, ....) and have pieced together over several years of observations. The OMM prices the dividend into the option price. As the ex-dividend day gets near, the dividend premium gets 100% reflected into the PUT and 0% reflected into the Call. That is why Intel call options are so cheap when compared to the puts. The day of ex-dividend, the dividend effect springs back to normal with near 50%/50% match of put/call premium. Arbitraging is "trying to take advantage of this pricing discontinuity". The OMM is a special trader who combined the short + selling the option to make a profit. He made sure that he could short the stock at a high enough price to guarantee a small profit before he did it. Someone entered a trade that required the OMM to supply 5000 puts. He filled the order when he could short INTC at a price that made the equation work: STRIKE PRICE + DIVIDEND + costs + PENNY PROFIT = SHORT + PUT PREMIUM The spread on the options allows for him to do this. One reason that shares trade near strike prices is that OPTION PREMIUMS are highest at the strike prices because the leverage is highest. NOTE: many times that the option trades are complex and involve many legs. If you read on synthetic option strategy .... and understand the SYNTHETIC LONG and SYNTHETIC SHORT you will be on your way. synthetic option arbitrage</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360076194219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:56:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360076399855-37</Id><Topic><Title>IMPORTANT INFO - INTC</Title><Username>hollyfrancoisn937</Username><Timestamp>1360076318037</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:58:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is turning out to be a great pick, these guys alerted it first.</Msg><Username>ladonnajcl718</Username><Timestamp>1360076399855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:59:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360076640499-38</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts Continue Giving It Back, Giving It Back</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360073538529</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:12:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mistakenly believe that shorts didn't cover. Of course many do and the price falls. Unthinkable to you, but they force sales and cover.....again and again, but you just don't recognize it. You also believe shorts are one huge block. They aren't They are just traders. Long money has been very weak. You can see that right? You believe you know so much that you can learn nothing at all.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1360076640499</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:04:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360076716717-39</Id><Title>Why is ARMH stock outperforming INTC so badly??</Title><Msg>The sentiment needs to change very soon or there will be a "tipping point" in the industry &amp; Intel will have no more time left to compete.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1360076716717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:05:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360076907880-40</Id><Title>never see 22 again sucks</Title><Msg>sucks</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360076907880</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:08:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360077146836-41</Id><Topic><Title>INTC holding up in market retreat</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360002427686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:27:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The open interest left over from yesterdays trades that I described. The 5,000 $25 MAY puts &amp; calls are still open. The puts may be an exit following the ex-dividend or part of a different trade. It is rarely possible to tell whether an option trade was triggered by the OMM or someone else. It is also tough to know who was on which side and what their motive was. 8.8k Jan 2015 $15 strike OPEN INTEREST 8.4k 1.6k Jan 2015 $13 strike OPEN INTEREST 328 38k Jan 2014 $15 OPEN INTEREST 2.7k looks like 35000 call contracts involved 2k Jan 2014 $13 OPEN INTEREST 118 3k Jan 2014 $10 OPEN INTEREST 113 26k Feb $20 OPEN INTEREST 2.9k looks like 20000 call contracts involved around 50,000 call contracts missing and reflects about 5,000,000 INTC shares.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360077146836</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:12:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360077367484-42</Id><Title>I thought INTC closed at 21.15 yesterday?</Title><Msg>what is going on.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1360077367484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:16:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360077571858-43</Id><Topic><Title>Asus Fonepad - 7" Android Tablet running on Intel Lexington - $265</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1360069873211</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 08:11:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting product. This is just beginning of Intel's transformation of the tablet and smartphone industry. We will see Intel inside every device category and every price point with performance and features that are best-in-class. Over the next 24 months Intel will deliver innovation and improvements on a schedule never before seen by Intel, or anyone else. Improvements on this pace and scale are unprecedented in the semiconductor industry and it is very likely it will reset everyone's exectations what performance means.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360077571858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:19:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360078176513-44</Id><Topic><Title>INTC could happen to be the ticker to watch this quarter.</Title><Username>hammondalan846</Username><Timestamp>1360067410040</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:30:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thats why i signed up</Msg><Username>hillschristopher621</Username><Timestamp>1360078176513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:29:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360078275622-45</Id><Topic><Title>I thought INTC closed at 21.15 yesterday?</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1360077367484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:16:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>minus the dividend .225.</Msg><Username>jin_18do8</Username><Timestamp>1360078275622</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:31:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360078728994-46</Id><Title>sucks never see my cost sucks</Title><Msg>sucks</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360078728994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:38:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360079495251-47</Id><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Msg>can someone tell me if this is another 52-week high... or if it's a new all-time high... ARMH just released its numbers... up 20% from a year ago... WOW !!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360079562046-48</Id><Title>Good Thing So Many Sold at Lower Prices Yesterday to Miss Out on Free Cash</Title><Msg>So I could buy their shares for less and keep the free cash.</Msg><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1360079562046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:52:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360079614426-49</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No surprise. Mobile is a rapidly growing industry and they've had the market mostly to themselves. That era is ending.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360079614426</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:53:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360079644291-50</Id><Topic><Title>sucks never see my cost sucks</Title><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360078728994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:38:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Must suck to be you, crybaby. Sure sucks to see your non-stop whining. If you listen to Lucy's in-law, Wilder Blitch, you'd know that Intel always returns to 23.02.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360079644291</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:54:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360079750051-51</Id><Title>Dell Buyout = $24.4 Billion Cash to Drive INTC Prices Higher</Title><Msg>But please keep selling the day before the free cash dividend so I can buy more of your cheaper shares and keep more of the free cash.</Msg><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1360079750051</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:55:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360079976614-52</Id><Topic><Title>IMPORTANT INFO - INTC</Title><Username>hollyfrancoisn937</Username><Timestamp>1360076318037</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:58:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the pickers over at this site really comprehend how the stock market keeps going.</Msg><Username>lorettagcf830</Username><Timestamp>1360079976614</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:59:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360080055553-53</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In a rapidly growing industry... growth is NOT a zero-sum game... Looking ahead to growth in BIG DATA... as you said, "That era is ending." ARM will be everywhere ... !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360080055553</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:00:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360080789266-54</Id><Title>Next Year $44 ARMH May Earn What $21 INTC Pays in Diividend</Title><Msg>ARMH should just issue more ARMH shares using the proceeds to buy INTC shares to collect the big dividends and ARMH earnings would grow 2x more.</Msg><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1360080789266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:13:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360080854471-55</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In a growing market the total unit size may grow but it is a zero sum game because at any given time there are a finite number of customers for all product categories. What analysts will be looking for going forward is how much of the new growth, and market share, will Intel take - and how much will be at ARM's expense. That is inevitable.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360080854471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:14:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360080895480-56</Id><Topic><Title>Why is ARMH stock outperforming INTC so badly??</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1360076716717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:05:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seek professional help.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1360080895480</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:14:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360081062940-57</Id><Topic><Title>Why is ARMH stock outperforming INTC so badly??</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1360076716717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:05:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's a jerk that gets please out of creating outrage. He thinks it's funny. Put him on ignore. I'm going to do it as of right now. He brings nothing to the forum other than chaos and lies about buying 10k shares every month.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1360081062940</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:17:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360081074156-58</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>East And if you look at where this stuff is starting to generate royalty, then we saw our first 28-nanometer royalties as well during this quarter and than And so the same equipment is available for everybody, and there's no reason why Intel should have a long-term sustainable lead. I think this comment really reveals how naive East is. There are two choices: 1.) quit like TI or scale back like Freescale, ST 2.) spend a ton on capex and live with lower margins TI is in great position compared to other ARM players because they are very strong in analog. gotta be careful shorting ARM - some people are more stupid than one can imagine.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360081074156</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:17:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360081413816-59</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey 61 - tell that to NVDA - Me think East is getting decoupled from reality And so the same equipment is available for everybody, and there's no reason why Intel should have a long-term sustainable lead.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360081413816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:23:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360082090768-60</Id><Title>Dellnot worth HALF of what it wants- STAY AWAY FROM</Title><Msg>Don't put good money after bad</Msg><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1360082090768</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:34:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360082356781-61</Id><Topic><Title>INTC could happen to be the ticker to watch this quarter.</Title><Username>hammondalan846</Username><Timestamp>1360067410040</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:30:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great strategy imo</Msg><Username>morrison.erro</Username><Timestamp>1360082356781</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:39:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360082534944-62</Id><Title>4% yeild this thing seems safer than</Title><Msg>30 year bonds. if your time line is 30 years no worries.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1360082534944</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:42:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360082798295-63</Id><Topic><Title>Why is ARMH stock outperforming INTC so badly??</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1360076716717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:05:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because you don't own it. Buy some and it will go down for you. ;)</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1360082798295</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:46:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360083723664-64</Id><Topic><Title>Next Year $44 ARMH May Earn What $21 INTC Pays in Diividend</Title><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1360080789266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:13:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's...actually a really profound idea.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360083723664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:02:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360084277867-65</Id><Topic><Title>Why is ARMH stock outperforming INTC so badly??</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1360076716717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:05:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are comparing stock price to product and market. The sentiment to which you refer is the stock price. However, industry will not ignore a superior product if it is available. Stop sniveling, you show your ignorance.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1360084277867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:11:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360084313593-66</Id><Title>Writing on the wall for ARMH</Title><Msg>I didn't go to CES this year but one of my friends went and said there wasn't a lot to get excited about. No real big introductions. I mentioned that ARM based products really haven't improved dramatically since last year. He said that what he saw was newer versions of the same old same old. So, don't take my word for it, go over to the ARMH website and read the blog about CES. Someone named Jim Wallace wrote about ARMH at CES. In the article he mentioned ARM 9 times. Here's the first paragraph "CES was a great show for ARM, there were plenty of ARM powered smartphones, families of Mali™ GPU enabled Android tablets, from entry level brands to the latest Google Nexus 10 with 2.5K displays, and larger than ever Mali GPU enabled 4K smartTVs." Smart TV's and 4K TVs? The Smart TV was on display last year at CES. They were neat to play with for a few minutes, but it wasn't anything that made me want to go out and buy one. The 4K displays were also demo'd last year. The panel makers are in a bit of a loss. They felt certain that consumers wanted 3D TV. Nope. In order to enjoy 4K you need two things. a TV large enough to really show all 4000 pixels and a hell of a lot more data coming in to populate all those pixels. Consumers demanding 4K tvs in the next year or two isn't a pipe dream, it's a crack pipe dream. We're talking about consumers, the people who are happy streaming movies in 720p. So what was missing from CES for ARMH? The dangling carrot. Every year there has been something that ARM has presented that made consumers say "Wow, I need that." If it didn't happen at CES we'd know that Apple would have it a few weeks later at a press conference. Neither happened this year. ARMH has stated again and again that it has a two year lead with Intel. It could use this lead to distance itself from Intel. I am not saying that ARMH isn't a strong company or it doesn't have a viable future. All I am asking is what is it doing with this lead? Where is the next big thing for ARMH? I see plans of down the road things like data centers and 4K TVs. What is the hot ARMH product consumers are dreaming about that they can get this year? A Nexus 10 tablet? Anything else?</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1360084313593</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:11:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360084636340-67</Id><Topic><Title>Writing on the wall for ARMH</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1360084313593</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:11:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just how exactly does ARM have a 2 year lead on Intel in anything?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360084636340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:17:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360084736502-68</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Hey 61 - tell that to NVDA - " NVDA is down for their R&amp;D is a year behind their roadmap... "Me think East is getting decoupled from reality " Reality is ARMH is at new highs... !!!!! "there's no reason why Intel should have a long-term sustainable lead." Yes, even with superior fabs... ya won't need x86... The world is going ARM...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360084736502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:18:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360084794171-69</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'ARM will be everywhere ... !!!!' ... except in successful profitable Nvidia chips ;-). This is not an all time high, they did $48.60 in y2k. Their eps just made expectations which shows margins are getting squeezed contrary to their BS story. We are near the top of this bubble and ARMH will be $10-15 within 5 years around the same time when INTC will be $40-50. A15 is going to be a commercial failure, it's too hot to run at full clockspeeds in phones, it will be outperformed in performance/power by Atom and performance by Core processors. Never mind any future fabrication dead-ends they have already reached a design dead-end with A15. Nvidia has to create a portable console to sell theirs because no-one is interested in putting it in a tablet or phone ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360084794171</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:19:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360085085356-70</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank You... just have to settle for another 52-week high... as previously claimed... ARMH is a rubber stamp... Time will show what the world can do with their ISA... starts 2014</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360085085356</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:24:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360085481898-71</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NVDA is down for a lot more reasons than just being one year behind on an already poor roadmap. They are 2 years behind in reality if you go back far enough in time to see their Project Denver projections for 2012 ! Tegra is not a successful commercial product and does not look likely to be in the near future. It was supposed to replace the motherboard business profits and has failed in that regard. Low to medium end discrete gpus are being squeezed out of the market by each new generation of Intel and AMD on-die gpus and that's just going to continue with Haswell. Nvidia is a company treading water on legacy business, you should have put your money in ARMH instead if you like their business model so much because NVDA is not going anywhere fast for the foreseeable future.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360085481898</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:31:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360085558174-72</Id><Topic><Title>I thought INTC closed at 21.15 yesterday?</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1360077367484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:16:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so the div came off stock price close yesterday? it did not pay yesterday did it...even if it did should not come off stock price?</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1360085558174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:32:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360085741371-73</Id><Topic><Title>INTC recent info</Title><Username>rexhiver24</Username><Timestamp>1360079630499</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:53:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool picks.</Msg><Username>adianst0cks01</Username><Timestamp>1360085741371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:35:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360085749504-74</Id><Topic><Title>I thought INTC closed at 21.15 yesterday?</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1360077367484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:16:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that really makes no sense...the share holder pays for his own div?</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1360085749504</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:35:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360085996150-75</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"you should have put your money in ARMH" already did... "NVDA is not going anywhere fast for the foreseeable future." It's why they now have a dividend...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360085996150</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:39:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360086163772-76</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At what price did you buy ARMH ?</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360086163772</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:42:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360086443879-77</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mid twenties... bought on the way down... then bought more as it jumped back up had a great run... stops now at 40... just in case...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360086443879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:47:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360087564073-78</Id><Topic><Title>I thought INTC closed at 21.15 yesterday?</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1360077367484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:16:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On EX-DIV date (which is today 02/05/2013 for INTC) the price of the stock is reduced by the amount of the dividend (in this case 22.5 cents). The company pays the share holders the dividend, unless you are short, in which case you pay the dividend. Google "what is ex-dividend date" and it will hopefully make more sense. Basically, the company is worth that much less after paying the dividend, so the stock price is adjusted to reflect that.</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1360087564073</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 13:06:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360087617282-79</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I break wind in your direction.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1360087617282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 13:06:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360087627402-80</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And so the same equipment is available for everybody, and there's no reason why Intel should have a long-term sustainable lead. you still don't get it do you? Don't quote out of context - I understand that was not the first time "Yes, even with superior fabs" what are fabs equipped with - you just contradict yourself. And so the same equipment is available for everybody . East is applying the ARM model to the equipment industry/ process technology - there are 2 things: 1.) the equipment that everybody can buy 2.) than there is process technology to make real chips - it's not a plug and play like East #$%$umes. How many years did it take for TSMC to figure out HKMG - sure they could buy all the equipment that Intel bought. Do I give a rats #$%$ about ARM at 52 week high - hell not BECAUSE I know ARM eco system will spend tons on capex just to keep up</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360087627402</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 13:07:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360088147774-81</Id><Topic><Title>I thought INTC closed at 21.15 yesterday?</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1360077367484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:16:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hummm...did not know that thanks. so did we get paid the div?</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1360088147774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 13:15:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360088180232-82</Id><Topic><Title>Writing on the wall for ARMH</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1360084313593</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:11:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was the bold statement the little elf of a president of ARMH made last year. You cannot deny that ARMH has a lead in mobile. My point is that they have done nothing to increase the distance, if anything they've fallen behind making catching up for Intel a little bit easier.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1360088180232</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 13:16:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360088525650-83</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How many years did it take for TSMC to figure out HKMG - sure they could buy all the equipment that Intel bought." How many years has did it take INTC to get MIC... ?? INtel even gave up on the GPU architecture side of it... So repeat: "Yes, even with superior fabs"</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360088525650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 13:22:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360088555652-84</Id><Topic><Title>Asus Fonepad - 7" Android Tablet running on Intel Lexington - $265</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1360069873211</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 08:11:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gsmarenaDOTcom/xolo-x500-gets-benchmarked-sports-intel-atom-z2420-cpu/ Xolo X500 and its Intel Atom Z2420 CPU get benchmarked, get pretty good scores January 31st, 2013, 20:20 bySunil26 comments Xolo X500, which was launched a week ago in India, has just been benchmarked. The smartphone is designed for emerging markets with low cost at higher priority than stellar performance, but it did surprisingly well. Perhaps a part of the explanation is that the Intel chip also uses its hyper threading technology, which has better multi-tasking ability. The smartphone is powered by a 1.2 GHz Intel Atom Lexington Z2420 processor along with Power VR SGX540 GPU. The Atom-powered Xolo X500 is right behind the Xolo X900, which is powered by the Medfield chipset in the Quadrant benchmark tests. However the X500 managed to beat its more expensive sibling at the AnTuTu benchmark. The smartphone aggregates 12859 points in the AnTuTu 3.0 benchmark, which is not bad at all. Xolo X500 is on top of Vellamo 1.0 browser benchmark tests too and scores a hefty 1168 and 421 points in the HTML5 web browser tests and CPU subsystem performance respectively The X500 also managed to max out the NenaMark 2 benchmark. At the onscreen GLBenchmark test it only managed 18fps, but it should still do pretty well with all but the heaviest games.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1360088555652</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 13:22:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360088814584-85</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many years has did it take INTC to get MIC... ?? What does this have to do with manufacturing ? Absolutely nothing</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360088814584</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 13:26:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360089159503-86</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As always !!! You remain oblivious to architecture... With INTC having superior fabs... ARMH breaking new highs...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360089159503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 13:32:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360089487555-87</Id><Topic><Title>I thought INTC closed at 21.15 yesterday?</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1360077367484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:16:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb and Dumber! TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360089487555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 13:38:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360090238757-88</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good trading but your stops show you realize it's a bubble unsupported by its relatively poor real earnings ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360090238757</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 13:50:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360090594285-89</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Back to East statement And so the same equipment is available for everybody, and there's no reason why Intel should have a long-term sustainable lead. As always !!! You remain oblivious to architecture... Ask TI - I red the reviews of TI chip from last year . Everybody seemed to be very impressed - so what happened 61? TI was first in figuring out a cut throat business coupled with higher cost. Intel CPU and SoC now in synch Intel will leverage CPU volume to get very low cost for SoC's - The days of "cheap" ARM 4xnm are a thing of the past - now it's all about huge fix cost and how to deal/absorb them quickly. ARM is loosing its edge with respect to power/performance and even more importantly with regards to cost</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360090594285</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 13:56:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360090860866-90</Id><Title>getanid61 &amp; Marsavian</Title><Msg>@ getanid61 Do you not know what a bubble is? ARM is expected to make $0.86/share in 2013. That, for the mathematically challenged, bubble-loving ARM pumpers, is $394M in net income. Intel pays out $1.1B/quarter in dividends. They literally just give away 3x ARM's net income to people just for holding a piece of paper that says "I own Intel". @ marsavian What's your bet on when the ARMH bubble pops? What catalyst do you think it will take to get people running for the exits?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360090860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:01:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360091029715-91</Id><Topic><Title>Writing on the wall for ARMH</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1360084313593</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:11:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kinda sucks when your competitor makes $11 - $12B per year in net income, after of course spending $10B/yr in R&amp;D. ARM's revenues are what? Gonna be $1B next year? LOL</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360091029715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:03:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360091260506-92</Id><Title>WAH WAH--I want my freaking country back you surrender monkey republicans.</Title><Msg>I thought you were going to go Clint Eastwood and hold strong against Obummer but now I see you are in complete surrender mode like a Confederate seeing Sherman Yankees in Georgia. Yeah I see--all you GOP governors who said you WOULD not do Obama care are all caving and saying it is great now. Arizona and Ohio governors looking like Obummers little bbbtccches. Pathetic. I will hold up in a hole under my yard and make sure that I have food for years. I do not need sex, I am #$%$. I do not need work--I am retired and useless. Yeah sure--I could go help young people and be nice but I would rather cry like an old angry Rushfatbaugh man. I would rather suck my own #$%$ that give into you Libs. What? You Libs say suck your #$%$ too? I will ask Clint and get back to you on that. Intel to 40 and my Repuke party to hhhaeeeeelll.</Msg><Username>amdsuckks</Username><Timestamp>1360091260506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:07:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360091269123-93</Id><Topic><Title>getanid61 &amp; Marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360090860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf Eassa is another of Waldo's aliases. NEVER FORGET THAT WALLIS IS ALWAYS HERE! HI-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360091269123</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:07:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360091311899-94</Id><Topic><Title>getanid61 &amp; Marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360090860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360091311899</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:08:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360092246919-95</Id><Topic><Title>WAH WAH--I want my freaking country back you surrender monkey republicans.</Title><Username>amdsuckks</Username><Timestamp>1360091260506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:07:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Calling ALL G0P Cl0wns t0 the Big Top Pee Wee Cl0wn Circus!!!</Msg><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1360092246919</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:24:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360092577653-96</Id><Title>Ron Paul hits home with the truth. GOPtards are so so stupidl</Title><Msg>Chris Kyle's death seems to confirm that "he who lives by the sword dies by the sword." Treating PTSD at a firing range doesn't make sense</Msg><Username>amdmonkey7</Username><Timestamp>1360092577653</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:29:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360092629887-97</Id><Topic><Title>INTC recent info</Title><Username>rexhiver24</Username><Timestamp>1360079630499</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:53:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just joined.</Msg><Username>davidhanzzs</Username><Timestamp>1360092629887</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:30:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360092636304-98</Id><Title>Caution- Sucker Alert!</Title><Msg>Market overextended. Insiders selling. People like Nuff buying on margin with both fists.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1360092636304</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:30:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360093023158-99</Id><Topic><Title>I thought INTC closed at 21.15 yesterday?</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1360077367484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:16:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I should have said they pay the dividend on the Pay Date which in this case is March 1, 2013. As long as you bought or held the stock yesterday, you will collect the the dividend.</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1360093023158</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:37:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360093094989-100</Id><Topic><Title>WAH WAH--I want my freaking country back you surrender monkey republicans.</Title><Username>amdsuckks</Username><Timestamp>1360091260506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:07:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>angry little guy. why so mad little fella?</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1360093094989</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:38:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360093257927-101</Id><Topic><Title>IMPORTANT INFO - INTC</Title><Username>hollyfrancoisn937</Username><Timestamp>1360076318037</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:58:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get awesome penny stock picks 5 minutes before everyone else!</Msg><Username>gracestaton</Username><Timestamp>1360093257927</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:40:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360093960581-102</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Ask TI - I red the reviews of TI chip from last year . Everybody seemed to be very impressed - so what happened 61? " There are winners &amp; losers... TI lost... "ARM is loosing its edge with respect to power/performance" Never really had it... was due to academic simplicity in their cores... ARMH is a rubber stamp...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360093960581</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:52:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360093968503-103</Id><Title>Dell going private - not good for Intel</Title><Msg>According to the analysts all over TV today. PC is dead is their mantra. of course, Paul O. says &amp; does nothing to protect the PC &amp; Intel's brand.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1360093968503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:52:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360094266835-104</Id><Topic><Title>Writing on the wall for ARMH</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1360084313593</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:11:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clearly both Intel and ARM have opportunities to go after each other's markets but all things considered Intel is far better positioned to capture ARM's business than vice versa. - Lenovo K900 released to very good reviews and the benchmarks shows Intel's dual-core SoC's rivaling Samsung's quad-core in Galaxy phones. - The x86-based Surface Pro arrives to retail this week. This introduces a totally new class of tablets for enterprise and those needing to do more than play games. - New Ultrabooks and convertibles are arriving on the market that can displace some iPad and Android tablet sales. - New low x86 Android tablets arriving on the market (see the Asus product) that will compete head-to-head against Android tablets with ARM. - And Intel's product release schedule this year and next is absolutely phenomenal. But where is ARM's competition to Intel's server business? It's hardly more than a dream.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360094266835</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:57:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360094571821-105</Id><Topic><Title>Caution- Sucker Alert!</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1360092636304</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:30:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Insiders sell every January in this company-- market may be overextended some but INTC is too good a company with way too much R and D $$$ and talented brainiacs to not be successful long term.</Msg><Username>erasedbygrace</Username><Timestamp>1360094571821</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:02:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360094816329-106</Id><Title>BUY BUY BUY the market. CNBC the market can never go down BUY,BUY,BUY NOT WALL STREET is selling</Title><Msg>BUY BUY BUY the market. CNBC the market can never go down BUY,BUY,BUY NOT WALL STREET is selling</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360094816329</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:06:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360095079748-107</Id><Topic><Title>Dell going private - not good for Intel</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1360093968503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:52:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So when Dell goes private they are going to exit the PC business? What are they going to do instead, make toilet paper?</Msg><Username>bot_feeder</Username><Timestamp>1360095079748</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:11:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360095495065-108</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ask TI - I red the reviews of TI chip from last year . Everybody seemed to be very impressed - so what happened 61? ---- TI was a big supplier to Nokia... with the jump to Windows, meant a jump to Qualcomm's chips.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1360095495065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:18:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360095736688-109</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A15 is going to be a commercial failure, it's too hot to run at full clockspeeds in phones, it will be outperformed in performance/power by Atom and performance by Core processors. Never mind any future fabrication dead-ends they have already reached a design dead-end with A15. Nvidia has to create a portable console to sell theirs because no-one is interested in putting it in a tablet or phone ;-). ---- :) I think you are going to be surprised at the performance/power/price profile of the A15 family over the next few months...</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1360095736688</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:22:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360095820974-110</Id><Title>ARM Breaking New Highs and Getting Ready to Break</Title><Msg>Thinking this would be a good time to don some earmuffs. It's gonna blow. ARM bubble trouble and fading fabrication. A combustible combination. Wall Street just sent out for more ARM-flavored Kool-Aid...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360095820974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:23:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360095966292-111</Id><Title>Upstream supply chain sees good profit from Intel Classmate PC shipments</Title><Msg>Despite fierce competitions within the notebook and the tablet markets, netbook and tablet products are currently still seeing good demand in the education segment, especially Intel's Classmate PC and Studybook products, which have a higher gross margin than standard PC products and can assist their upstream suppliers to achieve profit, according to sources from the upstream supply chain. Intel has already shipped more than 10 million Classmate PCs since the launch of the device and is expected to ship 3-4 million StudyBook tablets in 2013. Intel's Classmate PC orders are mostly from emerging markets such as China, Turkey, Thailand and India as well as countries in Eastern Europe and Latin America. From Monica Chen</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360095966292</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:26:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360096070319-112</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH - breaking new highs...</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360079495251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>":) I think you are going to be surprised at the performance/power/price profile of the A15 family over the next few months..." [Well, that or the lack of...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360096070319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:27:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360097435552-113</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Breaking New Highs and Getting Ready to Break</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360095820974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:23:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The rapidly growing mobile market can easily mask the impact Intel's assault will have on ARM for a while (possibly even a year ) because Intel's presence will not show up as fewer total sales to ARM but rather as a slower rate of growth for ARM which is more difficult to identify as many market expansion can be influenced by many things. However, once the slower growth-rate has been spotted in ARM's business, along with concurrent rise in Intel's, the inflection point will have occurred and the bubble will have ended. One undeniable fact is that ARM cannot remain unaffected by Intel's focused pursuit of the mobile business.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360097435552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:50:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360097459453-114</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES INTC</Title><Username>christopherlee418</Username><Timestamp>1360091341355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:09:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that is an ad that hints at every possible outcome, nonsense.</Msg><Username>instock123</Username><Timestamp>1360097459453</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:50:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360097552004-115</Id><Topic><Title>Caution- Sucker Alert!</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1360092636304</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:30:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Insider selling across the board, not Intel in particular. Also, referring to short term. Am balls to the walls long myself but don't want to hold this forever.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1360097552004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:52:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360097688346-116</Id><Title>Mixed messages from top brokerage firms</Title><Msg>As of this month , 5/8 analysts i follow HOLD. Rest slightly bullish with buy, but at risk. Hold at risk.</Msg><Username>instock123</Username><Timestamp>1360097688346</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:54:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360098587972-117</Id><Topic><Title>Writing on the wall for ARMH</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1360084313593</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:11:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The thing that you have to appreciate about Intel is that they don't stop. If they introduce a product and it's bad they'll introduce another one that is better, and follow it up by another one that is even better. This is the thing that ARMH needs to worry about the most. Their problem in a nutshell is that they cannot improve as quickly as Intel can. Tic Toc , Tic Toc.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1360098587972</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:09:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360098753323-118</Id><Title>ARM Holdings plc (ARMH) - $43.69 +1.74( +4.15%)</Title><Msg>LOLOL INTC getting creamed. Look at the last 5 years, bet ya wished you had bought ARMH instead of this POS</Msg><Username>armhisit</Username><Timestamp>1360098753323</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:12:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360099758789-119</Id><Topic><Title>getanid61 &amp; Marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360090860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'What's your bet on when the ARMH bubble pops?' This time next year for the start of the sea change in both ARMH and INTC. Haswell, Atom and Windows 8 will be having a noticeable effect on the ARM ecosystem by then. 'What catalyst do you think it will take to get people running for the exits?' Reality not matching forecasts. Could also just be hard resistance as AAPL found when it hit 700. I think all the analysts have got confused with the initial adopter enthusiasm for a new form factor e.g. tablets being the start of a trend that will never end but the market will get saturated in time like all the other form factors and not everyone will change their iPad/Android tablet when a new model comes along just like they don't now with PCs and laptops. Forecasts will be adjusted to fit reality and ARMH will start to suffer then.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360099758789</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:29:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360099771530-120</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Suppliers</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359086777970</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 23:06:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"All of Apple's suppliers have tanked. Except ARM. They're next..." Yeah, ARMH is just getting decimated. Meanwhile, INTC is on fire!</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1360099771530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:29:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360100198005-121</Id><Title>armhisit</Title><Msg>Yet another new one man shill show user ID. With Intel moving up nicely today he had to fabricate something to get himself out of the fetal position. Who's your daddy, shill show? I guess shouting, "Tora, Tora, Tora!!!" didn't get the job done today...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360100198005</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:36:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360100633534-122</Id><Topic><Title>armhisit</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360100198005</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:36:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"With Intel moving up nicely today" We Walluses set the bar extremely low these days, eh?</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1360100633534</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:43:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360101095355-123</Id><Title>MWC 2013: Intel Takes Offensive in Battle for Mobile Supremacy</Title><Msg>MWC 2013: Intel Takes Offensive in Battle for Mobile Supremacy Two new SoCs: Atom Z2580 and Atom Z2420 Mobile Devices News Published: February 5, 2013 4:18 PM By Régis Jehl Translated by: Hugh Ehreth Send to a friend Three weeks from now, at the Mobile World Congress in Barcelona, Intel will be presenting two new SoCs for mobile devices. Should Nvidia, Qualcomm and Samsung be worried? At CES 2013 in Las Vegas, Intel's biggest talking point was its upcoming mobile SoC, Bay Trail. This new addition to the Atom range will have a new architecture with a finer transistor process. But it won't be released until late 2013/early 2014.</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1360101095355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:51:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360101158983-124</Id><Topic><Title>MWC 2013: Intel Takes Offensive in Battle for Mobile Supremacy</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1360101095355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Until then, the Santa Clara firm isn't just sitting on its laurels; it has just announced that it will be launching the Atom Z2580 and Z2420. The Z2580 is a high-end system-on-chip that will be featured in the Lenovo K900 smartphone. It has a 1.3 GHz dual-core processor with a turbo mode that boosts the clock rate up to 1.8 GHz and supports Hyper-Threading. As a result the SoC will behave as though it had four cores, two physical and two logic</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1360101158983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:52:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360101304594-125</Id><Title>Lenovo K900</Title><Msg>This is the kind of phone that im really waiting for. For sure this will land early in the Philippines after its launch in PRC,. . . Very elegant, this phone has distinctive personality and style. . . Lenovo phones are getting better. I predict that lenovo will outshadow samsung in china and south east asia in the near future! . . . I will definitely buy this one . . . Great design and specs' clover trail is amazing! . . .Gudluck LENOVO :-) more power!</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1360101304594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:55:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360101405606-126</Id><Topic><Title>MWC 2013: Intel Takes Offensive in Battle for Mobile Supremacy</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1360101095355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all this is good.............the day when Intel inside phones with LTE is launched in US - I will consider Intel has won the battle. Hope they do it soon!</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1360101405606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:56:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360101540461-127</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K900</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1360101304594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:55:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you just break out your Paul.Otelini alias and break down how the K900 will get Intel to 3.00 EPS ???!!</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1360101540461</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:59:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360101577725-128</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K900</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1360101304594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:55:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"sujit_98" is another Wallis alias</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1360101577725</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:59:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360102131491-129</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K900</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1360101304594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:55:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel plans big splash for Mobile World Congress By Don Reisinger | February 4, 2013 Submit Share Print More On android intel mobile world congress windows 8 Intel will be on hand later this month at the Mobile World Congress (MWC) in Barcelona with some smartphone technologies in hand, The Verge has reported</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1360102131491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:08:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360103456454-130</Id><Title>East on Windows RT</Title><Msg>Well, 2012 was the launch of RT, and our expectation was really satisfied that Microsoft proved they could bring a Windows operating system up on ARM technology. And it works, and it's fine. It is a very controlled release that Microsoft had done. They have very tightly controlled the number of chips, chip companies they're working with and the number of chips that they're working with and the number of OEM customers whom they're working with as well. Hello Samsung just dumped RT just picking up bits and pieces from East - mixture of kooky and nutty -IOW a typical Brit</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360103456454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:30:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360104007651-131</Id><Title>Not buying at this price</Title><Msg>Watching, but would not buy at this price.</Msg><Username>bdianed</Username><Timestamp>1360104007651</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:40:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360104154075-132</Id><Topic><Title>East on Windows RT</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360103456454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft must have also done a tightly controlled relase of customers too because there aren't very many of them. East has become the stand-up comic of semi's.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360104154075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:42:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360105051164-133</Id><Title>rally to 2200 pray list bust intel up</Title><Msg>buyback</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360105051164</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:57:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360107905497-134</Id><Topic><Title>East on Windows RT</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360103456454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>--- Microsoft must have also done a tightly controlled relase of customers too because there aren't very many of them. ---- That's true for both RT and Pro versions of Win8 tablets... It has nothing to do with ARM and everything to do with MSFT.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360107905497</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 18:45:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360107905577-135</Id><Topic><Title>East on Windows RT</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360103456454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>--- Microsoft must have also done a tightly controlled relase of customers too because there aren't very many of them. ---- That's true for both RT and Pro versions of Win8 tablets... It has nothing to do with ARM and everything to do with MSFT.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360107905577</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 18:45:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360108621588-136</Id><Topic><Title>East on Windows RT</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360103456454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surface Pro hasn't been available to consumers yet so on what basis are you making judgement on Win 8 Pro's success for tablets? The public has had access to the ARM based Win RT and they definitely weighed on that with a big yawn. Even Samsung canceled their RT product for the U.S. market for lack of interest. And yes, Win RT's disappoint has everything to do with ARM because it is not x86 compatible and can't run native Windows OS code or the legacy apps of the world's largest software ecosystem.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360108621588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 18:57:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360108882633-137</Id><Topic><Title>getanid61 &amp; Marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360090860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you attempting to put me down for choosing the horse that won ?? Attempting to let me know I'm a fool for making money... "Intel pays out $1.1B/quarter in dividends. " "They literally just give away 3x ARM's net income to people just for holding a piece of paper that says "I own Intel"." Yes, keeps support for the stock.. How low do you think INTC would be if they didn't pay a dividend...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360108882633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 19:01:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360109143992-138</Id><Topic><Title>East on Windows RT</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360103456454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oops. I posted this a bit early. I'll be sure to repost it in a couple of weeks when #$%$ sales numbers start to come out for it okay?</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360109143992</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 19:05:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360110399914-139</Id><Topic><Title>I thought INTC closed at 21.15 yesterday?</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1360077367484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:16:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whos on third? No Whos on first.....why i oughta.....</Msg><Username>dcchesnut</Username><Timestamp>1360110399914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 19:26:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360110592881-140</Id><Topic><Title>getanid61 &amp; Marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360090860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Are you attempting to put me down for choosing the horse that won ?? Attempting to let me know I'm a fool for making money..." [We have no evidence that you chose ARM with anything other than your mouth and not your wallet. Because it's after the fact. You need to post your buys in real time, fabrication boy...] [We're not trying to put you down because you like ARM. We dislike that you've come to the Intel board with your suite of lies, distortions and ARM propaganda just to bash Intel, not to mention your school boy angst and immaturity. If you want to pump ARM, then go hang out on the ARM board. You won't be missed. You're a punk...] [On second thought, stick around so we can all mock you when the ARM bubble pops and their fabrication fades to black...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360110592881</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 19:29:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360110705305-141</Id><Topic><Title>East on Windows RT</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360103456454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Oops. I posted this a bit early. I'll be sure to repost it in a couple of weeks when #$%$ sales numbers start to come out for it okay?" [BuzzBoy, what difference does it make if you make things up now or make them up later?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360110705305</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 19:31:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360112190227-142</Id><Topic><Title>getanid61 &amp; Marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360090860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>getanid61 was pumping NVDA at 22$ range</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1360112190227</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 19:56:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360113074921-143</Id><Title>I don't know why people keep comparing ARM vs Intel. ARM is nowhere in the picture</Title><Msg>when it comes to power, performance and price against Intel. Inferior ARM chips at a higher price cannot win the marketplace. Everything about ARM is Yesterdays news. If you look ahead, ARM has nothing going for it.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360113074921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 20:11:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360114376688-144</Id><Topic><Title>getanid61 &amp; Marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360090860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with Marsavian's timing projection but for different reasons. Towards the end of this year, Intel's game changing 22nm OOO trigate LP mobile SOC processor will be released. I think it'll take a few months for people to realize how it completely changes the mobile SOC game and they'll start exiting in hordes after that. ARMH is currently priced sentimentally, and Intel's holiday introduction will shake people out.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360114376688</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 20:32:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360114848641-145</Id><Topic><Title>I don't know why people keep comparing ARM vs Intel. ARM is nowhere in the picture</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360113074921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 20:11:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If you look ahead, ARM has nothing going for it." Doesn't ARM64 count for something... btw, did you notice ARMH is at a new 52-week high</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360114848641</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 20:40:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360114952302-146</Id><Topic><Title>armhisit</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360100198005</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:36:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How's that armh bashing working out there Waldo? holding INTC since 24.00 in June 2010 has kept you underwater for almost 3 years, dividends included. You talk about shorts giving up gains, and you've given up ripe ops to sell way up there at 29, 27.50, and the last best at 23.00. An old fool who has failed to learn any new tricks in years</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1360114952302</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 20:42:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360115818889-147</Id><Topic><Title>getanid61 &amp; Marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360090860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pot calling the kettle black there Waldork. We all know you've constantly been bashing ARMH, but had no guts to short it, otherwise you would have posted that trade in real time, just like you always do. what a doofus.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1360115818889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 20:56:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360116028838-148</Id><Topic><Title>I don't know why people keep comparing ARM vs Intel. ARM is nowhere in the picture</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360113074921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 20:11:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zdnetDOTcom/nvidia-high-performance-arm-servers-one-or-two-years-away-7000006513/ Nvidia: High performance ARM servers 'one or two years' away Summary: Nvidia believes that high-performance servers will remain the domain of the x86 architecture for the next few years, but that ARM processors, combined with the power of the GPU, will eventually take over. By Adrian Kingsley-Hughes for Hardware 2.0 | October 29, 2012 -- 09:43 GMT (02:43 PDT) While there's a certain allure to using ARM processors for server applications because of their low power consumption, Nvidia believes the chips won't be ready for high performance applications for a couple of years. Sumit Gupta, general manager of Nvidia's Tesla accelerated computing unit, sees the x86 architecture as being the king of the server room, for the time being at any rate. "Performance of these ARM cores is still not where it needs to be for servers. It is getting there; the new ARM64 is going to get it part of the way," said Gupta, as reported by The Inquirer. "One day I think ARM will at least get to similar performance levels as X86 performance. The belief is that over the next one or two years these ARM SoCs will be good enough for cloud applications and web serving. I think it will take some more time to be good enough for accelerated computing".</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1360116028838</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 21:00:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360116152344-149</Id><Topic><Title>I don't know why people keep comparing ARM vs Intel. ARM is nowhere in the picture</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360113074921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 20:11:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Arm64 hipe is inflated as arm's pe</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1360116152344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 21:02:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360118372418-150</Id><Topic><Title>I don't know why people keep comparing ARM vs Intel. ARM is nowhere in the picture</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360113074921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 20:11:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM64 is going to get it PART of the way? in 1-2 years? Intel's Atom 64bit is already there and selling for $50. And ATOM64 will only get a lot better with Baytrail and 22nm. ARM64 will ALWAYS be INFERIOR to Atom64, and with NO software compatibility, its as good as DOA.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360118372418</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 21:39:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360118992452-151</Id><Topic><Title>getanid61 &amp; Marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360090860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A SoC might be a different "beast" compared to CPU but there should be no difference in how SoC or CPU wafers are processed (similar process flow) - IOW by the time the Intel 22nm SoC hits the process should be more or less fully debugged. Intel processed millions of trigate wafers - and that's how yields are being improved and fine tuned and that should be real advantage for Intel SoC cost structure. SoC and CPU are different when it comes to test equipment at least to my knowledge</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360118992452</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 21:49:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360119194067-152</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is going to $15</Title><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1360067574540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:32:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First, I made this name when bush was in office, okay newb? Second, bribes, extortion and fraud won't work forever. At some point you have to innovate, and I don't mean itanium. Good luck but time will tell.</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1360119194067</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 21:53:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360119257703-153</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is going to $15</Title><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1360067574540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 07:32:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ask your mom, she's right next to you.</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1360119257703</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 21:54:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360120003141-154</Id><Topic><Title>I don't know why people keep comparing ARM vs Intel. ARM is nowhere in the picture</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360113074921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 20:11:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How well did MIPS64 work out for MIPS?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360120003141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:06:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360120315773-155</Id><Topic><Title>getanid61 &amp; Marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360090860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will go with Marsavian's prediction with one slight change. The market will see rapidly increasing adoption of Intel SoCs next year. However, I think Intel stock will start reacting positively (and ARMH negatively) over the next few months - starting with MWC. The stock market is always looking forward and there will be enough good news for Intel (bad news for ARMH) with regard to dual-core, tablets, Haswell, Bay Trail, etc. which will get the big guys to start accumulating.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1360120315773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:11:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360122128539-156</Id><Title>Dell buyout to start bidding wars</Title><Msg>Just like the patent bids, tech companies like hp, intel, amd will increase in value. Expect money to roll in on these companies.</Msg><Username>optimismiscontagious</Username><Timestamp>1360122128539</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:42:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360122300008-157</Id><Title>M&amp;A Boom: How much would Intel sell for?</Title><Msg>This will be discussed in the upcoming days and the money should pour into pc companies.</Msg><Username>optimismiscontagious</Username><Timestamp>1360122300008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:45:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360122460995-158</Id><Topic><Title>I don't know why people keep comparing ARM vs Intel. ARM is nowhere in the picture</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360113074921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 20:11:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I understand what you are saying BUT, it is not Arm but Qualcomm which makes the chips using Arms designs which is hurting Intel now. Lots of people are using tablets and phones in place of their Computers now. Intel Intel gets volume sales into those markets, people will not see growth from Intel. Yes, I would bet that Intel will win the fight but it is going to take a few years and that is causing pain for Intel NOW! By the start of 2014 Intel needs to be in the phone and tablet markets in a meaningful way. We are talking 20% market share or more.</Msg><Username>hothectors</Username><Timestamp>1360122460995</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:47:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360123515640-159</Id><Title>Dell investors to increase stake in Intel</Title><Msg>All of the money by institutions and retail investors will now flow into other pc related stocks. So you should expect a high dividend stock like Intel to benefit.</Msg><Username>gerard08853</Username><Timestamp>1360123515640</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 23:05:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360123691707-160</Id><Title>8 billion from Vanguard &amp; Blackrock</Title><Msg>were invested in Dell's 2.3% dividend stock. Imagine how much of that is going to go into Intel's 4% stock.</Msg><Username>spongebarb_squaredance</Username><Timestamp>1360123691707</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 23:08:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360124822330-161</Id><Title>CERP up Friday 8%, Monday 24%, today 47% Biodegradable Plastic Maker on fire!</Title><Msg>Just a little stock with some huge potential trades for pennies down from $5.00 after a recent complete company restructure things are picking up for CERP in the past 4 weeks they have landed almost one million in new sales! IMHO</Msg><Username>mobiletechsolutions</Username><Timestamp>1360124822330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 23:27:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360125011598-162</Id><Topic><Title>Dell buyout to start bidding wars</Title><Username>optimismiscontagious</Username><Timestamp>1360122128539</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:42:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, but if it goes the way Dell went, the stocks you mentioned will languish for years at lower prices before being taken private. And bear in mind, Michael Dell is a key player in this. Who is it you think is going to take Intel private? You think maybe Robert Noyce will make a come back?</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1360125011598</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 23:30:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360125164921-163</Id><Title>Mossberg really loves the Surface Pro!</Title><Msg>This is excellent news for INTC! "But just as the Pro is compromised as a tablet, it's compromised as a laptop." Yeah, that'll get them rushing out to the stores to buy it!</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1360125164921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 23:32:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360125501168-164</Id><Topic><Title>M&amp;A Boom: How much would Intel sell for?</Title><Username>optimismiscontagious</Username><Timestamp>1360122300008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:45:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This will be discussed in the upcoming days and the money should pour into pc companies." It will get discussed alright. Just as HP's acquisition of Compaq got discussed. Just as Time Warner's acquisition of AOL got discussed.</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1360125501168</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 23:38:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>