<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366430462819-1</Id><Topic><Title>Focus is mobile now</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366419437120</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:57:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel integrated a 802.11b device into their mobile CPU chipset. Intel value priced the extra chipset functions. Intel does not compete on price. Since the mobile CPU and mobile chipset supported 802.11b automatically, there was no need for any extra stand alone 802.11b chips. Intel probably increased the mobile chipset price by more than Intersil charged for their 802.11b part. There were just many, many fewer dedicated 802.11b sockets for Intersil and Broadcom to sell into. Intel is similarly integrating SoC functions AND MORE into their products. Reverse engineer? Not unless Intel is begging for a patent lawsuit from the patent owners. With all the mobile market patent lawsuits, royalty and licensing fees .... Intel will be very careful to avoid infringement. I DO agree with your basic assessment about Intel cramming functions in the package. That is why Intel has spent the last several years accumulating clean title to the mobile patents they now have. "</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1366430462819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:01:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366430937138-2</Id><Title>DRAM contract 1.H april up</Title><Msg>5% to 10%according to dramexchange</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1366430937138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366431480476-3</Id><Topic><Title>Focus is mobile now</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1366419437120</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:57:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I saw this in the 90s when hrs then isil developed 802.11b wireless. Harris developed it spun off Intersil and for 2 years isil stock boomed" yeah the happy days - a friend of mine told me about Intersil back than... they are now an "analog" company</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1366431480476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:18:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366433177700-4</Id><Title>46k in 2 months? net PROFIT</Title><Msg>i only play explosive alerts picks now i bought there last stock pick SKTO an made 46k on it google them explosive alerts!</Msg><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1366433177700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:46:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>32</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366461981457-5</Id><Topic><Title>Can Otellini stay on?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366408969846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As is usually in our lives, making a change has some consequences. Just because we make a change doesn't necessarily ends in a better outcome so then easy to say P.O. should go but we need to look at the alternative and the criteria in choosing his replacement. Stacy strikes as "more-of-the-same" alternative so then the end result will accomplish no observable positive results, no negative results either. Counter viewpoints are welcomed.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1366461981457</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366476873114-6</Id><Topic><Title>Can Otellini stay on?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366408969846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Otellini has brought us FinFET and the end of the ARM era. I see no reasons for him to go and a lot for him to stay...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366476873114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:54:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366482815026-7</Id><Topic><Title>Jigsaw puzzle falls into place - Intel Bay Trail Tablets with built-in LTE</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366305192061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 13:13:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. Intel already said they will be shipping the multi-mode XMM 7160 later in the year (this was from MWC), so should be available for Haswell, Bay Trail launch. Things are definitely coming to together. Maybe Intel can do a promotion like - buy an Intel tablet, get 1 free month of Intel TV.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366482815026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:33:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366483677124-8</Id><Title>Intel-powered Android laptop-tablet hybrids reportedly on the way</Title><Msg>digitaltrendsDOTcom/computing/rumor-intel-powered-android-laptop-tablet-hybrids-coming/ "The question is, if it’s true, will you buy Intel-powered Android tablet-laptop convertibles as your main computing devices, or will you stick to more traditional desktop operating systems? [Does not matter whether people buy Android or windows, Intel wins either way]</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366483677124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:47:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366487832806-9</Id><Topic><Title>Intel-powered Android laptop-tablet hybrids reportedly on the way</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366483677124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:47:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Android tablets or convertibles are useful secondary content consumption devices but they aren't a replacement for a traditional desktop and desktop OS. If the tablet was Haswell-based with dual boot W8, or Ubuntu or another 64 bit OS, and had a Thunderbolt-like docking capability to connect to large monitors, network drives, etc the model could change a bit.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1366487832806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 15:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366489121162-10</Id><Title>Any thoughts on how Intel will benefit from HTML5?</Title><Msg>HTML5 - Intel Inside! Written by Mike James Friday, 19 April 2013 13:00 What is Intel up to? It has just released a set of really good HLML5 tools, potentially the best yet, that allows you to create apps that are platform independent. This raises more questions that it answers. Why is an "Intel Inside" sticker on HTML5 so important? If you are creating or thinking of creating a Web app using JavaScript then you need to know about what Intel is up to. Its latest offering makes it possible, and in fact easy, to create a web app that will work on mobile and desktop devices and then package it for all of the app stores you want to support. If this is as good as it seems to be, it is a winning tool and a way to really make apps that are write once and run everywhere. Intel took the opportunity of launching its revamped developer offering for HTML5 apps at the Intel Developer Forum in Beijing in April. The aim is very high as you can tell from the title of a recent blog post - "One Code Base to Rule Them All". You might think that this is a null claim as HTML5 is standardized, but this is to miss the point that an HTML app running on different platforms has a very different runtime environment. The APIs available in a desktop browser aren't the same as those in an Android Phone and there are even differences between a Chrome and a Firefox packaged app.</Msg><Username>agermangymnast</Username><Timestamp>1366489121162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366497638646-11</Id><Title>Where are the shorts?</Title><Msg>I notice there are long stretches where there are absolutely no short posters. This suggests to me all those annoying posters are done by one person.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366497638646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:40:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366498802976-12</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the shorts?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366497638646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:40:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>None of the bashers are short. They just think something they say might send the stock to the teens, where they want to buy.</Msg><Username>singhlion2011</Username><Timestamp>1366498802976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:00:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366503702143-13</Id><Title>Wallis, RE: Intel's investor meeting for 2013.</Title><Msg>They have moved it from May to mid November this year. Any idea as to what was the reason for it?</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1366503702143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:21:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366504698391-14</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on how Intel will benefit from HTML5?</Title><Username>agermangymnast</Username><Timestamp>1366489121162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:18:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i. innovation, media, intel-tv &amp; apps. II. breaking the stigma that Intel is one plan game Microsoft done that and developed many branches and sub branches (xbox, games, surface etc) - doing well</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1366504698391</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:38:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366504825164-15</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, RE: Intel's investor meeting for 2013.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1366503702143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:21:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the Intel site just now. Where did you find the November information? Annual Stockholder Meeting 05/16/13 -8:30 AM PT Location: Intel Corporation Santa Clara Campus, Building SC-12 3600 Juliette Lane Santa Clara, CA 95054 US</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1366504825164</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366507003436-16</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the shorts?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366497638646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:40:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I notice there are long stretches where there are absolutely no short posters. This suggests to me all those annoying posters are done by one person." *** There's a simple explanation any time there is an absence of basher posts: 1.) Dana is on vacation 2.) Dana is in a location without internet service 3.) Dana is in the fetal position 4.) Dana got fired</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366507003436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:16:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366507295628-17</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, RE: Intel's investor meeting for 2013.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1366503702143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:21:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Investor Meeting appears to be different from the Annual Stockholder Meeting. Dunno why they moved the Investor Meeting but maybe because it will be clear by fall that the ARM era really is over. Maybe they want to synchronize some events...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366507295628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366507740831-18</Id><Topic><Title>Jigsaw puzzle falls into place - Intel Bay Trail Tablets with built-in LTE</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366305192061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 13:13:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think we are going to see all types of deals with discounted pricing from carriers and other players just like smartphones: - convertible/detachable hybrids with a wide range of screen sizes - built-in LTE - voice over IP (Skype, Vonage, etc.) - discounted contract-pricing by carriers and other large players (could include Google, Amazon, Microsoft, Best Buy, Walmart, etc. (a lot of them may be reselling LTE from AT&amp;T, Verizon, Sprint/Clearwire, T-Mobile/Metro PCS) - mobile anywhere/anyplace TV from Intel Complete packages (hardware, LTE, TV including cable channels) should generate a lot of interest from people who like to consume content on-the-go.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366507740831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366507894155-19</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, RE: Intel's investor meeting for 2013.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1366503702143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:21:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Intel goes ahead with the current plan and appoints a new CEO in Otellini's place, it should take a few months for the new CEO to come up to speed and be completely prepped for the Investors Meeting. Unless, of course, the new CEO is an insider such as Stacy Smith or Dadi Perlmutter. It just helps to have a few months in any case....</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366507894155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:31:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366508127911-20</Id><Topic><Title>Intel-powered Android laptop-tablet hybrids reportedly on the way</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366483677124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:47:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I tend to agree. Most smartphone and tablet apps are very lite. I would go with a Windows/Android combination device so that there are no surprises in terms of regular applications not working and archived files not being compatible. Just as an example, my Sony camcorder does not provide its software for Macs. I'm sure they don't provide and will not be providing the software on Android.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366508127911</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:35:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366508397945-21</Id><Topic><Title>Intel-powered Android laptop-tablet hybrids reportedly on the way</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366483677124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:47:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But, I'm sure current users of Android who want a content consumption device (with which they can use their library of Android apps) with some light content creation capabilities would go for pure-Android laptop or convertible. So the market for Intel should expand vastly, especially if Bay Trail can beat Snapdragon, Tegra, and Exynos hands down. From current indications, it appears that it will.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366508397945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:39:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366513266862-22</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, RE: Intel's investor meeting for 2013.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1366503702143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:21:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm guessing they want to synchronize with something also. Here's what Intel IR emailed me. "As stated in our Q4’12 earnings call, our investor meeting has been moved to the fall. Subsequently, we have set a date, it will be on November 21st, 2013. Thank you. Tiffany Intel Investor Relations"</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1366513266862</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:01:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366514644266-23</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, RE: Intel's investor meeting for 2013.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1366503702143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:21:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple/Intel deal will be announced before that with Apple/Intel products ready to sell for Holiday Season. Intel rescheduled meeting to explain full impact of deal.</Msg><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1366514644266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:24:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366516346558-24</Id><Title>Apple/Intel deal in the works way back in 2011</Title><Msg>Statements made in May/2011: Tom Kilroy, a senior vice president at Intel, told the Reuters Global Technology Summit in New York on Wednesday that the runaway success of the iPad and other Apple products shapes how Intel thinks about future devices and the chips that will power them. "We work very closely with them and we're constantly looking down the road at what we can be doing relative to future products. I'd go as far as to say Apple helps shape our roadmap," Kilroy said. "Apple -- they push us hard," he said. "There are certain customers that would be interesting to us and certain customers that wouldn't," Chief Financial Officer Stacy Smith told journalists after an investor event in London on Thursday. He said Intel would be happy to produce chip cores based on its own architecture for other companies but that allowing rival architectures to be manufactured in its plants would be a tough decision. "If Apple or Sony came to us and said 'I want to do a product that involves your IA (Intel architecture) core and put some of my IP around it', I wouldn't blink. That would be fantastic business for us." "Then you get into the middle ground of 'I don't want it to be a IA core, I want it to be my own custom-designed core,' and then you are only getting the manufacturing margin, (and) that would be a much more in-depth discussion and analysis."</Msg><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1366516346558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:52:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>