<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359979897147-1</Id><Topic><Title>dell going private would be good for intel</Title><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1359855938269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 20:45:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AAPL is able to buy just about any company if .... 1.) they want to buy and 2.) if AAPL is able to get regulatory approval. If AAPL put a bid for INTC, a number of PC and server companies would raise very, very, very strong objections. I am not sure why AAPL would want to buy INTC. AAPL faces a discontinutity in their product lines. They have x86 on the high end. The x86 extends down to the tablet products. ARM on the low end. I am sure today that the AAPL Senior VP of MAC products have various x86 tablet prototypes AND the AAPL Senior VP of iPad products has ARM MAC prototypes. They are both pitching the expansion of their influence to Cook. I doubt that AAPL is interested and I think it would be tough to pull off legally.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359979897147</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 07:11:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359981353684-2</Id><Title>AMD is ROADKILL. Simply irrelevant now. It is all about Samsung and Qualcomm now.</Title><Msg>AMD is so yesterday. Is it still in business? Like who cares? What--you held it from 49 down to 2.00? That is sad but not my problem is it. Speaking of sad. Intel is pretty pathetic as well hanging in the low 20s still with shrinking Net profits. One has to be a true believer to be all in on Intel nowadays. It is all about mobility and we are talking phones, tablets, and small notebooks. Certainly it appears as if Intel should break out and be able to crush its competitors in the CPU game but that is roadmap stuff and nobody is investing in potential these days. Cisco, Motorola, ---And a major china breakout in mobility for Intel this year would be game changers and I am not talking about negatives like palin. Intel would break up. Like in the Movie, Field of Dreams, Intel is using the if you built it, they will come--strategy. Certainly the thought of 14 nm trigate chips in phones with all the add ons is a nightmare for any company that tries selling phones that are using far less.</Msg><Username>amdsuckks</Username><Timestamp>1359981353684</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 07:35:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359981534070-3</Id><Title>Intel SoCs for Windows Phone?</Title><Msg>Otellini has indicated several times that Intel's goals are to make x86 being the port of choice for all major OS by providing the best SoCs/CPUs. Looks like Intel is on the path of making it happen for Windows Phone. ============= Intel Wants Windows Phone Engineers Yup, Intel is set to make a splash at Mobile World Congress later this month with a slew of smartphones, tablets and Ultrabooks, and we have also seen how LinkedIn was used to help recruit folks to help out with the upcoming Motorola X phone. Well, LinkedIn is in the spotlight again now, as we have word that Intel has published a job opportunity on LinkedIn which is looking out for Windows Phone engineers. One can read into that however one wants to, but how about this – could Intel be looking into a mobile platform as part of their future investment? The job listed at LinkedIn specifically requested for those who are experts in the Windows Phone environment, and it would be interesting to see what else the future will bring. At this point in time, Windows Phone devices are powered mostly by ARM with Qualcomm as the exclusive chip provider, but two is definitely company from our perspective, and neither do I think that three’s a crowd. The job description’s opening pitch reads as such, “Windows Phone Engineers: Intel would like to talk to you. If you have Windows phone expertise, the Intel site in Redmond would like to talk to you.” ubergizmoDOTcom/2013/02/intel-wants-windows-phone-engineers/</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359981534070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 07:38:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359982607608-4</Id><Topic><Title>Intel SoCs for Windows Phone?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359981534070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 07:38:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would appear Intel is trying more of a shotgun approach to market impact as opposed to having one or two really big customers. Perhaps as the market evolves and the big players among its customers emerge it will narrow down its focus. Its a huge company with the deep pockets to support multiple platforms with its mobile chips. Windows Phone makes a lot of sense for Intel to target in the long run because the whole point of the Low Power IA project was to offer a unified ISA across power operating points. You can imagine Microsoft going for a much larger integration in the future than the one it did for tablets and laptops with Windows 8, where it integrates Windows 8 with Windows Phone. When that happens, the value proposition of having microprocessors speaking a single ISA across the power spectrum will go up. Having said that, not everyone is convinced integration, in this way, makes sense. We'll get more data on this as the adoption numbers for Windows 8 come in.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359982607608</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 07:56:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359982873468-5</Id><Topic><Title>Anybody think Intel can end up in ALL the Motorolla-made Razr's?</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1359931709205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 17:48:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Motorolla X phone will have Intel inside and make all the ARM-based Razr's extinct. JMHO.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359982873468</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 08:01:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359983366598-6</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>poisoninsara</Username><Timestamp>1359740614322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:43:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job. Informational article.</Msg><Username>otiositiesgeraldine</Username><Timestamp>1359983366598</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 08:09:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359985913968-7</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a difference between "big app" and a useful app. Angry Birds is the kinda thing people download to kill time waiting in line, or something they give to their kid to play with while mom is shopping in the women's department at Sears. If you look at most of the popular apps that are downloaded for phones you'll see many of them are designed to waste time. That's why they have been regarded as consumption devices instead of creation devices.</Msg><Username>lti.steve</Username><Timestamp>1359985913968</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 08:51:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359986408812-8</Id><Topic><Title>Dell going private on Monday - not good for Intel</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1359846848336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 18:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Merlo's post from 2/3 at 2pm was right on the money. If you augment the horizontal capabilities product model with vertical reference designs then you can draw in OEMs and ODMs just like Intel is doing with its current crop of mobile customers (without coming out with their own branded solution and alienating anyone). We did this with PCs first with the soon to be eol'd Motherboard business group, and also with the PC chipset business that sprung up around the company's introduction of the original PCI bus as the I/O backbone back in early '90s. Note that going strong into chipsets was not without its controversy as companies like HP and Compaq who did all their own engineering were #$%$ that Intel was leveling the field around them for the likes of Dell who built a huge business by latching and running with our chipsets, processors and motherboard kits. But they all got over it eventually. Reference designs were done back then too with far out form factors,... I remember one that resembled a toaster,.... But they were not production worthy examples, they were for blue sky technology showcasing. The handheld reference designs are production worthy so that an Orange, or a Lava, or even a Lenovo can take it to market very quickly, layering their differentiating features on top of the HW platform. But doing direct branded solutions in competition with existing, and hopefully future customers would be foolish. And as Merlot pointed out, if Intel had continued to pursue that direction back when the PC was being ramped, Intel would never have been as successful as they have been over the last 20 years.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1359986408812</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 09:00:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359986520766-9</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've been able to port MSOffice back and forth to PDA's since the mid 90's. It was built into Windows CE. This got them no traction for years. Why is it suddenly going to be a factor now? Consumers won't switch to a new OS unless their apps are on it. Microsoft has had the big ones since day one including Angry Birds, Facebook, Twitter and the other heavily downloaded apps. What they will have a problem with are the less popular free apps like the ones offered from banks and the ones from stores like Starbucks that help you find them. There are also numerous free and useful apps like ones that help you find the cheapest gas in the area. If an app starts out small it usually is only written for iOS and then eventually Android. Windows 8 is way down the list.</Msg><Username>lti.steve</Username><Timestamp>1359986520766</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 09:02:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359987456440-10</Id><Topic><Title>This one know it all alerted INTC right before everyone else.</Title><Username>adamstevens694</Username><Timestamp>1359983842192</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 08:17:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>report is number 1</Msg><Username>trent.marschel</Username><Timestamp>1359987456440</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 09:17:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359988046691-11</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8, a real first look</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1359931755628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 17:49:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One thing I didn't mention was the overall integration of Windows 8. A fatal flaw Android devices have is the assumption that only one person is going to use it. This works well for phones but not as well for tablets. On a Windows 8 device each person in the family can use the device and sign in with his or her profile. It more or less requires you to have a Microsoft Live or Hotmail account. But if you do you will have access to your Skydrive (7GB free storage) and perhaps one of the most advanced photo sharing pieces of software around. I know this doesn't sound like much but when you use it, it really is a huge deal. Android has always been clunky when it comes to integration of its own apps. Microsoft is silky smooth, nearly like an Apple experience. The problem that Microsoft needs to address is the same bridge Apple ran across years ago. When Apple came out with iTunes it had to come up with a PC version of it. Microsoft needs to come to terms with the fact that people will have other e-mail services. I'm surprised that it's not built in right now. Google has ways to integrate other e-mails into your Gmail address I'm sure Microsoft could do the same thing. I think the thing that will screw people up the most is the name Windows 8. It's not the next generation of Windows. If they had named it "Windows Mobile" and realized that people don't really want it on their desktop computers it would have been off to a better start. Oh well, maybe next generation.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1359988046691</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 09:27:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359990632204-12</Id><Title>The Future will have Intel inside</Title><Msg>The Future Will Have Intel Inside By André Mouton Feb 04, 2013 9:00 am Why the company's next line of processors might be a game-changer. Whether it's the smartphone we consult every five minutes, or the laptop that gets thinner each year, we're continuously reminded of the ways in which technology makes things smaller. What we sometimes forget is that it also allows us to build larger, and think bigger. Touchscreens have made possible both the tablet and the table PC. An iPhone will fit in your pocket, while a rumored Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL) television set will not. The growth in handheld portable devices over the last decade has created a belief that power-efficiency is what defines a successful hardware manufacturer. The truth is more complicated. With machines becoming both larger and smaller, and serving more functions than ever before, what matters most is scalability. Intel Corp. (NASDAQ:INTC) understands this. The company is now aiming to do with processors what Microsoft (NASDAQ:MSFT) is trying to accomplish with Windows 8: to provide a continuous environment throughout the range of PC and post-PC devices. This would provide an efficiency for the company—one size fits all—and an attractive situation for software developers and original equipment manufacturers, who would enter a more integrated market. In practical terms, this means designing a chip that can be scaled large or small, and built to emphasize either power-efficiency or performance. Later this year, Intel will release Haswell, an update of its Core line of processors—and Haswell will do just that. Intel is predicting as much as a doubling of battery life with the new chipset, and that's a big deal for the expanding market in Windows 8 tablet PCs and convertible notebooks. The next generation of these machines might offer life spans of 10 hours or more, at a performance level many times that of anything running ARM-based (NASDAQ:ARMH) hardware. Ultrabooks—Intel's attempt to refresh an uninspired laptop market—could also get a new lease on life. Sales have been poor, as consumers see little reason to upgrade their computers, but Windows 8 and Haswell might be the team to change the ball game. On the other hand, scalability only extends so far. The virtue of Intel's products is that they do many things well, and have few weakness. They offer a neutral environment for software developers, and an open one for the end-user. Chipsets built with ARM's architecture tend to be stronger in manufacturer-defined areas like graphics processing. Each approach is useful in its own way, and it's wrong to characterize the difference between them as one of efficiency. They're efficient at different things. Intel has a natural advantage in PCs, where it can satisfy many different demands with a handful of product lines. It's cheaper to sell everyone a processor that does more than they need, if it means greater scale. Elsewhere, specialized hardware makes more sense. You are not, in any likely scenario, going to run spreadsheets on your smartwatch. And while the 4-inch screen on your iPhone is OK for watching videos, playing music, or reading tweets, it becomes a little sadistic the moment you have to actually input something. Size and battery life are limitations Intel has proven it can work with, but devices like these are additionally constrained by the fact that there are so many things you don't want to do on them. A more versatile CPU doesn't increase their usefulness, it just wastes power. This has limited the success of Intel's low-powered Atom line of processors. They've gained some ground in tablets —where Haswell is likely to cannibalize them —and in niche areas like automobile consoles, but made almost no headway in smartphones. While the Atom is competitive on battery life and performance with the chips being offered by Nvidia (NASDAQ:NVDA) and Qualcomm it's also larger and more costly, and Intel wastes its considerable advantages as a manufacturer trying to overcome these handicaps. The company is fighting a foreign war, and one that it could have waged a lot more effectively had it never sold its ARM line, XScale, to Marvell Technology. It could be that the Atom was simply an attempt to buy time for improvements higher up the product chain, like the kind we're seeing with Haswell, and to prevent ARM from entrenching itself too deeply in tablets. If so, it was an expensive strategy. It's also an unfortunate distraction, because Intel's efforts elsewhere may soon pay off—and at much better margins. The PC isn't dead, but it is moving beyond the beige box, and it's bringing with it the openness, and the limitless sense of freedom that made this the digital age. If Intel is suffering a crisis of confidence over the departure of CEO Paul Otellini, it shouldn't be. The future's bright, and it has</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1359990632204</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:10:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359991244919-13</Id><Topic><Title>Intel SoCs for Windows Phone?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359981534070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 07:38:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, the only 3 big OS companies in computing/smartphones are Microsoft, Apple, and Google - with Tizen being a distant possibility. - Intel has been a partner of Microsoft for over 2 decades - Intel has been working with Apple for about a decade - Intel and Google have a partnership going through Motorola Mobility With its "port of choice" strategy, Intel has been working on expanding existing relationships at Microsoft (Windows Phone) and Apple (iOS). Intel is a chip/manufacturing powerhouse. It has the reach and resources to handle its partnerships with Microsoft, Apple, and Google...and continue to dabble in Tizen. So the very idea that Intel is trying a shortgun approach is laughable.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359991244919</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:20:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359991777771-14</Id><Topic><Title>WoW !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>insiderpigs</Username><Timestamp>1359653148223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 12:25:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UP again!</Msg><Username>jennifer_jkarim</Username><Timestamp>1359991777771</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:29:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359991803070-15</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Want A Stock That's Going Nowhere or One Headed To New Highs?</Title><Username>druggy52</Username><Timestamp>1359132851598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:54:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is the question.</Msg><Username>jennifer_jkarim</Username><Timestamp>1359991803070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:30:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359993035644-16</Id><Topic><Title>Intel SoCs for Windows Phone?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359981534070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 07:38:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Tizen being a distant possibility" Search for SAMSUNG and TIZEN and you will see that it appears that Samsung is going to adopt Tizen. Intel has always taken an OS neutral position but willing to apply extra resources on request.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359993035644</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:50:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359993781466-17</Id><Title>Bright future for Intel</Title><Msg>Hi Longs: Nice to see Intel fighting for a place in the Sun on Mobile Business arena, with its new double core processor. And nice to see bright prospects on Cable TV new disruptive proposals a new "a la carte content business".. We´ll see some light in Mobile World Cogress in Barcelona... I hope you enjoy it. Have a nice day guys. By the way.. Enjoy the dividend... Love from Spain.</Msg><Username>eaglesssnest</Username><Timestamp>1359993781466</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:03:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359994850969-18</Id><Title>sell now I will be taking INTC down tomorrow below 21.15.</Title><Msg>What the price go down tomorrow. I will be right again</Msg><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1359994850969</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:20:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359996501486-19</Id><Topic><Title>Intel SoCs for Windows Phone?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359981534070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 07:38:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tizen becoming a viable OS would make it even more interesting - if Intel could squeeze out Samsung's own Exynos and become the platform of choice for Tizen, what is there not to like? However, to reiterate my previous post: With just 3 (or 4 including Tizen) OS choices, Intel's strategy was/is very methodical rather than being a shortgun approach. First, it went after rapidly-expanding Android Smartphones (since Apple and Microsoft had made their own platform choices) Second, it wanted to protect its PC turf against Windows RT - and it seems to be doing that effectively with Clover Trail and lower-end Core processors for Tablets and Convertibles/Hybrids. Third, it is looking to expand its platform for Smartphones by venturing into Windows Phone. And it might be doing the same play for iOS - for both Smartphones and Tablets. I don't see any shortgun approach here!</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359996501486</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:48:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359996620175-20</Id><Title>WOW how come there selling INTC off with the dividend tomorrow? OH NO</Title><Msg>WOW how come there selling INTC off with the dividend tomorrow? OH NO</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1359996620175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:50:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359996772078-21</Id><Topic><Title>sell now I will be taking INTC down tomorrow below 21.15.</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1359994850969</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:20:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you mean $20.92 since the price will be adjusted down for the dividend at the close. $21.15 adjusted for the 22.5 cent dividend is $20.92. Or do you mean that you are going to take INTC down from $21.15 +22.5 cents or $21.37 ? I bet you mean the second.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359996772078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:52:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359996895633-22</Id><Topic><Title>sell now I will be taking INTC down tomorrow below 21.15.</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1359994850969</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:20:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh no sell, sell ,sell oh no, how low will intc go</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1359996895633</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:54:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359996953820-23</Id><Topic><Title>Anybody think Intel can end up in ALL the Motorolla-made Razr's?</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1359931709205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 17:48:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Motorola's Razr's are high quality phones. They compare very favorably to Samsung's best and generally have superior radios and higher build quality. This is not surprising as Moto has about a zillion years experience building radios for police, fire &amp; rescue. They know a thing about making devices that last. A new Razr with Intel's latest will be a killer product.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1359996953820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:55:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359996953986-24</Id><Topic><Title>WOW how come there selling INTC off with the dividend tomorrow? OH NO</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1359996620175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:50:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>someone just bought 5,000 straddle contract position for May $25 options. The option market maker could skip hedging the calls but had to hedge writing the puts. He shorted 500,000 shares.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359996953986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:55:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359997401273-25</Id><Topic><Title>sell now I will be taking INTC down tomorrow below 21.15.</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1359994850969</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:20:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is a dividend arbitrage and happens every quarter. If you feel uncomfortable with the risk, you should sell. If you don't feel uncomfortable with the risk, you should go about your day.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359997401273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:03:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359997407651-26</Id><Topic><Title>INTC listed at position 6 on a top 10 most Undervalued index over on Extreme Value Stocks Seems like a serious site.</Title><Username>carloc23</Username><Timestamp>1359994390628</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:13:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems like serious morons are spamming .</Msg><Username>pentomic</Username><Timestamp>1359997407651</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:03:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359997569496-27</Id><Title>Will Inetl buy NVDA</Title><Msg>First would it make sense? Second at what price? Intel will spend over $10 bil for R&amp;D and acquistions this year.</Msg><Username>jin_18do8</Username><Timestamp>1359997569496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:06:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359997960907-28</Id><Topic><Title>Anybody think Intel can end up in ALL the Motorolla-made Razr's?</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1359931709205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 17:48:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the INTC production costs can be managed, there is a very good chance of this happening.</Msg><Username>investment925</Username><Timestamp>1359997960907</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:12:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359998700315-29</Id><Topic><Title>Dell going private on Monday - not good for Intel</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1359846848336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 18:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>backbay - A useles idiot that must be ignored..Bye moron !</Msg><Username>pentomic</Username><Timestamp>1359998700315</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:25:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359999147348-30</Id><Topic><Title>Dell going private on Monday - not good for Intel</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1359846848336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 18:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh no!!! A useless idiot!!! that is not good!!</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1359999147348</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:32:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360000655179-31</Id><Topic><Title>Will Inetl buy NVDA</Title><Username>jin_18do8</Username><Timestamp>1359997569496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:06:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is potential synergy between Nvidia's graphics technology and Intel but Intel's built-in graphics capability is advancing so quickly that it will soon displace the need for discrete graphics components in all but the most high-end gaming and video editing applications. While Nvidia can survive serving the high-end markets, the volume mass market is going to be taken away from them. If Intel were interested in acquiring Nvidia's they should wait until the market has reset Nvidia's value to its new reality.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360000655179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:57:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360002427686-32</Id><Title>INTC holding up in market retreat</Title><Msg>Maybe it's imminent x-div day, and/or maybe it's just a darn great investment.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360002427686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:27:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360002675266-33</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>poisoninsara</Username><Timestamp>1359740614322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:43:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love this report.</Msg><Username>obliqmable</Username><Timestamp>1360002675266</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:31:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360002973560-34</Id><Title>go up on 1500 dell buyout</Title><Msg>ok</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360002973560</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:36:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360004163679-35</Id><Title>Intel Foundries MEMS for Fuel Cell Start-up Nectar/ mobile power system</Title><Msg>certainly small fish but interesting Intel Foundries MEMS for Fuel Cell Start-up Nectar By #$%$ James..... I started this blog off by talking about Intel, then veered off into a description of the Nectar charger – what was I babbling about? Well, when I was looking at the charger at CES I had a word with Sam Schaevitz of Lilliputian Systems, which developed the Nectar, and asked him who made the MEMS, expecting to hear about of one of the MEMS foundries that are around. (Lilliputian is a spin-off of MIT – Sam is founder and CTO.) Much to my surprise, he answered "Intel"! As I said at the beginning, there has been quite a bit of comment about Intel moving to the foundry model, but nothing about them being in the MEMS business. It turns out that the work is done at Intel’s fab in Hudson, Mass., which those with long memories will recall was the DEC fab bought by Intel when DEC went under back in 1998.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360004163679</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:56:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360004473740-36</Id><Title>Done Deal</Title><Msg>How much did Intel pay Motorola Mobility for its baseband chip design unit?</Msg><Username>inovermyhead_2000</Username><Timestamp>1360004473740</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:01:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360004975438-37</Id><Topic><Title>INTC holding up in market retreat</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360002427686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:27:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are buying the deep calls to execise early before ex-div. The option activity dampens the trading range. 8.8k Jan 2015 $15 strike 1.6k Jan 2015 $13 strike 38k Jan 2014 $15 2k Jan 2014 $13 3k Jan 2014 $10 26k Feb $20</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360004975438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:09:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360006134249-38</Id><Topic><Title>INTC holding up in market retreat</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360002427686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:27:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why deep calls instead of the stock outright?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360006134249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:28:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360006485753-39</Id><Title>IF INTC BUYING NVDA???</Title><Msg>At what price?</Msg><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1360006485753</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:34:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360006985582-40</Id><Topic><Title>INTC holding up in market retreat</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360002427686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:27:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I too saw this - why would they be doing that? can you pls explain. Tomm when it becomes ex div the stock price will drop by the dividend amt and the price of calls will fall too to reflect that drop.</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1360006985582</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:43:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360007888359-41</Id><Title>divident</Title><Msg>if i buy today, will i get a divident?</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1360007888359</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:58:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360008478560-42</Id><Topic><Title>divident</Title><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1360007888359</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:58:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no but you will get a dividend. it goes ex tomorrow.</Msg><Username>adsfjdsakfjdsal</Username><Timestamp>1360008478560</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:07:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360008831639-43</Id><Topic><Title>Will Inetl buy NVDA</Title><Username>jin_18do8</Username><Timestamp>1359997569496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:06:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks,you're right, plus amd got PS4 and new xbox (life span probably 4years). Let's hope Intel's chips are decent enough for the lower end mobile.....glta, IMO,will accumilate more share if PPS stay at this level for the long term...</Msg><Username>jin_18do8</Username><Timestamp>1360008831639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:13:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360009519538-44</Id><Topic><Title>WOW how come there selling INTC off with the dividend tomorrow? OH NO</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1359996620175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:50:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC down big tomorrow, Selling INTC down before the dividend is not a good thing</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360009519538</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:25:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360009722472-45</Id><Topic><Title>divident</Title><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1360007888359</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:58:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well of course tomorrow will be a dividend event and a dent in the stock price!</Msg><Username>herbwll</Username><Timestamp>1360009722472</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:28:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360010245565-46</Id><Topic><Title>INTC holding up in market retreat</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360002427686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:27:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somehow, before the stock goes ex-dividend, they are using options and stock to lock in a position that is neutral BOTH before and after ex-dividend when taken as a pair. They then exerise the call early. Capture the dividend and then take their escape using most likely a PUT option. You can see that buying the call options today has no premium. The put has 100% of the 22.5 cent drop. I think there are several ways but it has to be someone with cheap commissions, deep pockets, knowledgeable, patience and tax laws. The one way that I think that it could be done is to buy a very wide straddle. You pay $10.20 for a $15 call and a $25 put. Then shave the 2.5 cents off. They are messing with the stock to trim pennies off. There were 5,000 put options bought for May $25. Those 5,000 could be the escape hatch for 500,000 shares and the extra call volume just be day trading. I would expect Intel to finish today at STRIKE + DIVIDEND.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360010245565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:37:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360010397708-47</Id><Topic><Title>INTC holding up in market retreat</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360002427686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:27:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The call premium will increase by 11 cents and the put premium will drop by 11 cents. the 22.5 cent premium is 100% found in the puts.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360010397708</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:39:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360010831101-48</Id><Topic><Title>WOW how come there selling INTC off with the dividend tomorrow? OH NO</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1359996620175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:50:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Down, down, down, not good, not good , not good</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360010831101</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:47:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360011061755-49</Id><Topic><Title>INTC holding up in market retreat</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360002427686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:27:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jan 2014 $15 call volume 165,000 contracts. A few minutes ago it was at 128,000</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360011061755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:51:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360011339286-50</Id><Title>Today could be the start of a much larger market correction?</Title><Msg>I guess, it doesn't matter, it will even out, just would like to have more money set aside for when it does correct. Tomorrow should be interesting. I think we may be looking at more drops tomorrow and Wednesday. Anyway, INTC should be a buy by the end of the week for sure.</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1360011339286</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:55:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360011610029-51</Id><Title>Of course, why would Intel take the opportunity to buy back shares today?</Title><Msg>As it is the shares are so over priced right? Why not wait until hedge funds take it down to $12? Great job you buffoons.</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1360011610029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:00:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360011852229-52</Id><Topic><Title>Of course, why would Intel take the opportunity to buy back shares today?</Title><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1360011610029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:00:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what makes you think that they did not buy back?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360011852229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:04:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360011904205-53</Id><Topic><Title>INTC holding up in market retreat</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360002427686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:27:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alex, regarding the May 25 stradele ,the 5000 contracts that is (you mentioned in a different post). When you get a chance check what are the break even points, the low and the high? ( i wanna make sure i calculate it correctly ). Isn't it a bulish stance since the selected a higher strike price then current? in any case it seem a massive gamble that the pps will move either above or below the the break even points to be profitable. imo.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1360011904205</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:05:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360012974908-54</Id><Title>22open on dell buyout</Title><Msg>22</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360012974908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:22:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360013479557-55</Id><Topic><Title>INTC holding up in market retreat</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360002427686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:27:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Arbitraging can take many forms. Taken alone, it is a bearish bet. Assuming that we just consider JUST the 5,000 May $25 put and calls contract as: someone bought the calls they also bought the puts That is a bet on volatility. They are betting that INTC goes farther away from the $25 strike than they paid for the $4.xx they paid. The $25 strke would seem to be bearish. INTC would have to reach $29.xx for them to break even. As the calls gain value, the puts lose value. IMO, the option trading was NEUTRAL and only concerned with shaving a penny or two in guaranteed profits. They are playing arbigrage games across the exdividend. One example (vertical ITM calls) would be for them to BUY a DEEP call at zero premium and sell a shallower call. They exercise their calls, grab the dividend and let the shallower call be exercised. If someone else exercises there call and takes the shares, they just pass the shares they just exercised on through. One more example (wide ITM strangle) where they buy a deep call and a deep put. The premium and costs have to be less than the dividend. The MAY $25 puts looked like they had between 10/20 cents bid/ask premium on them when I looked at them. You buy the deep call at zero premium and the MAY $25 puts, exercise the calls, get the dividend and then exercise the puts when you want.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360013479557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:31:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360013668274-56</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>poisoninsara</Username><Timestamp>1359740614322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:43:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got it. It's awesome.</Msg><Username>kontorfunksjonglenna</Username><Timestamp>1360013668274</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:34:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360014406100-57</Id><Title>POOPTEL CLOSES IN THE REDDDDDDDDDDDDD</Title><Msg>So what's new??? HI-HO WEAVERINO!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360014406100</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:46:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360015190339-58</Id><Topic><Title>22open on dell buyout</Title><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360012974908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:22:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>god bless you</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360015190339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:59:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360016739255-59</Id><Topic><Title>sell now I will be taking INTC down tomorrow below 21.15.</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1359994850969</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:20:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you blew the INTC closing bell price on friday... you're getting you tail handed to you lately... one more mistake and you will be getting the ignore button</Msg><Username>funniebucket</Username><Timestamp>1360016739255</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 17:25:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360018367157-60</Id><Title>Intel shrinks its Solid State Drives</Title><Msg>Intel shrinks its Solid-State Drives, aims for tablets Jon Gold (Network World) 04 February, 2013 20:06 Intel's new Solid-State Drive 525 packs performance identical to a standard 2.5-inch SSD into a device one eighth of the size, the company said in an announcement last week. The SSD 525 comes in 30GB, 60GB, 90GB, 120GB, 180GB and 240GB sizes, and uses the same 25nm memory architecture as Intel's larger solid-state options. The drives use mini-SATA connectors, which allow them to be plugged into smaller PCIe slots common to notebooks while still providing a full SATA 6GB/s data rate. [ MORE INTEL MOBILE: Intel rolls 'Yolo' smartphone into untapped foreign markets ] [ Stay connected with the latest on networks and the NBN in Computerworld's Networking newsletter ] The diminutive new line could help raise Intel's profile in the mobile marketplace -- despite its desktop and laptop dominance, the company has not seen its processors widely used in smartphones and tablets, and could benefit from an improved reputation among mobile OEMs. Intel also hopes that the SSD 525 line will appeal to embedded device makers, for applications like digital signage and in-flight entertainment. Intel says that the SSD 525 series offers 50,000 I/O operations per second of random read speed and 550MB/s of sequential read, as well as 80,000 IOPS random write and 520MB/s sequential write -- the same numbers as the larger SSD 520 series. Independent testing by noted review site AnandTech found that the SSD 525 line was "almost equal" to the best of the full-size solid-state drives currently on the market. The 120GB and 180GB models are already shipping, and Intel has promised that the rest of the drive sizes will be available within the quarter.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360018367157</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 17:52:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360018627848-61</Id><Title>Oracle takes aim at Cisco by buying Acme Packet for 2 Billion</Title><Msg>just announced</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1360018627848</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 17:57:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360022350611-62</Id><Topic><Title>22open on dell buyout</Title><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360012974908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:22:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I pray list</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360022350611</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 18:59:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360023197211-63</Id><Topic><Title>22open on dell buyout</Title><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360012974908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:22:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>god help me</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360023197211</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 19:13:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360024446699-64</Id><Topic><Title>22open on dell buyout</Title><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360012974908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:22:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>with jesus help to go to 22.00</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360024446699</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 19:34:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360028509755-65</Id><Title>Do you think INTC = SPAM</Title><Msg>108</Msg><Username>visnoh</Username><Timestamp>1360028509755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 20:41:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360029172482-66</Id><Topic><Title>WOW how come there selling INTC off with the dividend tomorrow? OH NO</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1359996620175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:50:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHY OH WHY does WALL STREET just keep selling INTC, JUST keeps going lower and lower</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360029172482</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 20:52:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360030578121-67</Id><Title>Odds Intel decreses it's Dividend and when?</Title><Msg>They can't raise the Dividend forever and at some point they'll have to decrease it. When will the raises stop/decreases begin?</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360030578121</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 21:16:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360031947131-68</Id><Title>Nobody wants Tegra 4</Title><Msg>Why? Because TSMC still can't get enough 28nm HKMG wafer out - pay attention to TSMC transcript. TSMC is aiming to increase HKMG output 50% in 2013. Who says manufacturing does not matter ? for sure it isn't NVDA. NVDA and AMD will be dogfighting of what is left from discrete graphic while Intel will unleash Haswell. AMD is paying 6% to get money - they are living off their credit cards. ... Tegra 4 itself will be built on TSMC's 28nm HPL (low-power) process, and the the total die size is around 80mm. ... The i500 will be built on TSMC’s 28nm HP HKMG process.... Nvidia claims that the Icera softmodem approach saves a great deal of die space compared to a hardware radio, but die size isn’t going to be the only consideration. 4G/3G/WiFi radios consume a significant percentage of a smartphone or tablet’s power budget. There are only a handful of smartphones on the market that use Icera’s softmodem tech and none of them have decent battery life. As far as technical details go, the i500 will be capable of category 3 LTE (100Mbps), WCDMA, HSPA+, EDGE, and GSM. VoLTE is supported as well. Support for category 4 LTE will be added later, via a software update (one of the neater aspects of a softmodem). The i500 will be built on TSMC’s 28nm HP HKMG process.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360031947131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 21:39:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360033912346-69</Id><Topic><Title>Odds Intel decreses it's Dividend and when?</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360030578121</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 21:16:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Odds that Intel will decrease its Dividend: 0.0001% When: Intel cash flow would have to fall more than 2/3 what it is today ( since it is 30%) for over a year before it would be considered. If Intel revenue and earnings collapsed tomorrow and stayed at the low rates, a reduction to the dividend would be most likely in Q1/2015.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360033912346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 22:11:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360040399609-70</Id><Topic><Title>WOW how come there selling INTC off with the dividend tomorrow? OH NO</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1359996620175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:50:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW even the dividend could not stop the selling in INTC today</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360040399609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 23:59:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>