<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369630595340-1</Id><Topic><Title>Posting Culture</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369619494168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 21:51:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you post good stuff - one of your posts long time ago pointed out the difference between gate first and gate last and the implication (long before anybody understood what it implied). My request - don't waste time on garbage like nuff, waldblow, or Chump. How do you punish your dog? you don't beat him - you ignore him if you focus on content and ignore the garbage all the garbage will dissapear -</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1369630595340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 00:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369631831754-2</Id><Title>I enjoy posts from Ashraf and Wallis, but....</Title><Msg>I enjoy Wallis and Ashraf's posts. I find them informative, interesting and enjoyable. I even enjoy the encouragement from Vinny. I would also love to see INTC at $40 by the end of the year and it is doable, if.... and if .... and if.... However, none of what we say, and there are very few of us on this board, makes any difference if people don't buy. Whatever the pumpers/dumpers/bashers/cheerleaders say is irrelevant if wallets don't open. INTC can, and does imho, make the best products in the world, but if no one buys, then the stock in going nowhere. Personally, I have an iPhone 4 I can't wait to get rid of. In 2010 it was the best phone I could find, but living in the tiny Apple universe is painful. Don't tell me what I can and can't do with my computer. It's my computer, not a privilege bestowed on me from The Jobs. I'm waiting to buy a new phone and tablet. I want to wirelessly (3G/date too) share from my phone to my computer and then to my tablet. I want to put a USB into my tablet and see my friends pics from my wedding, then copy the ones I like. I want my computers/tools to do whatever I tell them, not pick from a list of things I can do with my own property. Thus, I wait. As for this board, keep doing what you're doing. I have an ignore button that's easy to use. Sometimes you're funny when you're angry. Sometimes you have a great macroeconomic point that counters a technical advantage. But none of us can make people buy or sell. This isn't 1996. The Motley Fools are no longer moving markets and message boards have lost their ability to move a stock. Have a great day.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1369631831754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 01:17:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369632448126-3</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Short Interest: 5/15/2013 224,949,744 : down 8.5m shares</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369453689114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 23:48:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Value investors? The funny thing is that conservative funds in their search for yield are one of the major sources of shares to loan for shorting." how can this be fixed? request the stock certificate mailed to me? but they do naked shorting anyway - why let short sellers get by so easy? the only time i shorted a stock was to lock in stock options - I was not really betting against the stock</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1369632448126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 01:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369632449127-4</Id><Title>When Apple announces an Intel deal, this stock will shoot up.</Title><Msg>Not because Apple means much in profits, but just a change in perception about Intel missing the mobile boat.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369632449127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 01:27:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369633496986-5</Id><Topic><Title>When Apple announces an Intel deal, this stock will shoot up.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369632449127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 01:27:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Apple announces an Intel deal, this stock will shoot up. will yu you the apple deal pumper aren't you ? do you follow your own logic?. the harder you pump an Apple deal the less likely? but just a change in perception You're right on this one - the market ihs relative dumb why is option volume so high for Intel by such a huge margin compared to other DOW components?</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1369633496986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 01:44:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369635867959-6</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Short Interest: 5/15/2013 224,949,744 : down 8.5m shares</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369453689114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 23:48:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fixed? I don't think there is any way to stop the pension plans and long term holders from taking some extra money to allow their shares to be borrowed for a fee. That increases their effective yield and they know that they can stop it at any time. how can be stopped? As I understand it, the standard margin agreements that people sign at their broker includes approval for the broker to loan your shares. Shares in a broker CASH account cannot be loaned. Most people don't have enough shares to make a dent and the limitations with a cash account are a pain. naked shorting? Naked shorting is illegal by anyone, even the options market maker. Insert typical anti-SEC rant here. FAILURE TO DELIVER is the naked shorting beyond the 3-day delivery period for borrowed shares. The FAILS data is delay-released to the public like short interest and the website failstodeliverDOTcom shows a chart of the failures to deliver. Brokers (Schwab, Etrade, Scott, Fidelity, ... ) are not the source. You have to locate and borrow shares or they will sell you out. shorting against options? I think this is a VERY GOOD strategy when it makes sense for you. It took me a very long time to figure out how to lock in option gains during after hours trading. If you have options and the stock is trading crazy after hours and you think the price will correct back, shorting (or buying) against option positions is a proxy for cashing them out. Buy some calls/puts just before earnings report. If the stock pops/drops then you short/buy and then exercise your option. NICE!!!! and share this nugget with others.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369635867959</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 02:24:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369636521343-7</Id><Title>HP Intros Haswell-Based Mobile AIO PC, the ENVY Rove20 May 26, 2013 1:00 PM</Title><Msg>HP Intros Haswell-Based Mobile AIO PC, the ENVY Rove20 By Kevin Parrish May 26, 2013 1:00 PM - Source: HP This is a 20 inch mega-tablet, or a robot in disguise. HP revealed on Friday its first mobile AIO PC, the HP ENVY Rove20, which sports Intel's fourth-generation "Haswell" Core processors. "Mobile" means you can treat this rig as a big-screen 20 inch tablet, as it's light enough to carry around the house without straining a few back muscles. Ten-point touch input makes it great for multiplayer games, and a 1600 x 900 IPS LED panel makes it easy to view in a wide number of angles. tomshardwareDOTcom/news/ENVY-Rove20-Windows-8-Mobile-AIO-Multitouch-Haswell,22774DOThtml</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369636521343</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 02:35:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369636796542-8</Id><Title>HP adds five new towers to its desktop lineup, Haswell offered across the board May 23rd, 2013</Title><Msg>HP adds five new towers to its desktop lineup, Haswell offered across the board By Dana Wollman posted May 23rd, 2013 at 12:01 AM engadgetDOTcom/2013/05/23/hp-refreshes-its-desktop-lineup-with-haswell/ If you think HP's new battery-powered all-in-one is a gimmick, fear not: the company's still churning out all manner of traditional desktop towers. In fact, the outfit just refreshed its lineup with five new models, ranging from a space-saving mini to a high-end gaming rig. There's a lot to digest in the way of specs and pricing, so to keep things simple we laid out a neat list just after the break. Read on for the full break-down. HP Envy Phoenix 800, Envy 700, Pavilion 500, Slimline 400 and the HP 100</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369636796542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 02:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369655643131-9</Id><Topic><Title>Posting Culture</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369619494168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 21:51:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now if you just followed any one of those rules.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369655643131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 07:54:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369659408444-10</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Short Interest: 5/15/2013 224,949,744 : down 8.5m shares</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369453689114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 23:48:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nasdaqtraderDOTcom/ seem not to have many other stocks info. i.e. BAC, C, AA etc interesting</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1369659408444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 08:56:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369670868938-11</Id><Title>Intel to release N2805, N2810 and N2910 ULV processors</Title><Msg>Intel today added three N2xxx series ultra-low voltage products to the official pricelist. New processors have N2805, N2810 and N2910 model numbers, and they are fabricated on 22nm technology. Despite the fact that they are listed in the "ULV Celeron M" section, their processor numbers follow naming conventions for Atom mobile products. Also, one of these "Celeron Ms" has 4 CPU cores and no Hyper-Threading, which suggests that they could be based on ValleyView core, or ValleyView-M, to be more precise. The price list contains very basic specifications for all three parts. According to them, N2800 series, which is currently comprised of N2805 and N2810 SKUs, has 2 CPU cores and 1 MB of last level cache. N2900 series includes N2910 chip, and it doubles the number of cores to 4 and the size of cache to 2 MB. None of the microprocessors support Hyper-Threading technology. The N2805 and N2810 operate at 1.46 GHz and 2 GHz respectively. The quad-core N2910 is clocked at 1.6 GHz. It's not obvious if the processors support Burst mode or not. Compared to previous Atom generation, the N2910 should provide very significant CPU performance boost. The N2810 may also run on a par, or be faster than the N2800 "CedarView" chip, as significantly improved IPC should compensate for the lack of Hyper-Threading feature. cpu-worldDOTcom/news_2013/2013052601_Intel_to_release_N2805_N2810_and_N2910_ULV_processorsDOThtml [Are these Celeron or ValleyView SKUs?]</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1369670868938</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 12:07:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369676382542-12</Id><Title>intel and samsung in galaxy tab 3</Title><Msg>25 tuesdays open..</Msg><Username>dimebag_eddie</Username><Timestamp>1369676382542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:39:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369678461727-13</Id><Topic><Title>May/June Events</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369552586311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 03:16:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I listened to their (ARM's) entire 2 hour+ presentation and came away thoroughly impressed that their design capability is very, very credible, and they do have a way to catch up to Intel's process advantage. So, imo, it was not a disaster at all, instead, their recent stock price performance is just a normal correction somewhat amplified by the turmoil in the markets......for which we have to blame Bernanke." [Well, it seems that you missed the point. Yes, there is a way for ARM to move into FinFET. But not only is WHEN totally in question, IF is actually in question as well. And this is just to follow Intel down the FinFET path. The chances of ARM catching up, as you say, are almost nonexistent. ARM has to do 20nm first and there's no solid evidence that volume production will occur in any certain time frame even at that node. So, ARM might have a half-step to FinFET in some unknown period of years. That's just one point. The major point is that it is not nearly enough for ARM to tread water. With that enormous P/E they have to be expanding at a fantastic rate. And that's what came out of investor day - that the rate of expansion is dropping and that margins are dropping. The gathering storm of Intel competitiveness has now been recognized as well as maturing of the mobility market. It appears that ARM can no longer justify the assumption that they will build at the same incredible rate for years and years into the future. The stock price is based on this assumption or at least it was. It's a new day. And everything points towards the end of the ARM era as we have known it. It appears that Intel is poised to make major gains in mobility while they continue to freeze ARM substantially out of PCs and servers...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369678461727</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 14:14:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369679551798-14</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to release N2805, N2810 and N2910 ULV processors</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1369670868938</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 12:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Atom. Intel seems to be killing the low end Celerons.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1369679551798</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 14:32:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369679657346-15</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to release N2805, N2810 and N2910 ULV processors</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1369670868938</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 12:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Erm, my bad. They are Celeron SKUs.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1369679657346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 14:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369680215476-16</Id><Title>The Haswell News Cycle Ramp</Title><Msg>With Haswell less than a week away, it appears that there is an enormous flood of positive press on the way. While it seems that the buzz might have started to dissipate, a new factor has been injected to provide new life and excitement. The new factor is the news that the Samsung Galaxy Tab 3 (10.1) will use an Intel chipset. And it's the unknown nature of this news that will continue to drive the Haswell news cycle. There are supposedly two possibilities. One is that the Intel processor will be one of three offered on the Galaxy Tab. This would be bad for shorts and presents a serious risk. The other possibility is that the Intel processor will be the ONLY one offered on the Galaxy Tab. This would be devastating to shorts. There is speculation that Samsung will reveal the answers at Computex. The result of this is that there will continue to be speculation through this week and into Computex next week. So, a news cycle that was started to look saturated now has new energy. Of course, once Computex starts (and even now stories are breaking) there will be an exceptional number of new product announcements to also pump energy into the Haswell news cycle. Here's the calendar: June 3: Intel to release Haswell - In the final countdown stage. June 4: Computex Opening Keynote-Tom Kilroy, executive vice president and general manager, Intel's Sales and Marketing Group, will deliver a keynote on Intel's vision for continued innovation to reinvent people's computing experiences across a range of devices. June 4: Computex-Computing Reinvented Satellite Event and Media Q&amp;A-Kirk Skaugen, senior vice president and general manager of the PC Client Group, will host the computing reinvented satellite event where he'll demonstrate and provide details on the new experiences delivered by 4th generation Intel Core processor-based Ultrabooks, laptops, desktops and all-in-one devices. June 5: Computex-Mobile and Communications Satellite Event and Media Q&amp;A-Hermann Eul, VP/GM, Mobi</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369680215476</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 14:43:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369680446797-17</Id><Title>Tech2 Reports That Intel Is The Only One</Title><Msg>Last week, we reported on benchmark tests showing a Samsung tablet powered by an Intel Clover Trail processor. And now a source familiar with the tablet project has told VentureBeat that Samsung has indeed chosen to go with Intel instead of using their own Exynos mobile processor or any other competing ARM-based chip. The earlier benchmark scores revealed that the tab will be using the Intel Atom Z2560 processor clocked in at 1.6GHz with hyper-threading. A PowerVR SGX 544 MP2 graphics processor with a clock speed of 400MHz was also revealed through the benchmarks, while the display was shown to have a resolution of 1280x800. The tablet will most likely be running Android 4.2.2 Jelly Bean. This could be a big boost for Intel and the company's plans to take their mobile processor business to newer heights. It could also pave the way for Intel with other OEMs, if the chipset used makes a good impression in terms of performance and power management. If such a tablet is in the works, it would be the first time that Samsung has gone with an Intel chip for a mobile device. The inclusion of the chip in an Android tablet could be a part of a larger deal for Samsung with Intel for Windows 8 tablets and touchscreen PCs.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369680446797</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 14:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369680822660-18</Id><Title>A More Intriguing Possibility</Title><Msg>An even more intriguing possibility is that Samsung is developing a more expanded relationship with Intel in order to disenfranchise Apple from doing the same things. While Apple bonding with Intel is a major opportunity for them to go one up on Samsung, the possibility exists for Samsung to do the same thing. Could the Galaxy Tab 3 be the first evidence of this? Samsung could be planning a major Tizen move with Intel as well. If Samsung bonded with Intel and squeezed Apple out, could anything then stop them from continuing the ramp they are currently on???</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369680822660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 14:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369681417061-19</Id><Title>Samsung to unveil new devices at June 20 Event</Title><Msg>Another date to add to your list Wallis: appleinsiderDOTcom/articles/13/05/27/samsung-teases-new-android-windows-devices-for-june-20-event "On the heels of launching its latest flagship smartphone, the Galaxy S4, Samsung is now gearing up to introduce more Android devices, as well as new Windows products, at a June 20 event in London."</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1369681417061</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 15:03:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369682029344-20</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung to unveil new devices at June 20 Event</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1369681417061</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 15:03:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Samsung has hired Earls Court 2 for the event, which is a huge venue, so it obviously has something big planned." from cnet</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1369682029344</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 15:13:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369682060645-21</Id><Title>May/June Calendar with Samsung Event Update</Title><Msg>June 3: Intel to release Haswell - In the final countdown stage. June 4: Computex Opening Keynote-Tom Kilroy, executive vice president and general manager, Intel's Sales and Marketing Group, will deliver a keynote on Intel's vision for continued innovation to reinvent people's computing experiences across a range of devices. June 4: Computex-Computing Reinvented Satellite Event and Media Q&amp;A-Kirk Skaugen, senior vice president and general manager of the PC Client Group, will host the computing reinvented satellite event where he'll demonstrate and provide details on the new experiences delivered by 4th generation Intel Core processor-based Ultrabooks, laptops, desktops and all-in-one devices. June 5: Computex-Mobile and Communications Satellite Event and Media Q&amp;A-Hermann Eul, VP/GM, Mobile and Communications Group, will host a satellite event to showcase the growing number of tablets for Windows and Android, smartphones and other ultra-mobile devices with Intel Inside. June 4-6: Dell Enterprise Forum-Enterprise Solutions Keynote: Built for Where Business Is Going June 10-14: Apple's WWDC - Macs about to get a major upgrade thanks to Intel’s new “Iris” graphics processors? June 20: Samsung announces new Windows and Android products in London. June 26-28: Microsoft's Build Developer Conference - Rumors of next Surface Pro announcement</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369682060645</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 15:14:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369683674532-22</Id><Topic><Title>Posting Culture</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369619494168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 21:51:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Credibility? ARM overvalued at 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49 and 50 says Wallisweaver. Keep throwing s**t against the wall, moron.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1369683674532</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 15:41:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369684157204-23</Id><Topic><Title>Posting Culture</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369619494168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 21:51:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Listen idiot, everyone is tired of your stupid Wallis attack posts. Nobody gives a s what you think. Why don't you do us all a favor and get lost?</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369684157204</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 15:49:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369684239574-24</Id><Topic><Title>Posting Culture</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369619494168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 21:51:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm here to show the world that this board is full of sleezy scmucks. You want me to leave? I'll post more now.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1369684239574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 15:50:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369684339876-25</Id><Title>bacbacker and vinnie_bagodonilz is same guy</Title><Msg>Putz freaked out and dumped Intel recently because of a rumor of a Haswell glitch and once it was cleared up he as "back in!" He pumps furiously...........but at the end of the day he'll dump his shares at the drop of a hat. Wuss.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1369684339876</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 15:52:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369684353733-26</Id><Topic><Title>Posting Culture</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369619494168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 21:51:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get ready to cover your short position loser.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369684353733</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 15:52:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369684443262-27</Id><Title>Samsung's Galaxy Tab 3 will have Atom inside</Title><Msg>If Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) wants to prove it has staying power in a post-PC world, it needs to get more of its chips in high-profile tablets. Sources have confirmed that Intel is taking a step into the winner’s circle by teaming up with Samsung on its new Galaxy tablets. According to VentureBeat, the Intel Atom will be the processor of choice for the Tab 3, though Samsung could have used its own chip to power the device. The third-generation Galaxy tablets, which run the Android OS from Google (NASDAQ:GOOG), is a step up for Intel and its Atom chips. Previously, the Atom could be found in several inexpensive PCs and some tablets running Microsoft’s (NASDAQ:MSFT) Windows 8. Latching on to the wildly popular Galaxy line will increase exposure and test the Atom’s processing ability on the biggest stage yet.</Msg><Username>stok1mom</Username><Timestamp>1369684443262</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 15:54:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369684463190-28</Id><Topic><Title>Posting Culture</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369619494168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 21:51:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've never shorted any stock in my entire life, and never will. Guess again, skumbag. I'm your conscience.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1369684463190</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 15:54:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369684536377-29</Id><Topic><Title>bacbacker and vinnie_bagodonilz is same guy</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1369684339876</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 15:52:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'm not bacbacker fool. but you are obviously that idiot fourteennanometer idiot, so obviously you have multiple alias's. Get ready to cover your short position, you're in deep s if you are short INTC.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369684536377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 15:55:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369685069045-30</Id><Topic><Title>The iWatch is coming! The iWatch is coming!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369108005464</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This news will push INTC towards $40 by end of year</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369685069045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:04:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369685096349-31</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung To Use Intel Atom Processor In Its New 10” Tablet [REPORT]</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369166720178</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 16:05:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$40 by end of year shorties!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369685096349</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369685212992-32</Id><Topic><Title>World's first 8-inch Windows 8 tablet Acer W3 appears on official website</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369054186444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:49:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel's chips with its ability to run both Windows 8 (and legacy sw) and Android will be the reason by Intel will dominate tablet market in near future</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369685212992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369685335399-33</Id><Topic><Title>ANOTHER 10" ANDROID TABLET INTEL WIN: ASUS ME302C</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369618269082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 21:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By holiday season, market will be flooded with 7", 8", 10" tablets as well thinner, lighter with all day battery life hybrids/ultrabooks. All of them running both Windows 8 and Android.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369685335399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:08:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369685401663-34</Id><Topic><Title>When Apple announces an Intel deal, this stock will shoot up.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369632449127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 01:27:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agree</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369685401663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:10:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369686643187-35</Id><Title>lots of new things happening with intel lately</Title><Msg>but why is it a sitting duck. it needs major upgrading or some major announcement from the company</Msg><Username>jake_718</Username><Timestamp>1369686643187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:30:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369686708470-36</Id><Topic><Title>World's first 8-inch Windows 8 tablet Acer W3 appears on official website</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369054186444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:49:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely correct. Once tablets give users Android and Windows' vast ecosystem of apps every other tablet will seem like a toy. The iPad will simply be outclassed with no ability to run a professional OS natively or deliver equivalent performance.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369686708470</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:31:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369686810162-37</Id><Title>Chump.weaver</Title><Msg>Don't bother responding to him. Better to just click on the Flag button, then click on "Click Here to contact the Yahoo Abuse Team", then on Report Abuse. Then you can choose either Harassment or Other. If you choose Other you will get a dialog box where you can type something in. The space scrolls so you can type more than in just that space. I've started putting in "Stalks, bullies, harasses and abuses posters on the board." I suggest doing this for each of his posts outside the boundaries of appropriate behavior. If enough people file abuse complains, then Yahoo actually will do something about him. He needs to know that there are repercussions for a consistent pattern of bullying, abuse, harassment and stalking.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369686810162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:33:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369686943754-38</Id><Topic><Title>lots of new things happening with intel lately</Title><Username>jake_718</Username><Timestamp>1369686643187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:30:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"it needs major upgrading or some major announcement from the company" [LOL. You must be the only guy on the planet who missed the Silvermont announcement and doesn't know about the Haswell announcment next Monday...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369686943754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:35:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369687287627-39</Id><Topic><Title>Chump.weaver</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369686810162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:33:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No bullying here. I log on here and see people pumping or bashing stocks for their own gain, like you do every single day. I'm pretty sure Yahoo has employees that are decent people like myself that find it disgusting as well. Stalking? Please.... You sound like the type of guy that cuts someone off in traffic, then flips them the bird. You pump and bash here daily and YOU are the victim? Disgusting.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1369687287627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:41:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369687488160-40</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Short Interest: 5/15/2013 224,949,744 : down 8.5m shares</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369453689114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 23:48:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try just nasdaq and not nasdaqtrader .... I just checked and BAC, C and AA are all there. nasdaqDOTcom the SHORT INTEREST link is down near the bottom on the LEFT column. BAC Settlement Date Short Interest Avg Daily Share Volume Days To Cover 5/15/2013 162,791,412 134,646,027 1.209032 4/30/2013 164,258,453 142,335,510 1.154023 4/15/2013 167,802,833 122,953,135 1.364771 3/28/2013 156,727,798 155,280,618 1.009320 3/15/2013 155,764,079 163,759,298 1.000000 2/28/2013 161,307,947 181,250,048 1.000000 2/15/2013 166,002,570 164,707,397 1.007863 1/31/2013 150,487,517 139,039,374 1.082337 1/15/2013 164,349,915 181,401,404 1.000000 12/31/2012 186,643,980 175,856,595 1.061342 12/14/2012 208,335,829 174,829,542 1.191651 11/30/2012 208,756,718 130,449,612 1.600286 11/15/2012 203,816,430 169,458,376 1.202752 10/31/2012 186,109,646 147,756,356 1.259571 10/15/2012 190,594,520 136,800,527 1.393229 9/28/2012 191,483,651 134,240,482 1.426423 9/14/2012 204,515,743 203,075,817 1.007091 8/31/2012 216,419,831 109,499,787 1.976441 8/15/2012 220,297,162 90,230,803 2.441485 7/31/2012 224,563,797 147,102,809 1.526577 7/13/2012 225,438,149 116,626,780 1.932988 6/29/2012 231,004,224 175,726,130 1.314570 6/15/2012 254,590,796 209,511,590 1.215163 5/31/2012 263,184,398 201,200,575 1.308070 5/15/2012 150,700,826 182,987,165 1.000000</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369687488160</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369689777229-41</Id><Topic><Title>Chump.weaver</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369686810162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:33:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tooofunnky att4glte aintezbeingreen wdblawgrow wallisdreamweaver fourteennanometer itakebackmyapology dominateamerika itakebackrnyapology singhlion2001 coinmaker77 Those are just some of your alias. You are one sick individual. I have reported you to Yahoo.</Msg><Username>iknow.whoyouare</Username><Timestamp>1369689777229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 17:22:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369690255104-42</Id><Topic><Title>Chump.weaver</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369686810162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:33:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3 foul balls and your out. LOL, the pumping and bashing daytraders here can't STAND a non-skumbagg amongst them. Hilarious!</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1369690255104</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 17:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369690528617-43</Id><Topic><Title>Chump.weaver</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369686810162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:33:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would get rid of your computer and change internet service provider if I were you :)</Msg><Username>iknow.whoyouare</Username><Timestamp>1369690528617</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 17:35:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369691863291-44</Id><Topic><Title>Chump.weaver</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369686810162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:33:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You just threatened me. I've never threatened anyone here, so that makes you much less of a person than me, Ashraf. :)</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1369691863291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 17:57:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369693550346-45</Id><Title>Lets face it, this stock is headed down with the market correction.</Title><Msg>Mr Weaver and his catalysts mean nothing. LOL.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369693550346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 18:25:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369694857448-46</Id><Topic><Title>The Haswell News Cycle Ramp</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369680215476</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 14:43:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung move continues to get big press...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369694857448</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 18:47:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369694922253-47</Id><Topic><Title>A More Intriguing Possibility</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369680822660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 14:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung seems to want a closer partnership with Intel...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369694922253</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 18:48:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369695056802-48</Id><Topic><Title>Posting Culture</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369619494168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 21:51:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5.) Credibility is earned by informative posts, stated in a lucid manner with supporting facts, logic and thoughtfulness. [It seems the shills will never learn this...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369695056802</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 18:50:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369695697926-49</Id><Title>Intel talks about next generation flash memory – goes 3D</Title><Msg>Intel thinks it can make NAND memory cells as small as 7 nm using current manufacturing processes and hopes to take NAND technology further with 3D technology. Keyvan Esfarjani, vice president technology &amp; manufacturing at Intel and co-CEO of IMFT said this during the IMEC Technology Forum. IMFT is the joint venture between Intel and Micron and working on 3D NAND. This new NAND type should deal with the scaling limits that are soon reached with current NAND manufacturing processes.At the moment the smallest NAND memory commercially available in SSDs is 19 nm small and with traditional manufacturing methods it’s expected that a size as small as 10 nm can be reached. Beyond that size the regular 2D NAND will likely not scale well anymore. Simplified, NAND memory works by controlling flow of electrons with a so called ‘gate’. The gate is controlled by applying a voltage to it. Without any voltage the gate is down and electrons can’t flow. If a voltage is applied the gate is up and electrons can flow. Using 3D technology in chips is nothing new, Intel also uses 3D transistors in their CPUs. However 3D NAND technology is different, exact details aren’t clear, except that t will consist of multiple layers of cells and that the 3D NAND will use Gate-All-Around structures. This seems to mean that the gate does not open by just going up and down, but can also be closed from left to right.The challenge to refine this technology seems to be finding the right materials that can deal with the different way the 3D NAND will work. It’s expected that the 2D NAND will be used for the coming years, but that eventually the 3D NAND will take over. Also Sandisk/Toshiba, SK Hynix and Samsung are working on similar technology. The latter expects to go in commercial production around 2014. From myce</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369695697926</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 19:01:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369699391513-50</Id><Topic><Title>Lets face it, this stock is headed down with the market correction.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369693550346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 18:25:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's with the laugh? If holding and it heads down, people will lose money. Why is that funny? See, why you are hated. Also, if you predict every day that a stock will go down, eventually you will be right. Does this mean you are highly intelligent? No, it means that you are a cowardly fool who guesses on the outcome of things, isn't long or even short (by your own admission) and taunts people who take a position. You were the kid everyone enjoyed beating up and were always picked last (if at all) when choosing sides for a game.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369699391513</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 20:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369699593582-51</Id><Topic><Title>A More Intriguing Possibility</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369680822660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 14:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Galaxy Tab 3, 10.1 inch and 8 inch are great wins if true. You could say the same about QCOM and the Galaxy 4 phone. Sammy used Samsung Octo (or Cat &amp; Dog 2 times 4-legged) silicon outside the US. Intel components have extra value when running legacy apps has extra value. Samsung is probably making a Win8 tablet and the Intel part makes more sense in that case. A corporate division at Samsung is just like any other corporation. The division is managed by an aggressive type-A personality who wants to move up the corporate ladder. If using Intel will make his division more successful then he will not hesitate. It is better to think if companies like Samsung as a collection of smaller companies than as one monolith that is strategically thinking like you are suggesting. PaulO said that turning Intel was like steering a tanker. Turning Samsung must be like steering a continent.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369699593582</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 20:06:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369699766922-52</Id><Topic><Title>Lets face it, this stock is headed down with the market correction.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369693550346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 18:25:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i hope it does go down so i can buy more of it. This stock is undervalued, and is about to do very well with Haswel. Im a bit of a computer nerd and I know the PC community is excited about this new chip and plan on buying it as soon as it becomes available. june 22 calls are a good buy ATM</Msg><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1369699766922</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 20:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369700956687-53</Id><Title>AMD Tesmash nightmare for Intel:The Acer Aspire V5-122 is a Windows 8 notebook with an 11.6 inch, 1366 x 768 pixel display and an AMD Temash processor. It’s expected to have a starting price of $450, which makes it one of the most affordable touchscreen notebooks around.</Title><Msg>The Acer Aspire V5-122 is a Windows 8 notebook with an 11.6 inch, 1366 x 768 pixel display and an AMD Temash processor. It’s expected to have a starting price of $450, which makes it one of the most affordable touchscreen notebooks around. The notebook reportedly features an AMD A6-1450 “Temash” quad-core processor with Radeon HD 8280 graphics, 2GB of RAM, a 500GB hard drive, WiFi, Bluetooth, VGA, HDMI, USB 3.0, and gigabit Ethernet. Acer’s notebook has a 3 cell battery and weighs about 3.3 pounds.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369700956687</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 20:29:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369701060263-54</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Tesmash nightmare for Intel:The Acer Aspire V5-122 is a Windows 8 notebook with an 11.6 inch, 1366 x 768 pixel display and an AMD Temash processor. It’s expected to have a starting price of $450, which makes it one of the most affordable touchscreen notebooks around.</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369700956687</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 20:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>clover Trail vs Tesmash AMD aims to win the converged device era with new Xbox One-like chips With Temash, Kabini, and Richland, AMD plans to take on Atom and Core i3. AMD is announcing today three new families of chips that it hopes will dominate the market of high-end tablets, low-end laptops, and converged hybrid devices. The chips—which will come to market variously as the A4 and A6 Elite Mobility series; the A4, A6, and E series; and the A6 and A10 Elite series—are close siblings to the processors found in both the Xbox One and PlayStation 4 consoles. Most of the processors are built around the same building blocks: two or four Jaguar CPU cores, paired with AMD's Graphics Core Next (GCN) GPU. They support AMD's heterogeneous uniform memory access technology, too, designed to make it easier to share data and computation between the CPU and GPU. The differences are their power usage, clock speeds, and number of GPU cores. Formerly codenamed Temash, the A4 and A6 Elite Mobility series are full systems-on-chip, adding PCI express, SATA, USB, and other I/O controllers to the CPU and GPU. SKUs range from a 3.9W dual-core 1GHz part with a 225MHz GPU to an 8W quad-core 1.4GHz (maximum)/1GHz (base) part with a 400/300MHz (maximum/base) GPU, the A6-1450. Enlarge / Temash's line-up. AMD AMD is positioning these three chips up against Intel's Clover Trail and low-end Ivy Bridge Core i3 processors, hoping to ship them into what it calls "performance tablets": tablet devices with better performance than ARM chips currently offer, and capable of running the full range of traditional x86 software. Performance comparisons are thus far hard to come by. AMD's publicity materials include many, but due to their selective nature, it's difficult to make any direct comparisons. AMD believes that the Elite Mobility parts fill a hole in Intel's tablet line-up between the Atom and Core i3. They're a little more power-hungry than the Atom but less so than the Core i3, with performance that's more or less in between the two. The GPU and gaming performance of the Temash parts will pull significantly ahead of the Clover Trails, with AMD claiming a Left 4 Dead 2 frame rate of 6.7fps for the dual-core, quad-thread 1.5 GHz Atom Z2760, compared to 15.6fps for the A4-1200, 16.4fps for the A4-1250, and 22.8fps for the A6-1450 at a screen resolution not actually specified, but presumed to be 1366×768. Benchmarks on a leaked A6-1450 suggest a performance in the SunSpider browser benchmark that's approximately twice that of the Clover Trail. The A4, A6, and E series, formerly codenamed Kabini, share the design and integration of Temash but with higher power envelopes and higher clock speeds. There are three dual-core E-series parts, from 9W to 15W, and a pair of A-series parts, one at 15W, the other at 25W. Enlarge / Kabini line-up. AMD AMD is aiming these chips at the mainstream laptop segment, putting them against Intel's Celeron, Pentium, and Core i3 branded parts. There aren't (yet) any good performance comparisons, with AMD's own numbers again focusing on GPU and gaming performance, claiming that an A4-5000 system achieves 120 percent of the frame rate in Batman Arkham City that a comparable Pentium 2117U system achieves (with the Pentium being a marginally more power-hungry 17W chip), and an A6-5200 system achieving 140 percent of the performance of the Pentium system. Finally, AMD is introducing some SKUs codenamed Richland. They range from a 17W dual-core 2.6/2.0GHz part with a 554/424MHz GPU, the A4-5145M, to a 35W quad-core 3.5/2.5GHz chip with a 720/600MHz GPU, the A10-5757M. These are not full systems-on-chips, but rather what AMD calls "APUs;" accelerated processing units. Rather than the Jaguar CPU cores, they use the more powerful Steamroller cores, and their GPUs are a previous generation design. Enlarge / Richland line-up. AMD AMD is pitting these against Intel's Core i3 and i5 processors, and aiming them at the performance laptop market. Again its performance comparisons are GPU-focused, claiming a frame rate in Batman Arkham City of 27fps for the A10-5757M, compared to 16fps for a Core i5-3210M. In spite of the lack of concrete performance information, it's reasonable to believe these are all likely to be decent chips that will fill the needs of most computer users perfectly effectively. The Temash/Kaveri design is a flexible one; though the console processors double the number of cores to eight and likely have more substantial GPU resources (believed to be 12 GPU cores in the Xbox One and 18 in the PlayStation 4), they're fundamentally built from the same architecture with very similar performance profiles. The problem for AMD is one of positioning. While AMD is positioning them directly against various Intel models, the reality is that especially for the Elite Mobility parts, they fall between the gaps. Their major strength is their graphics performance, but while this is superior to Intel's GPU performance, sometimes by quite some margin, it rarely falls into the category of "good enough for actual gaming." And if you're not gaming, the GPU just doesn't matter that much; Intel's GPUs are perfectly adequate for desktop graphics and motion video. As such, AMD may struggle to turn that GPU superiority into something that buyers actually care about. To make a real success of these processors, AMD doesn't just need a few design wins: it needs to carve out an entirely new category of machines, where its performance profile provides tangible benefits to end-users. If the company can't do this, it may yet find some wins due to lower pricing, but it's difficult to see AMD upsetting Intel.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369701060263</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 20:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369701980258-55</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Tesmash nightmare for Intel:The Acer Aspire V5-122 is a Windows 8 notebook with an 11.6 inch, 1366 x 768 pixel display and an AMD Temash processor. It’s expected to have a starting price of $450, which makes it one of the most affordable touchscreen notebooks around.</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369700956687</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 20:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD always stakes out the low ground against the last generation Intel product. Maybe this time it will work. It certainly explains why they rushed the announcement to happen this week. Next week the AMD claims will look different compared to Haswell but they can continue to run this week's ads. You will have to correct the spelling when you start your new threads: "Temash" and not "Tesmash". You got it correct on the copy/paste but goofed it when you typed it out by hand. "AMD is positioning these three chips up against Intel's Clover Trail and low-end Ivy Bridge Core i3 processors, hoping to ship them into what it calls "performance tablets": tablet devices with better performance than ARM chips currently offer, and capable of running the full range of traditional x86 software"</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369701980258</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 20:46:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369706101046-56</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Short Interest: 5/15/2013 224,949,744 : down 8.5m shares</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369453689114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 23:48:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks!</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1369706101046</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 21:55:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369706507503-57</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Tesmash nightmare for Intel:The Acer Aspire V5-122 is a Windows 8 notebook with an 11.6 inch, 1366 x 768 pixel display and an AMD Temash processor. It’s expected to have a starting price of $450, which makes it one of the most affordable touchscreen notebooks around.</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369700956687</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 20:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is not good. With all the superior resources Intel has, how do they let AMD upstage them with the #1 PC vendor?</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369706507503</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 22:01:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369706986425-58</Id><Topic><Title>Intel talks about next generation flash memory – goes 3D</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369695697926</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 19:01:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"IMFT is the joint venture between Intel and Micron and working on 3D NAND. " MU had a nice run. Intel next.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1369706986425</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 22:09:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369707278512-59</Id><Title>Days to cover for shorts has doubled since last month. ouch.</Title><Msg>run and look for cover, it could be painful.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1369707278512</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 22:14:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369707688225-60</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Tesmash nightmare for Intel:The Acer Aspire V5-122 is a Windows 8 notebook with an 11.6 inch, 1366 x 768 pixel display and an AMD Temash processor. It’s expected to have a starting price of $450, which makes it one of the most affordable touchscreen notebooks around.</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369700956687</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 20:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess that you didn't read the exciting conclusion from your own post, which clearly indicates that it is not in any way, shape or form a nightmare for Intel: "As such, AMD may struggle to turn that GPU superiority into something that buyers actually care about. To make a real success of these processors, AMD doesn't just need a few design wins: it needs to carve out an entirely new category of machines, where its performance profile provides tangible benefits to end-users. If the company can't do this, it may yet find some wins due to lower pricing, but it's difficult to see AMD upsetting Intel."</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369707688225</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 22:21:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369707893335-61</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Tesmash nightmare for Intel:The Acer Aspire V5-122 is a Windows 8 notebook with an 11.6 inch, 1366 x 768 pixel display and an AMD Temash processor. It’s expected to have a starting price of $450, which makes it one of the most affordable touchscreen notebooks around.</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369700956687</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 20:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Indeed, Temash is more of a problem for ARM than Intel. As if ARM needs any more problems at the moment. "hoping to ship them into what it calls "performance tablets": tablet devices with better performance than ARM chips currently offer,"</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369707893335</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 22:24:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369708086850-62</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Tesmash nightmare for Intel:The Acer Aspire V5-122 is a Windows 8 notebook with an 11.6 inch, 1366 x 768 pixel display and an AMD Temash processor. It’s expected to have a starting price of $450, which makes it one of the most affordable touchscreen notebooks around.</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369700956687</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 20:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This is not good. With all the superior resources Intel has, how do they let AMD upstage them with the #1 PC vendor?" [As usual, your ability to read, decipher and draw conclusions is fatally flawed. Go back and try the last paragraph again where the author spells out the conclusion so directly that even you should be able to understand it...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369708086850</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 22:28:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369708086975-63</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Tesmash nightmare for Intel:The Acer Aspire V5-122 is a Windows 8 notebook with an 11.6 inch, 1366 x 768 pixel display and an AMD Temash processor. It’s expected to have a starting price of $450, which makes it one of the most affordable touchscreen notebooks around.</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369700956687</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 20:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A 3.3 lb 11 inch notebook, with 4 hr battery life? These days thats like a BIG BOX system. Acer is just producing it to keep Intel honest. I doubt they'll sell very many.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369708086975</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 22:28:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369709941218-64</Id><Topic><Title>AMD Tesmash nightmare for Intel:The Acer Aspire V5-122 is a Windows 8 notebook with an 11.6 inch, 1366 x 768 pixel display and an AMD Temash processor. It’s expected to have a starting price of $450, which makes it one of the most affordable touchscreen notebooks around.</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369700956687</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 20:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is not good. With all the superior resources Intel has, how do they let ACER do something so dumb. After releasing an AMD product like this, ACER will have no respect left from anyone. You will need the extra capacity battery to get the 4 hour operation. The average battery life is 3.5 hours. You can watch the battery meter drop in real time. You can hear the power being drained. From AMAZON ... Average Battery Life (in hours) 3.5 hours</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369709941218</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 22:59:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>