<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372913301141-1</Id><Topic><Title>This is my favorite quote from Paul Otellini re: TMSC and 22nm and smaller production</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372898201500</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:36:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not Intel's 14nm but its 10nm that will probably be the death knell for ARM's preeminence in mobile application chips. If ARM is still jerking around with 20nm back-end chips by then, even if they have smaller 14-16nm FinFETS at the front, it's going to look like AMD then with its uncompetitive bigger hotter chips than Intel. The result will not be pretty for the whole ARM business model and ecosystem.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372913301141</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 00:48:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372914793599-2</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS GOING ON?????</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368550155862</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:49:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how legit!</Msg><Username>chris_lamby</Username><Timestamp>1372914793599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 01:13:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372939535635-3</Id><Topic><Title>Bernstein Research</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372896322079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:05:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The whole market has been ruined by Daytrading losers. NOBODY gets rich daytrading other than a guy or two here and there that "hit the jackpot." Most end up losing everything over time. Brokers love it as the transactions fees pile up and make them rich. It's a mess. Buy at 19, hold and cash those Dividends is the only way to "stick it" to the market.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372939535635</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 08:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372940225053-4</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>All eyes will be on the jobs report on Friday. The S&amp;P 500 has been in an oversold bounce in the past week. The bounce stopped right at the resistance near the 50-day moving average, and the broader market index had been stuck in the 1600-1625 range over the past few sessions. The Friday's jobs report could help the market find a direction. But which way the S&amp;P 500 is going to take to break out of its current range will probably depend on the coming earnings season. Technically, the S&amp;P 500 is still in the downtrend started on May 22. The downside support stands at 1600, followed by the 1560-1575 area, its June low. Should earnings disappoint, we could see the index pull back to the low 1500 area near its 200 day moving average. Have a great 4th of July!</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372940225053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 08:17:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372941168028-5</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Bay Trail benchmark appears online, crushes fastest Snapdragon ARM SoC by 30%</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372858960542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:42:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>loyal opposition eh?:) If I had any spare cash I'd be long Intel. Although I don't buy Intel's mobility story (certainly for the next few years). As for the fab argument, it's much more complicated than just talking about node size and the type of transistor.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1372941168028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 08:32:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372941890233-6</Id><Title>Two of them!</Title><Msg>Look at the tell signs on both the NASDAQ/NYSE. What is happening is stagnation in the major indices. This happens when the large derivative players are shifting their positions. They are now moving money and are going to bet against both markets. In the past this is when large corrections take place (over 10 percent). The large derivative players are the ones that run the indices. For example look at Warren Buffet; he is a heavy derivative player that has, over the last five years, substantially decreased his position in stocks and gone the derivative route. Smart, rich player. Derivative are an easy way to hide money.......so large losses can be covered up. The SEC does not understand this and they cannot track this. The result is no regulation. It will only take one major, dishonest derivative player to send our financial systems into ruin.</Msg><Username>geraldomcginty</Username><Timestamp>1372941890233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 08:44:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372942029086-7</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Bay Trail benchmark appears online, crushes fastest Snapdragon ARM SoC by 30%</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372858960542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:42:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, I've used benchmarks as part of my arguments in the past, so if that argument turns away from me, then I fully expect to get abuse:) I don't think alexander was having a go per-say, as we've discussed Geekbench many times. While I share many of his views on the benchmark, it's still the best we've got in a bad bunch. Geekbench is reasonably transparent (compared to other mobile benchmarks), the algorithms are shown, all the subsets are broken down so you can remove scores that you don't like (ie, the fp image scores for medfield/clovertrail) as well as the threaded/ none threaded scores to get rough apples-to-apples comparisons.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1372942029086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 08:47:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372942736704-8</Id><Topic><Title>Today's ARM upgrade</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372874179061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am sure they do understand the differences. As you know these nodes are just 'names'. What is the actual gate size of all these processes? What are the design rules involved? As an example, Intel's 22nm node has an actual gate size of around 26nm, and with more conservative design rules than TSMC it is entirely possible for the same IP block to be larger on Intel's process than on TSMC's 28nm process.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1372942736704</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 08:58:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372942925459-9</Id><Title>we are ready for liftoff! look at this post ASAP</Title><Msg>I’ve grown and improved by a trader simply by following their picks. All you have to do is Text the word Alert without quotes to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT and follow their picks. Easy money. Text the word Alert without quotes to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT</Msg><Username>barryanthony489</Username><Timestamp>1372942925459</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:02:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372943524247-10</Id><Topic><Title>Web TV developments</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372895888613</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:58:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No these developments are not good for Intel's Web TV. It is already announced that TWC subscribers will be able to stream live TV to Xbox. Maybe TWC will strike a similar deal with Apple but the pre-condition for subscribers doing it is that they must first be paying customers of TWC's video service. This means there is no compelling need for Intel's steaming service. All the cable companies will have a similar offering so in effect Intel's streaming service is pre-empted before launch. The best course of action for Intel is to try to get a similar arrangement with the cable operators for its settop box.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372943524247</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:12:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372946914420-11</Id><Topic><Title>Today's ARM upgrade</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372874179061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how do you measure the gate size of 3D? what are the analysts doing: certain analysts are creating deliberately the perception that TSMC, Samsung and Glofo FinFets are equivalent to Intel TriGate - that is utter none sense and the analysts know it.... from the process point of view it is very,very difficult to scale the backend... it is NOT trivial (why does Intel gets constantly attcked by Goldman for spending capex while TSMC, GloFo and Samsung combined capex exceeds Intel capex by are factor of 2! Why is that? it's the same BS technique in creating false perceptions, does Intel ever brag about tape outs?) if it would be easy to scale the back end TSMC et al would have done it - now they are stuck with limited shrink until 10 nm ! 10nm ! that when they going to be able to scale the backend to 14nm I am very curious what Intel is going to do @ 10nm</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372946914420</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 10:08:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372947597293-12</Id><Topic><Title>Today's ARM upgrade</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372874179061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>certain analysts are creating deliberately the perception that TSMC, Samsung and Glofo FinFets are equivalent to Intel TriGate - ---- My understanding is that they are equivalent? Samsung, GF and UMC are using IBM's version, while TSMC are using their own version.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1372947597293</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 10:19:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372950044558-13</Id><Title>Intel Labs gearing up for Groundbreaking Chips</Title><Msg>Intel (INTC) Prepares Another Super Chip for Business, Intel Labs Gearing for Groundbreaking Chips By Precious Silva | July 4, 2013 4:42 PM EST Intel is the leading tech giant because of the company's ability to pack excellent computing performance in transistors or processors that seem to decrease in size by the day. Even when computing devices shifted from huge desktop computers to small and slim ultrabooks, Intel manages to create a chip that is just right. Recently, the company has been venturing into mobile chips, computing and power efficiency. Intel spends billions of dollars on their research and development every year. Justin Rattner, who served as the company's chief technical officer, previously met with Tom Simonite about the Intel's investment on mobile chips. Mr Simonite is the senior IT editor of MIT Technology Review. Mr Rattner explained to Mr Simonite how Intel sees mobile chips as the company's ticket to overtaking their competitors and creating new opportunities. Mr Rattner just announced his stepping down as the Intel's CTO - he will be returning to the company in a position that is defined clearly yet. Rattner shared with MIT Technology Review the idea behind the new technologies the company is working on including "lab venture." "We have started taking a very select set of technologies from Intel Labs and building new businesses around them [while keeping them inside the Intel Labs organization]. The problem, and it's not unique to Intel, is businesses are busy with their current products and customers, and someone comes along and says 'If you just put another $50 million into this, we'll have this great product' - - that rarely happens. Silicon photonics is the first of those ventures and the only one we've talked about publicly. We've separated the team and started hiring product, design, test, and production engineers. We haven't detailed when we will announce products in this space," Mr Rattner said.</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372950044558</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:00:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372950064958-14</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Labs gearing up for Groundbreaking Chips</Title><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372950044558</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:00:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He also explained the idea behind the first silicon photonics product. "It's a 100-gigabit-per-second transceiver [a device that sends data between computers along an optical fiber]. We use conventional CMOS [chip] fabrication techniques to actually build the lasers into the chip. We showed a 50-gigabit-per-second link a few years ago that was built in the lab (see "Computing at the Speed of Light"); the current chip can do 100 gigabits per second, but the connector, which we teamed up with Corning to build, has the ability to go to 1.6 terabits per second." The silicon photonics will be useful for data centers. Facilities can access more bandwidth for a fraction of a cost. This will be a definite win for those looking for energy efficiency and excellent performance. Data centers are very keen on anything that can provide excellent performance but the cables that come with these capacities can be problematic. Intel Labs is working getting rid of those cables without sacrificing performance or efficiency. I think we're in a period of fairly rapid innovation. The industry built the same transistor for 40 years, and it just got smaller," Mr Rattner added.</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372950064958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:01:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372951633486-15</Id><Topic><Title>Apple just made a huge mistake by signing with TSMC</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372895929756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing to watch out for is if Apple sticks with the 40nm node from TSMC. And if it's truly a year out then the next node Apple may want from TSMC may be 28nm. I have faith that by next year TSMC can finally make 28nm in sizable enough yields to satisfy Apple. Lets be really clear about Apple. Up until last year they were still selling a few computers with Core2Duo processors. That' a processor that dates back to 2006! So, no they don't need the fastest processors, or so they think. The problem is that these Intel 14nm processors will be all over the market and Apple will once again will be two nodes behind. The iPhone will feel a bit sluggish compared to Intel based Android phones. Battery life will be questionable. If you look at the latest Apple press conference iOS7 looks like they copied Android homework very nicely. Apple seems to be running out of ideas, and they are slow to change hardware. You are thinking that Apple will have some amazing 20nm processor from TSMC and facing stock outages. That's not a good thing because Apple fans will wait 3 months for their new phone to arrive. I am thinking that in order to avoid the stock outages they will not take the first batches from the newest nodes from TSMC. They will most likely stick with 28nm. That's better for Intel because more consumers would fall off the iPhone bandwagon. Apple seems to happy to just be a player in the phone market providing just enough interesting stuff to keep consumers somewhat loyal. The lack of leadership from Cook makes Apple just a player instead of a leader in the smartphone segment. Sooner or later consumers will get tired of their small phones and lackluster performance and move on. Android is really the only other game in town.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372951633486</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:27:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372951913440-16</Id><Title>Leaked Skylake Info</Title><Msg>techspot (dotcom) /news/53129-intels-14nm-skylake-platform-to-support-ddr4-pcie-40-sata-express.html</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372951913440</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:31:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372952068164-17</Id><Topic><Title>Leaked Skylake Info</Title><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372951913440</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:31:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By Shawn Knight On July 4, 2013, 8:00 AM Comments 5 A leaked Intel Xeon roadmap purportedly sheds some light on what the chip maker has in store for Skylake, the successor to the yet-to-be-released Broadwell platform. Chips aren’t slated to hit the market for a couple more years but when they do arrive, they’ll be carrying an array of new tech with them. The 14-nanometer processor will be the first of its kind using that manufacturing process and will introduce Intel’s ninth generation Intel HD IGP. It’ll also be the first platform to support dual-channel DDR4 memory but not the first to deliver DDR4 in general as Haswell-E will support quad-channel DDR4 next year.</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372952068164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:34:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372952091594-18</Id><Topic><Title>Leaked Skylake Info</Title><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372951913440</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:31:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The new platform will additionally support PCIe 4.0 which is said to essentially double the bandwidth offered by the current generation PCIe 3.0 standard. This will likely be a welcomed addition as more powerful graphics cards from AMD and Nvidia could use the extra bandwidth. If that weren’t enough to get you interested, perhaps SATA Express support might do the trick. This standard will boost maximum bandwidth to around 16GB/s which is more than 2.5 times as much as the existing standard allows for. Hopefully solid state drives will evolve enough to actually make use of the extra bandwidth. The slide doesn’t give an exact date as to when Skylake will be ready for prime time but we’re hearing that Intel will likely launch the new platform sometime in late 2015 or beyond. It looks like I’ll be holding off on upgrading my main system until then.</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372952091594</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:34:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372952807530-19</Id><Title>SA removes awful anti-Intel post</Title><Msg>There was a post on Seeking Alpha a few days ago known as "Going for Intel may not be smart, for now" which was pure garbage. It was written by a young Asian woman with her daughter in her profile pic. It was pro ARM and very negative on Intel. She made the claim that Apple may go full ARM in the near future, and that the CEO for the last 30 years just stepped down. It was such a horrific piece of garbage that she was called out almost instantly by legions of Intel fans who took issue with nearly everything she said. Well, as it turns out, even Seeking Alpha has standards and this mindless dribble was too far below their standards that it was yanked. The post was put up on July 2nd, and removed by July 4th. Say what you want about my boy Ashraf Eassa , his stuff doesn't get yanked. It's okay to take aim at Intel, but as time goes on you're taking a minority opinion. Call it wrong, or use a little of the BS platform that Warren East made famous and you can look foolish. Its one thing to come on to a chatboard with a handle and spout off nonsense. When you put your name and face to it on Seeking Alpha you can't get away with it</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372952807530</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:46:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372952959349-20</Id><Topic><Title>Today's ARM upgrade</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372874179061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" My understanding is that they are equivalent? Samsung, GF and UMC are using IBM's version, while TSMC are using their own version." [Why do you say they are equivalent? Samsung, TSMC, and GF are all using bulk finfet and using the 20nm backend. IBM is moving to SOI for 14nm because it will use them in their own servers where the high cost can be absorbed. Does anybody know what TSMC's and the others finfet will look like? Experts At The Table: Changes In The Ecosystem Thursday, June 20th, 2013 By Ed Sperling Semiconductor Manufacturing &amp; Design sat down with Michael Buehler-Garcia, director of design solutions marketing at Mentor Graphics; Seow Yin Lim, group director for marketing at Cadence; Kevin Kranen, director of strategic alliances at Synopsys, and Tom Quan, director at TSMC. What follows are excerpts of that conversation. SMD: What’s changing in the ecosystem and how will it continue to change over the next couple process nodes? Quan: If you look at 28nm, and even at 40nm, we started working with EDA companies with our design rule manual earlier than in the past. Version 1.0 is basically production. At 28nm, we started working with our partners on version 0.1, which is very early, then version 0.5 all the way up to 1.0. With 16nm finFETs, we’re now working on version 0.1. These can change every few days, so the commitment from Synopsys, Mentor and Cadence has to be very high because you have to have a way to synchronize these activities to get to the next version.]</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1372952959349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:49:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372953981638-21</Id><Topic><Title>Today's ARM upgrade</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372874179061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just using the same word as semi_equip_junkie:) enDOTwikipediaDOTorg/wiki/Multigate_device</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1372953981638</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:06:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372954137962-22</Id><Title>With the Increased battery life of baytrail over ARM, everyone is clamoring for</Title><Msg>baytrail in their tablets. ARM is a battery guzzling power hog, No one will use it for tablets, now that baytrail is out.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372954137962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372954168495-23</Id><Topic><Title>Today's ARM upgrade</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372874179061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes the Fins provide performance improvement but they are not going to provide the cost advantage a shrink would provide. Intel does both. It's funny that certain analysts always point out Intel's margin getting squeezed due to SoC manufacturing - the same analysts are completely ignorant to the fact that TSMC's FinFet does not provide the cost advantage compared to planar. TSMC should be downgraded due to margin pressure The lack of shrinking the FinFet will impact the margins of the entire ARM food chain. Even G61 admitted that TSMC alone will not do the heavy lifting by itself Going from 28nm to 20nm is a capex increase of 1.7 approx than they need to spend capex to get to FinFet but the cost advantage due to shrink is muted - (I am heavily invested in chip equipment companies - so I know what's coming down the pipe - Covello covers both equipment and Intel - he should know what TSMC et al are facing with respect to capex and its impact on TSMC's margin - nevertheless he only bashes Intel - he even suggests Intel to CUT capex! Covello IS one of the worst manipulators and he's backed up the money ) In DRAM manufacturing with razor thin margin the biggest #$%$ is shrinking - shrink is very powerful because one shrinks dies in x axis and y axis and you end up with a lot more dies per wafer Intel SoC will have cost advantage - than comes 450mm which is supposed to provide 30% cost reduction - that's why Intel is already spending $2 billion on 450mm. Of course Intel gets slammed by Covello for doing so.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372954168495</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:09:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372954343657-24</Id><Title>Why anyone would have new ARM based tablet designs is beyond me.</Title><Msg>Now that baytrail is out, and everyone knows its capabilities.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372954343657</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:12:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372956008313-25</Id><Topic><Title>SA removes awful anti-Intel post</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372952807530</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The worst post I ever saw was your profile pic on S.A. with Jesus Christ giving the middle finger. Tasteless.........and disgusting.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372956008313</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:40:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372956661573-26</Id><Topic><Title>SA removes awful anti-Intel post</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372952807530</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jamulmike • Jul 1, 2013 11:52 AM 0 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 0 Reply 22nm Haswell? Snore. It's 14nm Skylake time!!!. FinFET, too!!!! Microsoft says it's picking up the pace on software. The 20th rollout of every 2-3 years gone. Look for 1 year or less from now on. Bless the Mobile guys and their history repeating innovations. These are truly, truly... Very exciting times!!!! Cymer times!!!!!!! Haswell is pretty sweet, but it's old news. Say hello to Skylake - the "tock" that follows Broadwell: The details on this core are still scarce, but we know the following: Built on the 14nm process (so that gives the chip designers a lot more room to play with on both power and transistor count) Utilizes next generation DDR4 memory Supports the next generation PCIe4 standard (the AMD (AMD) bulls/Nvidia (NVDA) bears that claim that Intel is killing PCIe look pretty foolish right now) Supports the AVX3.2 instruction set Now, the last part is pretty important because we know that AVX3 brings yet another doubling of the peak floating point throughput for the processor cores: This suggests that for anything involving floating point intensive calculations (think games, spreadsheets, 3D modeling, and even all of the perceptual computing stuff that Intel keeps touting), and assuming Intel's software developer relations team does its job right, Skylake should be a monster. Now, the interesting thing is that Intel is going to be packing this kind of processing power into Ultrabooks and high end tablets. Less</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372956661573</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372963056364-27</Id><Topic><Title>Why anyone would have new ARM based tablet designs is beyond me.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372954343657</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:12:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They will continue to get more inexpensive and they do have their value. Single tablet: 10.1' disposable plate Level an uneven table. Firewood replacement Dog Frisbee. Door stop. A stacks of 10 duct taped together: Artificial reef Sea wall Childs booster seat. Tire blocks Kitchen step stool. fill in pot holes freeway median dividers</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372963056364</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:37:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372965975558-28</Id><Topic><Title>Apple just made a huge mistake by signing with TSMC</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372895929756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with you but I think Apple is up to something...I believe they know Intel's advantages but going with TSMC might be for a different reason..not sure what but they are up to something.</Msg><Username>clemsyn</Username><Timestamp>1372965975558</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:26:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372965998813-29</Id><Topic><Title>SA removes awful anti-Intel post</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372952807530</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, I have a great idea. Why don't we dig up the worst 20 things I've ever said or done on here, and I'll have Wallis dig up the worst 20 things you've ever said and done here. Since you are such an outstanding Christian I will sit down with you in front of your minister, priest, or whatever man of the cloth you go to and let him sort it all out for us. I am serious, I will fly in to your town and just let him see what you've been up to online. I'm sure he's got no idea. I love the fact you fake up Christian moral outrage when it's convenient and otherwise act like a person you would never own up to in reality. Please don't play the morality card, you're playing with an empty hand.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372965998813</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:26:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372967585041-30</Id><Topic><Title>Apple just made a huge mistake by signing with TSMC</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372895929756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"but going with TSMC might be for a different reason..." in order to understand you must travel back in time - approx 2 years. what was Intels mobile situation back than? Apple decision to go with TSMC @ 20nm was NOT made based on today's data - that's important to consider. - matters have changed dramatically to Intel's advantage in the last two years. Intel now has a highly competitive SoC and a solid road map... Even semiwiki doubted that any decisions were made in regards to Finfet and 10nm</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372967585041</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:53:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372967879008-31</Id><Topic><Title>SA removes awful anti-Intel post</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372952807530</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I never said I was religious, LOL. Can you say ANYTHING in less than 10 paragraphs? I'm serious. What an arrogant windbag you clearly are. PS, religious or not, laughing at religion makes you a clown. Nothing but a clown.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372967879008</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:57:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372967899481-32</Id><Topic><Title>Why anyone would have new ARM based tablet designs is beyond me.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372954343657</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:12:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[LOL. And LOL again...] "They will continue to get more inexpensive and they do have their value. Single tablet: 10.1' disposable plate Level an uneven table. Firewood replacement Dog Frisbee. Door stop. A stacks of 10 duct taped together: Artificial reef Sea wall Childs booster seat. Tire blocks Kitchen step stool. fill in pot holes freeway median dividers"</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372967899481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:58:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372967932152-33</Id><Topic><Title>SA removes awful anti-Intel post</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372952807530</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LTI STEVE, ladies and gentleman. Biggest boob on the internet, bar none.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372967932152</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:58:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372968448502-34</Id><Topic><Title>SA removes awful anti-Intel post</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372952807530</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I remember him. Getanid61 had him so scared that he ended up kissing his butt. That exchange was hilarious. I see he wants to get on a plane again and chase a stranger. His skin sure is thin.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372968448502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 16:07:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372971062145-35</Id><Topic><Title>Making 100k a year trading!</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368346134909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 04:08:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FMCC</Msg><Username>chris_lamby</Username><Timestamp>1372971062145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 16:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372971770350-36</Id><Topic><Title>SA removes awful anti-Intel post</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372952807530</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are worthless. You are scared of your own shadow. Go ahead and hide behind aliases and calling people out. You have nothing productive to say, ever. You aren't smart enough to spar on here with your wits and a real point of view, so instead you act like a 14 year old. GetanID16 at least had something of interest to say. After our fun and games were over we got along quite well. And for the record I love whenever TheBlueeyedMonk writes on here. That guy has called me out so many times I've lost count. I don't always agree with everything he says but I certainly learn a lot. I've learned nothing, and I do mean nothing from you.. Neither has anybody else. After all these years of writing on here can you point to three things that people found of interest? You're a dimwit, you're weak, and you're worthless. And you're as big a loser in real life as you are on here.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372971770350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:02:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372971780349-37</Id><Topic><Title>Apple just made a huge mistake by signing with TSMC</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372895929756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I agree with you but I think Apple is up to something...I believe they know Intel's advantages but going with TSMC might be for a different reason..not sure what but they are up to something." [Yeah, that's what I've been thinking but then we never see anything. Now I start to wonder if when we see it, if it will still matter. Apple is losing the cool factor. Once it's gone, it's really hard to get it back. They seem afraid to do anything bold and/or decisive. I think that's the Tim Cook effect. So far being careful has done nothing but trim the stock price. Intel, on the other hand, is showing the willingness to take some risk. The web TV may not work out but I applaud Intel for trying. You have to throw the long ball periodically to make the competition believe that you will throw the long ball. I think it's a good risk...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372971780349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:03:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372971887902-38</Id><Title>Futures Indicate</Title><Msg>That the doom and gloom crowd is going to experience more palpable disappointment tomorrow...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372971887902</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:04:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372971993382-39</Id><Topic><Title>Wanna make 300% on your next stock trade??</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1366937596462</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:53:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YAUT</Msg><Username>chris_lamby</Username><Timestamp>1372971993382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:06:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372972193534-40</Id><Title>A few days ago</Title><Msg>A few days ago, analysts said that Intel Atom will overtake ARM based processor in three years. Well. The current trend shows that this is slowly becoming truth. Another Intel powered device is approved in China – ZTE V975. According to the filing of Telecommunication Equipment Certification Center MIIT in China, the ZTE V975 has cleared the hurdle and ready for launch in the Chinese market. ZTE V975 is an Intel-powered phablet. From gsminsider</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372972193534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:09:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372972422092-41</Id><Topic><Title>SA removes awful anti-Intel post</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372952807530</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A grown man with children that posts a picture of Jesus Christ holding up his middle finger on a public forum claiming someone else is a loser. Pardon me while I step outside and laugh so hard that I snot all over the front lawn.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372972422092</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:13:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372972505345-42</Id><Topic><Title>46k in 2 months? net PROFIT</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1366433177700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OLCD</Msg><Username>chris_lamby</Username><Timestamp>1372972505345</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:15:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372972750399-43</Id><Topic><Title>One trade + $4,500 On the day..</Title><Username>rogerwalker513</Username><Timestamp>1371785363137</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 23:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WPNV</Msg><Username>chris_lamby</Username><Timestamp>1372972750399</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:19:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372972750797-44</Id><Topic><Title>Apple just made a huge mistake by signing with TSMC</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372895929756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at the last Apple press conference. The only excitement was about Intel based products. You are right, Tim Cook is flying the plane on autopilot and is to afraid to touch the controls. Not going with Intel for iPhone is less and indictment on Intel than a symptom of them being to scared to play with their formula. X% of the market will only buy Apple products, cool or not. They have enough business to not really worry much about things and enough money in the bank to not have to face reality for decades.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372972750797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:19:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372973363044-45</Id><Topic><Title>One trade + $4,500 On the day..</Title><Username>rogerwalker513</Username><Timestamp>1371785363137</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 23:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THUMBS UP</Msg><Username>merri.evans</Username><Timestamp>1372973363044</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372974073411-46</Id><Title>Faster, more efficient than ARM</Title><Msg>["Intel’s fortunes in mobile might be about to change for the better."] Bay Trail benchmarked, looks good Intel’s fortunes in mobile might be about to change for the better. The first benchmarks of Chipzilla’s new Bay Trail SoC have showed up in Antutu and the chip looks very good indeed. A Bay Trail-T part clocked at 1.1GHz ends up about 30 percent faster than Qualcomm’s Snapdragon 800 at 2.3GHz. Intel’s little chip just gets more done per clock cycle, which means it uses less power to deliver more performance. At the moment ARM is the king of the frugal mobile chip market, but Intel’s trump card looks a bit better. It scored 43,415 in Antutu, while Snapdragon 800 devices score about 30,000. Samsung’s Exynos 4412 used in the Galaxy S3 scores around 20,000, while Nvidia’s Tegra 3 hits 15,000. Furthermore, Bay Trail-T is expected to ship with clocks in excess of 2GHz, which means upcoming commercial devices based on the new chip could end up even faster. It’s not just about performance. Bay Trail-T seems to use a lot less power under load than competing ARM chips. Intel claims Bay Trail-T will be more power efficient than dual-core ARMs, but at the same time it will outpace quad-core ARM chips. From Fudzilla</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372974073411</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372974329767-47</Id><Title>Intel: Responding To Piper Jaffray's Downgrade</Title><Msg>I've always tried to keep an open and honest relationship with my readers. I always try to carefully lay out my assumptions, and I'm always happy to listen to arguments that run counter to my conclusions and assumptions. I don't purport to know everything (far from it), despite what I believe to be extensive due diligence, but I do my homework and believe that my understanding of both the business as well as the technological side of the Intel (INTC) story allows me to offer up unique insights. Very recently, the sell-side firm Piper Jaffray reiterated its "underperform" rating and $20 price target on Intel and cited, what I believe, to be unfair assumptions to justify the downgrade. I certainly understand the bearish argument(s) - and there are certainly valid ones - but I believe that the arguments presented by the team at Piper Jaffray simply do not hold water. From Ashraf Eassa</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372974329767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:45:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372974570654-48</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Responding To Piper Jaffray's Downgrade</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372974329767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excerpt: So, Piper Jaffray made a big deal about Intel not winning this business [Apple] as though it were a surprise; it's not and anybody seriously following Intel would know that an Apple-Intel foundry deal was never likely, no matter how much short term traders wanted it to happen. Now, Piper Jaffray believes that since Intel didn't win the Apple foundry deal, and since it's not going to win every Samsung device ever, that it's shut out of the mobile market for CY2014 and CY2015. Are these guys serious? Do they forget that the tablet market is just beginning and that many companies are playing to win big time? While Intel has a good relationship on the PC side of things with Samsung (and again, Intel is in both the Galaxy Tab 3 10.1" and the Ativ Tab - two flagship designs based on older Atom silicon, not the new good stuff coming later this year), these analysts forget that there's an army of players - all of whom have excellent relationships with Intel - coming to market in force with both Windows and Android tablets (and Intel can participate in both). These firms are, ASUS Lenovo Dell HP Acer Toshiba Sony Fujitsu Of course, it helps that every major Taiwanese ODM will be building around the upcoming "Bay Trail" platform, so you will see the market full of Intel based tablets this Holiday season from all of the aforementioned OEMs. So, with a huge army of Android and Windows tablets coming with Intel silicon ranging from 7" to 11" and from sub $199 to $499, does it really matter that Intel isn't building Apple's A-chips? No, and in fact, each one of these Windows and/or Android tablets that gets sold is a lost sale for Apple and a market share shift in Intel's favor...and Intel gets more than just foundry margins for these chips. From Ashraf Eassa</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372974570654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:49:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372974586947-49</Id><Title>Olivetti Olipad W808, W809 and W810: Windows 8.1 tablet with Intel Bay Trail in October</Title><Msg>Intel will have a hard time keeping the lid on all the products that will hit the market in late Q3 &amp; Q4. Olivetti used the TI OMAP and NVDA Tegra 3 CPU in their current line up. The product names seem to be "W8" for Windows and size of the tablet: 8, 9, and 10 inches. Olivetti may soon come on the market thanks to three Windows 8 tablet that without any fuss are shown on the official website with a lot of technical information supplied. We are, in fact, before the first tablet based on the platform Intel Bay Trail , particularly waiting for the promised generational leap, with much better performance than dual-core Atom Z2760 and consumption equal to the current ones that come to autonomies and exceed the eight-hour . Olipad W808, W809 and W810 will not see the light before you start Autumn, inevitable then assume a launch to coincide with the debut of Windows 8.1 that will be of considerable progress in different fields. The W808 is the smallest of the three, with 8.1-inch display which makes it in fact the third tablet with this diagonal based on the Microsoft platform: resolution of 1280 × 800, 2GB RAM, 32GB iNAND flash (expandable), 3G and a weight of 750g. The processor is not specified in detail, but the card reads: OS Microsoft Windows 8 (likely 8.1 right now) Intel Core Baytrail - T Screen 8.1 "LCD 1280 × 800 2 GB DDR2 RAM, 32 GB iNAND Flash Connectivity 3G 7.2 DL / UL 5.76 Mbps; Wi-Fi 802.11 b / g / n, Bluetooth 4.0 MicroUSB port, Micro SD card slot up to 32 GB; Posterior chamber 2 Mpix, 0.3 Mpix front GPS; Dimensions 220x136x12mm, Weight 750 gr</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372974586947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:49:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372974697183-50</Id><Title>Not only are Intel's upcoming chips better, Qualcomm ,etc. will suffer from Manufacturing</Title><Msg>Double Whammy. That's how I see it.</Msg><Username>mark.steffenhagen</Username><Timestamp>1372974697183</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372975026428-51</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Responding To Piper Jaffray's Downgrade</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372974329767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting that you bring this up, since YOU pumped it. What a jerk.... Friday Apple Rumors: Alternate Choice (Intel and not TSMC!) by wallisweaver•Jan 4, 2013 9:49 PMFlag . Alternate Choice: Despite a growing chorus of reports that Apple will partner with TSMC to produce chips for its mobile devices, Forbes notes that many Silicon Valley experts increasingly expect it to tap Intel instead. Apple has been reportedly moving to reduce its dependence on Samsung as a manufacturing partner as the two companies have become global competitors in the mobile device market. Previous rumors have suggested the TSMC has begun preparing test runs to make Apple’s A6X mobile processors. However, MKM Partners analyst Daniel Berenbaum suggest that Intel is a more logical choice for the role since it’s greater chip-making capacity could allow it to act as an Apple chip foundry without the need for new capital investment. Rumors suggest that TSMC has been investing heavily to accommodate Apple’s anticipated orders. But Berenbaum says that TSMC’s chip-making capacity remains too restricted to meet Apple’s heavy demand</Msg><Username>mark.steffenhagen</Username><Timestamp>1372975026428</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:57:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372976104921-52</Id><Topic><Title>Making 100k a year trading!</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368346134909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 04:08:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IUTR</Msg><Username>merri.evans</Username><Timestamp>1372976104921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:15:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372976667142-53</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Responding To Piper Jaffray's Downgrade</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372974329767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess Wally doesn't follow Intel seriously or he would have known? What an incredible con man and hypocrite. Just unreal.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372976667142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:24:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372976829773-54</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Responding To Piper Jaffray's Downgrade</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372974329767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>STEFFENHAGEN - intresting name - are you related? Arno Steffenhagen (born 24 September 1949 in Berlin) is a retired German professional football player who played in Germany for Hertha BSC (Berlin), Hamburger SV and FC St. Pauli, in South Africa for Hellenic FC, in the Netherlands for Ajax, and in North America for Chicago Sting, Toronto Blizzard and Vancouver Whitecaps. He also won one cap for the German national side in 1971.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372976829773</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:27:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372976988576-55</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Responding To Piper Jaffray's Downgrade</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372974329767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, Google Mark Steffenhagen Arnold Palmer......that's me !</Msg><Username>mark.steffenhagen</Username><Timestamp>1372976988576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:29:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372978006014-56</Id><Title>If silvermont based tablets and smartphones get 10-12 hrs of battery life,</Title><Msg>will people still buy ARM based tablets and smartphones for 6-7 hrs of battery life? I'll bet the ARM fans think they'll do. LOL. ARM is dead. Long live X86.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372978006014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372978071554-57</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Responding To Piper Jaffray's Downgrade</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372974329767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cut back on the lemons, sourpuss...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372978071554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:47:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372979288789-58</Id><Title>Sights on Dana</Title><Msg>You're not too hard to find. . .</Msg><Username>getanid62</Username><Timestamp>1372979288789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:08:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372979830333-59</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Responding To Piper Jaffray's Downgrade</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372974329767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You pump Apple and Intel, then when it doesn't happen you link an article saying "anybody that knows anything knew it wouldn't happen anyway." Do you not understand how that makes you completely pompous? Probably not.</Msg><Username>mark.steffenhagen</Username><Timestamp>1372979830333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:17:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372981849192-60</Id><Title>Huge Gainer for Next Week!</Title><Msg>CCUR, currently $7.44, has 8.754mm s/o, a market cap of $65.13mm, cash of $22.37mm, no debt, and an enterprise value of $42.76mm. CCUR's enterprise value is only 0.68X revenues of $63.23mm, 6X operating cash flow of $7.13mm, and 7.64X free cash flow of $5.6mm. CCUR's EPS was up 175% last quarter and it just raised its dividend by 100% to $0.48 per share for a yield of 6.45%. CCUR leads the video on demand (VOD) delivery business with over 2.4mm VOD streams shipped globally and 4 of America's 6 largest cable TV operators as clients. The #2 VOD tech vendor SEAC finished yesterday at $11.83 and is about to break through its 52-week high of $12.10. SEAC has an enterprise value of $273.2mm or 1.75X revenues of $156.11mm, 15.67X operating cash flow of $17.43mm, and 20.12X free cash flow of $13.58mm. An enterprise value of 1.75X revenues would value CCUR at $15.20. An enterprise value of 15.67X operating cash flow will value CCUR at $15.32. An enterprise value of 20.12X free cash flow will value CCUR at $15.43. In addition, CCUR provides the #1 Big Data Analytics software solution for cable TV operators. CCUR tracks the customer behavior of 35 million cable TV subscribers across linear TV, VOD, and nDVR and has already processed 15 billion media transactions. Big Data Analytics is the #1 hottest industry on Wall Street. DATA recently had its IPO at $31 and hit a new 52-week high yesterday of $61.45 for a gain of 98%. DATA's enterprise value is currently 24X revenues vs. CCUR's enterprise value of 0.68X revenues! CCUR's business is booming big time as cable TV service providers upgrade their systems to provide new Network DVR, start-over, and look-back services. CCUR is also powering multi-screen video delivery to tablets, smartphones, and other IP connected devices for major cable TV operators like TWC! Plus, CCUR provides content delivery network (CDN) video solutions and just signed a major CDN contract with Virgin Media, the #1 pay-TV operator in the UK!.</Msg><Username>goodwe212</Username><Timestamp>1372981849192</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:50:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372986181018-61</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Responding To Piper Jaffray's Downgrade</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372974329767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, no - not more lemons, sourpuss - less lemons...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372986181018</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372986458498-62</Id><Title>Intel 530-series SSDs coming next week</Title><Msg>In a bunch of sizes and form factors Intel’s next generation 530-series SSDs are about to be launched, probably next week. The new drives are based on 20nm MLC and the same LSI Sandforce SF-2281 controller used in previous Intel SSDs. The 530 series will eventually replace all 520 and 525 series drives. It will come in three form factors, the standard 2.5-inch 7mm, mSATA and NGFF M2. There’s also a generous choice of capacities, 80GB, 180GB, 240GB and 360GB for mSATA and NGFF M2 drives. The far bigger 2.5-inch will have a choice of 180GB, 240GB, 360GB and 480GB drives. There is still no word on performance, but the new series should end up noticeably faster than 520/525 drives. From Fudzilla</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372986458498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:07:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372987234080-63</Id><Title>Can’t choose between Windows, Android, Linux? Choose all three</Title><Msg>Italian company Ekoore created quite a stir recently when it launched an 11.6-inch tablet with not one, not two but three operating systems. The Ekoore Python S3 can be purchased running Windows 8, Android 4.2 or Ubuntu 13.04 – or all three running together. The x86-based tablet features 1.1 GHz Intel Celeron 847 dual-core processor, 32GB of solid-state memory and comes with a detachable display – which also boasts an HDMI output, USB port, micro SD card and headphone jack. The included keyboard dock boosts battery time by 5 hours to 12 in total. The Ekoore Python S3 is now available in Italy for around €599 ($770) but can also be ordered online. From tabtimes</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372987234080</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372988104376-64</Id><Title>Walliswaver made to look like a total dweeb.......yet again</Title><Msg>So So sad. He posted "Apple and Intel" for MONTHS.........and now that it doesn't happen, he copies and pastes an Ashraf article saying "only clueless fools would have thought it would happen." ROFL! This dolt called himself a fool.....but watch him brush it under the chair like it never happened.......like his call on intel 30........the loser takes zero responsibility for his wreckless, trashy and deceptive pumps.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372988104376</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372988775808-65</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Responding To Piper Jaffray's Downgrade</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372974329767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"IF" Intel had won the Apple business, Covello and his margin minions would have mounted their "LOW MARGINS ARE COMING" horses and rode along the New Jersey beaches, sounding the alarm. He would have hypothesized that Intel would have to sell Apple the parts below cost in order to win business and the Apple products would then cannibalize other Intel products sold at high margins. It is a beautiful Catch22. Half the analysts pitching one view and half the other. If you win Apple, it will destroy margins and your business. If you lose Apple, you can't keep your fabs full and destroy your margins. He would have lowered INTC from his SELL rating and $16 target to a "REALLY SELL, BUY PUTS, CONVICTION SHORT" list and lowered his target from $16 to $9.42.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372988775808</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:46:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372990355936-66</Id><Topic><Title>Sights on Dana</Title><Username>getanid62</Username><Timestamp>1372979288789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:08:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just what I thought, you're a big man when you think nobody knows who you are. Just remember I own you now.</Msg><Username>getanid62</Username><Timestamp>1372990355936</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 22:12:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372990445774-67</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Responding To Piper Jaffray's Downgrade</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372974329767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd love to hear the analysts explain how ARM drops 14 bucks due to looming competition with Intel without Intel moving up a dime. In fact, Wall Street has moved Intel down by a couple of bucks. The only way this would make any sense is if the mobility market is shrinking. It's not. It's still experiencing strong growth and Intel is getting a larger and larger piece of a growing pie. Welcome to you can't have it both ways, Wall Street! Is it possible that Wall Street still doesn't get it? After Silvermont? After Haswell? After the Samsung deal and new tablets? After the Bay Trail performance news? After FinFET? After ARM's failure to get traction with RT or in servers? With volume 14nm FinFET production just around the corner? No, it's not possible. Wall Street is looking for an exit strategy and is looking to unload its losing Intel short positions to whomever it can convince in the short-term that the sky is falling. ARM is great they say - couldn't be better, all fears are overstated. Just pay attention to who has his hand in your pocket, groping around for your wallet. Look up and you'll spot James Covello, Stacy Rasgon or Gus Richard. They are on the make because they are running out of time...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372990445774</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 22:14:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372990901729-68</Id><Topic><Title>Walliswaver made to look like a total dweeb.......yet again</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372988104376</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since you have it so well figured out why don't you enlighten us all on the correct moves in the stock market should be? Are you going to cheer for TI some more, or did you give up on that move a couple of years ago. Oh, come now, did I say something wrong?</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372990901729</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 22:21:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372992015235-69</Id><Title>What Mr Weaver should pump about is that the high end smartphone market is done</Title><Msg>for ARM, but is just beginning for Intel. Intel is just beginning to take marketshare in the high end smartphones, and it has a long way to go. Use this Mr Weaver and Mr ESSA and pump away for the next 6 months.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372992015235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 22:40:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372992916050-70</Id><Topic><Title>What Mr Weaver should pump about is that the high end smartphone market is done</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372992015235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 22:40:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Fabless is fabulous" Man you thought you were so clever when you wrote that.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372992916050</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 22:55:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372995632804-71</Id><Topic><Title>Apple iWatch Rumors: Release Date Expected In Late 2013 As Trademark Gets Filed In Japan</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372726449484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 20:54:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>iWatch will be big seller</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372995632804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 23:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372995719253-72</Id><Topic><Title>ANALysts really have it wrong</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372731133141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 22:12:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good points..Intel will easily make their target for the year</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372995719253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 23:41:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372995796343-73</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Bay Trail benchmark appears online, crushes fastest Snapdragon ARM SoC by 30%</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372852272552</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 07:51:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bay Trail has no competition!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372995796343</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 23:43:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372995846870-74</Id><Topic><Title>First Intel Bay Trail benchmark score appears online, squashes ARM scores like an insignificant bug</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372858269116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>arm is an insignificant bug haha</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372995846870</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 23:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372995978060-75</Id><Topic><Title>'Lenovo K900 has been a top 5 selling device in the Chinese smart-phone market '</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372871982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>smartphones will add significant revenue this year. Next Year will be year of the smartphone for Intel with Merrifield. Revenue will go parabolic</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372995978060</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 23:46:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372996444969-76</Id><Topic><Title>Olivetti Olipad W808, W809 and W810: Windows 8.1 tablet with Intel Bay Trail in October</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372974586947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:49:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>these are teasers...wait until the big boys announce...Samsung, Lenovo, Asus, Acer, Sony, Dell, HP, Microsoft....My bet is Apple will announce a product based on Bay Trail too...there's a price gap between iPad ($499) and MacBook Air ($999)</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372996444969</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 23:54:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>