<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-15"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358226242484-1</Id><Title>"Having 35 years of experience in the electronics business..."</Title><Msg>Having 35 years of experience in the electronics business during the "Inventor Generation" has provided me with some interesting insights from people who went on to be very influential movers and shakers in the business. One late night discussion many, many years ago involved the idea of measuring companies by their ability and willingness to do the difficult things, and to do those difficult things first. Xilinx (XLNX), for example would always produce the largest FPGA (Field Programmable Gate Array) in a new, proprietary, series of parts first. The rationale was that if they could successfully produce, with good yield, the largest part in the series, backfilling with the smaller parts later would be a piece of cake. Another example would be with a manufacturer of commodity devices. I would generally try to determine whether they could service the largest and, therefore, the lowest priced piece of business that I knew of in their market. The rationale here is that if they could match the lowest price on the highest volume business, they could also handle any smaller level of business at a probable higher price. If not, they were doomed to lose the big pieces of business to the more efficient suppliers in the market. What does this have to do with Intel? Three things: When Intel announces a new X86 architecture or a process shrink, the first parts available are the high end i7 devices, filled in later with the i5 and i3 devices. Much like the Xilinx example, Intel makes sure that the most complex devices work well, which makes manufacturing the less complex devices a "walk on the beach." In the market for high performance computing chips, Intel has recently moved into production on the Xeon Phi chip. The chip is capable of "well over a teraflop." The Phi chip has 62 cores and is over a square inch in chip area. The high performance computing market is not large, but Intel needs to be involved in this computing "high ground" as a challenge to the company as a whole. Intel, last week introduced the Lexington SoC (Z2420) with the XMM 6265 3G+ baseband modem. This platform is described as a "value solution" for the very large, price conscious, emerging markets. This multi-chip solution is about 100 square millimeters of silicon run on 32nm fully depreciated Intel production lines. The Intel cost on these chips is about $6 combined with a resale of $12 to 15 in the huge volume markets. The part has all of the functions expected for an entry level smartphone, plus it has an FM radio (poor man's iTunes). My iPhone doesn't have an FM radio! The new Intel chip can transmit content to a TV wirelessly, my iPhone can't do that either. It has dual SIM (subscriber identification), so it can be used in a two service provider mode (no contract). This platform has a cost and sale price that will make it more than competitive in the highest volume, lowest price markets in the world, thus making a $100, feature rich, entry level smart phone a reality. This "cheap, but good" strategy fulfills the requirements of the above second example of doing the difficult things first. Tackling the billion people population centers like China and India first is smart for Intel, because anything after that will seem easy. Keep in mind that China Mobile has more cell phone subscribers than the U.S. has people. Rumors are that we will see the Intel high end smart phone solution next month at the World Mobility Conference. It is becoming clear that Intel now has the leading solutions for their legacy businesses of PC, severs, and super computers, and competitive to leading solutions for the emerging markets of tablets and both low and high end smart phones. Is there any other company that has this kind of leverage on the worldwide computing market? Those three underutilized Intel fabs will soon be producing low price, but high margin, entry level smart phone chips. Let's not forget the automotive infotainment business that Intel is targeting. And what is this Intel Television thing all about? Apparently the intent is to trump Apple (AAPL) TV. I don't have a clue what they have in mind here, but the recurring thought I have is: Today Intel derives about $25 per year from the PC-using public ($100 CPU chip in a product that renews on a four year cycle.) Whatever this TV thing is would probably produce $25 worth of cost free service revenue to Intel each month on a similar sized using population. That's 12 times the current CPU revenue. Since the blow-out numbers of 2009 and 2010, Intel has been assembling the assets to enable another sprint to a size that could be in the range of 2X the revenue of today. Since that near-term growth has a very high probability of happening, I am using calls and LEAPs to play Intel. If you, as I am, are convinced of a doubling or tripling in the Intel stock price, it would be foolish to not use every bit of leverage the market allows. I'm buying INTC Jan 2014 30 calls for a dime to $.15. From Russ Fischer</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358226242484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 00:04:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358227323598-2</Id><Title>we know google will not exceed earnings forcast..</Title><Msg>but Apple has a shot..+ enormous cash Flow, shares buyback, dividend increase. This is either MM's, at their finest, or the best opportunity of the year. I still see nothing that is causing this negative media frenzy..Apple is cheap, a mkt leader and with more cash than some countries..I'm adding and I hope I'm not sorry.glta</Msg><Username>hisstik</Username><Timestamp>1358227323598</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 00:22:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358230440280-3</Id><Title>literally 18-28 range safely is what this stock does= 28 next</Title><Msg>going to 28 then back down then up a little then stable then up a little then down more then up......</Msg><Username>raygeo2003</Username><Timestamp>1358230440280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 01:14:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358249722094-4</Id><Title>ARMH down large pre-market</Title><Msg>Wonder what happened there?</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1358249722094</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 06:35:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358252388429-5</Id><Title>HaYYYYYY Getanid61, will ARM see a new high agaYn todayyyyyy</Title><Msg>ARM Holdings /quotes/zigman/67211/quotes/nls/armh ARMH +0.28% /quotes/zigman/254777 UK:ARM -4.35% fell nearly 5%. A string of downgrades have hit the chip maker in the last two days, including a cut to equal weight from overweight at Morgan Stanley, a drop to neutral from overweight at Piper Jaffray and a cut to hold from buy at Investec. While downgrading the stock on Tuesday, Morgan Stanley analysts called ARM a “great story” but said that current share prices imply a “near-perfect trajectory in ARM’s market share and royalty rate for the next two years.” Read more in London Markets</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1358252388429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:19:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358252757987-6</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K900 Benchmarks fly past quad core Snapdragon</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358221736919</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 22:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lenovo K900 benchmarks fly past quad-core Snapdragon Leaked benchmarks point to huge speed advantage for Intel Atom By JR Bookwalter 17 hrs ago Dual-core Intel Atom-powered smartphone blows away the competition in benchmarks Few of us buy smartphones based purely on specs, but the Intel Atom-powered handset Lenovo debuted at CES 2013 could put even the latest quad-core Snapdragon benchmarks to shame. PhoneArena reported on Friday that Lenovo's forthcoming IdeaPhone K900 might establish a new bar for smartphone processors, judging from impressive benchmarks leaked to the internet. Powered by a 2GHz dual-core Intel Atom processor, the IdeaPhone scored upwards of 27,000 points on the AnTuTu benchmark, leaving competitors like the HTC Droid DNA in the dust with a mere 14,000 average. HTC's device is powered by the quad-core Snapdragon S4 Pro, but Lenovo's benchmark also eclipses the Samsung Galaxy Note 2 with a 1.6GHz Exynos 4412 processor. Impressive score It remains to be seen how Samsung's next-generation Exynos 5 Octa processor will fare against the dual-core Intel Atom, but the chip has yet to wind up in any currently announced smartphone or tablet. The report is quick to note there's always a chance the Lenovo IdeaPhone K900 benchmarks are a fake - and competitors are likely hoping that's the case. Assuming these AnTuTu benchmarks are for real, the Lenovo IdeaPhone K900 could impress even further when the handset is out of testing and finally released with an Android build optimized for its powerful engine.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1358252757987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:25:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358253163660-7</Id><Topic><Title>"Having 35 years of experience in the electronics business..."</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358226242484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 00:04:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This multi-chip solution is about 100 square millimeters of silicon run on 32nm fully depreciated Intel production lines. The Intel cost on these chips is about $6 combined with a resale of $12 to 15 in the huge volume markets." 100mm of 32nm silicon has $6 Intel COST with a $12 to $15 resale? Now if Intel replaces one of their $100 chips with these, they will have to sell a lot of them to break even. If Intel sells a TON of them to break even on revenue or profit. If Intel sells them independently of the $100 CPU, their revenues increase. $6 for 100mm can be very competitive.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358253163660</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:32:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358253297710-8</Id><Topic><Title>"Having 35 years of experience in the electronics business..."</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358226242484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 00:04:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM Holdings /quotes/zigman/67211/quotes/nls/armh ARMH +0.28% /quotes/zigman/254777 UK:ARM -4.12% fell nearly 5%. A string of downgrades have hit the chip maker in the last two days, including a cut to equal weight from overweight at Morgan Stanley, a drop to neutral from overweight at Piper Jaffray and a cut to hold from buy at Investec. While downgrading the stock on Tuesday, Morgan Stanley analysts called ARM a “great story” but said that current share prices imply a “near-perfect trajectory in ARM’s market share and royalty rate for the next two years.” Read more in London Markets</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1358253297710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:34:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358255129757-9</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH new 52-week high today... AGAIN !!</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358216502409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 21:21:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Seriously, what part of the obvious do you not get...??? ARMH new 52-week high today !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!" Yeah, that's usually how a bubble ends -- the guys holding distribute to the momo suckers.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358255129757</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 08:05:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358255588189-10</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>marthaije606</Username><Timestamp>1357915910195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 09:51:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got it for free. Thank you</Msg><Username>rakpmhtzhxb144</Username><Timestamp>1358255588189</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 08:13:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358259586599-11</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>marthaije606</Username><Timestamp>1357915910195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 09:51:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>need more info on this please</Msg><Username>hlmumremzlsu8391</Username><Timestamp>1358259586599</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:19:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358259672171-12</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>marthaije606</Username><Timestamp>1357915910195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 09:51:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this one keeps me thinking</Msg><Username>hlmumremzlsu8391</Username><Timestamp>1358259672171</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:21:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358259989210-13</Id><Title>Lenovo very close to being #1 smartphone supplier in China.</Title><Msg>One of the most promising markets in the world for smartphone growth is China. And the leader is not Apple. Apple is not even close. The leader currently is Samsung, but the growth in market share of Lenovo will soon make Lenovo the leader. They are building a plant now to produce 30 to 40 million smartphone units a year. And with the K900 design, looks like one of the biggest or maybe even the only beneficiary will be Intel's chips. Imagine Lenovo selling over 40 million smartphones a year, with only Intel chips. With just one supplier, Intel will gain huge market share. And with the success, Motorola USA and others will jump in the bandwagon very quickly, leaving ARM in the dust.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358259989210</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:26:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358260358884-14</Id><Title>Wallis: Regarding ARMH.</Title><Msg>Has the downward slide slided? The stock is down $2 in the early morning hours. Looks like it was due to downgrades. How low do you think it will go in the next 3 months? I can sell my puts at profit now, but I'm wondering if I should hold til low $30's.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358260358884</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:32:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358260372779-15</Id><Title>ARM -- 52 Week High?</Title><Msg>Nope. Not today, boys. Not today.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358260372779</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:32:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358260465635-16</Id><Topic><Title>ARM -- 52 Week High?</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358260372779</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:32:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No driveby hit and run message from Getanid61 today? Darn....</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1358260465635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:34:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358262270279-17</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH new 52-week high today... AGAIN !!</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358216502409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 21:21:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fyi..... - 4.5%</Msg><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1358262270279</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:04:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358262994208-18</Id><Topic><Title>Is Anyone Making Money WIth INTC?</Title><Username>newtontodd714</Username><Timestamp>1358014743482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:19:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome stock</Msg><Username>rossday278</Username><Timestamp>1358262994208</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:16:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358264128978-19</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>marthaije606</Username><Timestamp>1357915910195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 09:51:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have it already. It's the best.</Msg><Username>hoppznatxmgzgxwols5706</Username><Timestamp>1358264128978</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:35:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358264791559-20</Id><Title>Intel earnings expected to disappoint at bizjournals 10:06am EST</Title><Msg>see Yahoo News HI-HO WEAVERINO!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358264791559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:46:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358265673133-21</Id><Topic><Title>Intel earnings expected to disappoint at bizjournals 10:06am EST</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358264791559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:46:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awwww, you poor little sour grapy. I guess you gotta keep trying since you missed out on that Immentent Intel Warning call, among all your other hideous calls (Intel from 19 to 15, you said..........before it ran to 29 plus..) ROFLMAO. Keep trying, little kid!</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358265673133</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:01:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358266290496-22</Id><Topic><Title>Intel earnings expected to disappoint at bizjournals 10:06am EST</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358264791559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:46:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the response. #$%$ nozzles like you keep me posting. HI-HO WEAVERINO!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358266290496</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:11:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358266454093-23</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH down large pre-market</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1358249722094</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 06:35:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can only wish INTC was all the way down to $40</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1358266454093</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:14:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358266739794-24</Id><Topic><Title>Intel earnings expected to disappoint at bizjournals 10:06am EST</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358264791559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:46:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice try, you ammature psychologist.... I want you to post here every single day of your life so we can so how useless it was with all the dumb calls. Keep posting !!</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358266739794</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:18:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358266786893-25</Id><Topic><Title>An INTEL WARNING IS IMMINENT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354739684483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 15:34:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO. I notice your research sukkked, again!</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358266786893</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:19:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358267578720-26</Id><Title>INTEL HAS HAD A SPECTACULAR RUN!</Title><Msg>From $29 down to $21! TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358267578720</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:32:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358267691667-27</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL HAS HAD A SPECTACULAR RUN!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358267578720</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:32:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad you said it was going to 15 from 19 before it ran to 29. How'd that work out for you? Oh, yeah, you bought Cisco and road it from 20 to 13. LOL! Keep posting, little sour grapy boy.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358267691667</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:34:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358267715319-28</Id><Title>Would like to take a dump in a shoe box</Title><Msg>and then mail it to Nuff along with some plastic spoons.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1358267715319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:35:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358267765607-29</Id><Topic><Title>I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1293550442000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-12-28 10:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great call. You missed out on 50 percent gains on Intel to ride Cisco to 13 for nearly 50 percent losses. Keep posting, little drummer boy!</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358267765607</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:36:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358268974085-30</Id><Topic><Title>I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1293550442000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-12-28 10:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see nothing wrong with owning both INTC and CSCO. As a matter of fact, I purchased batches of Cisco years ago averaged at just under $13 per share. My INTC buys were not that great. My average is over $22.50. The point is, both are here to stay, will continue to grow steadily and reliably, and will pay a respectable dividend. I may add on dips from time to time but I'm not going to waste my funds buying and selling without some good sound reasoning based on more than just a hunch.</Msg><Username>ngaibruce</Username><Timestamp>1358268974085</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:56:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358269305480-31</Id><Topic><Title>An INTEL WARNING IS IMMINENT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354739684483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 15:34:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't INTC always warn about something?</Msg><Username>ngaibruce</Username><Timestamp>1358269305480</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:01:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358269563974-32</Id><Topic><Title>Intel earnings expected to disappoint at bizjournals 10:06am EST</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358264791559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:46:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So how many shares of AMD have you papered your bedroom with Funny? Are you shorting INTC? Remember to make those dividend payments, okay?</Msg><Username>ngaibruce</Username><Timestamp>1358269563974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:06:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358269705187-33</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>marthaije606</Username><Timestamp>1357915910195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 09:51:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like spam, smells like spam, could it be spam? I'll not be going there!</Msg><Username>ngaibruce</Username><Timestamp>1358269705187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:08:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358270132129-34</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to move on earnings this week</Title><Username>garyg474</Username><Timestamp>1358043800187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:23:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reason they often beat the numbers is that they have very conservative outlook and always warn about something. Should they ever provide a rosy outlook, that is when I'll really load up. Otherwise, nothing wrong with collecting the dividend as we wait for the better days that are sure to come.</Msg><Username>ngaibruce</Username><Timestamp>1358270132129</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:15:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358270165447-35</Id><Topic><Title>Intel earnings expected to disappoint at bizjournals 10:06am EST</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358264791559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:46:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I had yo mama in city hall and the kids came out playin' basketball. TOOOOO FUNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358270165447</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:16:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358271692812-36</Id><Title>BARRONS: ultrabook machines promoted by Intel (INTC) not panning out as expected</Title><Msg>Today, Morgan Stanley’s Francois Meunier cut his rating to Equal Weight from Overweight, writing “While 12 months ago investors were worried about ARM’s position vs Intel, we believe the current share price implies a near perfect trajectory in ARM’s market share and royalty rate for the next two years.” Everything hoped for has come true for ARM, writes Meunier, including stuff like Apple (AAPL) introducing the iPad mini, and the ultrabook machines promoted by Intel (INTC) not panning out as expected.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358271692812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:41:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358271802823-37</Id><Topic><Title>An INTEL WARNING IS IMMINENT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354739684483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 15:34:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is in its quiet time before earnings release and cannot comment earnings? Intel sets conservative targets and a $1b range. If they are not going to hit that range, they say something before they enter the quiet period. Since they did not warn before entering the quiet period, they are going to hit or exceed the range.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358271802823</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:43:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358272158251-38</Id><Topic><Title>An INTEL WARNING IS IMMINENT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354739684483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 15:34:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your opinion in here, Al. You know that the so called "quiet periods' are toothless and that any publicly traded company can say anything it wants about anything it wants at anytime it wants so long as there is no selective disclosure. That aside, you also must know that it's not about the earnings, it's about the forward statement.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358272158251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:49:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358272736643-39</Id><Title>Go Nuff, Go</Title><Msg>You're really in your element today. You must be tweeking.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1358272736643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:58:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358273451524-40</Id><Topic><Title>BARRONS: ultrabook machines promoted by Intel (INTC) not panning out as expected</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358271692812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:41:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More sour grapes from the guy who has held Cisco at 20 since 2011. LOL!</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358273451524</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:10:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358274046141-41</Id><Topic><Title>BARRONS: ultrabook machines promoted by Intel (INTC) not panning out as expected</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358271692812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:41:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are a lot of problems as far as consumer acceptance goes with Ultrabooks. One big marketing issue is they look just like notebooks and the new notebooks are so much thinner and lighter than the old ones. My employer bought 6 new tablets, instead of either the UB or NB, they were cheap and the marketing /sales guys wanted them.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1358274046141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:20:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358274373853-42</Id><Topic><Title>An INTEL WARNING IS IMMINENT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354739684483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 15:34:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"My opinion"? Yes, I guess so. My opinion is based on the historical Intel behavior and their results. I can't find any case of Intel ever missing their target range without saying something before they entered the quiet period. Do you know of a quarter that Intel missed their range without warning? Otherwise, I expect (my opinion) their results to be like other times. I expect the results to be inside or above the target range that they forcast. Quiet period enforcment is as toothless as the staff enforcing them and varies from administration to administration. A company can say anything it wants to. It can even say some things that violate the rules and risk prosecution or maybe have a 3rd party like their PR agency release information accidently. Didn't AAPL do this? I know that the forward statement is important and affects the views of the company. I just think of a warning as an unexpected release outside the formal results release and foreward statement.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358274373853</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:26:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358274630547-43</Id><Topic><Title>BARRONS: ultrabook machines promoted by Intel (INTC) not panning out as expected</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358271692812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:41:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your employer doesn't know how to run a business. (nor pick good employees, since you waste so much company time posting on the Intel board).</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358274630547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:30:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358274817105-44</Id><Topic><Title>Why Windows RT Is Hurtling Toward Disaster - PCWorld</Title><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1358274038980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:20:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bravo! Nobody wants an ARM tablet that could not run the usual Windows games and applications. May as well opt for Android as there could be more software in that OS platform.</Msg><Username>rehsab33</Username><Timestamp>1358274817105</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:33:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358275203858-45</Id><Topic><Title>Go Nuff, Go</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1358272736643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:58:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nuff seems especially desperate today. Observing his posts is like a shrink watching his patients in a psychiatric ward.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1358275203858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:40:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358276710198-46</Id><Topic><Title>BARRONS: ultrabook machines promoted by Intel (INTC) not panning out as expected</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358271692812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:41:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe the business is really related to the posting on the Yahoo boards. A 6-person marketing/sales organization is about the right size for a family business. Mabye the marketing/sales crew (the kids) would have more preferred any brand of hand-held game device over the cheap tablets.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358276710198</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:05:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358277805319-47</Id><Title>Guy showing Lenovo K900 at CES</Title><Msg>There's a video, just search Lenovo K900. He's reviewing it and says it blows the Galaxy Notes away. How thin and light ht is also amazed him.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1358277805319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:23:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358278023160-48</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>marthaije606</Username><Timestamp>1357915910195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 09:51:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People I can not to make some revenue with this tips.</Msg><Username>ziiladrkpptybhv6705</Username><Timestamp>1358278023160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:27:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358279014958-49</Id><Title>A One Man Shill Show Warning Is Imminent</Title><Msg>Warning, warning!!! The one man shill show is required by his paid shill agreement to record frivolous and hopefully scary posts about margins, inventories and revenue warnings not just once but several times a quarter regardless of actual results and performance. As the one man shill show is a lazy jerk, he is behind or he would have gotten these in sooner (waiting on bad news that never came; D'oh). Therefore look for these warnings up to and including Thursday. As if you care. LOL</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358279014958</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:43:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358279081341-50</Id><Title>45 cents per share is the number to beat.</Title><Msg>Intel (INTC) is expected to report poor fourth quarter earnings on Thursday, January 17, 2013 with analysts expecting a 29.7% drop in earnings from a year ago. The consensus estimate is 45 cents per share, down from earnings of 64 cents per share a year ago. The consensus estimate is down from three months ago when it was 54 cents, but is unchanged over the past month. Analysts are projecting earnings of $2.11 per share for the fiscal year. Analysts project revenue to fall 0.9% year-over-year to $13.76 billion for the quarter, after being $13.89 billion a year ago. For the year, revenue is projected to come in at $53.43 billion. A decline in revenue in the third quarter snapped a streak of three consecutive quarters of growing revenue. Revenue fell 5.5% in the third quarter and rose 3.6%in the second quarter, 0.5% in the first quarter and 21.2% in the fourth quarter of the last fiscal year. The company has seen net income fall in each of the last three quarters. In third quarter, net income fell 14.3% from the year earlier, while the figure fell 4.3% in the second quarter and 13.4% in the first quarter. This sucks. Better be some good news and a beat of this number.</Msg><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1358279081341</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:44:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358279756203-51</Id><Title>Intel CES 2013: A Game Changing Year Ahead</Title><Msg>"Intel identified the fourth generation Ultrabook Convertible as the real game changer and I believe it will be, especially over time. It's a no brainer for the majority of the world with Apple being the odd man out. I've already presented my view about Apple not challenging the Ultrabook as being a potential mistake and I'll leave it at that for now in this report." "At the end of the day, who knows which device will end up being the winner in 2013? For now, I still believe that the Ultrabook Convertible will be one of the top selling devices over time because the notebook will always play a major role with enterprise professionals and students. Finally combining a modern notebook with voice, advanced touch capabilities and biometric security with the convenience of one-touch display detachment for casual tablet surfing, communications and presentations, the Ultrabook Convertible will deliver the ultimate all-in-one mobile device experience that most of us have been waiting for." From PatentlyApple</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358279756203</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:55:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358279764304-52</Id><Topic><Title>45 cents per share is the number to beat.</Title><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1358279081341</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:44:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel (NASDAQ:INTC) reports on Thursday, January 17. Expectations are lower there, too, in part because Intel has not yet seen much of a payoff for all the money and energy it has put into promoting its “ultrabooks.” - Minyanville</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358279764304</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:56:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358279797406-53</Id><Title>Hilarious</Title><Msg>Hey Tim, Yes, you Tim COOK ┌∩┐(◣_◢)┌∩┐ . From, Your shareholders</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1358279797406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:56:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358279855351-54</Id><Topic><Title>Why is ARMH stock outperforming INTC so badly??</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357838146159</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 12:15:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I said 5 days ago '... There will be a future event which will trigger a similar mass stampede out of it that won't stop until it hits its proper price around $10-15. It maybe a missed earnings/bad forecast or just all the Analysts changing their story ...' Looks like the Analysts are changing their story but the funny thing is even the new story is ridiculous, I didn't realize these clowns actually had some reasoning behind their crazy valuations but they really do, let's examine them ... http://blogs.barrons.com/techtraderdaily/2013/01/15/armh-morgan-stanley-cuts-to-hold-on-surge-in-valuation/?mod=yahoobarrons "While we (and many investors) used to describe ARM as a ‘5p EPS stock’ for many years (2002-2009), consensus earnings expectations have risen significantly in the past three years to 18p for 2013 […] While we (and many investors) used to describe ARM as a ‘5p EPS stock’ for many years (2002-2009), consensus earnings expectations have risen significantly in the past three years to 18p for 2013 […] We now forecast 20p EPS for 2013, and that assumes a 17% increase in smartphone ASPs from 29c to 34c. Assuming that the ASPs of chips that ARM sells are down a mere 5%, this implies a 20% increase in royalty rate across the board. While we remain a strong supporter of the idea that ARM will increase its royalty rate, we continue to believe that this will be gradual (i.e. it is unlikely to be above 20% in a year across the board) […] It also implies that the blended ASP for mobile phones will have doubled by 2015-2016e vs 2010 – and that is a rare event in the semiconductor sector. On average, the 1.8bn devices sold in 2016 will have 30c of ARM content with a 2% royalty rate for $15 of silicon, i.e. as much as today for the smartphone category (600m this year)." This analyst is talking about royalty rate, well this means ARM A7, A8, A9 and A15. How the hell is smartphone asp going to increase in 2013 when only A7 and A9 is appreciably increasing in smartphones with A15 MIA and A7 is cheap and the price of A9 is dropping sharply as it get obsolete ? ARM gets no royalty for Qualcomm's S4 or Apple's A6 only licensing revenue. Blended asps to DOUBLE by 2015-6 ?! Really, with new competitive x86 mobile chips being released every year to take lumps out of A15, A9, A8 and A7 ?!! If they stay static over that time period under this new intense competition they will be doing well ! WOW so it's not just the pumpers that are making stuff up about ARMH that bare no relation to reality even the official ARM Analysts are doing it lol !</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358279855351</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:57:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358279935121-55</Id><Topic><Title>Guy showing Lenovo K900 at CES</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1358277805319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:23:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just looked at this amazing phone online and I liked it so much I bought Intel stock. At 9X earnings and 4% div., how can you lose?</Msg><Username>hoxstox</Username><Timestamp>1358279935121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:58:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358280406323-56</Id><Topic><Title>Why is ARMH stock outperforming INTC so badly??</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357838146159</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 12:15:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"On average, the 1.8bn devices sold in 2016 will have 30c of ARM content with a 2% royalty rate for $15 of silicon, i.e. as much as today for the smartphone category (600m this year)." No friggin way is there going to be 1.8bn ARM devices sold in 2016 with an asp of $15 ! Maybe half that asp.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358280406323</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:06:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358280885163-57</Id><Topic><Title>Guy showing Lenovo K900 at CES</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1358277805319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:23:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No-brainer. Welcome to the Intel family.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1358280885163</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:14:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358281528729-58</Id><Topic><Title>Good news for Intel .</Title><Username>josephvillalobos92</Username><Timestamp>1358281053542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks !</Msg><Username>johnrivas410</Username><Timestamp>1358281528729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:25:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358281762298-59</Id><Topic><Title>Intel started a tech war</Title><Username>johnmorrill470</Username><Timestamp>1358188833813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 13:40:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks !</Msg><Username>johnrivas410</Username><Timestamp>1358281762298</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:29:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358285186878-60</Id><Topic><Title>Max Pain is 22.50</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1358212395076</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 20:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 600 MA at 22.18 is the current roadblock, this may take some battering to get past. stockchartsDOTcom/c-sc/sc?s=intc&amp;p=D&amp;yr=1&amp;mn=0&amp;dy=0&amp;i=t24027281681&amp;r=1358284322422</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358285186878</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 16:26:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358290226908-61</Id><Title>good short</Title><Msg>This one look like it may be a good short. News comnig out sound like it will take a long time for INTC to come back as it once was</Msg><Username>bumptemp</Username><Timestamp>1358290226908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 17:50:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358290489349-62</Id><Title>TIME TO SHORT</Title><Msg>had a nice run; it lasted several days longer than I predicted. time to sell or short again until the longs get complacent</Msg><Username>bumptemp</Username><Timestamp>1358290489349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 17:54:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358291089998-63</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO SHORT</Title><Username>bumptemp</Username><Timestamp>1358290489349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 17:54:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you created a brand-spanking new alias to say this twice? Ok.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1358291089998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 18:04:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358291340955-64</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO SHORT</Title><Username>bumptemp</Username><Timestamp>1358290489349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 17:54:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumptemp is the latest fake shill user ID from the one man shill show. It's a new user ID with all of 2 posts, created of course to make it look like all the negativity is not just coming from the one man shill show. Which it is. All part of the shill agreement, like warning of a warning. Talk about ethically bankrupt...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358291340955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 18:09:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358291519397-65</Id><Title>Samsung Chromebox gets Intel</Title><Msg>Samsung's Chromebox gets an Intel Core i5 chip Posted January 15, 2013 - 10:56 by Trent Nouveau Google Chrome OS can best be described as a Linux-based operating system designed to work exclusively with web applications and Mountain View's cloud-based Google Drive. The operating system was announced on July 7, 2009, with the first Intel-based Chromebooks shipping on June 15, 2011. Since then, the Chrome concept has only increased in popularity, with Samsung launching a versatile ARM-powered Chromebook which quickly became a best-selling product on Amazon at a $250 price point. Of course, Samsung also sells a number of other Chrome-based devices, including the Series 5 550 Chromebook (Wi-Fi) and the XE300Mww_A01US Chromebox. Recently, a redesigned Samsung Chromebox boasting a slick new case with rounded corners tipped up online. The XE300M22-B01US is equipped with the same hardware as its predecessor, including the same audio, video, Ethernet, and USB ports, although the front-facing ports are covered by a plastic door. Additional specs include a 1.9 GHz Intel Celeron B840 processor, Intel HD graphics, 4GB of RAM, a 16GB SSD (solid state disk), WiFi, a 2W mono speaker, 6 USB 2.0 ports, a DVI port, headset jack and two display ports. This week, Samsung rolled out a new Chromebox (XE300M22-A01US) powered by an Intel Core i5-2450M processor - a second-generation Intel Core CPU with HD Graphics 3000. As Liliputing's Brad Linder notes, while the Core i5-2450M chip may be a generation behind Santa Clara's current processors, it does offer enough horsepower to handle most basic computing tasks, including HD video playback. Additional specs? 4GB of RAM, 16GB of storage (SSD), 6 USB 2.0 ports, WiFi, Bluetooth, Ethernet, a DisplayPort and DVI jacks. In terms of pricing, CompSource is currently charging $405 for the new Chromebox, while Amazon is shipping the device for $423.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1358291519397</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 18:11:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358291916738-66</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis: Regarding ARMH.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358260358884</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:32:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Has the downward slide slided?" [The next couple of days will be very interesting. I can't believe it held up this long. Heck of a big bubble...] "The stock is down $2 in the early morning hours. Looks like it was due to downgrades. How low do you think it will go in the next 3 months?" [I could see it dropping to $30. Lower depending on any big Intel deals getting signed...] "I can sell my puts at profit now, but I'm wondering if I should hold til low $30's." [If it's beer money, I'd hang in. If it's rent money, I'd sell half. I'd also recommend checking in with Alexander and Ashraf to see if they have any specific put structuring suggestions for ARM...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358291916738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 18:18:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358293795430-67</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO SHORT</Title><Username>bumptemp</Username><Timestamp>1358290489349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 17:54:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's see: stock following a six week, solid up trend; two days before earnings announcement; and lowered consensus, to boot! Yeah, good call, man. Go for it! I'll even help you cover... at $24 or so :-)</Msg><Username>livingsez</Username><Timestamp>1358293795430</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 18:49:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358293936455-68</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO SHORT</Title><Username>bumptemp</Username><Timestamp>1358290489349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 17:54:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>COINMAKER ALWAYS STARTS HIS THREADS IN ALL-CAPS.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358293936455</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 18:52:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358294856661-69</Id><Title>2 more reasons to dump MSFT</Title><Msg>There is no reason for INTC to be good if MSFT is not good.</Msg><Username>eshjg</Username><Timestamp>1358294856661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:07:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358295190134-70</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO SHORT</Title><Username>bumptemp</Username><Timestamp>1358290489349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 17:54:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$22----$19 range play in fraud street casino in usa</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1358295190134</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:13:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358296611773-71</Id><Topic><Title>2 more reasons to dump MSFT</Title><Username>eshjg</Username><Timestamp>1358294856661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:07:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah, so your premise is that Microsoft and Intel should run in parallel. But if you look at a chart with a comparison you will see that Intel gapped seriously below Microsoft for the last five months because of Wall Street's relentless and undeserved beat-down of Intel for no good reason. So, Intel has to move up considerably to run in parallel with Microsoft. So, your conclusion is totally erroneous. Intel has merely to parallel Microsoft again to have a big move up. In other words if the mindless disconnect resolves out, Intel will get a large bump, butkus...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358296611773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:36:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358297041145-72</Id><Title>Intel Shorts Give Back 14 Percent, ARM Longs Give Back 4 Percent</Title><Msg>Since the low of 19.23 on November 21st, Intel shorts have given back 14 percent. ARMs bubble trouble and fabrication fade continue...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358297041145</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:44:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358298840082-73</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis: Regarding ARMH.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358260358884</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:32:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just beer money. I guess I'll hand in for the ride. Low $30's sounds good enough for me. Don't really know how to talk to Alexander or Ashraf. If you have any strategies in puts, would be interested in hearing them. Thanks.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358298840082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:14:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358298970027-74</Id><Title>ARM server hype to start tomorrow</Title><Msg>Applied Micro will be showing off their shiny 40nm toys at the OpenCompute. Well, no. The chips haven't quite sampled yet, so they'll just be talking a lot about them :-)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358298970027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:16:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358299175470-75</Id><Title>We need to break thru the $22.20 wall</Title><Msg>She's tried &amp; failed twice. Earnings should be the catalyst. So much negativity built into expectations. Expect $23s within 2 weeks.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1358299175470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:19:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358299648968-76</Id><Topic><Title>ARM server hype to start tomorrow</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358298970027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:16:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The chips haven't quite sampled yet, so they'll just be talking a lot about them :-)" [Reality has never slowed down ARM marketing. I mean, look at GloFo. No 28nm but they'll have 14nm any day now...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358299648968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:27:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358299828499-77</Id><Topic><Title>Max Pain is 22.50</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1358212395076</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 20:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Heard that before. Towards the end of 2011. Just before the stock started its steady run to $29 plus. And the fuel behind it was pretty much the hopes of Intel making some indroads into mobile products, specifically the smartphones. I wouldn't count much on any max pain points holding at this time after seeing the Lenovo K900 smartphones to be sold initially in the Chinese market. And I would not pay much attention to the headlines about PC demand dopping off a cliff when Intel has continuously released processor price list of all of its chips not dropping one dime in price. Not even a penny.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358299828499</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:30:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358299977434-78</Id><Topic><Title>The Countdown Has Begun: 168 Days Left</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358033177243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:26:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>165 days left... No new news. This from a while back: ["After making those comparisons on process capabilities, Apple will have to consider what guarantees it can get on production volumes."] TSMC to make Apple processors this quarter David Manners Monday 07 January 2013 01:00 TSMC will start producing chips for Apple this quarter, reports Commercial Times, the Taiwan newspaper. This quarter's production will be of 'experimental' ICs, says the newspaper. It is thought that the experimental production will be to see if TSMC's gate-last 28nm process offers advantages over Samsung's gate-first 32nm process which Apple currently uses. It will also allow Apple to make comparisons with Samsung's gate-first 28nm process. At 20nm it is thought that everyone will go back to gate-last. After making those comparisons on process capabilities, Apple will have to consider what guarantees it can get on production volumes. If TSMC does get the volume production contract, it will be making Apple's A6 application processors.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358299977434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:32:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358300186742-79</Id><Topic><Title>ARM server hype to start tomorrow</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358298970027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:16:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm jealous. If INTC had these marketing guys, INTC would be at least $50.00/share and not where we are and I would be rich!</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1358300186742</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:36:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358301930472-80</Id><Topic><Title>ARM server hype to start tomorrow</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358298970027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:16:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are currently two processor board specifications. 1. Intel E5-2600 Dual CPU The OCP specification for the Intel v2.0 motherboard uses two Intel® Xeon® E5-2600 processors and 16 DIMM slots per board. Intel developed their own version of the board,… 2. AMD The OCP specification for the AMD v2.0 motherboard is a dual AMD G34 socket motherboard (Magny Cours or Interlagos) with 16 DIMM slots (PCB mechanical and motherboard mechanical... 3. No ARM spec opencomputeDOTorg/specs/ Do you think that Open Compute Org will disclose an ARM version of the spec???</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358301930472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 21:05:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358304526874-81</Id><Topic><Title>2 more reasons to dump MSFT</Title><Username>eshjg</Username><Timestamp>1358294856661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:07:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not talking about stock movement. The stock can move regardless of the fundamental. What I am talking about is the relationship between these two companies in the business. If MSFT near term forecast is not good, it will be the same to INTC. How stock will move is different thing given the market is totally controlled by MM.</Msg><Username>eshjg</Username><Timestamp>1358304526874</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 21:48:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358305568618-82</Id><Topic><Title>2 more reasons to dump MSFT</Title><Username>eshjg</Username><Timestamp>1358294856661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:07:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ITNC only follows MSFT for the part of its chip business relating to the Windows PC client. For server and phone they,re more linked to Linux and Android. With PC clients become progressively less relevent in consumer purchases, the link between these two will probably become weaker. You can already see Window on ARM in products this year, an indicator of things to come.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1358305568618</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 22:06:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358308086865-83</Id><Topic><Title>2 more reasons to dump MSFT</Title><Username>eshjg</Username><Timestamp>1358294856661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:07:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, and every way you cut it, it comes out that Intel should be doing at least as well as Microsoft or better. Windows on ARM is a substantial failure. No bump for Microsoft there. ARM on Windows is not a sign of things to come - it's a sign of things that came and failed, never to return. The six or twelve month graphs of Microsoft vs. Intel both show what happens when the skumbags on Wall Street target your company. Now they are having trouble perpetuating the story they made up. The result is the ARM bubble and the Intel disconnect. Both will resolve out in spite of the best efforts, manipulation and stupidity on Wall Street...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358308086865</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 22:48:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358308579153-84</Id><Topic><Title>2 more reasons to dump MSFT</Title><Username>eshjg</Username><Timestamp>1358294856661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:07:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I am not talking about stock movement. The stock can move regardless of the fundamental. What I am talking about is the relationship between these two companies in the business. If MSFT near term forecast is not good, it will be the same to INTC. How stock will move is different thing given the market is totally controlled by MM." [If what you are saying is true, then there is no point in bringing it up. Plus it depends on who is making the forecast. We have seen gross errors. But Intel's future is much brighter than that of Microsoft. Your point that Intel can't do better than Microsoft simply isn't true. Intel because of its fabrication is going to do very well. Microsoft has no corresponding advantage. Intel will take over a large part of the mobility business. Microsoft has no corresponding market potential of anything near the same size. Intel doesn't make PCs - Intel makes processors. Dunno, maybe no one told you...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358308579153</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 22:56:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358311937668-85</Id><Topic><Title>2 more reasons to dump MSFT</Title><Username>eshjg</Username><Timestamp>1358294856661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:07:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The PC client business is Intel's largest cah cow. That market segment is going down taking both Microsoft and Intel with it so you should be sayiong Intel should be doing as bad as Microsoft, because Microsoft is learly on its way down.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1358311937668</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 23:52:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>