<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-06"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362546101061-1</Id><Title>ZTE AND INTEL</Title><Msg>ZTE today announced a strategic collaboration with Intel focused on the new Intel® Atom™ Processor Z2580 platform recently announced at Mobile World Congress. The platform will bring significant performance enhancements to the next generation of ZTE smartphones with Intel Inside®.INTEL SMART MONEY.</Msg><Username>mugnmunch</Username><Timestamp>1362546101061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 00:01:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362546311072-2</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft to offer discount on Windows 8 OEM prices</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362541865913</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 22:51:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"My conclusion from these numbers would be the market is not ready for these futuristic products that are being introduced before their time." [Yeah touch screen. We've never seen that before. And a reference to a 10-year old movie. Thanks but I'm going to get my predictions of the future from someone who at least knows what happened in the last decade... ]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362546311072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 00:05:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362546922017-3</Id><Topic><Title>Would Qualcom raise its Diviend 40% if it saw problems due to ARM?</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362526589855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 18:36:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee, let's see if we can think of any other interpretations for Qualcomm raising its dividend by 40 percent: 1.) They can't think of anyone to buy with the cash that would grow earnings. 2.) They can't spend it on fabrication - TSMC won't dedicate space to them and Intel won't touch them. 3.) They are so far behind Intel that it's useless to spend it on R&amp;D. 4.) Declaring a big dividend is so much easier than thinking outside the box. 5.) The board and top executives have a lot of stock and would like to increase their compensation. In short the best reason for a big increase in dividends is that you simply can't figure out how to use it to grow profits. Not what I'd want from a company I own...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362546922017</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 00:15:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362547234860-4</Id><Title>The global economy is really in a funk. The market will correct.</Title><Msg>PC sales are a leading indicator about the state of the global economy.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362547234860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 00:20:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362547325579-5</Id><Topic><Title>If TSMC can't do 20nm until 2015, what will it mean for Apple's ARM chips</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362531833044</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 20:03:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC has already delayed their 20nm to mid 2014 from late 2013. 20nm is not easy to achieve.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362547325579</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 00:22:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362547655097-6</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft to offer discount on Windows 8 OEM prices</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362541865913</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 22:51:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try Raymond Kurzweil. He works for Google now.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1362547655097</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 00:27:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362549238246-7</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH closed at a 52 week high today</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362534395697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 20:46:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would imagine share value growth is completely orthogonal to current market value. e.g. Look at Apple or Google.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1362549238246</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 00:53:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362562749771-8</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft to offer discount on Windows 8 OEM prices</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362541865913</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 22:51:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Windows Vista "product" itself provided a strong reason for upgrading to Win7 immediately. There was also a pent up demand to upgrade from Windows 7 (64-bit) and skip Vista which had a number of big problems. End of Feb, 2013: 44.55% Windows7 38.99% WindowsXP 5.17% Windows Vista 2.67% Windows8 2.61% MAC OS X v10.8 1.96% MAC OS X v10.6 1.93% MAC OS X v10.7 2.11% Other (Credit: Net Applications) Windows XP August 24, 2001. Windows Vista July 22, 2005 Windows 7 July 22, 2009. Windows 8 October 26, 2012.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1362562749771</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 04:39:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362562788286-9</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>carl.hand</Username><Timestamp>1362392578308</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:22:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great news!!!!</Msg><Username>charlesjohn584</Username><Timestamp>1362562788286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 04:39:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362571066077-10</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>Yesterday's breakout concluded the "correction" started in late February. It suggested a new leg up and probable more near term upside. The 1565 level could become a magnet to pull the S&amp;P 500 up. However, although the major indexes are at all-time or multi-year highs, their technical indicators, as well as market internals, are showing negative divergences. I find it difficult to chase this rally. If you have large long positions, consider adjusting stops upward as the prices rise. Have a nice day.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1362571066077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 06:57:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362571350832-11</Id><Title>Ya'll Saw What Happened to NOK, Blackberry</Title><Msg>and more same will happen to ARM, just give another year or two it will be history once intel goes to 14nm.goodluck</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1362571350832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:02:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362574054234-12</Id><Title>Intel's slow move up.</Title><Msg>Disappointing. I think MSFT has killed the PC. I have no interest in buying a Win 8 machine, and it would be hard to avoid now. This is hurting INTC.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362574054234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:47:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362574099012-13</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's slow move up.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362574054234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:47:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't stand Steve Ballmer... what a trogolodyte... any chance MSFT will dump him?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362574099012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:48:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362574639054-14</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH closed at a 52 week high today</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362534395697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 20:46:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARMH is having its moment in the sun. That is fine for their shareholders for now. In my opinion, they were in the right place at the right time. It is important to understand the difference between ARMH and Intel. Although both are in the microprocessor area, ARMH is more of a licensing company then they are a chip building company. Intel designs and builds its own processors. They are apples and oranges. The other thing is that past performance is not indicative of future results. I am prone not to look in the rear view mirror to see where I am going to go. I purchased INTC at 20.5 very recently not 5 years ago and added more a couple of days ago. So far that is a nice positive gain in a short amount of time. Not sure what the point of your post is by posting on an INTC board bragging about ARMH but I will only say that over the next year, I expect that INTC will outperform ARMH and that is really all I care about when I invest. A year ago everyone said how great APPLE because it went up so much now a lot of people hate it because it is off 40%. Perceptions change when the market turns against your company. ARMH had a market all to itself for awhile in much the same way that APPLE did. Just as APPLE is experiencing real competition and having a hard time adjusting, I see the same thing is going to happen with ARMH. Intel is going after that market big time this year. Now if you are not concerned about an inflated multiple to earnings then fine stay with ARMH but some of us buying INTC we are buying it because it makes a lot of sense to buy a company that is trading at 9x earnings pays an over 4 percent dividend and is a proven competitor in the market place vs one at over 40 pe with a .5 percent dividend with a shorter track record. Intel underestimated the growth in mobile but make no mistake they are fixing this fast.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1362574639054</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:57:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362574915053-15</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's slow move up.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362574054234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:47:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel and Microsoft have hyped up the PC into a device that is supposedly really useful. People have started realizing that it isnt and most of the time they're only using it for simple things like checking email or web surfing. Tablets and smartphones have opened people's eyes. "Go do something wonderful with your PC"</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1362574915053</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:01:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362574961017-16</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH closed at a 52 week high today</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362534395697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 20:46:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have plenty of good things to say about ARMH at 44, like how much money can be made shorting it.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1362574961017</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:02:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362575546310-17</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>carl.hand</Username><Timestamp>1362392578308</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:22:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report</Msg><Username>jackbrown538</Username><Timestamp>1362575546310</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:12:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362575917281-18</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH closed at a 52 week high today</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362534395697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 20:46:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Arm is entrenched in mobile that is true but it doesn't mean things can't change. RImm and NOK are good examples in the market place of companies that had a big market share that quickly evaporated. If they have such a big market share in mobile they have a lot of share to lose and very little to gain. There is a reason that they are not in servers because because that space is owned by Intel. Intel wrecked a lot of companies in that space. Remember DEC? How about even IBM and how about Sun Microsystems chips? They all lost the battle with Intel. AMD is nearly finished off. There are a lot of companies that can design chips, that is the easy part but very few left that can build them. If you want someone to make your chips you have very few places to turn. Samsung, TSMC and Intel. Until recently Intel would not build any chips for anyone but themselves.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1362575917281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:18:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362576325333-19</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's slow move up.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362574054234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:47:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I use my PC for Adobe Illustrator (to illustrate my books), photoshop, for Sibelius VI to compose music, for powerpoint presentations, for xcel spreadsheets, Mathematica, etc etc etc.. Only a teenager would view it the way you do. You must be a dumb teenager at that.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362576325333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:25:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362576502203-20</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's slow move up.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362574054234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:47:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, I forgot: MS Word to write my books (the publisher demands that format) and all sorts of pdf read and print, Turbotax software... gosh, I made over $300,000 last year....that's what happens when you actually USE a PC to leverage your acheivables..</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362576502203</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:28:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362576661106-21</Id><Title>Get Rich: Buy a PC</Title><Msg>Stay Poor: Buy a Tablet.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362576661106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:31:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362577224163-22</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's slow move up.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362574054234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:47:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and I may need to use a "PC" to get work done, but that's not the case for everyone. The original point is also valid, the reality is that the "PC" has become dull (Intel is trying to do something about it with various initiatives). Case in point from Torvalds: Torvalds asks 'Why do PC manufacturers even bother any more?' Linux Lord may adopt Chromebook Pixel as main machine ... after proper Linux install By Simon Sharwood, APAC Editor, 5th March 2013 Posting on Google+, Torvalds lauded Google's newest creation, writing "... the screen really is that nice" [his emphasis] and that "I think I can lug around this 1.5kg monster despite feeling fairly strongly that a laptop should weigh 1kg or less." He even thinks the 12.85-inch, 2560-by-1700, 239 pixels-per-inch display and its a 3:2 aspect ratio is so good that it puts the efforts of all other laptop-makers to shame, offering the following opinion on the current laptop computer market: One thing that the Chromebook Pixel really brings home is how #$%$ normal laptops have become. Why do PC manufacturers even bother any more? No wonder the PC business isn't doing well, when they stick to just churning out more #$%$ stuff and think that "full HD" (aka 1080p) is somehow the epitome of greatness. Torvalds doesn't think Google's computer is perfect; he wants more than Chrome OS because "For a laptop to be useful to me, I need to not just read and write email, I need to be able to do compiles, have my own git repositories etc.."</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1362577224163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:40:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362577269690-23</Id><Title>Steady as she goes</Title><Msg>Great stock, great company.</Msg><Username>hankg1030</Username><Timestamp>1362577269690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:41:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362577449342-24</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's slow move up.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362574054234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:47:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The PC is not dead. It always was the tool for productivity. How many people do you think got burned by thinking otherwise? The aging boomers will not stay with tiny keyboards and hard-to-read screens. My 85 year old Mom still instists on a desktop to play Freecell on, despite my attempts to to get her into tablets and laptops. This form factor thing is fad. It is not raison d'etre of chips...performance is that.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362577449342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:44:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362577667139-25</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft is partly to blame for poor PC sales. Ballmer must go.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362539456067</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 22:10:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are absolutely right. In recollection I have sat out every other MSFT software revamp because the reception to them was so awful (eg Vista, etc). MSFT Office has become a standard suite of tools, (especially xcel and ppt, as Word is always a disaster after every "upgrade") . But there is no doubt that MSFT stands for shoddy.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362577667139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:47:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362577792405-26</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>linkosarah</Username><Timestamp>1362149300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:48:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got it. Good job mate.</Msg><Username>ommateadolly</Username><Timestamp>1362577792405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:49:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362578081055-27</Id><Title>Best thin MSFT could do</Title><Msg>Re-release their best classic op systems and classic Office configurations. Yahoo should do the same thing...bring back the classic message boards, or spin-off some company that will do that. Like, was the Kay violin better than the Stradivarius?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362578081055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:54:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362578281611-28</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's slow move up.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362574054234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:47:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The PC is not dead. ----- I never said it was. The upgrade cycles have become longer (less compelling reasons to upgrade) and you *have* new form factors that some people are going for.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1362578281611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:58:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362578310040-29</Id><Title>ZTE is number 4 smartphone manufacturer in the world.</Title><Msg>ZTE is now collaborating with Intel to produce cutting edge smartphones. Lenovo making a huge splash themselves with the K900 Intel based smartphone and being China's number one PC manufacturer, with over 1.3 Billion population. And Motorola, being a Google company, having a multi year contract to produce Intel based smartphones while Google itself is optimizing its Android software to work with Intel chip. These are huge developments for Intel in the smartphone arena. Yet ARM thinks Intel will not be a major player in the smartphone market. The fact is that Intel will eventually command over 50 percent of this market.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1362578310040</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:58:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362578725049-30</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft is partly to blame for poor PC sales. Ballmer must go.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362539456067</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 22:10:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, and in Bill Gates' time he tweaked the quality mantra among companies at that time,.. (Quality is Job 1),... to something consistent with what has become the norm for these guys,....."At Microsoft quality is Job 1.1 " They have routinely flooded the market with #$%$, gotten their customers to do free quality assurance for them by having then ending up wringing out the bugs, and then do an update. I sincerely hope Microsoft gets receives their just deserts by crashing and burning. And I hope Ballmer is man enough to go down in flames with his misguided ship.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1362578725049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 09:05:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362578793754-31</Id><Topic><Title>Steady as she goes</Title><Username>hankg1030</Username><Timestamp>1362577269690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:41:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>see you @ $25</Msg><Username>hankg1030</Username><Timestamp>1362578793754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 09:06:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362578847357-32</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE is number 4 smartphone manufacturer in the world.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1362578310040</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:58:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes..and this comes after I just read some inane Seeking Alpha article telling me that ARMH will continue to own the mobile chip market because it has destroyed the Intel "hegemony." Please cut and paste this as a reply to that idiot. The problem for INTC pps is that it is a matter of perception...not a matter of understanding.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362578847357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 09:07:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362578881876-33</Id><Topic><Title>Steady as she goes</Title><Username>hankg1030</Username><Timestamp>1362577269690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:41:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when do you think we'll see $25, so my short puts are no longer under water?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362578881876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 09:08:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362579024164-34</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's slow move up.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362574054234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:47:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SONY invented the "form factor" way back in the late 1950's with the first pocket size transistor radios, then walman, discman, etc. Jobs simply took this concept to the PC. Form factor SONY sound systems never displaced the stereo shelf system.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362579024164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 09:10:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362579255122-35</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Update for INTC. Read Now!</Title><Username>emanuellewis59</Username><Timestamp>1362577047124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:37:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>best out there</Msg><Username>theodore.pfeffer</Username><Timestamp>1362579255122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 09:14:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362579641081-36</Id><Title>Intel makes big bet on Android</Title><Msg>March 5, 2013 11:30 AM Devindra Hardawar Add Intel Capital to the growing list of companies eager to work with Bluestacks. Intel has invested an undisclosed amount in the startup, BlueStacks told VentureBeat today. BlueStacks “LayerCake” technology runs Android apps on any Windows PC and Mac, bridging a gap between mobile and the desktop that neither Google or Apple have tackled yet. Primarily, Intel wants to make sure that BlueStacks’ software is optimized for its chips. The investment could also be a major help for Intel’s smartphones, like the Europe-only Motorola Razr i, which run its x86-based mobile processors instead of the ARM-based processors that power most other Android phones. Intel claims its mobile chips can run 95 percent of Android apps due to the chip architecture difference with its phones. “Intel has an extremely powerful PC ecosystem, and they are looking to move into mobile in a big way,” said John Gargiulo, the vice president of marketing and business development at Bluestacks in an interview with VentureBeat. “There are more and more Intel chips on Android phones, so I think the alignment is clear.” Intel just recently announced a new dual-core Atom mobile processor, but it’s at a severe disadvantage since it only started focusing on mobile chips a few years ago. Meanwhile, competitors like Qualcomm, Samsung, and Nvidia have had years to hone their mobile chips. BlueStacks forged a deal with AMD to power its AppZone back in September, so Intel likely felt the need to step up its relationship. The news also comes on the heels of BlueStacks’ largest deal yet with Lenovo, a similar partnership with Asus, and the launch of a Surface Pro-optmized app. “Consumers expect to have similar experiences across all devices, and that includes having access to the same popular apps,” Dave Flanagan, a managing director at Intel Capital, said in a statement. “Bluestacks technology is a key catalys</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362579641081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 09:20:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362579797502-37</Id><Topic><Title>Intel makes big bet on Android</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362579641081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 09:20:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>catalyst for us in enabling mobile apps to run on any type of device.” Intel also relies on Bluestacks for its AppUp app store. Twenty-three apps on AppUp, like the popular news reader Pulse and Talking Tom, are listed as coming “via BlueStack Systems,” according to a Google site search. BlueStacks’ client powers those apps when you download them to your PC. It’s a particularly helpful partnership for Intel, since it brings popular apps to its fairly barren app store. The Campbell, Calif.-based BlueStacks has also raised $15 million so far from Andreessen Horowitz, Ignition Venture Management, Citrix Systems, and others.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362579797502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 09:23:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362579962049-38</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Update for INTC. Read Now!</Title><Username>emanuellewis59</Username><Timestamp>1362577047124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:37:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fantastic info on report</Msg><Username>carl.vandusen</Username><Timestamp>1362579962049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 09:26:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362580631083-39</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Update for INTC. Read Now!</Title><Username>emanuellewis59</Username><Timestamp>1362577047124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:37:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looking good</Msg><Username>robertfawcett51</Username><Timestamp>1362580631083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 09:37:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362581469721-40</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Update for INTC. Read Now!</Title><Username>emanuellewis59</Username><Timestamp>1362577047124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:37:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good potential</Msg><Username>sean_depasquale</Username><Timestamp>1362581469721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 09:51:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362582499870-41</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Update for INTC. Read Now!</Title><Username>emanuellewis59</Username><Timestamp>1362577047124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:37:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yea im in</Msg><Username>rodney_leboeuf</Username><Timestamp>1362582499870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:08:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362583124303-42</Id><Title>still some selling</Title><Msg>Excellent analysis and commentary! They regularly provide the best rundown on the US market. These guys are awesome!! With this great analysis, and there is no way I could have made money this year without this site! I signed up for there FREE daily videos. See for yourself, you will be glad you did! copy and paste and put info this link SUCCESSFUL-STOCK-TRADER</Msg><Username>stephenalex667</Username><Timestamp>1362583124303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:18:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362583439329-43</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Rumored to be bought out!</Title><Username>ericking531</Username><Timestamp>1361967974894</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 07:26:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>important information !</Msg><Username>perkins.jack</Username><Timestamp>1362583439329</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:23:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362583499334-44</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft to offer discount on Windows 8 OEM prices</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362541865913</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 22:51:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft should offer an even greater discount for devices that don't have touch screens and can't use Metro. At least that would help compensate the user for all the effort they have to go to make W8 function like W7.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1362583499334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:24:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362583574865-45</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Update for INTC. Read Now!</Title><Username>emanuellewis59</Username><Timestamp>1362577047124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:37:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>listen to the masters</Msg><Username>robertsterry518</Username><Timestamp>1362583574865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:26:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362583708145-46</Id><Title>INTC ShortSellers, Let Me Unburden Your Cash Piles From Your Stock Accounts</Title><Msg>Please shortsell more INTC shares to me at these low prices as I do not mind hauling away those heavy burdensome cash piles from your stock accounts.</Msg><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1362583708145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:28:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362583989517-47</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>carl.hand</Username><Timestamp>1362392578308</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:22:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>perfect one</Msg><Username>johnbussell595</Username><Timestamp>1362583989517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:33:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362584811577-48</Id><Title>Been slowly rallying ever since Foundry annoucement</Title><Msg>Finally, something to make the Intel-watchers happy.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362584811577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:46:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362585568889-49</Id><Topic><Title>Been slowly rallying ever since Foundry annoucement</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362584811577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:46:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the share buyback was designed to SHAPE THE CHART so the shares could be bought back but the most value would be to make the TECHNICAL CHART attractive to the chart readers. The buyback is nibbling on the bid line and making it so buyers have to hit the ASK in order to get all the shares they want. You probably have the short sellers still pushing down on the stock but there are now buyers. The analyst "SELL or UNDERPERFORM" reiterations have nearly vanished. Romit Shah finally stopped. He has not chimed in on any of the recent Intel news. From June 2011 through Jan 2013, he would reiterate his SELL and lower target every time there was news on Intel.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1362585568889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:59:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362585782029-50</Id><Title>Microsoft's view of future 3D pc's and gaming</Title><Msg>extremetechDOTcom/computing/150110-microsoft-research-shows-off-force-feedback-3d-touchscreen</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1362585782029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:03:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362586108406-51</Id><Topic><Title>Been slowly rallying ever since Foundry annoucement</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362584811577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:46:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Makes you wonder if Shah is an Intel Long as of 19's late last year. Makes me sick.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362586108406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:08:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362586130286-52</Id><Topic><Title>Been slowly rallying ever since Foundry annoucement</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362584811577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:46:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, it's nice to finally hear some good news. I never really lost confidence in INTC though considering its performance over its competitors.</Msg><Username>risk_hedger</Username><Timestamp>1362586130286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:08:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362587911311-53</Id><Title>The market is giving Cisco a 25% premium in PE over Intel</Title><Msg>Thats just pathetic. Reflection of poor leadership &amp; communication of vision at Intel.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1362587911311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:38:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362588020405-54</Id><Topic><Title>Been slowly rallying ever since Foundry annoucement</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362584811577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:46:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The short interest has been increasing about 1mil shares per day since Intel started dropping from $29. It is hard to absorb 1mil extra shares per day short for 6 months and behave normally. The short information for the last half of Feb (released late on 3/11) will be interesting. I want to see if the shorts are still active or covering.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1362588020405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:40:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362588185535-55</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Update for INTC. Read Now!</Title><Username>emanuellewis59</Username><Timestamp>1362577047124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:37:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job. Appreciate this.</Msg><Username>parkerthomas337</Username><Timestamp>1362588185535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:43:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362588397700-56</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>carl.hand</Username><Timestamp>1362392578308</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:22:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>love that report!</Msg><Username>frederickstone909</Username><Timestamp>1362588397700</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:46:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362588548858-57</Id><Topic><Title>The market is giving Cisco a 25% premium in PE over Intel</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1362587911311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:38:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time to buy another 10,000 shares.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1362588548858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:49:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362588823085-58</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Update for INTC. Read Now!</Title><Username>emanuellewis59</Username><Timestamp>1362577047124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:37:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they are amazing fact</Msg><Username>more.reynolds</Username><Timestamp>1362588823085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:53:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362589142509-59</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft to offer discount on Windows 8 OEM prices</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362541865913</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 22:51:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's quite fine for Microsoft to add a Metro interface to tablets and devices that have touch, but that is not what Microsoft did. Since W8's launch they forced it on every new desktop, laptop and notebook including those without touch and didn't give consumers a choice. It was clear to everyone in the industry that devices with touch would take a good part of a year for the industry to launch the new models and because those models would carry a price premium many consumers wouldn't buy them. In the interim hundreds of millions of consumers are stuck using W8 on a device that not only can't benefit from its main feature, but are further frustrated by al the effort to overcome W8's flaws. Indeed, Intel's effort to make touch-based devices more available will help going forward, but that isn't an excuse for Microsoft to push it's ill fit products on consumers and wait around for Intel and others to correct their mistake.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1362589142509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:59:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362589415290-60</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Update for INTC. Read Now!</Title><Username>emanuellewis59</Username><Timestamp>1362577047124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:37:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>love this</Msg><Username>jacksonvan87</Username><Timestamp>1362589415290</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:03:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362590912220-61</Id><Title>Why is HP using ARMH CPU's in their "Moonshot" Servers?</Title><Msg>"Big blow to INTC" (see article)</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362590912220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:28:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362591105250-62</Id><Topic><Title>Why is HP using ARMH CPU's in their "Moonshot" Servers?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362590912220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:28:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TXN's chips aren't being used because they're ARMH...they're being used because of TI's excellent DSP tech. The ARM cores are there because they need some kind of general purpose processor. Intel doesn't have TI's DSP tech, so for the workloads TXN's aiming at, Intel doesn't have a comparable solution.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1362591105250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:31:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362591580351-63</Id><Topic><Title>Ya'll Saw What Happened to NOK, Blackberry</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1362571350832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:02:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM, NOK, Blackberry - three very different situations. One element of commonality - ARM, Blackberry, and to a degree Apple, are one trick ponies - as the iPhone gets competition, margins shrink, sales growth declines; for Blackberry, if the new device sells, they're ok for awhile, but outlook isn't great; in contrast, NOK is restructuring, partnering with Microsoft, and now has good phones at every price point, globally. If Intel wants to sell a lot of chips, they'll partner with Nokia. I think they will. Nokia has a lot of patents in LTE and mobile, Nokia has a history with both Intel and Infineon. Unlike with Apple and Samsung, Intel has no significant conflicting business interests with Nokia (or Microsoft). Most will remember "Wintel" for PCs. An update, for global mobile - Wintelkia. It makes sense to me....</Msg><Username>clcellve</Username><Timestamp>1362591580351</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:39:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362592085037-64</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>carl.hand</Username><Timestamp>1362392578308</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:22:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>floydpotter938</Username><Timestamp>1362592085037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:48:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362592215582-65</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Insider Trading Reported.</Title><Username>ray.mary</Username><Timestamp>1362317312220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:28:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks !</Msg><Username>almeda.mosley</Username><Timestamp>1362592215582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:50:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362592253248-66</Id><Topic><Title>The TRUTH about Intel Corporation...</Title><Username>wayne.garza</Username><Timestamp>1361975360186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks !</Msg><Username>almeda.mosley</Username><Timestamp>1362592253248</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:50:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362592396043-67</Id><Topic><Title>Ya'll Saw What Happened to NOK, Blackberry</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1362571350832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:02:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Littlestew and Herbal_dude show up at the same time after both being absent for months......shocking! (not).</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362592396043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:53:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362592550762-68</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Update for INTC. Read Now!</Title><Username>emanuellewis59</Username><Timestamp>1362577047124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:37:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>biggest winners around</Msg><Username>richardspaul58</Username><Timestamp>1362592550762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:55:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362592636884-69</Id><Topic><Title>Why is HP using ARMH CPU's in their "Moonshot" Servers?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362590912220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:28:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So are you agreeing that this is a big blow to Intel?</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362592636884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:57:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362593484876-70</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Update for INTC. Read Now!</Title><Username>emanuellewis59</Username><Timestamp>1362577047124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:37:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yup cash in</Msg><Username>donaldvoss80</Username><Timestamp>1362593484876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:11:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362593642149-71</Id><Topic><Title>Why is HP using ARMH CPU's in their "Moonshot" Servers?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362590912220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:28:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wait a minute here. As I read the article from yesterday, I saw this: "Moonshot" is using BOTH Intel and ARMH (Texas Instruments) chips and as a matter of fact that ARMH part of the project is being sent out to select customers just to test. Your headline is deceiving, making it sound like HP's doing a project only using ARMH.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362593642149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:14:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362593924091-72</Id><Topic><Title>Why is HP using ARMH CPU's in their "Moonshot" Servers?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362590912220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:28:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is not a big a blow as the MSFT announcement that they were doing WinRT. The importance of this announcement will depend on how successful it is. TI has been shopping the DSP around since SC11. It is probably a bigger blow to Calxeda since this is the type of socket they were looking to occupy.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1362593924091</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:18:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362594066506-73</Id><Topic><Title>Why is HP using ARMH CPU's in their "Moonshot" Servers?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362590912220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:28:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After reading more, I see that the first projectd is due out next month and we don't know if it's an Intel or ARM server. I also saw this from the article: Gemini gets its power savings from a new Intel Atom chip known as Centerton, which Intel has said consumes 6 watts of power, far less than its Xeon chips</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362594066506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:21:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362594152430-74</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are actually getting Texas Instruments chips, which is a blow to ARM....not a positive as you suggest.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362594152430</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:22:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362594313410-75</Id><Topic><Title>INTC to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>almeda.mosley</Username><Timestamp>1362591601010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:40:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome report !</Msg><Username>braden.brian</Username><Timestamp>1362594313410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:25:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362594316021-76</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"hey are actually getting Texas Instruments chips, which is a blow to ARM...." Texas Instruments is ARM based... another boost as the world goes ARM... "not a positive as you suggest." as positive as it gets...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362594316021</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:25:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362594487528-77</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"as the world goes arm" _________ I didn't notice the world going very ARM with MSFT RT. In fact, several vendors INCLUDING HP and Samsung won't touch it. Should I post the articles for you to review??</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362594487528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:28:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362594573675-78</Id><Topic><Title>Why is HP using ARMH CPU's in their "Moonshot" Servers?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362590912220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:28:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lucysuxwang, Not really. This doesn't affect Intel's core server MPU business, and represents just one niche within the new, greenfield microserver opportunity.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1362594573675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:29:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362594672901-79</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I didn't notice the world going very ARM" Then you didn't notice that ARMH is at a 52-week high...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362594672901</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:31:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362595033888-80</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have their revenues doubled?</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362595033888</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:37:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362595081330-81</Id><Title>ARMH, Apple on QCOM only red on my watchlist</Title><Msg>They all have one thing in common.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362595081330</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:38:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362595102493-82</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH, Apple on QCOM only red on my watchlist</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362595081330</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:38:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"ARMH, Apple and QCOM"</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362595102493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:38:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362595284089-83</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You missed your chance to get out at 44.4, back in the 43s now. It's pretty good that all these companies all pretending to be cpu designers chose ARM for their amateur experiment as undoubtedly it is the worst performing RISC of all time, even slower than Sparc and that takes some doing ;-). Intel will find very easy beating all of them.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1362595284089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:41:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362595648890-84</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Getanid61 is like a 1st level Help Desk Techician......as soon as you show up with a question of any relevance or some facts..........you someone how get hung up on.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362595648890</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:47:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362595708498-85</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You missed your chance to get out at 44.4, back in the 43s now. " Stops at 40... otherwise, I'm a holding for the ride... "worst performing RISC of all time, even slower than Sparc" I wondered why MIPS didn't take hold ?? great royalty rates too...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362595708498</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:48:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362595843815-86</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Update for INTC. Read Now!</Title><Username>emanuellewis59</Username><Timestamp>1362577047124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:37:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do work</Msg><Username>bradley.lilienthal</Username><Timestamp>1362595843815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:50:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362596336593-87</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"any relevance or some facts" HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362596336593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:58:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362596447887-88</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>carl.hand</Username><Timestamp>1362392578308</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:22:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great, thanks!</Msg><Username>georgethompson382</Username><Timestamp>1362596447887</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:00:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362596519199-89</Id><Title>Hedge market gains now, urgent opportunity.</Title><Msg>I gave a buy signal beginning at 20.70 or so with of course additional entries as it went down towards 20 as always implied (i never enter everything instantly so my first entry is always premature in hindsight on purpose, i use 3 steps if needed , in this cycle 2/3 were used). Now at +2sd at 21.78 i see a significant sell signal risk and although intel is fundamentally undervalued permanently it seems, near term a hedge is wise. I also spot march 22 puts at unreal volatility bargain at only 0.38 with real current value 0.22and over 8 days to go. Since developments once near 2sd are almost always rapid, 8 days is enough of a hedge. Instead of selling a position here one can buy a ton of 22 puts cheap and then if we min crash towards 20-21 area again liquidate it and use the money to buy more leaps, shares etc. If we continue to rally to 2.5-3sd levels as result of news or momentum its also ok, the puts wont go to 0 real fast even if we went to 22.1 now say in a couple days. So having kept the long position in case we continue to move and having removed the risk from below seems ideal at this spot. So i suggest a hedge of that type now and i do not view it as a waste of money for nothing with 8 days to go on a rally point we touch 2sd. Events usually are dramatic within 8 days of such points enough to justify the price which by the way seems to be corresponding to a remarkably low (implied) volatility that is ultra bargain for puts.</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1362596519199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:01:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362597491754-90</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Chinese choosing MIPS as their national micro-architecture might have a little something to do with it. BlueRedMonk has given some low level tactical technical reasons but if you are looking for a big strategic reason the Chinese connection is as good as any i.e no-one really wants to strengthen the IP-disrespecting Chinese any more than necessary. Even now the MIPS64 chips already in use as network chips would give Intel more trouble in server environments than the underpowered ARM64 chips planned if software was ported to it, Xeon derivatives are already MIPS major competitor in that network space.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1362597491754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:18:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362597662686-91</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Then you didn't notice that ARMH is at a 52-week high..." [I noticed that the stock as of this moment is a buck lower than its 52-week high...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362597662686</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:21:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362597996404-92</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362597996404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:26:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362598399641-93</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I must admit being a great fan of MIPS for decades now, I have not seen a single implementation which I did not think was quite neat and unique in some way whereas I have not seen a single ARM implementation that I thought was not fundamentally flawed in some way ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1362598399641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:33:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362598646863-94</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I have not seen a single ARM implementation that I thought was not fundamentally flawed in some way ;-)." mobile &amp; toasters ?? or are you referring to servers ??</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362598646863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:37:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362598664018-95</Id><Topic><Title>Why is HP using ARMH CPU's in their "Moonshot" Servers?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362590912220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:28:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The whole point of the project is to reduce amount of energy consumed by server farms. I don't think the issue is ARM vs Intel rather it is high power vs low power. HP decided to use Intel chips as well as the ARM chip and let the market dictate which chip it prefers.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1362598664018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:37:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362599157923-96</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All the Cortex-A chips are flawed in some way IMO both at the high micro-architectural level and in practice as some of the benchmarks in some apps are really poor which do not indicate a balanced design.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1362599157923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:45:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362599346039-97</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"some apps are really poor " which apps ??</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362599346039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:49:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362599441267-98</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH, Apple on QCOM only red on my watchlist</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362595081330</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:38:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot TSM</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1362599441267</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:50:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362599576952-99</Id><Topic><Title>Been slowly rallying ever since Foundry annoucement</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362584811577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:46:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a lot of hype in the ARM camp about matching Intels TriGate technology. ALTR is one of leading FPGA companies that depends heavily on advanced manufacturing technology. Bohr always emphazised Intels leadership but this is the first time a third party (ALTR) basically said TSMC FF won't cut it. Analysts that used to mock about Intel's manufacturing lead received a wake up call</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1362599576952</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:52:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362599593758-100</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ones where x86 beat ARM by many factors and they are not rare lol. If you have seen many other RISC vs x86 comparisons like I have in my life you will know this is not usual with perhaps the exception of the old Sparcs.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1362599593758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:53:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362599653196-101</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A15 also has too much power for its main mobile market.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1362599653196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:54:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362599791220-102</Id><Topic><Title>Been slowly rallying ever since Foundry annoucement</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362584811577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:46:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the problem with Intel is that investors and analysts take an overly simplistic approach to valuing INTC. Very much the common thinking is that INTC is totally tied to the desktop PC market. PC sales don't really look too hot and so folks are bashing INTC based on that outlook alone. Although INTC derives a good portion of its profits from PC sales they are into other sources of revenue. I think most drive by analysts can't see past that. Now folks are starting to see that INTC has other ways to make money not just PC sales so they can see a path for better earnings growth. The ALTR announcement was just part of that. Folks are still overly dismissive of INTC initiatives in the mobile chip space. Right now I think they are very small in that space but 2-3 years out I can see them with half the market. By the end of the year they will be very much noticing that and bidding up the shares.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1362599791220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:56:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362599855006-103</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>since you didn't name any, we'll go wtih javascript... where x86 trounced ARM... much of that is SW, where INtel has invested a great deal... From NVidia's Tegra 4 benchmarks, they had quite impressive results...!! We'll know for sure when independent reviews come on-line..</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362599855006</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:57:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362600079159-104</Id><Topic><Title>HP's Project Moonshot Servers to Get ARM Chips</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362505603628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 12:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>on the SAmsung 32nm it does... Honestly, it left me with more questions... How much of that is A15 vs turning up the clock on a low-power process... Promoting that it's A15 is that NVidia, &amp; others, are going A9 on their mobile...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362600079159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:01:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362600169695-105</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH, Apple on QCOM only red on my watchlist</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362595081330</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:38:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That translates to a LOT of GREEN for me since I'm short ARMH @43.75.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1362600169695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:02:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362600207285-106</Id><Title>ARM Down 82 Cents, Intel Up 24 Cents</Title><Msg>Quite the differential today. Looks like the ARM descent has begun...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362600207285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:03:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362600547512-107</Id><Topic><Title>Been slowly rallying ever since Foundry annoucement</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362584811577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:46:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Although INTC derives a good portion of its profits from PC sales they are into other sources of revenue." Intel can leverage huge CPU volume towards SoC - that's why Intel SoCs will be (more than) cost competitive. It's all about fix cost that require volume - this is really no "rocket science" but analysts seem to be slow getting it</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1362600547512</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:09:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362600841149-108</Id><Topic><Title>= = Analyst Predicts Decline to 17.07 =SEE REPORT=</Title><Username>blackscott588</Username><Timestamp>1361404069367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job mate. Thank you</Msg><Username>henryclark930</Username><Timestamp>1362600841149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:14:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362600997161-109</Id><Topic><Title>INTC to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>almeda.mosley</Username><Timestamp>1362591601010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:40:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing !</Msg><Username>douglas.goddard</Username><Timestamp>1362600997161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:16:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362601311445-110</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (INTC)</Title><Username>frankbryant786</Username><Timestamp>1361483522525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:52:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job mate. Thank you</Msg><Username>henryclark930</Username><Timestamp>1362601311445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:21:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362601319050-111</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Insider Trading Reported.</Title><Username>ray.mary</Username><Timestamp>1362317312220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:28:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing !</Msg><Username>douglas.goddard</Username><Timestamp>1362601319050</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:21:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362601498313-112</Id><Topic><Title>The TRUTH about Intel Corporation...</Title><Username>wayne.garza</Username><Timestamp>1361975360186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing !</Msg><Username>douglas.goddard</Username><Timestamp>1362601498313</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:24:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362602441048-113</Id><Title>CSCO, PFE and GE ARE DOGS BUT</Title><Msg>they are all OUTPERFORMING smelltel.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1362602441048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:40:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362602929522-114</Id><Title>P/E 10</Title><Msg>Really???</Msg><Username>technospec</Username><Timestamp>1362602929522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:48:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362605679823-115</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO, PFE and GE ARE DOGS BUT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1362602441048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:40:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nuff, want you to finally admit they you are a total failure not only as an investor but as a human being overall. You aren't worthy enough to even breathe the same air as everyone else. Your access to air should be restricted at the very least if not totally closed off.</Msg><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1362605679823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 16:34:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362606413930-116</Id><Topic><Title>P/E 10</Title><Username>technospec</Username><Timestamp>1362602929522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:48:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes really</Msg><Username>funtoday89</Username><Timestamp>1362606413930</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 16:46:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362607083787-117</Id><Topic><Title>Ya'll Saw What Happened to NOK, Blackberry</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1362571350832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:02:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hold Intel and Nokia and expect both to prosper together.</Msg><Username>robmxaa</Username><Timestamp>1362607083787</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 16:58:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362607233639-118</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>linkosarah</Username><Timestamp>1362149300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:48:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was really looking for some great news. Now I found it.</Msg><Username>knutsen1lorraine</Username><Timestamp>1362607233639</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 17:00:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362607357042-119</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>carl.hand</Username><Timestamp>1362392578308</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:22:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well done</Msg><Username>stevenhill681</Username><Timestamp>1362607357042</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 17:02:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362609439378-120</Id><Title>Capital intensity is going up, up, up</Title><Msg>"LONDON – Spending on fabrication equipment for wafer fabs is going to remain flat at about $31.7 million in 2013 before increasing by 24 percent to $39.3 million in 2014, according to industry body SEMI. Depending on various macro-economic risk factors, SEMI projects that fab spending in 2013 could be between -3 percent to +3 percent of the 2012 total. However, the construction of wafer fab shells will increase by 6.7 percent in 2013. Equipment spending is moving forward at the leading-edge and fab equipment spending for 17-nm and below is expected to start in 2013 and then climb to $25 billion in 2014, more than half the total." I believe neither DRAM nor NAND are below 17nm - assuming Intel capex@ $10 billion the three ARM foundries are going to spend a whopping $15 billion on their FinFet process. Now the bad news is that the die shrink going from 20nm planar to 16/14 FF is somewhat limited because it's still 20nm chip. When the fabless companies will learn about the price tag they will be like deers in a headlight. They're not going broke but I predict some serious margin declines for the ARM food chain BTW in 2010/2011 Intel R&amp;D was $ billion 6.576 (16%) / 8.350 (17%) TSMC compares to Intel: 0.943 (7%) / 1.156 (8%) Eventually all that R&amp;D is going to pay off As I said before the way to play ARM is buying equipment stocks because ARM eco system has NO choice</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1362609439378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 17:37:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362609755377-121</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight!</Title><Username>carl.hand</Username><Timestamp>1362392578308</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:22:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please tell me no one falls for these idiotic spammers trying to install keyloggers on your system. Somebody must fall for it or they wouldnt do it... Geez.</Msg><Username>joshuawann</Username><Timestamp>1362609755377</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 17:42:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362611277250-122</Id><Title>How to remove the spam clutter</Title><Msg>Recently we seeing more and more s p a m messages infesting the MBs all over. One can click 'Ignore' then refresh to remove the noise but that's not as efficient if yahoo will give the option to 'hide' a whole thread w/o they need to even open that thread. I wonder when will yahoo resolve this issue.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1362611277250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 18:07:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362615955935-123</Id><Topic><Title>How to remove the spam clutter</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1362611277250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 18:07:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hopefully soon so I don't have to read your threads.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362615955935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 19:25:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362618380357-124</Id><Topic><Title>P/E 10</Title><Username>technospec</Username><Timestamp>1362602929522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:48:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lowest PE of any tech stock. Ridiculous. We need a new CEO that has shareholder wealth as his #1 priority.</Msg><Username>back_bay_professor</Username><Timestamp>1362618380357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 20:06:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362618682693-125</Id><Topic><Title>P/E 10</Title><Username>technospec</Username><Timestamp>1362602929522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:48:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coming 5-2-13. Just 8 more weeks.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1362618682693</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 20:11:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362619317894-126</Id><Topic><Title>If TSMC can't do 20nm until 2015, what will it mean for Apple's ARM chips</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362531833044</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 20:03:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like INTC is going to be testing 52 week highs shortly with TSM delays.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1362619317894</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 20:21:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362619497627-127</Id><Title>ARM Server maker can port x86 to ARM</Title><Msg>March 06, 2013 ARM server maker offers cloud service to port x86 code Boston provides the tools to port x86 code to ARM, which can then be tested over the cloud, reducing the need to buy an ARM server By Agam Shah | IDG News Service . ARM processors are used mostly in smartphones, but Boston Limited is offering a service through which developers can port existing x86 applications to work on ARM servers, which can then be tested via a cloud service. As part of the effort, Boston is partnering with software company Ellexus to help developers port the code to ARM servers, and is offering, via the cloud, quad-core ARM processors on which the ported code can be tested. This reduces the need for companies to purchase ARM servers to test code.</Msg><Username>armh_fanbois</Username><Timestamp>1362619497627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 20:24:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362620730743-128</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Server maker can port x86 to ARM</Title><Username>armh_fanbois</Username><Timestamp>1362619497627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 20:24:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"reducing the need to buy an ARM server" What does porting x86 code to ARM do to the need for x86 servers...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362620730743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 20:45:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362621472565-129</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Server maker can port x86 to ARM</Title><Username>armh_fanbois</Username><Timestamp>1362619497627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 20:24:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are not targeting users who wish to host services in the cloud -- Web or mail etc. -- this is really designed for companies or software developers to get access to ARM servers, fully loaded with development libraries and profiling tools, to assist them with migrating to ARM," said Apostolos Lambrianides, a marketing executive at U.K.-based Boston, in an email. ARM processors are widely used in smartphones and tablets, but are drawing interest for use in servers to process high volumes of Internet transactions tied to search and social media. ARM cores typically draw less power than x86 server processors, and are thus seen as an efficient way to process Web requests. But ARM has virtually no presence in the server market, and most of the server software development is taking place for x86 processors like Intel's Xeon or AMD's Opteron. Companies are approaching ARM servers with caution as there are still many hardware and software issues to overcome. ARM cores are capable of only 32-bit addressing, while x86 processors are 64-bit, which allows for larger memory and storage support. ARM servers do not interoperate with x86 chips, and thus would require a separate infrastructure in data centers, for which companies would need to invest. Another problem is the lack of a software ecosystem, which Boston hopes to address with its new service. Boston is one of the few companies commercially selling ARM servers today. Top server makers Hewlett-Packard and Dell are offering experimental ARM servers for customers to test code and benchmark. ARM's CEO Warren East in a recent interview said he expected the ARM server market to be viable starting in 2014.</Msg><Username>armh_fanbois</Username><Timestamp>1362621472565</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 20:57:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362624179399-130</Id><Topic><Title>How to remove the spam clutter</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1362611277250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 18:07:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least I'm not whining on the MB with baby tears every hour or two like you do. If you can't stand the heat get out of the kitchen doushbag .</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1362624179399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 21:42:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362624904867-131</Id><Topic><Title>How to remove the spam clutter</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1362611277250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 18:07:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mystk7 • Jan 7, 2013 2:07 PM Flag 0 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 1 The new AMZN is here just much better : FB watch it</Msg><Username>armh_fanbois</Username><Timestamp>1362624904867</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 21:55:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362625045054-132</Id><Topic><Title>How to remove the spam clutter</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1362611277250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 18:07:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've got like Eighteen Hundred aliases lmao.</Msg><Username>armh_fanbois</Username><Timestamp>1362625045054</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 21:57:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362625822830-133</Id><Topic><Title>How to remove the spam clutter</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1362611277250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 18:07:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I've got like Eighteen Hundred aliases lmao" Yes you do have many, but the stink is the same, that's how we spot you.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1362625822830</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 22:10:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362626071082-134</Id><Topic><Title>How to remove the spam clutter</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1362611277250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 18:07:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I smell the stench of a hack daytrader trying to pump Facebook to the moon by trying to trick people into thinking it's the next Amazon. You have no integrity, you tiny little twit.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1362626071082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 22:14:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362626323046-135</Id><Title>INTEL INVESTED IN BLUE STACKS</Title><Msg>Intel Capital, the chip company's venture-capital arm, has invested in software maker BlueStacks. The companies announced the deal yesterday but didn't say how much Intel Capital invested. BlueStacks offers software, called App Player, that lets users run their mobile applications on a Mac or Windows PC. According to BlueStacks, the company's platform has been downloaded more than 5 million times and supports the most-popular titles, including Angry Birds Space and Instagram. BlueStacks' technology has excited more than a few mobile-software lovers. Since applications are designed for mobile platforms running on ARM architecture, getting them to run on an Intel-based Mac or Windows PC requires another development. App Player makes the conversion for users and runs the apps in full screen. Now that it has invested in BlueStacks, Intel Capital has an awfully deep portfolio. Among the companies it's invested in: Baidu, Box, and Clearwire, among dozens of others. (Via Venturebeat)</Msg><Username>mugnmunch</Username><Timestamp>1362626323046</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 22:18:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362626505164-136</Id><Topic><Title>Ya'll Saw What Happened to NOK, Blackberry</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1362571350832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:02:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've been on the lookout for signs of collaboration between Nokia and Intel, and I've seen none. On the other hand, it just makes sense for Intel, Nokia, and Microsoft to be working together. There are a couple of billion people out there who would like a data phone. Nokia sells a lot of phones, and will be buying a lot of chips. In the hyper-competitive sectors of mobile, the friend of my friend is my friend....</Msg><Username>clcellve</Username><Timestamp>1362626505164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 22:21:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362626518873-137</Id><Topic><Title>How to remove the spam clutter</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1362611277250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 18:07:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can switch as many aliases you want, as i said the stink is the same. As for FB, that's all you got, a post months back ? 1. I suggested FB will go up since it was below 20$, you keep missing that part though. 2. If you follow people advise on MB w/o doing your own DD or understanding time horizon I suggest you order investing 101 to begin with.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1362626518873</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 22:21:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362626623682-138</Id><Topic><Title>How to remove the spam clutter</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1362611277250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 18:07:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>None of that refutes the fact that you have no Integrity and try to get people to buy what you are holding, you 2 bit worm.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1362626623682</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 22:23:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362627674494-139</Id><Title>INTC could go up BIG to $23 on this rally, before it corrects back to $20. LOL.</Title><Msg>Wall St hates this company. They like the fact that Intel is doing foundry. We got some of the Analysts busy calculating how much it would increase revenue, like $3B in 3 years or something. Those boys are having fun with this. LOL.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362627674494</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 22:41:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362628163407-140</Id><Title>ARM: Major Concerns Even Outside of the Fabrication Issues</Title><Msg>"Late last year, the company CEO also issued a warning about possible slowdown in demand. While the company is still on a growth trajectory and announced strong quarterly results, the rate of its ascent seems to be cooling down. Its arch rival Intel's move to capture the lower end of the mobile segment may also hit ARM Holdings hard as these lower priced smartphones are popular in emerging markets and that's where the next smartphone boom is going to come from. ARM Holdings does not seem prepared for it. The company valuation is another cause of concern. Though, generally traditional metrics fail to capture the scope of high growth companies, however, Price Earnings ratio of 84 is still too high to be ignored, especially when its rival Intel trades at a single digit P/E ratio. ARM Holdings has little competition and has a lion's share of the market. However, many other companies with equal risk profile are trading at considerably lower multiples. High valuation also indicates that the price already has most of the positive growth baked in it. The stock is also seeing high insider selling activity, which is generally not a good omen for any stock." [ARM Concern Recap: 1.) Many other companies with equal risk profile are trading at considerably lower multiples. 2.) Positive growth already baked in. 3.) High insider selling activity. 4.) Intel going after the low-end smartphone market. 5.) Slowdown in demand and 6.) ARM's Windows RT was a bust 7.) Intel is picking up ARM cash cow foundry customers like Acronix and Altera 8.) Intel's Haswell arrives in June 9.) Intel's 14nm FinFET arrives at the end of the year 10) ARM's fabrication process will soon be two nodes behind that of Intel. A huge competitive disadvantage for ARM...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362628163407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 22:49:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362629054994-141</Id><Title>ARM, Intel Technicals</Title><Msg>Today Intel moved ahead of both the NASDAQ and ARM on a 30-day comparison. And the gap has gotten wider over the last 4 days. ARM's 77 cent drop today can only be viewed bearishly as it continues to support the conclusion that ARM investors are exhausted as the stock has tried and failed three times over the last month to break in an upwards direction. And there are plenty of macro dynamics supporting an ARM move down. ARM had few major smartphone announcements at MWC 2013. It needs continuous product refreshment in order to maintain its huge P/E ratio. Apple is struggling. Nvidia won't have Tegra 4 products until the end of the year and has only one design win. ARM's fabrication roadmap ends after 20nm and 20nm is thought of as damaged goods because it is planar and not FinFET. Intel is preparing to open up a two process node lead over ARM. Couple this with significant insider selling and you have to ask what has been holding the ARM stock price up for this long?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362629054994</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 23:04:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362629388171-142</Id><Title>Intel and ZTE team up for Atomic phones</Title><Msg>[These are the types of announcements that we are seeing more and more often. Does Wall Street think they really don't mean anything???] Intel and Chinese smartphone juggernaut ZTE have inked a deal to develop a new generation of Atom powered smartphones. According to PC Magazine, ZTE said that it will enter a “multi-year relationship” with Intel to develop a new series of Atom phones, building on the success of ZTE’s Grand X IN handset. The Grand X IN was one of ZTE’s flagships last year and the company now plans to expand its line-up of Intel phone. Intel showcased its new Clover Trail+ Atom Z25xx SoCs at the Mobile World Congress in Barcelona last month. The new chips feature a lot more graphics muscle, along with bumped up CPU cores. However, Intel’s mobile Atoms are still stuck at 32nm. Intel’s next step is to offer integrated LTE modems in next generation chips and these 22nm parts are expected in 2014. From Fudzilla</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362629388171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 23:09:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362629447098-143</Id><Title>Earnings estimates</Title><Msg>Current estimates for 1st and 2nd quarters are 0.42 and 0.41 respectively. That's a major drop from last year. Why are they so low? I don't think stock can rebound if earnings are this low. Thoughts?</Msg><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1362629447098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 23:10:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362630121668-144</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Server maker can port x86 to ARM</Title><Username>armh_fanbois</Username><Timestamp>1362619497627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 20:24:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who has time to wait for it to finish?</Msg><Username>optermoron</Username><Timestamp>1362630121668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 23:22:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362630729715-145</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE is number 4 smartphone manufacturer in the world.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1362578310040</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:58:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I haven't seen this article, but if you can then by all means cut and paste my post as a response to the article.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1362630729715</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 23:32:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362630780872-146</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Server maker can port x86 to ARM</Title><Username>armh_fanbois</Username><Timestamp>1362619497627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 20:24:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Easier said than done. Just ask Microsoft and nVidia with their Windows RT bust. Porting code cannot be done easily and will be not be perfect. This is the reason why ARM will not make a dent in server market, especially now that Intel has low power Atom server chips. It is the same with the PC market - ARM PCs won't make a dent. Corporations have all their software running on x86.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1362630780872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 23:33:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362631447443-147</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings estimates</Title><Username>wildandwacky39</Username><Timestamp>1362629447098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 23:10:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The main reason is that Intel's investments are mostly front ended this year where they are planning huge investments for future gains in all types of computing device from smartphones all the way up to servers. Intel is very confident in its capabilities of gaining some serious market share given their technological advancements. So the lower bottom line numbers are mostly due to investing in capex for the future. Analysts complaining are being hypocrytes here. Because if Amazon doe it, they say it's okay. And before anyone brings up Amazons revenue growth, that part of the story is due to Amazon pretty much doing what Warren Buffet doesn't like. Which is "Selling a dollar for 50 cents". Intel is basically investing in a huge success in mobility and very much necessary growth in servers which they are very confident of. Investors would be much wiser to pay attention to Intel's current actions and words rather than what any analysts have to say.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1362631447443</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 23:44:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>