<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-04"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367640037340-1</Id><Title>How will Haswell release affect prices?</Title><Msg>Many computer enthusiest have not upgraded in years and are waiting for this chip. I expect sales to be good for haswell, big question is how will it affect stock price?</Msg><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1367640037340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 00:00:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367644868886-2</Id><Title>Another June Catalyst for you Wallis</Title><Msg>Apple's WWDC June 10-14 wallstcheatsheetDOTcom/stocks/will-apple-macs-change-forever-with-this-shot-of-intelDOThtml</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367644868886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 01:21:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367645622274-3</Id><Topic><Title>ARM P/E is now 80.43!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367627011968</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 20:23:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you are completely unable to do DanaWdblawgrow is to make any case that ARM deserves its stock price or P/E ratio. In fact, this is yet another content-free post. The simple truth is that you don't know enough to actually mount any kind of argument on either Intel or ARM. Every post is simply some sort of diatribe based on stock prices only that devolves into childish character assassination. Until you can defend the stock (ARM) valuation with something substantive, put a sock in it. No one who knows as little as you do about technology, fabrication, manufacturing or computing has the right to an opinion...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367645622274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 01:33:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367645980626-4</Id><Title>May and June Intel Catalysts</Title><Msg>Two BIG announcements on Monday!!! May 1: Microsemi Foundry News - Buzz should last at least a week or ten days May 6: Intel to announce Silvermont - Buzz should last all year May 6: Lenovo K900 release in China May 10: Lenovo K900 in India May 15-17; Google I/O Developers Conference - Buzz depends on announcements. Good potential. May 16: Intel's Annual Stockholder Meeting June 3: Intel to release Haswell - Buzz should last all year June 4: Computex - Buzz depends on announcements. Good potential June 10-14: Apple's WWDC - Macs about to get a major upgrade thanks to Intel’s (NASDAQ:INTC) new “Iris” graphics processors? June 26-28: Microsoft's Build Developer Conference - Rumors of next Surface Pro announcement 2013: Year of the Intel Tablet 2014: Year of the Intel Smartphone</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367645980626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 01:39:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367646348359-5</Id><Topic><Title>ARM P/E is now 80.43!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367627011968</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 20:23:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PS. I love ARM investors. There are so many reasons. They are totally fearless. They are afraid of literally nothing. Not Haswell, not ARM's fading fabrication. Not Clover Trail, not Bay Trail, not Airmont, and not being years away from FinFET production. Not afraid of Intel doubling tablet sales every quarter. Not Intel's new traction in smartphones. Now some might say that this is not fearless, it's stupid. But that would be rude. And non-factual. Surely none of these things will have any effect on ARM's future. Don't worry, be happy. And fearless. They have humble expectations. They are totally happy with just a dab of earnings. Almost no earnings at all will send them happily driving the stock to new 52-week highs. In fact, that have almost no expectations of ARM at all, other than it continue to stay in business. They are the essence of humility. They are in it for the long term. The fact that it takes over 80 years to earn back the price of a share of ARM stock doesn't bother them in the least. Hey, if they don't benefit from the purchase of ARM shares then their grandkids or great grandkids will surely reap the rewards. What other investors are able to take such a multi-generational approach??? None, I think. They are exuberant. Not since the dotcom era have we seen the exuberance that they express every single day. The past month is a great example that there is no threat that will dull their enthusiasm. Their sheer exuberance will work for them in the same way it did for those exuberant souls during the dotcom era. No doubt. Well, there you have it. Just some of the many, many reasons why I just love those ARM investors. And it's just as clear that Wall Street loves them too...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367646348359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 01:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367646555763-6</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft hit a 52 wk high today. Looks like PC sales are STRONG. Analysts</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1367637113335</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 23:11:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"will praise Microsoft and bad mouth Intel next week." [Don't you ever get tired of competing for the "stupid post of the day?"]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367646555763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 01:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367646818792-7</Id><Title>Unannounced Acer Iconia W3 8-inch tablet leaks on Amazon, priced at $380</Title><Msg>Acer's Iconia W3 tablet hasn't been formally announced, but that hasn't stopped Amazon from giving the TBA product a shiny new home on its website. The page appears to be a bit incomplete, with the summary listing an "1.5 GHz Apple A4" in the processor field, which we can't imagine is correct. The product description below might be a bit more on point, though. There you'll find a dual-core Atom Z2760 processor, an 8.1-inch 1280 x 800-pixel CrystalBrite LCD display, integrated graphics with 64MB of memory, 32 gigs of internal storage, 2GB of RAM, 802.11a/b/g/n WiFi, 2-megapixel front- and rear-facing cameras, and a two-cell 3,500mAh battery, keeping the Windows 8 tab powered for up to 8 hours. There's no word on when the 1.1-pound slate is set to ship (or when it'll make an official debut, for that matter), but assuming the Amazon web producers have managed to input pricing info correctly, you'll be able to pick one up for $380 sometime in the future. From engadget</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367646818792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 01:53:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367647350573-8</Id><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Msg>Haswell is an engineering marvel. According to Intel, it's the single largest improvement in battery life from generation to generation. Yet we think its destined for failure. Why? Who needs better battery life? Intel powered laptops -- that's a clear win. Intel powered tablets -- people aren't buying Intel powered tablets because Windows 8 based tablets are not a success in the market. So Haswell is not going to find customers in the tablet space. Desktops? Since these run off the mains, Haswell gives almost no improvement over the previous generation except for better graphics. Therefore, for people buying desktops, the upgrade doesn't buy them a whole lot. Therefore, the only device category that Haswell is really going to add value to is Intel powered laptops and as we know from market trends this is a relatively flat market. Haswell sales are therefore projected to be relatively flat with last year's chip sales.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367648529864-9</Id><Title>Whatever the catalyst is</Title><Msg>It better be good. If it's good the stock could shoot up to 30 and possibly finish the year low to mid 40s. Looking at MSFT that's my prediction.</Msg><Username>jake_718</Username><Timestamp>1367648529864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367648872293-10</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What this author doesn't account for is the way Windows 8 convolutes the mix. With Windows 8, the line between tablet and laptop/desktop completely blurs since the OS fully supports both platforms. Secondly, as you can see, Intel is bringing down the power consumption of its elite core series chips down to tablet levels. What we are going to see is desktop and laptops being replaced by a slew of touch enabled form factors all combining the features of laptops with tablets with touch. From the consumer's perspective, they are buying devices that have all the power and functionality of a desktop/laptop with the added convenience of a tablet. Its a win-win for the consumer and Intel. Since we're starting from the laptop/desktop end, you can expect them to pay the same price that they were used to before. Since we're also supporting the tablet form factor with a hybrid design, the total size of the market grows to include the tablet market.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367648872293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:27:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367651313029-11</Id><Title>So Intel stock has been performing poorly?</Title><Msg>Not since they released their earnings. Stock has gone up over 9% while the Dow has only gone up 1.4% since April 16, the day of Intel earnings call. We're off to a great start and there are alot more gains to come for the rest of 2013 at least.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367651313029</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 03:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367653650938-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I cannot find the article and have little trust in paraphrasing. Where is the original article? I think of 4 OS environments: Win8, Android, iOS and Mac OS/X. The x86 is the silicon for Win8 and Mac OS/X. The x86 version of Android has been highly optimized. iOS .... no publicly released version although Apple has undoubtedly done the port for each CPU. There is no problem with any of the OS running on x86. APPS ... not a problem either. Win8 ... native apps. Apple OS/X ... all the applications are Intel based. Apple iOS ... Apple development and they would Android apps .... running the x86 optimized version of Android (or variant). The pure Dalvik apps should run without problems. Android apps mixed with ARM native code will present problems. There are a couple of possibilities but the app developers are cleaning up that code to make their apps platform independent. There is no way an app developer would create an app that would only work on a fraction of the systems. IMO, the "tablet" form factor will can be occupied by a notebook convertible OR a "PC in a tablet form factor". The argument does not hold water.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367653650938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 03:47:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367653949445-13</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Silvermont - The ARM Killer</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367627395792</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 20:29:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The existing 32nm Clovertrail SoC, already beats ARM based phones on almost every benchmark. The 22nm Merrifield chip will add to performance and battery life. ---- No. There is only one 32nm Clovertrail SoC in the market place today. Once Clovertrail+ arrives (in phones) we'll have a better test environment to compare and it will be clear that ARM SoC's will beat in it in Javascript, Java, Geekbench etc.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367653949445</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 03:52:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367657191678-14</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Silvermont - The ARM Killer</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367627395792</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 20:29:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reason why this is not true is not anything to do with the Silvermont core, but with the SoCs that have been built around this core. They lack integrated 4G/LTE and hence can't compete with Qualcomm's Snapdragon which does. For a smartphone or tablet vendor shipping to the US market 4G/LTE is a critical feature. They only way Intel can provide the functionality is through separate standalone modems which are power hogs. This shows you an example of why ARM's IP licensing model makes better business sense.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367657191678</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 04:46:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367665910996-15</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Intel powered tablets -- people aren't buying Intel powered tablets because Windows 8 based tablets are not a success in the market. So Haswell is not going to find customers in the tablet space.' That is not true as shown to the rise to 7.5% from a 0% start. Just like we suggested Intel's advance into mobility will be far more successful than ARM's advance into PCs which still remains at 0% after the spectacular bomb of WindowsRT. 'Since these run off the mains, Haswell gives almost no improvement over the previous generation except for better graphics.' Haswell has substantial improvements on the cpu core side as well, double cache bandwidth and floating point as well as a third more integer not to mention the 128MB L4 eDRAM on the top models. Haswell is good and improved enough allround for *everyone* still on a pre-Core 2 chip to want to upgrade, watch its sales smoke as it gives a lie to the PC is stagnant fallacy.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367665910996</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 07:11:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367666660749-16</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Silvermont - The ARM Killer</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367627395792</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 20:29:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'For a smartphone or tablet vendor shipping to the US market 4G/LTE is a critical feature. They only way Intel can provide the functionality is through separate standalone modems which are power hogs.' Rubbish. It would be the same functionality just on another chip and there is nothing inherently power wasteful about that no matter how many times you spout this fallacy. Intel (Infineon) modems are known for their low power usage anyway. Modems burn less power than the application processor as well so it is not an important point in the first place. 'This shows you an example of why ARM's IP licensing model makes better business sense.' What an idiotic statement. Whether a modem is on the same chip as the application processor has absolutely nothing to do with its architecture as Intel modems are still ARM based for historical reasons i.e. that is what Infineon used. If you did not spout nonsense you would not spout any sense at all !</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367666660749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 07:24:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367666944486-17</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to CNET the Surface Pro, the flagship, has sold 400,000 units since launch. Is that 7.5%?</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367666944486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 07:29:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367667294807-18</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction, it's 900,000 units in Q1 according to IDC.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367667294807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 07:34:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367667375193-19</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i think your wrong about the tablet part. the surface pro with haswell will be huge success. Most of the reviews only knocked battery life and lack of apps on win 8 platform. come sufrace pro 2 think both will be adrressed. desktop market is shrinking also , but were win 8 really shines is all in one touch system with the extra graphics will help give small footprint without built of video card</Msg><Username>bill3442li</Username><Timestamp>1367667375193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 07:36:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367667743742-20</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surface Pro is not the only Windows 8 device !! Also that 400,000 figure was just the initial month sales on limited availability as MSFT underestimated its demand and overestimated the Surface demand meaning it still has unsold inventory of the latter. 7.5% is the figure given for all of Windows 8 devices for 2013Q1 by a respected marketing reporting source, do you dispute the figure ?</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367667743742</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 07:42:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367667989155-21</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367667989155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 07:46:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367668143080-22</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If 7.5% is for all Windows 8 devices, the figure for Windows 8 tablets of which the Surface Pro is the majority part is definitely less than 7.5%. It's in the noise compared to the 350 million chips Intel needs to sell annualy to stay flat, and that my point. No Haswell going into Windows 8 tablets because Windows 8 tablets hardly selling,</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367668143080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 07:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367668249275-23</Id><Topic><Title>This stock is going to the MOON!</Title><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1363965968442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:26:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will cover around $21.63. Thanks!</Msg><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1367668249275</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 07:50:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367668292479-24</Id><Topic><Title>This stock is going to the MOON!</Title><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1363965968442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:26:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure will.</Msg><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1367668292479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 07:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367668880522-25</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" No Haswell going into Windows 8 tablets because Windows 8 tablets hardly selling" This Xmas customers will be spoilt for choice in premier Windows 8 tablets containing both Bay Trail and Haswell. ARM ones will be in the bargain basement as a result.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367668880522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:01:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367669144230-26</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you're not reading into the numbers correctly. The numbers suggest people don't want Windows 8 tablets period. They want Windows 8 laptops and Android tablets or iPads but no Windows 8 tablets.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367669144230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:05:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367669650097-27</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are just making up your own lies to suit your personal fantasy view of the world as per usual. This is *exactly* what the report said ... "Microsoft captured a niche 7.4 percent global TABLET share in Q1 2013. Very limited distribution, a shortage of top tier apps, and confusion in the market, are all holding back shipments." strategyanalyticsDOTcom/default.aspx?mod=pressreleaseviewer&amp;a0=5351</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367669650097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:14:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367669683157-28</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Silvermont - The ARM Killer</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367627395792</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 20:29:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rubbish. It would be the same functionality just on another chip and there is nothing inherently power wasteful about that no matter how many times you spout this fallacy. Intel (Infineon) modems are known for their low power usage anyway. Modems burn less power than the application processor as well so it is not an important point in the first place. Actually multi chip solutions do use more power, but multi chip solutions are quite common at the top end in the ARM world - gives your more flexibility for different markets (at the cost of [slightly] more power and a more expensive BOM) and also can give you time to market advantages. Power use of modems is a complex topic, when in LTE mode they can burn quite a bit of power and they can also keep the app processor in higher states than they it needs to be. Intel's base bands are very good - even in the new (international S4)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367669683157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:14:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367670014433-29</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>khitchdee • Jan 30, 2013 11:09 PM Flag 1 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 0 Reply Don't worry, once the 14nm low power ramp happens towards the end of 2014 on Intel's accelerated schedule, it will light a fire under Apple and Samsung and force them to consider a switch to Intel chips. That should boost the stock price and in a few years, all the extra fab capacity that Intel has commisioned will start getting used to build smartphone chips, and the revenue will corresponding go up to far exceed Qualcomm</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367670014433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:20:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367670110149-30</Id><Title>Khitchdee</Title><Msg>khitchdee•Feb 5, 2013 8:32 PM 0users liked this postsusers disliked this posts0 Reply . I agree with Marsavian's timing projection but for different reasons. Towards the end of this year, Intel's game changing 22nm OOO trigate LP mobile SOC processor will be released. I think it'll take a few months for people to realize how it completely changes the mobile SOC game and they'll start exiting in hordes after that. ARMH is currently priced sentimentally, and Intel's holiday introduction will shake people out.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367670110149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:21:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367670183591-31</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So 900,000 Surface Pro's sold in 2 months of Q1 and Microsoft captured 7.4% of the tablet market. Let's list out the tablets being sold in the market iPad (19.5 million), Android tablets (27.8 million), Surface Pro (0.9 million). Are there any other major Windows 8 tablets that I'm missing in this list? Android and iPad combined are 47.3 million. That means Microsoft sold a total of about 4 million tablets, which means about 3 million were not Surface Pros. This report probably counts hybrids as tablets.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367670183591</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:23:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367670279240-32</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Silvermont - The ARM Killer</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367627395792</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 20:29:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel will wage its battle for tablets on two fronts, 1). Overall performance and battery life, and 2). Software flexibility giving the consumer access to real Windows and its millions of apps, plus Android and its apps. In all probability between Haswell and Bay Trail Intel will enjoy performance superiority across the entire range of tablet price points, but even if Intel's performance is only roughly equal to ARM tablets Intel still has the huge advantage of being able to give consumers access to all OSes and their apps. The latter puts the purchase decision on a qualitative "It runs Windows or not" question. This is something the consumer easily understands and the debate about benchmarks don't even matter. Now if Intel wins the performance benchmarks too, it won't really be much of a choice.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367670279240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:24:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367670400787-33</Id><Title>More from Khitchdee regarding Surface Pro</Title><Msg>khitchdee•Mar 15, 2013 2:13 AMFlag 0users liked this postsusers disliked this posts0 Reply . +The sales numbers have spoken. It looks like Microsoft has a veritable hit on their hands. With the intro of Haswell, some of the criticism around this PC will get addressed. Also, this leads the way for core series chips to be put to use in tablets which is probably a win for core series sales volumes. If I was Qualcomm or NVidia, I would be very scared about competition for tablet chips in this form which neither has a chance of competing with at least on the performance front. Windows 8 it seems is set to take off as a touch OS albeit a little slowly contrary to earlier reports</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367670400787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:26:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367670437527-34</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gosh you were only off by more than 100 percent.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367670437527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367670500402-35</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>or maybe you are lying by omission yet again. What about the odd dozen Clover Trail tablets ?</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367670500402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:28:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367670760107-36</Id><Topic><Title>Khitchdee</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367670110149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:21:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thoughts, Khitchdee?</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367670760107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:32:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367670803544-37</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its hard to believe those Clover Trail tablets combined for 3 million units in a quarter. I would guess 0.5 million.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367670803544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:33:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367670919113-38</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>khitchdee•Feb 5, 2013 8:32 PM 0users liked this postsusers disliked this posts0 Reply . I agree with Marsavian's timing projection but for different reasons. Towards the end of this year, Intel's game changing 22nm OOO trigate LP mobile SOC processor will be released. I think it'll take a few months for people to realize how it completely changes the mobile SOC game and they'll start exiting in hordes after that. ARMH is currently priced sentimentally, and Intel's holiday introduction will shake people out.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367670919113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:35:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367671385314-39</Id><Topic><Title>How will Haswell release affect prices?</Title><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1367640037340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 00:00:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The upgrade/replacement cycle question is a good one. Haswell is the first product release in years from Intel that truly obsoletes every laptop made before it - particularly in battery life. I know for myself every laptop older than 24 months will get replaced sometime in the second half of this year.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367671385314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:43:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367671430068-40</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So according to you each Clover Trail design sold about 50K in a quarter despite the fact they all killed WindowsRT at birth whose own sales were well over a million ? You are a grade 1 fantasist idiot.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367671430068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:43:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367671916550-41</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clover Trail tablets are sluggish when running Windows 8 and Windows 8 is not an interface that people want on their tablets in the first place. Sales of Clover Trail tablets have nothing to do with WindowsRT. Are you saying people considering WIndowsRT of which there were not many all rushed to buy CloverTrail tablets because they were equally power efficient and had legacy app support? I don't buy that.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367671916550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:51:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367672119002-42</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>khitchdee•Mar 15, 2013 2:13 AMFlag 0users liked this postsusers disliked this posts0 Reply . +The sales numbers have spoken. It looks like Microsoft has a veritable hit on their hands. With the intro of Haswell, some of the criticism around this PC will get addressed. Also, this leads the way for core series chips to be put to use in tablets which is probably a win for core series sales volumes. If I was Qualcomm or NVidia, I would be very scared about competition for tablet chips in this form which neither has a chance of competing with at least on the performance front. Windows 8 it seems is set to take off as a touch OS albeit a little slowly contrary to earlier reports</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367672119002</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367672214994-43</Id><Topic><Title>How will Haswell release affect prices?</Title><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1367640037340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 00:00:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont' forget Haswell in Servers....</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367672214994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:56:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367672269319-44</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Are you saying people considering WIndowsRT of which there were not many all rushed to buy CloverTrail tablets because they were equally power efficient and had legacy app support? I don't buy that. Are you saying people considering WIndowsRT of which there were not many all rushed to buy CloverTrail tablets because they were equally power efficient and had legacy app support? I don't buy that. ' I am not the only one saying that ... the whole World apart from you is saying that ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367672269319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:57:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367672275580-45</Id><Title>We are all waiting for Aeassa's Haswell Review</Title><Msg>IMO, it is the next catalyst to move the stock. If it's a positive review, we will probably see a 10% rise to test the $26 area.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367672275580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367672363608-46</Id><Topic><Title>Khitchdee</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367670110149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:21:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Khticdee hates ARM.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367672363608</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:59:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367672388299-47</Id><Topic><Title>More from Khitchdee regarding Surface Pro</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367670400787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:26:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Khtichdee gets giddy over Surface Pro sales.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367672388299</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:59:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367673538617-48</Id><Topic><Title>We are all waiting for Aeassa's Haswell Review</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367672275580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:57:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, the big news I'm personally waiting for is "Silvermont" architecture on Monday. We know Haswell will be amazing, but will the new Atom kick butt, too? :)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367673538617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 09:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367673696064-49</Id><Topic><Title>So Intel stock has been performing poorly?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367651313029</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 03:08:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hear, hear!</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367673696064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 09:21:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367673729891-50</Id><Topic><Title>Unannounced Acer Iconia W3 8-inch tablet leaks on Amazon, priced at $380</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367646818792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 01:53:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh wow, so Microsoft's Windows RT won't even live in the small form factors? Heh. So much for that.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367673729891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 09:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367674123751-51</Id><Topic><Title>REMEMBER APPLE/INTEL DEAL IN MAY AFTER MICRON PURCHASE OF ELPIDA IS COMPLETED</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1365725511465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:11:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The date is not set in stone, but Micron did mention they expected the appeal to be completed by about that time.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1367674123751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 09:28:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367676274705-52</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clover Trail CPU addresses a maximum of 2gb of memory. It only has 31-address lines running out of the chip. When you are running a bunch of Windows tasks and a couple of apps, you have exhausted memory and are paging to disk. That would be easily correctable if Intel wanted to change it. All they would do is make another address line available to the outside world and allow Clover Trail to support 4gb of memory. That line may already be exported and is defined as a NO CONNECTION or a PWR or GROUND connection. From Liliputing, Dec 2012:article "Intel’s Clover Trail tested: It beats most ARM-based chips… most of the time" "Here’s the short version: the Atom Z2760 chip is pretty slow by modern x86 processor standards. But when it comes to CPU-intensive tasks it’s faster than nearly every ARM-based processor on the market. The one exception is the Samsung Exynos 5250 ARM Cortex-A15 processor which outperforms the Clover Trail chip in some areas."</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367676274705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 10:04:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367677141135-53</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poorly designed OS that needs 2GB RAM to run on a simple tablet.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367677141135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 10:19:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367677401329-54</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see you are bashing Intel again, Khitchdee, just 2 months after saying INtel would BLAST ARM by the end of the year and that Surface Pro was a verifiable hit. Want me to repost your nonsense? You are playing devils advocate for your own #$%$ pleasures and it's going to stop.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367677401329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 10:23:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367677426373-55</Id><Topic><Title>Khitchdee</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367670110149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 08:21:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flip Flop.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367677426373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 10:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367678035706-56</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You opinion not mine. The article points out that Clover Trail is faster than nearly every ARM except the Exynos 5250 (at the time) which is faster on some metrics. If you hate the Clover Trail tablet performance, then you have to hate the slower ARM tablet performance because it is worse than the x86.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367678035706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 10:33:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367678197985-57</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Liliputing, Dec 2012:article "Intel’s Clover Trail tested: It beats most ARM-based chips… most of the time" ---- The data they show is for the Tegra 3 hardly the most competitive ARM SoC around... browserDOTprimatelabsDOTcom/android-benchmarks</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367678197985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 10:36:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367678409163-58</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's huge difference in the quality of the OS the two are running. The iPad doesn't seem slow.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367678409163</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 10:40:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367680006730-59</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Silvermont - The ARM Killer</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367627395792</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 20:29:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The existing 32nm Clovertrail SoC, already beats ARM based phones on almost every benchmark. The 22nm Merrifield chip will add significantly to performance and battery life. So, necessarily and indelibly, I shall have to go and tweak the benchmarks to unfavor Merrifield and favor Snapdragon and other ARMH things. I live on a bench you know. Surely, insistently, irrveocably so.</Msg><Username>thebluereddork</Username><Timestamp>1367680006730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:06:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367680065066-60</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>browserDOTprimatelabsDOTcom/ios-benchmarks then search for Z2760 to compare clovertrail.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367680065066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:07:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367680091111-61</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The article seemed to state that. They seem to say that Clover Trail and the Exynos 5250 had a similar performance. IMO, .... Geekbench is probably the worst benchmark to compare anything. The only thing that I think is worse is the ARM DMIPS metric that floats around. The Geekbench composite result list that you point to is not even generated the same way on ARM versus x86 chips. They are executing different codes that are then combined using some secret PrimateLabs algorithm. Geekbench weighting on tasks does not make any sense. Geekbench Integer performance for example .... 50% of the INTEGER performance is based on COMPRESSION/DECOMPRESSION (25% for bzip2 and 25% for 25% of the INTEGER performance is based on ENCRYPTION/DECRYPTION The last 25% of performance is from a LUA script.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367680091111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:08:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367680152940-62</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Silvermont - The ARM Killer</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367627395792</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 20:29:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The existing 32nm Clovertrail SoC, already beats ARM based phones on almost every benchmark. ---- Go on, prove it, you know you want too....*wink*</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367680152940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367680876324-63</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While geekbench has it's flaws, it's the best we have for this kind of discussion. We can use it to compare across OS's, bitness and device classes. It's reasonably open in terms of how figures are calculated so we can take threads/core into account (for example) and while there are more tests on x86 the final score can be used to compare to ARM based SoC's (my understanding, but could be wrong). If you dont want to be lazy, you can drill down to individual scores:) Encryption and compression are usually very good indicators of CPU integer performance. I know nothing about Lua (the language) so can't say if this is a good indicator or not:)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367680876324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:21:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367681543194-64</Id><Title>Khitchdee's greatest hits, in Chronological order</Title><Msg>khitchdee • Jan 30, 2013 11:09 PM Flag Don't worry, once the 14nm low power ramp happens towards the end of 2014 on Intel's accelerated schedule, it will light a fire under Apple and Samsung and force them to consider a switch to Intel chips. That should boost the stock price and in a few years, all the extra fab capacity that Intel has commisioned will start getting used to build smartphone chips, and the revenue will corresponding go up to far exceed Qualcomm khitchdee•Feb 5, 2013 8:32 PM I agree with Marsavian's timing projection but for different reasons. Towards the end of this year, Intel's game changing 22nm OOO trigate LP mobile SOC processor will be released. I think it'll take a few months for people to realize how it completely changes the mobile SOC game and they'll start exiting in hordes after that. ARMH is currently priced sentimentally, and Intel's holiday introduction will shake people out. _____________________ khitchdee•Mar 15, 2013 2:13 AMFlag +The sales numbers have spoken. It looks like Microsoft has a veritable hit on their hands. With the intro of Haswell, some of the criticism around this PC will get addressed. Also, this leads the way for core series chips to be put to use in tablets which is probably a win for core series sales volumes. If I was Qualcomm or NVidia, I would be very scared about competition for tablet chips in this form which neither has a chance of competing with at least on the performance front. Windows 8 it seems is set to take off as a touch OS albeit a little slowly contrary to earlier reports.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367681543194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:32:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367682098528-65</Id><Topic><Title>Khitchdee's greatest hits, in Chronological order</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367681543194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:32:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... I hafta admire your persistence In sticking to a game plan, That brings ya pain man, And at the end of the day nothing is gained. So listen to the voice within I'll see ya later, Pay heed to the Grand Oral Disseminator ... from "Reverence" by Faithless</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367682098528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:41:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367682149671-66</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Silvermont - The ARM Killer</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367627395792</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 20:29:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*wink* back atcha. Certainly, most assuredly.</Msg><Username>thebluereddork</Username><Timestamp>1367682149671</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:42:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367682737017-67</Id><Topic><Title>Khitchdee's greatest hits, in Chronological order</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367681543194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:32:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for freely admitting that you are a clown with no clue.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367682737017</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:52:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367683174876-68</Id><Title>Intel buys Networking Software firm Aepona</Title><Msg>Intel Buys Networking Software Firm Aepona By Jeffrey Burt | Posted 2013-05-03 Email this article Email Print this article Print The acquisition adds to Intel’s aggressive push into the networking space, including its recent efforts in the competitive SDN market. Intel is quietly adding to its networking capabilities, buying a small software company whose products enable telecommunications companies and cloud service providers to offer more services on their networks. Aepona is based in Ireland and has more than 300 employees in offices in Belfast and Dublin, as well as the United States and Sri Lanka. No financial details were disclosed. According to a statement from Intel, the deal will enable the chip maker to extend "its investments in solutions instrumental to build and deliver future network and cloud services across the spectrum of computing. Aepona's experience, customer relationships, and industry reputation will help Intel accelerate innovation and adoption in the ecosystem." Aepona develops software that lets service providers more easily open up their networks to developers by leveraging common language APIs, giving the developers the access they need to better develop services that the network providers can deliver to customers. The software not only gives the service providers more avenues to monetize their networks, but also better ways to manage them.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367683174876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367683318628-69</Id><Topic><Title>Intel buys Networking Software firm Aepona</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367683174876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:59:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aepona also offers a software platform that takes telecom technologies such as location, payment and authentication and puts them into a cloud services API. Telecoms and services providers are constantly looking for new ways to make money off of their networks by offering customers new services, and networking vendors are looking to meet that demand. For example, Cisco Systems in February introduced its Quantum portfolio of products designed to make it easier for carriers to better monetize and manage the rapidly growing amount of real-time data running across their networks from mobile and fixed Internet connections between people, their devices and various processes. For Intel, the Aepona deal is the latest step in developing a networking business that gives it one more growth area as the chip maker looks to diversify its product portfolio and open up new markets for its processors. Intel over the past several years has bought several businesses to help it grow its networking capabilities. That has included QLogic's InfiniBand business and Cray's high-performance computing interconnect assets. In 2011, Intel bought Ethernet chip maker Fulcrum Systems. In April, Intel made a significant push into the burgeoning and highly competitive software-defined networking (SDN) market. At the Open Networking Summit, Intel officials outlined the company's SDN strategy, which goes beyond simply supplying the processors for networking hardware. Intel also unveiled reference architectures designed to help enterprises, cloud service providers and telecommunications companies more quickly create hardware and software for SDN and network-function virtualization (NFV), which will bring the company into closer competition with the likes of Cisco and Broadcom. "SDN and NFV are critical elements of Intel's vision to transform the expensive, complex networks of today to a virtualized, programmable, standards-based architecture running commercial off-the-shelf hardware,"</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367683318628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 12:01:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367683371748-70</Id><Topic><Title>Intel buys Networking Software firm Aepona</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367683174876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:59:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rose Schooler, vice president of the Intel Architecture Group and general manager of Intel's Communications and Storage Infrastructure Group, said in a statement at the time. "The reference designs announced today enable a new phase in the evolution of the network and represent Intel's commitment to driving an open environment that fosters business agility and smart economics." Other moves Intel has made in the SDN space include investing $6.5 million in startup Big Switch Systems and becoming a founding member of the OpenDaylight Project, which aims to create a common, open SDN platform. The company also is working with the European Telecommunications Standards Institute's NFV project.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367683371748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 12:02:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367683394934-71</Id><Topic><Title>REMEMBER APPLE/INTEL DEAL IN MAY AFTER MICRON PURCHASE OF ELPIDA IS COMPLETED</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1365725511465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:11:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For now Apple is stuck with TSMC whether Apple likes it or not. See DT time article - one has to be more realistic with regards to time table. TSMC broke ground TWO years ago (April 2012) to provide fab space to Apple - IOW Apple deesion was made probably more than two years ago - and consequently it was based on data that was available two years ago. As we all know many things have changed - I believe during the last two years Intel made more progress than many expected and their future roadmap looks very good. TriGate compared to planar requires redesgn - I personally think Apple will make a similar move like ALTR. I think it would be ill advised for Apple to announce an Apple deal while in process of starting up 20nm - Apple can't just dump TSMC and walk away. According to DT TSMC to produce AP for phones - which leaves the question open what's going on with tablets ? Also Apple will continue to use Samsung. A possibility would be Apple to start using Intel for tablets at some point - and i phones could start using Intel @ 14nm. "Apple is expected to contract TSMC to manufacture all the application processors (APs) used in the 2014 model of its iPhone slated to launch in the second half of the year, industry sources have claimed. " Again be more realistic about the timing of an Apple/Intel announcement would Apple come to the same</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367683394934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 12:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367684428177-72</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IMO, the only thing that Geekbench is useful for is comparing the same CPU on the same OS. Cross OS or cross architecture is the weakest part of Geekbench. The worst part is that with the single number, it encourages people to do the most risky thing and compare across the boundaries. Geekbench runs each benchmark single and then multithreaded. x86 they also add a VECTOR run so for x86 they have 3 results for each subtest. How does Geekbench combine the TWO ARM results and the THREE x86 results and does it make sense? Is the method comparable. How does Geekbench weight x86 vector operations over a cross section of applications? They AVERAGE the single, multi-thread and vector versions. Yuk. After some playing around, it appears that they use an ARITHMETIC MEAN to combine the individual results and then some other mechanism to get the SINGLE result number. The arithmetic mean is sensitive to the runtimes and a single outlier result can easily distort the results. The stdlib WRITE, COPY and ALLOCATE are really how three small routines are implemented in the particular OS. memset and memcpy are very frequently called functions, having nothing to do with the CPU and contribute a large part of the result. Windows 8 currently has a very inefficient implementation of these (which I expect to be cleaned up in the Blue release). "Geekbench has its flaws" is a generous understatement. 8-)</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367684428177</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 12:20:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367686319723-73</Id><Topic><Title>Why Haswell is destined for failure</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367647350573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 02:02:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>P.O said that Intel looked very closely at A15 (and probably A57) - my guess Intel has its on "bench mark group" . Intel knows A15 and A57 inside and outside. If you compete with "something" you need to know the capabilities of the "something" and than design your own "something" to compete -</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367686319723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 12:51:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367690663586-74</Id><Title>Intel's and other stocks since earnings.</Title><Msg>Since April 16 earnings for Intel, their stock has gone up 9.5%. Dow has gone up 1.5% S&amp;P has gone up 2.5%. Nasdaq has gone up 3.5%. The other part of the "PC is dead" duo is Microsoft. So if the PC is really dying, why are they up 15.5% ? Indicating that Intel has more room to rise if they were only dependent on the Wintel duopoly. But Intel is not. Android is becoming more and more on Intel's side as well. TXN is up 3.5%. HPQ is down 1.7%. Cisco, Lucy's favorite is down 1.5%. I state these stocks just to show that interest is building up better in Intel stock recently relative to other major tech names. So some rotation may be happenning here plus Intel is the best paying dividend and the safest one, except for Cisco. Now for the ARM camp. Nvdia is up 6.7%. Apple is up 5.4%. QCOM is DOWN 3.1%. The biggest part of ARM other than Apple is actually down since Intel reported its latest earnings. At the same time, ARMH is up a whopping 21%. Now, Arm Holdings may have beat earnings expectations recently, but expectations don't really justify the multiples it's trading at already. But more importantly, its base is showing considerable weakness lately in relation to Intel stock. So clearly, the 21% rise does not make much sense. If investors have so much confidence in ARM stock, they should have almost similar confidence in the much lower PE major customer base of ARM. Things certainly don't add up in the ARM camp at this time. ARM should be considered to be overbought at this time. While Intel stock has much more room to rise, once they start showing more of the cards in their deck.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367690663586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 14:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367693326500-75</Id><Topic><Title>Is your Samsung Galaxy S4 overheating?</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1367614935807</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 17:02:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bwahahahahah! And ARM shareholders are paying $48.50/share for this #$%$?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367693326500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 14:48:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367693357110-76</Id><Topic><Title>Is your Samsung Galaxy S4 overheating?</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1367614935807</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 17:02:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you expect from 4x Krait cores jammed into a phone? lol</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367693357110</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 14:49:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367694536817-77</Id><Title>Battery life of Motorola Razr M.</Title><Msg>This is the one with the celebrated Qualcomm 1.5 GHz Chipset. I'm currently seeing the battery life drop by 1% every minute the phone does just about anything. As long as you're looking at the screen, whether it is talking, surfing, playing games, or anything. It drains by about 1% a minute. So the phone has to be recharged every 100 minutes or so. This is what makes ARM based chips so great?????</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367694536817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:08:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367694903518-78</Id><Topic><Title>Battery life of Motorola Razr M.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367694536817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The specs say 20 hours talk time and 17 days standby time. I don't believe the 20 hour talk time at all. I guess for it to get over 100 minutes of useage, the screen has to be completely turned off. Then what is the purpose of the smartphone to begin with. So the battery efficiency of ARM based chips, if there is any, means nothing. The phone is efficient only when not in use. I don't know how long that kind of marketing will fool people.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367694903518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:15:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367695004663-79</Id><Topic><Title>Battery life of Motorola Razr M.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367694536817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a Razr M also...battery life is a problem for me, too.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367695004663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:16:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367698516980-80</Id><Topic><Title>Battery life of Motorola Razr M.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367694536817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have a bad phone. I have a Razr M, also. I start mine at 100 percent each morning and it's at 45 to 55 percent at the end of the day with heavy surfing.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367698516980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:15:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367698539158-81</Id><Topic><Title>Is your Samsung Galaxy S4 overheating?</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1367614935807</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 17:02:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Best bechmarks in the industry. *wink*</Msg><Username>thebluereddork</Username><Timestamp>1367698539158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:15:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367698590829-82</Id><Topic><Title>Battery life of Motorola Razr M.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367694536817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Prove it. Benchmarks tell the story. *wink*</Msg><Username>thebluereddork</Username><Timestamp>1367698590829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:16:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367698849354-83</Id><Title>Acer shows off Aspire P3 Ultrabook, Aspire R7 laptop with innovative designs</Title><Msg>Summary: While the P3 converts to a Windows 8 tablet, the R7 offers a hinged display that can be moved to a variety of viewing positions. zdnetDOTcom/acer-shows-off-aspire-p3-ultrabook-aspire-r7-laptop-with-innovative-designs-7000014900/</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367698849354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:20:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367698998976-84</Id><Topic><Title>Acer shows off Aspire P3 Ultrabook, Aspire R7 laptop with innovative designs</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367698849354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:20:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>check the videos on youtube, very innovative!</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367698998976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:23:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367701936840-85</Id><Title>Acer W700 with Dual Boot (Android 4.2.2 and Windows 8)</Title><Msg>youtubeDOTcom/watch?v=060PBtDP0PI</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367701936840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:12:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367703755059-86</Id><Topic><Title>Acer W700 with Dual Boot (Android 4.2.2 and Windows 8)</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367701936840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:12:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uh Ohh. ARM's worst nightmare shows up in France.</Msg><Username>khitchdumb</Username><Timestamp>1367703755059</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:42:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367706481130-87</Id><Topic><Title>Acer W700 with Dual Boot (Android 4.2.2 and Windows 8)</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1367701936840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:12:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>c'est bien!</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367706481130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 18:28:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367714222601-88</Id><Title>Credit Suisee says Intel last man standing</Title><Msg>http://blogs.barrons.com/techtraderdaily/2013/05/03/intels-krzanich-subtle-shifts-in-strategy-likely-says-credit-suisse/?mod=BOL_hpp_blog_tt</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367714222601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 20:37:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367719837761-89</Id><Title>Two BIG announcements on Monday!!!</Title><Msg>From pc-tablet: The details of the Silvermont architecture will be revealed at a special event at Santa Clara, California, headquarters on May 6. Silvermont is the latest architecture which was introduced 5 years back in 2008. Right from its launch Atom has spread to not only tablets and smartphones but also embedded devices as well as low end microservers. Silvermont will represent the next gen architecture for future chips like the 22-nanometer “Bay Trail” for tablets. It will also feature in other devices which run on the Windows 8 OS platform as well as android platform. Atom will also feature in microservers Hewlett-Packard’s Project Moonshot systems which will have the Avoton which will replace the Centerton. From Tom's Hardware: The “Clover Trail+” powered Lenovo K900 smartphone is expected to launch on May 6 for just $480. The Lenovo K900 debuted at CES 2013 (see our hands-on here). Aside from offering a 5.5” display and impressively slim 6.9 mm stainless steel and polycarbonate body, it was the first smartphone we’ve seen that is powered by Intel’s new Atom “Clover Trail+” processor. May/June Calendar: May 6: Intel to announce Silvermont - Buzz should last all year May 6: Lenovo K900 release in China May 10: Lenovo K900 in India May 15-17; Google I/O Developers Conference - Buzz depends on announcements. Good potential. May 16: Intel's Annual Stockholder Meeting June 3: Intel to release Haswell - Buzz should last all year June 4: Computex - Buzz depends on announcements. Good potential June 10-14: Apple's WWDC - Macs about to get a major upgrade thanks to Intel’s (NASDAQ:INTC) new “Iris” graphics processors? June 26-28: Microsoft's Build Developer Conference - Rumors of next Surface Pro announcement 2013: Year of the Intel Tablet 2014: Year of the Intel Smartphone</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367719837761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 22:10:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367722831014-90</Id><Topic><Title>Credit Suisee says Intel last man standing</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367714222601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 20:37:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to Barron's blurb B.K. was in charge of 130 nm (.13 micron). As far as I recall this was the transition for Intel from 8 inch wafers to 12 inch wafers .... So B.K. should be the right man to lead Intel to 450mm wafers...</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367722831014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 23:00:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367725192528-91</Id><Title>seee market collapsing</Title><Msg>So over bought all worthless paper stocks/money. Yeah federal reserve games will crash world markets. Playing massive debt worthless paper money games.</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1367725192528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 23:39:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367725503330-92</Id><Topic><Title>seee market collapsing</Title><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1367725192528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 23:39:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You post this stuff on every stock board every month of every year. Be a real man and get a life.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367725503330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 23:45:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>