<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-25"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372135003390-1</Id><Title>OK where's tender offer?</Title><Msg>if it goes down tomorrow i'd tender my 20k share for 23.75</Msg><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1372135003390</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 00:36:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372135460930-2</Id><Title>Top Ten Reasons Why Stocks Are Down</Title><Msg>1.) Investors born without bones 2.) Investors born without brains 3.) Investors who hate the US economy 4.) Investors who hate the world economy 5.) Investors who hate any economy 6.) Big Wall Street firms that missed the run up. 7.) Investors who are afraid of their shadow 8.) Investors who are afraid of any shadow 9.) Investors who throw themselves off cliffs because of what they hear on CNBC 10.) Investors who are old, tired and scared</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372135460930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 00:44:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372136432007-3</Id><Title>The ARM Plunge</Title><Msg>Today was ARM's sixth pause on its plunge over the last 40 days. In all five of the previous ones, the stock quickly resumed its downward movement. If ARM were to move back up, what would be the catalyst? Certainly not the Apple/TSMC deal because that deal sent Apple down by 11 bucks today. Without any catalysts in sight and with Microsoft potentially announcing a new Intel-based Surface Pro on Wednesday and no mention of RT, what exactly would drive the stock higher? Especially after dropping 14 bucks in 40 days. I'm not seeing anything. If someone does, let's hear it...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372136432007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 01:00:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372137108853-4</Id><Title>A Lift for Intel Longs</Title><Msg>Intel longs needing a lift should run a graph comparison of Intel, ARM and the NASDAQ for the last six months. Six months ago was when Intel started making its move and even after Wall Street getting wacky the last few days, Intel is still up by $4.35 and has outperformed ARM and the NASDAQ for that period of time. Conclusion: The tipping point has arrived and the end of the ARM era is upon us. This is just a bump in the road. Intel shorts will hang in there, this will pass and shorts will once again give it all back. They think something is going to save them from Intel's road map, pipeline, product announcements, fabrication, technology, manufacturing and momentum. The graph says its not going to happen. Nothing is going to save them. But it will be fun to get their hopes up and crush them again...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372137108853</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 01:11:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372137776018-5</Id><Title>"someone forgot to tell Lenovo and Samsung..."</Title><Msg>New Windows 8 PCs use touchscreens, hybrid designs and Haswell to capture attention If the Windows PC market is in big trouble, someone forgot to tell Lenovo and Samsung. Late last week, within 24 hours of each other, the two Asian tech giants unveiled broad, new product lines. Following recent announcements from other major players, a critical mass of next-generation Windows 8 machines is now coming down the pike. But it’s not the quantity that’s most impressive—it’s the diversity: The arrivals cover every shape and form of portable PC, with touchscreens galore, and even some daring dual-boot systems. If the PC market is dying, vendors are responding not with resignation, but with innovation. And there are some good reasons this is happening, which you'll see as we take a peek at some of these beauties. The just-announced Samsung Ativ Book 9 Plus has no pricing or ship date yet, but it's an Ultrabook and then some. Weighing a mere 3.06 pounds, its 13-inch touchscreen display sports an outrageously high resolution of 3200 by 1800 pixels, and its aluminum chassis is just over a half-inch thick. Oh, and Samsung says its battery could last up to 12 hours. Notebooks like this could make you fall in lust with a Windows PC as easily as you could with the Macbook Air or a Chromebook Pixel. From PCWorld</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372137776018</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 01:22:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372141617993-6</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is low-balling growth estimate</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366415409484</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 19:50:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stacy Rasgon is a moron</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372141617993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 02:26:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372146293766-7</Id><Title>INTC $12 IN 6 MONTHS.</Title><Msg>MARKET IS RIGGED AS YOU KNOW</Msg><Username>sjim437</Username><Timestamp>1372146293766</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 03:44:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372155215430-8</Id><Title>What does MSFT &amp; Oracle partnership mean for Intel?</Title><Msg>Big news indeed! Share your thoughts!</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372155215430</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 06:13:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372156175493-9</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is low-balling growth estimate</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366415409484</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 19:50:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read it. Read it again. To me, these Intel execs are not low balling but see single digit growth overall, the best case scenario for this year. Got to factor in 2013 as another year of decreasing pc sales and therefore downward pressure on revenues, and 2014 and beyond when Intel new tech gets seriously reflected on financial statements. Of course this is just my reading and interpretation of these Intel exec's musings. Third and Fourth Qtr reports obviously will show accuracy of any and all previous pronouncements, including mine.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372156175493</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 06:29:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372157696215-10</Id><Topic><Title>OK where's tender offer?</Title><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1372135003390</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 00:36:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read up on TRC Capital outside the Intel tender. If Intel is above $23.75 on July 16th, TRC will withdraw their offer and not take your shares. Their offers only materialize if they can buy the shares below the trading price. If you DO offer your shares, then you are obligating yourself to hold the Intel to the July 16th expiration. If Intel is below $23.75, you will keep your shares because TRC will withdraw. If Intel is above $23.75, you will have to tender your shares at below market price. I am not sure why you would even think about tendering your shares if you wanted to exit your position. The TRC Capital Tender is really a method for THEM to create a 4,000,000 share FREE CALL OPTION. They pay $0 for the option to buy or not, your shares on July 16th for $23.75. CLIP TRC Capital and the Mini-Tender Menace By Roger Conrad on October 14, 2011 "TRC’s trademark strategy is to launch an unsolicited “mini-tender” offering to buy a small percentage of a company’s stock BELOW the market price. TRC then sells any shares tendered and pockets the difference. If the share price sinks below the offer price, TRC can walk away. In fact, it can legally keep investors from backing out, literally locking up their shares until it’s profitable to buy them out."</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372157696215</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 06:54:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372158579969-11</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is low-balling growth estimate</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366415409484</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 19:50:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Historically, Intel has provided a couple of general forecasts for the future range of revenue, gross margin and a couple of major expenditures (like below). They have been fairly accurate at hitting above the mid-point unless their is some external change, like the floods that wiped out the hard drive industry. Intel gets these numbers from a bottoms up roll up of discussions with their major customers. Analysts either take these numbers and judge them up or down OR the analysts do their own bottoms up prediction of results based on changes from IDC, Gartner, ... The average Q2 estimate from 40+ analysts is $12.89 billion. $100 million below the Intel forecast. They have a spread from a low of $12.70 to $13.02. Notice that all the analysts are inside the Intel forecasted range. The analysts take the Intel numbers and fudge them a bit this way and a bit that way and ta da ... they apply their black magic and generate target stock values from $16 through $30 per share. That is the spread where the analyst judgment is in question. Q2 2013 •Revenue: $12.9 billion, plus or minus $500 million. •Gross margin percentage: 58 percent, plus or minus a couple percentage points. •R&amp;D plus MG&amp;A spending: approximately $4.7 billion. •Amortization of acquisition-related intangibles: approximately $70 million. •Impact of equity investments and interest and other: approximately zero. •Depreciation: approximately $1.7 billion.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372158579969</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 07:09:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372159825436-12</Id><Topic><Title>A Lift for Intel Longs</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372137108853</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 01:11:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But it will be fun to get their hopes up and crush them again" You neglected to mention the good fun to be had when getting their money too.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1372159825436</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 07:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372162037605-13</Id><Topic><Title>A Lift for Intel Longs</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372137108853</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 01:11:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No lift needed, the whole market is in a pullback.</Msg><Username>commodityhq</Username><Timestamp>1372162037605</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 08:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372166574047-14</Id><Topic><Title>A Lift for Intel Longs</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372137108853</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 01:11:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey Waldork, yesterday and today ARMH is outperforming INTC, so put that in your nonstop pumping INTC pipe and smoke it. Will you let all your ARMH gains get away, you know the ones that failed to make up for the over 2.00 drop in INTC along the way</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372166574047</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 09:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372167331999-15</Id><Title>Lagging the general market</Title><Msg>as usual. Look out for the warning.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372167331999</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 09:35:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372168300225-16</Id><Title>Orders for U.S. Durable Goods Rose More Than Forecast</Title><Msg>Orders for U.S. durable goods rose more than forecast in May, reflecting broad-based gains that signal manufacturing is stabilizing. Bookings for goods meant to last at least three years climbed 3.6 percent for a second month, the Commerce Department reported today in Washington. The median forecast of 81 economists surveyed by Bloomberg called for a 3 percent increase. Excluding transportation equipment, where demand is volatile month to month, orders advanced 0.7 percent, also topping projections. Growing demand for cars and trucks and gains in homebuilding are helping counter weakness in export markets, benefiting manufacturers such as BorgWarner Inc. (BWA) and United Technologies Corp. (UTX) Businesses may also decide to replace aging equipment, which will help bolster expansion in the second half of 2013. “This is the missing piece for an upswing in economic activity,” said Millan Mulraine, director of U.S. rates research at TD Securities USA LLC in New York. “Business capital investment activity is off to a strong showing. If businesses start investing, they’ll add to their workforce.” From Bloomberg</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372168300225</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 09:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372168430345-17</Id><Title>U.S. Housing Prices Increased More Than Forecast in April</Title><Msg>Home prices climbed more than forecast in the 12 months through April, rising by the most in more than seven years and showing further strength in the U.S. housing market. The S&amp;P/Case-Shiller index of property values increased 12.1 percent from April 2012, the biggest year-over-year gain since March 2006, after advancing 10.9 percent a month earlier, a report showed today in New York. The median forecast in a Bloomberg survey of 28 economists called for a 10.6 percent advance. Short supply, record-low mortgage rates and an improving job market combined to boost housing demand and spark the rebound in prices. The recovery is probably far enough along to overcome the recent surge in borrowing costs after Federal Reserve policy makers said they may trim unprecedented accommodative measures meant to spur the expansion. “Housing’s doing really well and I don’t think the backup in mortgage rates to date is going to derail it,” said Brian Jones, senior U.S. economist in New York at Societe Generale, who projected a 12.3 percent rise in home prices. “We’re still well off the highs, but price increases could continue for the next several years.” From Bloomberg</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372168430345</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 09:53:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372168639662-18</Id><Title>Doom and Gloom Crowd Gets It Wrong - Again</Title><Msg>The disappointment of the bear, short and doom and gloom crowd is once again palpable as we have good economic news today on two separate fronts. And, of course, as the economy gets stronger, Intel prospects improve...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372168639662</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 09:57:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372168708506-19</Id><Title>OVER $24 TODAY</Title><Msg>INTC HAS TOO MUCH MOMENTUM</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372168708506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 09:58:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372168761353-20</Id><Title>BIG BUYERS STEPPING IN NOW</Title><Msg>WOW</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372168761353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 09:59:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372168814270-21</Id><Title>INSTITUTION INVESTORS BUYING LIKE CRAZY RIGHT NOW</Title><Msg>THEY ARE BUYING FROM WEAK SLEEPING RETAILERS</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372168814270</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:00:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372169120763-22</Id><Topic><Title>Stacy Rasgon how accurate</Title><Username>tmun1998</Username><Timestamp>1372111711807</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 18:08:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People that keep throwing the -14% Q1 number also fail to consider that Q1 purchases were heavily impacted by Windows 8 Metro that wasn't ready for the hardware being sold. This won't be a problem for 2H as Microsoft is releasing their fix by the end of the month.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1372169120763</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:05:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372169135863-23</Id><Title>"this deal may still be a fiction..."</Title><Msg>The report said TSMC would begin work on A8 chips as early as next month, starting with small-volume production. The company would also dedicate several facilities solely to the production of A-series chips for Apple. This deal would mean good business for TSMC, and it would help Apple separate itself from its rival, Samsung. However, this deal may still be a fiction. AppleInsider has noted that DigiTimes has a history of reporting on supply chain rumors in the technology industry that turn out to be false. Reports may not always be false, but the possibility still remains that an Apple-TSMC agreement hasn’t actually been reached. Rumors of a possible agreement between TSMC and Apple have been around for years, and it would make sense for Apple to replace Samsung with a different chip supplier. However, it will be difficult to judge the validity of reports that Apple has contracted TSMC until one of the companies confirms it. Of course, the details DigitTimes offered in its report suggest that July will be a telling month. If the two companies are in fact working together, TSMC will be working on A-series chips in July. If it doesn’t begin work on the chips, it can be assumed that the two companies haven’t actually entered a business arrangement. From Wall St Cheat Sheet</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372169135863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372169307199-24</Id><Title>Rates are going to skyrocket - after today's data</Title><Msg>Not good for fixed income &amp; big dividend stocks like Intel. Intel better show very good growth now or its going to $18 I'm afraid.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1372169307199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372169376559-25</Id><Topic><Title>"this deal may still be a fiction..."</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372169135863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Making today’s report a little less believable is the fact that DigiTimes says a TSMC manufactured “Apple A8 processor will be found in a new iPhone slated for release in early 2014.” Apple is of course largely expected to include a next-generation “A7″ processor in its next iPhone. If Apple is to keep with its fall release schedule as we expect, it’s hard to imagine where an A8-powered next-gen iPhone will fit into its cycle for early 2014. The report adds that “A9/A9X chips will be used in the newer-generation iPhone and iPad products.” The idea that Apple is looking to move its reliance on a sole chip supplier away from one of its biggest competitors is something that we’ve been hearing for a while now, but two years later Apple hasn’t made the switch. There could be truth to the rumors that Apple is considering a switch to TSMC in the coming years, but big investments by Samsung in its new Austin, Texas plant currently manufacturing chips for iPhone, iPad, and other Apple products indicate multi-year contracts are likely in place. From 9to5mac</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372169376559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:09:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372169591537-26</Id><Title>Gartner</Title><Msg>Gartner said it believed that consumers would become increasingly attracted to devices like the Chromebook and other thin and lightweight notebooks. Part of the newfound interest in these notebooks, Gartner said, will come as more of these devices include Intel’s new processors, called Bay Trail and Haswell, which raise performance and battery life. Gartner estimates that shipments of these notebooks, which it calls “ultramobiles,” will grow to roughly 20.3 million this year, up from 9.8 million last year. From nytimes</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372169591537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:13:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372169605515-27</Id><Topic><Title>"this deal may still be a fiction..."</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372169135863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yet TSM is up over 2 percent, nice bounce from rsi 30.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372169605515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:13:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372169674120-28</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's Hail Mary Pass</Title><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1372110229099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 17:43:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really, nothing to do with Semiconductors, are you sure about that? Or are you going to try to drag this into some pointless syntax debate?</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372169674120</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372169737131-29</Id><Title>How Many Shorts Covered at $23.41</Title><Msg>Let's see the hands. Hmmmm, so no one. Just as we thought...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372169737131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:15:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372169882085-30</Id><Topic><Title>"this deal may still be a fiction..."</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372169135863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am smelling a trial balloon. Something you do when you look like your over a barrel with Intel during contract debates. Or if you need a few days coverage to move out of ARMH before it retreats back to the twenties.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372169882085</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:18:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372169960870-31</Id><Title>This will be red</Title><Msg>real soon. They got you buying again today didn't they? You thought you would average that 26 with a high 23. It doesn't work with INTC especially at these nose bleed levels.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372169960870</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:19:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372170179183-32</Id><Topic><Title>"this deal may still be a fiction..."</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372169135863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"yet TSM is up over 2 percent, nice bounce from rsi 30." [Of course, they are up. Why else would they put out these fictions continuously. If people knew the truth about 20nm and FinFET half-step fabrication, the bottom would fall out of TSMC. And it will as soon as we start to see the delays. The downside of the news release is that it pegs volume production of 20nm to December. Ain't happening and now everyone will get to see the lie in all of this "happy, happy" marketing. The foundation has now been put in place at TSMC for an unmitigated disaster as customers will have demand for 20nm and somebody big or several big players are going to get left out. If Apple did get the contracts then Nvidia, Qualcomm and AMD will get left out in the cold. Destined to be a train wreck...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372170179183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:22:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372170247847-33</Id><Topic><Title>Doom and Gloom Crowd Gets It Wrong - Again</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372168639662</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 09:57:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good news is bad news causes rates to rise.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372170247847</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372170269780-34</Id><Topic><Title>It's Intel and Samsung vs. Apple and TSMC</Title><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372105361643</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 16:22:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel will make a ton of money and grow with, or without Apple. Samsung is smart and willing to swallow their pride if there is a better part out there. Apple, and their fanboys will go down with the ship because they are C-H-E-A-P and act like nobody should profit from their ideas. Dumb.</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372170269780</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:24:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372170411617-35</Id><Title>Laughing at Wall Street</Title><Msg>Wall Street is clearly having trouble accepting today's excellent economic news and continues to try to drive technology into the dirt. The problem for Wall Street is that earnings season is just around the corner and it will demonstrate that they have screwed the pooch once again. Wall Street and Intel shorts are today's queens of denial...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372170411617</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:26:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372170430605-36</Id><Topic><Title>Doom and Gloom Crowd Gets It Wrong - Again</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372168639662</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 09:57:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love how all of this Good news moves INTC about 10 pennies. As the economy strengthens, the bonds tumble causing interest rates to go up.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372170430605</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:27:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372170504224-37</Id><Topic><Title>Laughing at Wall Street</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372170411617</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:26:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope. WS knows that any improvement with the economy means bond prices get hammered.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372170504224</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:28:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372170846328-38</Id><Title>Somebody Please</Title><Msg>Somebody please walk over and knock Wall Street's fat rear end off of the stock price. Enough is enough - today is a good day to throw Wall Street under the bus...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372170846328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:34:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372170960515-39</Id><Title>WooHoo</Title><Msg>Shills still doing the monkey jumping today for your entertainment pleasure. No one told them the music stopped when they announced the durable goods and housing news this morning...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372170960515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:36:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372171007875-40</Id><Topic><Title>What do Kilroy, Holt, and Perlmutter know ...</Title><Username>walrusweener</Username><Timestamp>1372113275414</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 18:34:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who are these illustrious gentlemen, and what do they know that Wallis doesn't know?</Msg><Username>walrusweener</Username><Timestamp>1372171007875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:36:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372171073850-41</Id><Title>ARM Investors</Title><Msg>Still clinging to the edge of the abyss. Looks like their fingers are getting tired though...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372171073850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:37:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372171151954-42</Id><Title>INTC might blow up tomorrow! This is the key reasons why.</Title><Msg>Has any individual taken a look at the articles being presented? Unbelievable information that will assist any investor or trader. Link:- toDOTly/loOa (Remove DOT &amp; Use .)</Msg><Username>randklev.randall</Username><Timestamp>1372171151954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:39:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372171181727-43</Id><Topic><Title>WooHoo</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372170960515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:36:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your desperation is pitiful. It really is. You ALWAYS post furiously when the stock is down to pump and make yourself not seem so sad. Keep thinking out loud/posting like a wild dog to remove all doubt.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372171181727</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:39:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372171344694-44</Id><Title>DOW Should Be Up 350 and NASDAQ Should Be Up 100</Title><Msg>Wall Street once again with its foot on the neck of the American economy...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372171344694</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:42:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372171390121-45</Id><Topic><Title>"this deal may still be a fiction..."</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372169135863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC will ALWAYS get the benefit of the doubt while Intel gets slammed on regular base. Just consider look at capex: Intel spending some incremental capex to ramp mobile is bad TSMC doing exactly the same is good. It will take time before they comprehend the fallout from increasing capex - myth 1: ARM superior in power/performance - that's kind of crumbling myth 2 ARM SoC are cheap - they will deny it until the egg hits their faces</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372171390121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372171564081-46</Id><Title>Getting Tired</Title><Msg>Getting tired of the monkey jumping and non-stop, repetitive, content-free posting. Wish the shills could learn a new trick...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372171564081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372171740894-47</Id><Topic><Title>"this deal may still be a fiction..."</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372169135863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"myth 2 ARM SoC are cheap - they will deny it until the egg hits their faces" [By December there should be a lot more on their faces than egg: Shame, embarrassment, disappointment and little bits of crow...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372171740894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372171855590-48</Id><Topic><Title>Getting Tired</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372171564081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:46:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look in the mirror, shill. Hey everybody, look at Wallisweaver. He's talking to himself furiously today - he's in full meltdown mode over ANOTHER Intel let down.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372171855590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:50:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372171900423-49</Id><Topic><Title>DOW Should Be Up 350 and NASDAQ Should Be Up 100</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372171344694</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stop blaming your own stupidity on everyone else, ya 65 year old infant.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372171900423</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372172021682-50</Id><Title>when will these anuses announce a dividend increase</Title><Msg>it is long overdue..</Msg><Username>vertrosaht</Username><Timestamp>1372172021682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:53:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372172063174-51</Id><Topic><Title>"this deal may still be a fiction..."</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372169135863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like others still think an Apple/Intel foundry deal is still likely... Perhaps Cook and gang are going to work with both TSMC and INTC. Safety in diversification... From WS Cheat sheet. Lazard Capital semiconductor analyst Daniel Amir reinforced his buy rating on Intel (NASDAQ:INTC), asserting that he likes the company’s chances of landing a deal with Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL) to become a contracted chipmaker for the producer of the iPhone, iPad, and iPod. “Based on our recent checks across the supply channel, we highlight the impact and reasons why a widely anticipated deal with Apple as a potential foundry customer is becoming more likely,” writes Amir.</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1372172063174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:54:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372172710930-52</Id><Topic><Title>DOW Should Be Up 350 and NASDAQ Should Be Up 100</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372171344694</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Dow and Nasdaq are doing okay. INTC isn't.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1372172710930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:05:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372172758259-53</Id><Title>Way too much Insider Selling..WTH is going on?</Title><Msg>Has the new CEO even addressed shareholder value? A dividend increase? The new CEO seems like a stooge just like Paul O. was for 7 years.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1372172758259</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:05:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372172884194-54</Id><Title>All this weirdness makes sense...</Title><Msg>Here's the list: China's growth is slowing Japan is playing chicken with the Yen US economy starting to actually get on its feet QE is easing, well just the hint of easing means adjusting for easing... thank Greenspan for that trick Q2 is ending, so all big money is adjusting porfolios What does that mean for INTC, just weirdness. I'm jumping on the dips.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372172884194</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:08:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372173057182-55</Id><Title>Just Say No to Wall Street</Title><Msg>We don't have to listen to these cretins. Come on, America - show some backbone. The only thing Wall Street is interested in is bilking the average investor. Shorts are looking to create an exit strategy and a general economic beat-down is the only card they have to play ahead of earnings. Just say no...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372173057182</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372173061557-56</Id><Topic><Title>This will be red</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372169960870</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:19:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nuff knows all the pitfalls. At one time or another, he#$%$ them all and finds himself in at least one on a daily basis. Has very little money left. Uh oh, Intel up, better go work the board Nuff. Maybe you should bring out your moron: coinmaker, the cut and paste alias with the 3rd grade writing skills.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1372173061557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:11:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372173078271-57</Id><Topic><Title>Way too much Insider Selling..WTH is going on?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1372172758259</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:05:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are just posting about things that happened in the past. Please post about the future, especially how long you think it might be until the shares hit $30.</Msg><Username>walrusweener</Username><Timestamp>1372173078271</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:11:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372173321671-58</Id><Title>If posting 12 times in less than an hour is a sign or paranoia</Title><Msg>then Wallis just tipped his hat. He has a nervous twitch. You really don't have any real confidence about INTC do you?</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372173321671</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372173433915-59</Id><Topic><Title>If posting 12 times in less than an hour is a sign or paranoia</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372173321671</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:15:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You really don't have any real confidence about INTC do you?" He's an unpaid shill.</Msg><Username>walrusweener</Username><Timestamp>1372173433915</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:17:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372173578447-60</Id><Topic><Title>"this deal may still be a fiction..."</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372169135863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A planar design (20nm( does not plug into a Trigate/ 3D Let's assume Apple goes with TSMC: they need to make a design/layout for 20nm planar but in case TSMC starts moving to FinFet they need to redesign from scratch and scrap the planar design - they know they need FinFet but it's not ready. But you are correct - Apple should hedge but Intel is not stupid to share its Trigate family jewels with Apple while Apple is working with TSMC 20nm planar. One hedge would be to go with TSMC at 20nm (which I believe was decided some time ago) with the phone and plug Intel SoCs into the I pad (just like Samsung did). It's really hard to believe a supply guy like Cook would put all eggs in one nest - But Apple did EXACTLY that when they procured the AP, NAND, Mobile DRAM from Samsung. Also keep in mind Samsung Austin is staffed with US engineers - TSMC fabs are in Taiwan and staffed by Chinese. Ever listen to TSMC CC - it's terrible - very, very difficult to understand</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372173578447</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:19:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372173586063-61</Id><Title>Some Analyst is licking his chops waiting to bad mouth the pig.</Title><Msg>chops and pig. He he he he..</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372173586063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:19:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372173851013-62</Id><Topic><Title>Some Analyst is licking his chops waiting to bad mouth the pig.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372173586063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:19:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>alias switch</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1372173851013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:24:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372173876103-63</Id><Topic><Title>If posting 12 times in less than an hour is a sign or paranoia</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372173321671</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:15:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>alias</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1372173876103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:24:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372174001702-64</Id><Topic><Title>Just Say No to Wall Street</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372173057182</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are the quintisential average investor. will it bounce off 23.59? PUSH IT back up</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372174001702</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:26:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372174171738-65</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's Hail Mary Pass</Title><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1372110229099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 17:43:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple champions vertical integration. Their A processor line is at the bottom of their gadget design stack for iOS. The only way the could switch this to Intel would be if Intel were to go exclusive and build chips that targeted just iOS. Intel is a kid in the mobile market. They don't know the head or tail of this business. Being the bureaucratic org that they are, there's very little chance that they will adapt. TSMC has promised 2014 as the year for 20nm production. Apple mobile products in the second half could be based on this new node if all goes well. Apple's three year TSMC commitment means they see a strong roadmap they believe in. Intel has had first mover lead on process, but in this market the lead has been shrinking. The foundries will soon overtake on all fronts.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1372174171738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372174205647-66</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>Good morning folks, The stocks are oversold in the short term and hence the bounce and we could see some more bounce but profit taking will keep a lid on the stocks and will keep it subdued. But we will see a bounce as we go into the end of the quarter with window dressing. Goodluck.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372174205647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:30:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372174268355-67</Id><Topic><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372174205647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:30:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another nuff alias</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1372174268355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:31:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372174312635-68</Id><Title>TIC TOC guess what TIME is it ? Time for all the insiders to sell at once. ready one, two three all insiders SELL</Title><Msg>TIC TOC guess what TIME is it ? Time for all the insiders to sell at once. ready one, two three all insiders SELL</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372174312635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:31:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372174470406-69</Id><Title>APPLE IN DEEP SHEET, NO NEW PRODUCTS UNTIL MIDDLE OF NEXT YEAR...OMG</Title><Msg>TSMC WON'T HAVE 16NM UNTIL 2016...LOL</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372174470406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:34:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372174495425-70</Id><Topic><Title>TIC TOC guess what TIME is it ? Time for all the insiders to sell at once. ready one, two three all insiders SELL</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372174312635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:31:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You think they sell everyday weather its up or down. Wouldn't you think they would sell when it was up if they were going to. Do you ever have anything meaningful to say other than these idiotic remarks. If they were actually selling every time you post this stupid #$%$ they wouldn't have anymore shares, they would have to buy.</Msg><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372174495425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372174513502-71</Id><Title>SAMSUNG AND INTEL....NEW MOBILE COMBINATION</Title><Msg>INTEL PICKED THE RIGHT HORSE IN THIS RACE!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372174513502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:35:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372174520538-72</Id><Title>All About Earnings Now</Title><Msg>Things look much better than going into earnings last quarter. Wall Street must be terrified after what happened last time. They got the big PC report and still got skunked. This time the upside opportunity is even greater...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372174520538</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:35:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372174547487-73</Id><Topic><Title>TIC TOC guess what TIME is it ? Time for all the insiders to sell at once. ready one, two three all insiders SELL</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372174312635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:31:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should go blow yourself, oops, sorry, forgot, you have to use your finger.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1372174547487</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:35:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372174604819-74</Id><Title>Q3 AND Q4'S REVENUE WILL BE ~$15 BILLION EACH WITH MARGINS OF ~65%</Title><Msg>Earnings should be near $0.70 each...wow..$40 by end of year</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372174604819</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:36:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372174667649-75</Id><Topic><Title>Way too much Insider Selling..WTH is going on?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1372172758259</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:05:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The insider activity was on 6/3. Do you see anything newer? Dividend increase? That is easy, Intel current and historical policy has been to target a 40% payout ratio. The Q1 dividend was 44% payout. per Yahoo Statistics. When that Yahoo number is down to below probably 30%, Intel will look at a dividend increase. May 16th to June 25th is 6 weeks. You didn't even bother to wait for the quarter results. It would give your negative message more weight if you pretended to be more realistic. :-)</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372174667649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:37:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372174749097-76</Id><Title>BAY TRAIL WILL BE twice the performance at the same power level or 4.3x less power at the same performance AGAINST FUTURE COMPETITORS</Title><Msg>BAY TRAIL WILL BE twice the performance at the same power level or 4.3x less power at the same performance AGAINST FUTURE COMPETITORS...IT WILL BE A SLAUGHTER</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372174749097</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:39:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372174851423-77</Id><Topic><Title>If posting 12 times in less than an hour is a sign or paranoia</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372173321671</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:15:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis is only the 2nd most frequent poster. #1 is his negative twin.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372174851423</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372174895351-78</Id><Topic><Title>All About Earnings Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372174520538</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:35:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Q3 AND Q4'S REVENUE WILL BE ~$15 BILLION EACH WITH MARGINS OF ~65% Earnings should be near $0.70 each...wow..$40 by end of year</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372174895351</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:41:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372174945139-79</Id><Topic><Title>APPLE IN DEEP SHEET, NO NEW PRODUCTS UNTIL MIDDLE OF NEXT YEAR...OMG</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372174470406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:34:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTEL WILL BE ON 10NM BEFORE TSMC GETS TO FINFET</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372174945139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:42:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372175075337-80</Id><Topic><Title>APPLE IN DEEP SHEET, NO NEW PRODUCTS UNTIL MIDDLE OF NEXT YEAR...OMG</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372174470406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:34:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOOK AT AAPL STOCK GO DOWN ON TSMC DEAL LOL!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372175075337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372175181407-81</Id><Topic><Title>BAY TRAIL WILL BE twice the performance at the same power level or 4.3x less power at the same performance AGAINST FUTURE COMPETITORS</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372174749097</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:39:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MERRIFIELD Dual core (1W) at same performance use 2.4x less power than competition. At same power, performs 1.6x the speed of competition.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372175181407</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372175291604-82</Id><Topic><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372174205647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:30:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not helping INTC much, bounce that led to a lower low, way up here at 23.57. but that said, inclined to agree a bounce could take the markets back up to the break down points.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372175291604</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:48:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372175354857-83</Id><Title>Worst Fictional Poster of All Time</Title><Msg>coinmaker77 The personification of mindless stupidity. The absolute worst of the DanaLucy creations to date...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372175354857</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:49:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372175559712-84</Id><Title>SAMSUNG (WITH INTEL INSIDE) WILL HAVE APPLE FOR LUNCH</Title><Msg>Will be a slaughter....samsung galaxy note products with bay trail, then galaxy phones with merrifield next year</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372175559712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:52:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372175650691-85</Id><Topic><Title>SAMSUNG (WITH INTEL INSIDE) WILL HAVE APPLE FOR LUNCH</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372175559712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:52:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple just made the worst decision ever. They are lost with steve. No new products until middle of next year at best and then new new products after that until 2016 at best if tsmc ever gets to 16nm....apple is toast</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372175650691</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:54:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372175687866-86</Id><Title>INTC's earnings last year was .54 cents. They have dropped the forecast for Q2 all the way down to only .39 cents</Title><Msg>How much are they really going to miss lasts years .54 cents by and will they have to cut the dividend if they only make .39 cents</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372175687866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372175764243-87</Id><Topic><Title>Q3 AND Q4'S REVENUE WILL BE ~$15 BILLION EACH WITH MARGINS OF ~65%</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372174604819</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Record $54 billion in revenue this year...will be over $60 billion next year</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372175764243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:56:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372175802519-88</Id><Topic><Title>APPLE IN DEEP SHEET, NO NEW PRODUCTS UNTIL MIDDLE OF NEXT YEAR...OMG</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372174470406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:34:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>APPLE IS TOAST</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372175802519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:56:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372175806070-89</Id><Topic><Title>INTC's earnings last year was .54 cents. They have dropped the forecast for Q2 all the way down to only .39 cents</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372175687866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone ?</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372175806070</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:56:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372175829901-90</Id><Topic><Title>BAY TRAIL WILL BE twice the performance at the same power level or 4.3x less power at the same performance AGAINST FUTURE COMPETITORS</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372174749097</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:39:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2013: YEAR OF THE TABLET 2014: YEAR OF THE PHONE</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372175829901</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:57:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372175979725-91</Id><Topic><Title>INTC's earnings last year was .54 cents. They have dropped the forecast for Q2 all the way down to only .39 cents</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372175687866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whats your quess? One of your recent post you said you thought they would easily beat! How much to you think they will beat by?</Msg><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372175979725</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372175988822-92</Id><Topic><Title>INTC's earnings last year was .54 cents. They have dropped the forecast for Q2 all the way down to only .39 cents</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372175687866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Earnings hit by one time charges to upgrade to 14nm fool. Q3 and q4 everything with explode to the upside, margins, earnings...you will look like a fool</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372175988822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:59:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372176016467-93</Id><Topic><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372174205647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:30:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi, I am kind of surprised to see intel drop off so hard. Looks like the shorts are taking advantage of the situation. Besides profit taking lots of the hedge fundies and big investors that got creamed in the emerging mkts are selling their winners to ride out their losers in the emerging mkts instead of taking their loses. Also with the dollar being strong the #$%$ are selling out to get more yen while the going is still good for them. Lots of foreign money had poured into intel which is leaving but the selling seems to be getting exhausted and we will see intel ascend pretty soon into the quarter until the earnings are out. I believe they will beat estimates this time around showing growth again. have a nice day.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372176016467</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:00:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372176031139-94</Id><Topic><Title>SAMSUNG (WITH INTEL INSIDE) WILL HAVE APPLE FOR LUNCH</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372175559712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:52:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SAMSUNG AND INTEL, THE NEW MOBILE COMBO</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372176031139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:00:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372176034315-95</Id><Title>If INTC really only makes .39 cents this Q will INTC have to cut the dividend? .39 cents is a long way from the .54 cents they made lastyear</Title><Msg>If INTC really only makes .39 cents this Q will INTC have to cut the dividend? .39 cents is a long way from the .54 cents they made lastyear</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372176034315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:00:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372176085334-96</Id><Topic><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372174205647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:30:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your name spells out your brain and yr smartness.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372176085334</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:01:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372176130129-97</Id><Topic><Title>Q3 AND Q4'S REVENUE WILL BE ~$15 BILLION EACH WITH MARGINS OF ~65%</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372174604819</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The analysts are fooling retailer investors ...they make intc explode to the upside starting earning conference call</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372176130129</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:02:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372176153248-98</Id><Topic><Title>APPLE IN DEEP SHEET, NO NEW PRODUCTS UNTIL MIDDLE OF NEXT YEAR...OMG</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372174470406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:34:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>APPLE IS TOAST</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372176153248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:02:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372176360599-99</Id><Topic><Title>APPLE IN DEEP SHEET, NO NEW PRODUCTS UNTIL MIDDLE OF NEXT YEAR...OMG</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372174470406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:34:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure they will. They'll revamp the look of the icons in IOS and they'll call it a revolutionary user experience.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1372176360599</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:06:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372176462655-100</Id><Topic><Title>All About Earnings Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372174520538</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:35:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's not get grandiose here. It'd be terrific if the SP was at $30 by the end of the year. I'd be happy.</Msg><Username>angstromatic</Username><Timestamp>1372176462655</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:07:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372177109390-101</Id><Title>Eternally range-bound INTC stock</Title><Msg>Forever and ever. Einstein once said that "Insanity is repeating the same thing over and over without a change in the outcome." Wallis?</Msg><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372177109390</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:18:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372177164890-102</Id><Title>Maybe the 3 inside clowns can pump INTC up before earnings, INTC should beat the very lowered forecast of .39 cents</Title><Msg>Then look out 1,2,3, all the insiders SELL together</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372177164890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:19:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372177709134-103</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe the 3 inside clowns can pump INTC up before earnings, INTC should beat the very lowered forecast of .39 cents</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372177164890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:19:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ha you have major problems! Are you just trying to be funny or are you actually serious with this garbage?</Msg><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372177709134</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:28:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372178033897-104</Id><Title>Can Intel Land This Big Contract With Apple?</Title><Msg>Can Intel Land This Big Contract With Apple? By James Flaherty | More Articles June 25, 2013 Intel Lazard Capital semiconductor analyst Daniel Amir reinforced his buy rating on Intel (NASDAQ:INTC), asserting that he likes the company’s chances of landing a deal with Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL) to become a contracted chipmaker for the producer of the iPhone, iPad, and iPod. “Based on our recent checks across the supply channel, we highlight the impact and reasons why a widely anticipated deal with Apple as a potential foundry customer is becoming more likely,” writes Amir. Amir believes that Intel can adequately compete against contract foundry Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. (NYSE:TSM), and that the company has excess capacity thanks to new factories rolling out in coming years. According to Barron’s, Intel has also proven itself capable of handling large requests, having already completed orders for other large customers. Apple is Samsung’s (SSNLF.PK) biggest customer for contract chip manufacturers. Samsung is responsible for A-series chips that Apple designs and puts in its iPhone, iPad, and iPod Touch. Microprocessor chips from Samsung run on ARM Holdings (NASDAQ:ARMH) technology, a formidable competitor to Intel and one that makes any Apple-Intel deal more controversial. Amir believes that a deal with Apple could mean billions in revenue for Intel. NEW! Discover a new stock idea each week for less than the cost of 1 trade. CLICK HERE for your Weekly Stock Cheat Sheets NOW! “Currently, Apple uses Samsung as its fab, where it accounts for ~90% of Samsung’s foundry revenue, or ~$3.85B in FY12,” he writes. “Based on our assumptions for iPhone and iPad units (expected to grow ~20% Y/Y), we believe the potential revenue impact for Intel could be $2.97B.” Apple undoubtedly hates giving money to its strongest competitor in the smartphone and tablet market, and thus is more inclined to give Intel a fair look. However, Intel’s traditional X86 microprocessor has often been shunned in favor of ARM’s microprocessor chips. In order to continue with any deal, Apple must first establish that there would be no drop in product performance when switching to the X86 microprocessor or any future generations of it.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1372178033897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372178171867-105</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's Hail Mary Pass</Title><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1372110229099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 17:43:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahhh, Deju Moo, we've smelled this BS before. Seems like it was just only yesterday that this board was flooded with AMD fans who were preaching the virtues of the fabless model. As soon as GloFo had production problems they went away. "Apple champions vertical integration. Their A processor line is at the bottom of their gadget design stack for iOS. The only way the could switch this to Intel would be if Intel were to go exclusive and build chips that targeted just iOS" Could happen with Intel's new CEO. "Intel is a kid in the mobile market. They don't know the head or tail of this business. Being the bureaucratic org that they are, there's very little chance that they will adapt." Intel has been on the mobile PC platform for a very long time. As far as the mobile SoC market is concerned Intel can provide leadership and stability in this third world flea market of an industry. "Apple's three year TSMC commitment means they see a strong roadmap they believe in. " Now there are real doubts to the validity of the story. Too many questionable elements of the story, and besides, when was the last time Apple signed a 3 year exclusive contract for anything? "Intel has had first mover lead on process, but in this market the lead has been shrinking. The foundries will soon overtake on all fronts." Wishful thinking. The reality is that right now TSMC has been experiencing leakage issues at 28nm and has been tinkering with gate last while getting low yields. They don't have Finfet. Intel has FinFet at 22nm and is rapidly moving to the 14nm node. TSMC has nothing in it's hand, if it did it would be broadcasting press releases night and day. They are playing with an empty hand and we all know it. TSMC will eventually fix its issues, but when it does it will be far too little, and far too late.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1372178171867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:36:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372178591981-106</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe the 3 inside clowns can pump INTC up before earnings, INTC should beat the very lowered forecast of .39 cents</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372177164890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:19:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what's not true the 3 clowns or INTC's very lowered earnings forecast of .39 cents they made .54 a year ago.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372178591981</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372179020394-107</Id><Topic><Title>Way too much Insider Selling..WTH is going on?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1372172758259</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:05:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We shouldn't check annual reports also, nyet/nine/no to qtrly reports, for they are backwards looking. Don't look backwards for recent insider buying, because the last purchase was in October 2010, uninterrupted selling ever since. June 4, 2013 is also just too old. Check back in July 2013 and of course the information posted would be too old, because it didn't happen just at the same time and date you happen to find yourself looking.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372179020394</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:50:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372179169604-108</Id><Topic><Title>Way too much Insider Selling..WTH is going on?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1372172758259</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:05:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Posting about future events...prophecy indeed. Beats current and past info fer sure.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372179169604</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:52:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372179471443-109</Id><Topic><Title>INTC's earnings last year was .54 cents. They have dropped the forecast for Q2 all the way down to only .39 cents</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372175687866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Depends on their forecast.</Msg><Username>canuckkk</Username><Timestamp>1372179471443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:57:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372179505864-110</Id><Topic><Title>Way too much Insider Selling..WTH is going on?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1372172758259</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:05:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like you got all the insiders to tell you, DON'T look at the past my d#$%$, For the last 14 years when All the insiders are selling you better run. That was the TOP INTC going lower</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372179505864</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:58:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372179593860-111</Id><Topic><Title>NASDAQ Futures Up Big</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371184924051</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 00:42:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You use deception all the time, and, you are right.........it doesn't work.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372179593860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:59:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372179607252-112</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts Now Down $5.76 Since November</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371171499271</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 20:58:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I demand a recount.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372179607252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:00:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372179631205-113</Id><Topic><Title>Shills Expected a 50 Cents Drop Today, Instead Got a 40 Cent Bump</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1371150210573</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 15:03:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's down 2.50 since then. Your dissapointment in palpable...</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372179631205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:00:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372179697262-114</Id><Topic><Title>Running Out of Baskets</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370614471076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:14:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Short players just laughed and spit in your face.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372179697262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:01:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372179712481-115</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts Miss Yet Another Opportunity to Cover</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370614293036</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Laughable, content-free post.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372179712481</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:01:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372179777102-116</Id><Topic><Title>Running Out of Baskets</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370614471076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:14:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are joking...right?</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1372179777102</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:02:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372179821537-117</Id><Topic><Title>INTC's earnings last year was .54 cents. They have dropped the forecast for Q2 all the way down to only .39 cents</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372175687866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So why was earning only .40 cent in Q1 the.n if the is the Q for one time charges, INTC missed the boat and now its showing up in earnings and they missed the boat again in the gaming systems NOT GOOD it will show up even more in future earnings</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372179821537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:03:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372179854448-118</Id><Title>Buy LZB</Title><Msg>double in few days</Msg><Username>tejusveen</Username><Timestamp>1372179854448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:04:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372179963572-119</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down, Intel Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370354538559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More play by play by Wallisweaver that ends up being absolutely worthless wind at the end of the day.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372179963572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372179995147-120</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down, Intel Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370354538559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's Intel done since you wrote that? Hmmmmmmm</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372179995147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:06:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372180156032-121</Id><Topic><Title>INTC's earnings last year was .54 cents. They have dropped the forecast for Q2 all the way down to only .39 cents</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372175687866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I really don't know after Q1 was so bad only .40 cents and they missed the boat again on the only thing you know that will be sell this X mas ALL the NEW GAMING SYSTEMS. Is the fall off in computer sales faster they can make up other business, because the New business is lower margin.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372180156032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:09:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372180249328-122</Id><Topic><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372174205647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:30:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, you said something postive......but wait, you bought at 24.12 for a "swing trade". How convenient of you to say something good.....</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180249328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:10:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372180311612-123</Id><Topic><Title>Will $24 hold??</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1370463537910</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 16:18:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everytime Wallis Weaver gets cocky, the stock tanks big time. Textbook</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180311612</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:11:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372180340683-124</Id><Topic><Title>Shills Continue to Look Unsuccessfully for an Issue, Any Issue</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370372640657</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:04:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Humble Pie thrown in Wallis Weaver's face.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180340683</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:12:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372180364583-125</Id><Topic><Title>INTC's earnings last year was .54 cents. They have dropped the forecast for Q2 all the way down to only .39 cents</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372175687866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If INTC can't beat the very lowered forecast of .39 cents things are really bad at INTC</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372180364583</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:12:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372180401221-126</Id><Topic><Title>Shills: Spin, Spin, Spin</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370286408803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:06:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spin it, shill weaver, Spin spin spin it.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180401221</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372180426063-127</Id><Topic><Title>Short Pain is Palpable</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370268126173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 10:02:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How's today's dose of reality, Chump?</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180426063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372180554321-128</Id><Topic><Title>INTC's earnings last year was .54 cents. They have dropped the forecast for Q2 all the way down to only .39 cents</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372175687866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much they miss last years ,54 cents tells you how bad INTC is really doing, The lowered forecast of .39 cents is a joke and if they miss that look for dividend cuts</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372180554321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:15:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372180591324-129</Id><Title>How Intel Gets to 40</Title><Msg>1.) P/E ratio. A P/E ratio of 15 would get Intel to 30 instantly. A P/E ratio of 16 would get the stock price to 32. And a P/E of 17 would get the stock to 34. It would take a P/E of 20 to get the stock to 40 by itself. A little too much to hope for until we hear that Intel smartphone sales are doubling each quarter like is currently happening with tablet sales. I don't see 15 being unreasonable at all with Haswell, Bay Trail and tablet sales doubling each quarter. 2.) Increased capacity use. Intel easily has the capacity to generate revenues and profits that would support a stock price of 40. We have already seen some big foundry deals and will likely see more. ARM's fabrication struggles at 20nm and with FinFET will dramatically increase interest in Intel's foundry capabilities. We already know of a major mobility player deal that has yet to be announced. It is likely that there are many deals being currently negotiated. 3.) Increased mobility sales. The trend in tablets is obviously going to be a major driver of increased profitability going forward. The trend in smartphones and LTE will lag a bit but should be very much in evidence by the end of the year. 4.) Dropping Intel tablet ASPs. As Otellini noted in the earnings conference call, Intel will be able through new fabrication to offer tablets at some amazing price points. This should pave the way to big volumes as Intel makes major inroads into ARM tablet market share. 5.) 450mm Wafer Production. Intel is going to be first to 450mm wafers by a significant margin. This will provide an important new layer of improved economics that will reduce Intel's costs just as ARM is experiencing worsening economics and lessening performance improvements at 20nm. Let's not forget that 20nm is planar and doesn't offer the benefits of FinFET. 6.) Windows 8. I expect Haswell and Broadwell to pump new life into Windows 8 (not including RT) on a plethora of new form factors and to reinvigorate the Wintel relationship.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180591324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372180645386-130</Id><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Msg>Bloomberg reports. They just keep charging forward. Anybody think that this company isn't growing and changing with the times is crazy. Growth is here and is going to continue</Msg><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372180645386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:17:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372180746725-131</Id><Topic><Title>How Intel Gets to 40</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180591324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And while it's early on, I think Intel's web TV venture will get traction. It has the potential to shave a year off the time it will take for Intel to get to 40... 2013: Year of the Intel Tablet 2014: Year of the Intel Smartphone</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180746725</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:19:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372180758495-132</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372180645386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems strange that it would pop to $26 with lots of momentum and then come back down to these cheap level with nothing but good news.</Msg><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372180758495</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:19:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372180811765-133</Id><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Msg>Intel Corp. (INTC) said it plans to begin selling a set-top box offering Internet-based television service this year and is confident it can obtain programming. Eric Free, a vice president and general manager of the Santa Clara, California-based chipmaker, outlined plans for the product and service today at the TV of Tomorrow conference in San Francisco. Intel, the world’s largest semiconductor maker, plans to offer pay television through Internet connections, creating new competition for incumbent providers like Time Warner Cable Inc. (TWC) and DirecTV. (DTV) Intel has been demonstrating the service as it seeks programming from media companies such as Time Warner Inc. (TWX), Comcast Corp.’s NBC Universal and Viacom Inc. (VIAB). From Bloomberg</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180811765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:20:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372180822388-134</Id><Topic><Title>INTC's earnings last year was .54 cents. They have dropped the forecast for Q2 all the way down to only .39 cents</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372175687866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC will never get to 40 with lowered forecast earnings and earnings lower than last year, Just hope they don't miss the lowered .39 cents</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372180822388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372180855358-135</Id><Topic><Title>Eternally range-bound INTC stock</Title><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372177109390</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis?</Msg><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372180855358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:20:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372180920756-136</Id><Topic><Title>INTC's earnings last year was .54 cents. They have dropped the forecast for Q2 all the way down to only .39 cents</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372175687866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said they would though , right? So that means that its not bad right? Nice to finally have you wake up</Msg><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372180920756</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:22:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372181318561-137</Id><Topic><Title>Eternally range-bound INTC stock</Title><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372177109390</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Until INTC changes the good old boy system and the free share hand outs, INTC will never go higher and stay at a higher level. Because you keep getting all the insiders to sell all at once and the Wall Street companies that make the trades SELL before them , that is why the drops are so big and out of nowhere.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372181318561</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:28:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372181544747-138</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180811765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:20:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel had great confidence of WiMAX's success when they launched that. Then the wireless carriers they threatened with it joined forces and crushed WiMAX along with Intel's dreams of redefining the wireless carrier business. Like Mark Twain said, "It's not that history repeats itself, but it rhymes with it".</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372181544747</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:32:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372181741907-139</Id><Topic><Title>How Intel Gets to 40</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180591324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Continued dropoff in pc sales this year will have downward pressure on revenues in 2013. New tech but lower profit margins may or may not offset declining pc revenues. For a real banner revenues report, new tech must sell like water in hell, for the believers in here. Fer sure 2014 and subsequent years is where Intel's future will be prophesized, for the mystics out here.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372181741907</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:35:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372181987095-140</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180811765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:20:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mark Twain quotes or Wimax have nothing to do with INTC's new quality TV services success or failure,careful planning brainpower,execution &amp; finance does.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1372181987095</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:39:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372182033908-141</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180811765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:20:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the Intel insiders seem pretty confident that Intel TV is going to be a major flop. How else to explain their wholesale dumping of shares?</Msg><Username>walrusweener</Username><Timestamp>1372182033908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:40:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372182098845-142</Id><Title>Full court press</Title><Msg>The full court press continues hoping against hope that the weak and gullible will part with their shares. The big boys have over 200 million shares to cover before shareholders get wise and see what's coming from INTC.Stacy has weighed in and were waiting for Jimmy and Hans to join shortly. The Motley Fool has joined the BS with ARM and INTC getting into a price war. Last time I checked, ARM didn't manufacture anything. The only way you could have a price war is if all the foundrys and end users got togeather and conspired to fix prices against INTC. That would also assume they had equivalent products and they were able to supply them. That in itself is 2 major reasons it can't happen and then that price fixing thing usually doesn't work, especially since the SEC isn't allowed to sit around all day watching porn any more.</Msg><Username>newbee8801</Username><Timestamp>1372182098845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:41:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372182501845-143</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180811765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:20:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Definitely Intel will get its programming. It's paying up to 75% more than the competition. Neat trick if Intel can then price the package---box and programming---less than the competition's. If it does, then we are blessed to have witnessed a true miracle! A tidbit for you believers. Now for you skeptics: No cheating, now! I don't expect nor will I accept Intel eating losses, won't be good for revenues nor shareholders!</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372182501845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:48:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372182567715-144</Id><Title>What a bunch of psychopaths you guys are</Title><Msg>Watching every tick, unhealthy as can be. You had not one but TWO chances to buy in the 19's, hold, cash each Dividend and not have a worry in the world. Your average cost would go down a buck each year and five years from now you'd be averaged in the low teens. Greedy losers.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372182567715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:49:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372182834062-145</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180811765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:20:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great businesses are not built overnight I would expect some loss as it builds it's base. It sure has shorts all hot &amp; bothered though as it should LOL.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1372182834062</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372182960437-146</Id><Topic><Title>What a bunch of psychopaths you guys are</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372182567715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Punch a hole in that strategy..........you can't.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372182960437</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:56:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372183320031-147</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180811765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:20:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even with the strengths of Haswell and Bay Trail Intel has enough challenges battling ARM's global momentum. Intel must move from product launches to volume shipments producing real revenue in mobile and NOTHING should distract the company from this goal which is JOB #1. I further agree that shareholders will not tolerate Intel taking losses on a misguided business adventure that not only is a distraction from JOB #1, but also one they can't win.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372183320031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372183355281-148</Id><Title>INTC breaking through</Title><Msg>It broke through the long trough at ~23.65, by Friday it should be 24.5. July 25 open interest outstrips any other strike. should be 30 by year end</Msg><Username>trader_the</Username><Timestamp>1372183355281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:02:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372183411027-149</Id><Topic><Title>What a bunch of psychopaths you guys are</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372182567715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aren't you one of a*hole Nuff's aliases? He's been wet dreaming of getting in at 18 to 19 and tries to talk the stock down. He doesn't know his rear end from a hole in the ground.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1372183411027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:03:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372183542350-150</Id><Topic><Title>What a bunch of psychopaths you guys are</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372182567715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lucy nuff is a daytrading loser, just like you. Didn't think you could punch a hole in my strategy. You idiots on here jump in and out of the market with money you don't even have and are a hot mess. LOL bunch of clowns.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372183542350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372183726450-151</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180811765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:20:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. Not convinced this Intel TV was something the company needed, but once the ship left port we shareholders must endure the trip---may it prove profitable.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372183726450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:08:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372183781002-152</Id><Topic><Title>What a bunch of psychopaths you guys are</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372182567715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny watching nuff juggling his lame aliases around in vain LOL.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1372183781002</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:09:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372183967861-153</Id><Topic><Title>What a bunch of psychopaths you guys are</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372182567715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny watching you switch from your Jerry Blown alias to your William Davis alias in the same thread. Thanks for validating my post, psychopath. Look back through my post history - you'lll see that I'm not Lucy nuff. He's a liberal, welfare collecting waste of life. Liberals are disgusting. Have fun, dumbtrader.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372183967861</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372184276516-154</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180811765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:20:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An agreement wrapped in a limit---some losses, fer sure Intel to sell package higher than comp. Regardless, may it prove profitable in the long run.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372184276516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:17:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372184427941-155</Id><Topic><Title>What a bunch of psychopaths you guys are</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372182567715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clever trying to trash yourself but certain you are the henchman alias of Nuff. Each one of Nuff's aliases has their own personality. You're a schizophrenic mess and shouldn't be allowed to breath the same air as everyone else. BTW, not William Davis.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1372184427941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:20:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372184685294-156</Id><Topic><Title>What a bunch of psychopaths you guys are</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372182567715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That has to be the dumbest wag the dog post on this board.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1372184685294</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:24:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372184760608-157</Id><Topic><Title>What a bunch of psychopaths you guys are</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372182567715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Humor yourself, doesn't effect my life at all. Again, thanks for validating my post and showing how jealous you are of anyone that could and did buy at 19 (common freaking sense), hold (common freaking sense) and enjoy the Dividend. Later Jerry uhhh William uhhh Galba Tampon boy uhhh loser.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372184760608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:26:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372184941973-158</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's Hail Mary Pass</Title><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1372110229099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 17:43:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC don't have Finfet? You could argue they invented it. There was talk of them using at the 65nm node. They have taped out test Finfet chips @16nm. Google is your friend:) Also, TSMC are on the same side of the gate first/last argument as Intel, it's the IBM crew who are different. The other guys (Samsung, UMC, Global etc) are also using IBM's version of Finfet. TSMC are doing their own thing. As for this 'leak', who knows if it's true or not?</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1372184941973</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:29:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372184956747-159</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180811765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:20:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Meaning Intel sales price below cost. On the other hand (for the ambidextrous out here), Intel will underprice the competition, taking a loss. A loss-loss proposition?</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372184956747</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:29:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372185320942-160</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372180811765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:20:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or Intel sells for a profit per package unloaded...meant to say, package sold---much higher than the competition, therefore resulting in underwhelming sales figures, which calculates (for the math inclined among us) to a loss loss loss proposition, or losss x 3, or not getting enough no matter how you slice it, to use a cooking metafork.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372185320942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:35:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372185393265-161</Id><Topic><Title>OK where's tender offer?</Title><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1372135003390</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 00:36:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh thank you very much for making it very clear. in another word TRC wants to screw intel shareholders bending over backward. that is #$%$ insane.</Msg><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1372185393265</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372185572407-162</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's Hail Mary Pass</Title><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1372110229099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 17:43:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"TSMC don't have Finfet? You could argue they invented it. There was talk of them using at the 65nm node. They have taped out test Finfet chips @16nm. Google is your friend:)" [Hmmm. They invented it. They taped it out. So, they are done right? Hmmm. Still seem like there is something they are missing. Oh, right - they don't have any products shipping with it. And they don't have any volume production. And won't for who knows when. So, I'm glad that those other things give you solace but the bottom line is that "we'll have it someday" is pretty meaningless. Google may be your friend but reality isn't...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372185572407</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:39:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372185726051-163</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's Hail Mary Pass</Title><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1372110229099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 17:43:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The facts are the facts. You can choose to ignore them if you wish.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1372185726051</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372186044446-164</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372180645386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not the only stock to behave so. Besides, Intel hasn't reached $30 since at least 2003, introducing what was then new tech along the way. Incredibly, a decade-long resistance level. It will take very good revenues figures to move the stock northwards on a consistent, steady basis. Live lanky and prosper, Intel!</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372186044446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372186334882-165</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's Hail Mary Pass</Title><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1372110229099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 17:43:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There was talk of them using at the 65nm node So why didn't they? the FinFet will only improve power/performance - based on increasing capex for 3D coupled with inability to shrink they might turn Moore's law backwards. But there have NO choice.... It looks like TSMC and GF are hyping each other up while Samsung seems to be pretty quiet</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372186334882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:52:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372187158856-166</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's Hail Mary Pass</Title><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1372110229099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 17:43:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There was talk of them using at the 65nm node So why didn't they? ---- No idea,</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1372187158856</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 15:05:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372188594203-167</Id><Title>Buy LZB - easy double</Title><Msg>this week</Msg><Username>drhollars</Username><Timestamp>1372188594203</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 15:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372188638240-168</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's Hail Mary Pass</Title><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1372110229099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 17:43:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The facts are the facts. You can choose to ignore them if you wish." [The fact is that there aren't any ARM FinFET products on the market. When that changes you let me know...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372188638240</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 15:30:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372188646328-169</Id><Topic><Title>What a bunch of psychopaths you guys are</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372182567715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One of the descriptions you left out: you're a big time major league kweer.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1372188646328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 15:30:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372188819464-170</Id><Topic><Title>Apple's Hail Mary Pass</Title><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1372110229099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 17:43:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True. I'm sure others will beat me to it.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1372188819464</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 15:33:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372188855274-171</Id><Title>Microsoft Surface Mini Rumors: Tablet with Intel Atom Microprocessor to Launch During Q4 of 2013, Says Analyst</Title><Msg>[Okay, here comes the third element of the hat trick: Mac Upgrades, Samsung tablets and now the Surface...] Topology analyst Maxwell Change, during a media briefing, stated the Surface mini will be powered with the Intel Atom microprocessor and priced at $299. "Microsoft is likely to aim at taking on the iPad mini because it knows it is hard to compete with Android tablets in terms of price," said Chang. The report noted Microsoft has been in discussion with two or three Taiwanese manufacturers to produce the new Surface tablet. From latinospost</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372188855274</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 15:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372188946043-172</Id><Title>Digitimes is all BS all the time. They were getting low on hits so they</Title><Msg>fabricated Apple and TSMC's fabrication plans. Now all the internet blogs are repeating the same BS. Switch TSMC for Intel in the digitimes story and it makes sense. TSMC still doesn't have 28nm HPM going. Snapdragon 800 is delayed.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372188946043</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 15:35:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372188960864-173</Id><Topic><Title>How Many Shorts Covered at $23.41</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372169737131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:15:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's see the hands. Hmmmm, so no one. Just as we thought...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372188960864</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 15:36:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372189237615-174</Id><Topic><Title>Eternally range-bound INTC stock</Title><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372177109390</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know what you mean - but the pattern is going to change slowly. The bashers are overly confident that the pattern will reveal - and of course they count on GS et I won't praise the day before the sun sets but as Alex observed the final dumb is not was it used to be. Intel must continue to deliver and the pattern will change - it's idiotic to expect Intel to come out and defend the stock like one moronic poster constantly suggests</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372189237615</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 15:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372189608013-175</Id><Topic><Title>What a bunch of psychopaths you guys are</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372182567715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tis true. I didn't get in a 19 but did get in at 21. I pretty much feel the same way.</Msg><Username>masonma</Username><Timestamp>1372189608013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 15:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372189936375-176</Id><Title>Mr Weaver huffed and pumped today. Earned his keep.</Title><Msg>stock is up 1%. LOL. Thank gawd no analyst bad mouthed the pig.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372189936375</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 15:52:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372190763640-177</Id><Topic><Title>Full court press</Title><Username>newbee8801</Username><Timestamp>1372182098845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:41:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Volume still low but price is advancing. Wonder how long before the shorts start to capitulate?</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1372190763640</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372190913494-178</Id><Topic><Title>What a bunch of psychopaths you guys are</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372182567715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly. I originally got in in the 19's, 20's and low 21's, have held for 2 years and now am averaged just over 19, will be averaged just under 19 by the end of the year, around 18 end of next year, etc...One transaction, tons of Dividends and future stock price growth. The Bill Davis' and Jerry Blowsmen's of the world can't do that and hate hearing of anyone that does.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372190913494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372191080502-179</Id><Topic><Title>Full court press</Title><Username>newbee8801</Username><Timestamp>1372182098845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:41:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not yet. The short interest increased by 5.5 mil shares from 224 mil shares to 229 mil shares during the first 10 trading days of June. 6/14/2013 229,596,305 5/31/2013 224,423,045</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372191080502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:11:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372191256536-180</Id><Topic><Title>Mr Weaver huffed and pumped today. Earned his keep.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372189936375</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 15:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pity Waldo, in over 3 years, has ridden INTC from 24.00 to 23.90, 80 hour self employed work weeks and nothing of consequence to show for it. underperformed the SMH today as the stocks that were truly oversold, tsm, armh, bounced even higher.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372191256536</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:14:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372191428087-181</Id><Topic><Title>Full court press</Title><Username>newbee8801</Username><Timestamp>1372182098845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:41:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The Motley Fool has joined the BS with ARM and INTC getting into a price war. " I noticed that too - wanted to ask them who is the real fool here but I did not bother</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372191428087</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372191569613-182</Id><Title>How bout dem' Boston Bruins !!?????//</Title><Msg>ROFL! Epic COLLAPSE in the final minute.............EPIC! LOL!!!!!! aseijlfasdk;lfjadsk;lfjasldkfjdsklfjdslkfjd</Msg><Username>backpain_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1372191569613</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:19:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372191873645-183</Id><Title>Alexander</Title><Msg>there is an article about die size and margin using the die count caculator you mentioned a while ago. Why do you think the difference in layout ? Haswell 4:1 width: height and Baytrail 1:1 A 1:1 ratio gives slightly more dies per wafer compared to 4:1; what could be reason(s) to use 4:1 instead of 1:1?</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372191873645</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:24:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372192611649-184</Id><Title>POLL: Wallis Weaver's Intel average stock price is:</Title><Msg>A) 30 B) 35 C) 40 D) Higher E) No average, he's a paid shill</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372192611649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:36:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372192989890-185</Id><Topic><Title>POLL: Wallis Weaver's Intel average stock price is:</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372192611649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:36:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paid shill.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372192989890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:43:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372193006491-186</Id><Topic><Title>POLL: Wallis Weaver's Intel average stock price is:</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372192611649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:36:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm in at $30 and this stock will hit $20 before $30 so I will be greeting at Walmart until I'm 70! Maybe I can do adult diaper commercials. I have blown a couple of diapers this week already.</Msg><Username>wallyweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372193006491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:43:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372193731017-187</Id><Topic><Title>Shills: Spin, Spin, Spin</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370286408803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:06:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep yo pimp hand strong! ooops I just wet myself.</Msg><Username>wallyweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372193731017</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:55:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372193876542-188</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372180645386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More specifically it will take strong revenue growth with great gross margins to bump the stock. Rising revenue with only mediocre margins will simply add fuel to the argument that Intel can't compete in mobile. Hence, it becomes more important to jettison projects that are dead weight.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372193876542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:57:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372194187456-189</Id><Title>Intel going backwards</Title><Msg>Just like its thinking. Boneheads all</Msg><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1372194187456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 17:03:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372194246642-190</Id><Topic><Title>Intel going backwards</Title><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1372194187456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 17:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>speak for yourself, bonebrain.</Msg><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372194246642</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 17:04:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372194975006-191</Id><Topic><Title>Alexander</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372191873645</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:24:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haswell is like that because Ivy Bridge and Sandy Bridge were laid out that way. It would have to do with the dimensions of the Quad Cores (side by side) and the dimension of the GPU. Looking at the Haswell die photo map, there even appears to be some blank space below one of the cores near the middle of the die.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372194975006</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 17:16:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372197963065-192</Id><Title>Intels new CEO no better than the last one</Title><Msg>Stock price down, not a word from him and no Dividend increase. Sell this blitch.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372197963065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 18:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372198513327-193</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372180645386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"More specifically it will take strong revenue growth with great gross margins to bump the stock. Rising revenue with only mediocre margins will simply add fuel to the argument that Intel can't compete in mobile. Hence, it becomes more important to jettison projects that are dead weight." [The stock has moved up by $4.65 since November without any of the things you state as being required. And there you go again with the religious zealotry on the web TV project...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372198513327</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 18:15:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372201056090-194</Id><Title>Wi-Fi Woes in New MacBook Airs Latest Blemish for Apple</Title><Msg>Apple’s latest revision to its super popular line of MacBook Air notebook computers garnered mostly rave reviews, but customers are finding that a cutting-edge wireless feature may not be ready for widespread use. Yahoo Newsroom The new line, on sale since June 10, includes the very latest flavor of Wi-Fi, known as 802.11ac. The ‘ac’ standard is supposed to allow wireless connections up to three times faster than the previous 802.11n standard. But Apple customers have posted hundreds of messages on the MacBook Air discussion section of the company’s web site, complaining about mysterious disconnections and slow service. Some say they have had their laptops replaced by Apple or been contacted by Apple engineers working to isolate the problem. The web site 9to5Mac reported that Apple stores have been given a directive to “capture” misbehaving MacBook Airs brought in for service. Apple has not issued a statement yet. Problems seem most acute for customers connecting to older Wi-Fi base stations, and some have resolved the issue by updating the firmware on these stations. It’s a given that Wi-Fi connectivity is one of the top features laptop buyers need. And the rising volume of complaints comes at a difficult time for Apple, which is trying to prove to investors that it can regain momentum. Apple shares dipped below $400 on Monday for the first time since December 2011, and have lost 25% so far this year, despite a massive buyback and dividend plan announced in April. Another misstep won’t help regain investor confidence. The Wi-Fi snafu also raises memories of Apple’s last major wireless fiasco – the iPhone 4 reception controversy known as Antennagate. Within days after the iPhone 4 was released in June 2010, customers started complaining about lost reception if they held their hand over parts of the phone. Then-CEO Steve Jobs famously sent off one of his terse emails, advising users to “just avoid holding it that way.” But “Antennagat</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1372201056090</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 18:57:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372203988091-195</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372180645386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Investors want to see real revenue growth with attractive profit. At least Haswell is real and has launched and not surprisingly delivers obvious benefits over the competition. As a result of Intel's chip roadmap Intel's shares should do well but if for some reason Haswell, Bay Trail, or Merrifield fail to get traction in the marketplace that $4.65 bump will vanish in an instant. It's the reality of business.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372203988091</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 19:46:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372206434778-196</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Mini Rumors: Tablet with Intel Atom Microprocessor to Launch During Q4 of 2013, Says Analyst</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372188855274</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 15:34:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would like to see them stay with ASUS. It's a good company with a solid product. If I can get a full Win 8 version of a 8" tablet with all day battery life, I just found my new e-reader/couch-based news reader. Bonus if I can connect to my desktop and TV wirelessly.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372206434778</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 20:27:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372206720115-197</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372180645386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Investors want to see real revenue growth with attractive profit." [In saying this you are ignoring a factor that could raise the stock price by 50 percent. P/E ratio. Intel's P/E ratio deserves to be 50 percent higher. How do we know? The 14 buck drop in ARM tells us so. Their P/E ratio loss should be and will be Intel's gain...] "At least Haswell is real and has launched and not surprisingly delivers obvious benefits over the competition. As a result of Intel's chip roadmap Intel's shares should do well but if for some reason Haswell, Bay Trail, or Merrifield fail to get traction in the marketplace that $4.65 bump will vanish in an instant." [If Intel had gone to $30+ in reaction to the ARM drop, then I would agree with you. But at $23.88, no way...] "It's the reality of business." [Sound more like the reality of scare tactics...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372206720115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 20:32:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372210561912-198</Id><Title>BYOD Enterprise trending forward</Title><Msg>Per WSJ, CIOs are approving people bringing their own devices to work. This will serve to accelerate the global shift from traditional PCs to low cost options. The enterprise has always been a stronghold for the en-masse sale of Intel based PCs. Seems like even here people are for simple.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1372210561912</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 21:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372211162115-199</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Mini Rumors: Tablet with Intel Atom Microprocessor to Launch During Q4 of 2013, Says Analyst</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372188855274</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 15:34:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it can dual boot android, I'll buy in in a heart beat. I am using Nexus 7, and there are still plenty of website and video it can't open with Chrome.</Msg><Username>only_paper_money</Username><Timestamp>1372211162115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 21:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372211351201-200</Id><Topic><Title>BYOD Enterprise trending forward</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1372210561912</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 21:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It might be good for checking emails, hardly for serious Excel, Word, Programing, image processing, circuit engineering and the list go on and on. heck even a paid shill would prefers a PC to post his bs. lol, right khitch?! Surface Pro is a different story, but then again the screen size is way too small to be productive.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1372211351201</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 21:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372212609785-201</Id><Title>Intel links many screens into a giant, wireless display</Title><Msg>Intel links many screens into a giant, wireless display The so-called Display as a Service technology turns a wall of displays into a single giant screen James Niccolai (IDG News Service) 25 June, 2013 23:40 Intel has shown a wireless technology it's cooking up in its labs that's supposed to make displays of all kinds more flexible and useful. The technology allows a single screen image, such as a video playing on a laptop, to be shown on a whole wall of displays all working in unison, so that a piece of the original image is shown on each display. That type of setup is sometimes used at concerts to show a large image of the action on stage, or in a department store for advertising. But the displays typically must be connected with a jumble of HDMI or DVI video cables. [ Get served with the latest developments on data centres and servers in Computerworld's Storage newsletter ] Intel's technology works wirelessly. It essentially "virtualizes" the pixels on a display, separating them from the underlying hardware so that they can be sent via Wi-Fi and reassembled on other screens for viewing. Intel calls the technology Display as a Service, or DaaS, and it was one of several projects on show at an Intel research event in San Francisco on Tuesday. Technologies exist today that can mirror a display wirelessly onto another screen. They include Intel's own WiDi (Wireless Display Interface). But those systems can connect only two screens, while DaaS can operate among a potentially limitless number of screens, said Greg Leeming, program director for the Intel Visual Computing Institute.</Msg><Username>khitchdumb</Username><Timestamp>1372212609785</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:10:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372212653065-202</Id><Topic><Title>Intel links many screens into a giant, wireless display</Title><Username>khitchdumb</Username><Timestamp>1372212609785</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:10:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As well as taking the image on one display and breaking it up across multiple other screens, DaaS can also work in the reverse fashion -- taking the displays from several laptops and showing them side by side on a single, larger screen. That might be useful for collaborating at work, according to Intel. Four people could walk into a conference room and each have their laptop display appear on a big TV screen, for example, so they could all see what's on each other's computers. In both cases, the technology uses the H.264 video compression standard to compress what's on a display so that it can then be sent wirelessly to other screens. It also uses Internet Protocol-based networking software to tell the video where to send itself across the network and how to reassemble itself. The software includes additional metadata that tells the video things like how many screens it will be displayed on and how they are spaced relative to each other, so that the resulting image appears as a coherent whole, without gaps or distortion. DaaS is a joint project of the Intel Visual Computing Institute, the German Research Center for Artificial Intelligence (DFKI) and the Computer Graphics and Telecommunication chairs at Germany's Saarland University. Intel didn't say if or when it might offer the technology commercially. If it does, DaaS will probably be offered in the form of an API (application programming interface) and a chipset to be used in displays such as TVs. The displays in the network would all need to be IP-enabled - as many modern TVs are -- and they would need a piece of software installed so they can take part in the network of displays.</Msg><Username>khitchdumb</Username><Timestamp>1372212653065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:10:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372212808695-203</Id><Title>Intel set to sell set to box Internet TV this year</Title><Msg>Chip giant Intel rolling out set-top box Internet TV service Intel, the world’s largest semiconductor maker, plans to offer pay television through a set-top box with Web connections, creating new competition for incumbent providers like Time Warner Cable and DirecTV. By Cliff Edwards Intel said it plans to begin selling a set-top box offering Internet-based television service this year and is confident it can obtain programming. Eric Free, a vice president and general manager of the Santa Clara, Calif.-based chip-maker, outlined plans for the product and service Tuesday at the TV of Tomorrow conference in San Francisco. “Ultimately we want to deliver a better form of television,” Free said. “We’re very confident we’ll get the content we need to launch later this year.” Intel, the world’s largest semiconductor maker, plans to offer pay television through Web connections, creating new competition for incumbent providers like Time Warner Cable and DirecTV. Intel has been testing the service among employees as it seeks programming from media companies such as Time Warner, Comcast NBC Universal and Viacom.</Msg><Username>khitchdumb</Username><Timestamp>1372212808695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:13:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372212811006-204</Id><Title>Microsoft gets first corporate customer for the Surface RT!</Title><Msg>theregisterDOTcoDOTuk/2013/06/25/microsoft_spins_arm_story/ Here's some excepts: Microsoft has produced the name of a corporate customer in a fresh attempt to convince us Windows 8 is being adopted by businesses. Unfortunately, and in a sign of just how desperate things have really become, that customer is ARM - one of Microsoft's co-conspirators on Windows RT and Surface RT. .... With a straight face Microsoft told the opening of its TechEd conference Tuesday that Surface RT is allowing ARM's IT troops "to work more efficiently with features such as live tiles and notifications while being virtually always on and always connected." For those with short memories, which seems to include Microsoft's PR and marketing, Surface RT and Windows RT were built specifically to run on ARM in the first place. The closest Microsoft's announcement comes to conceding this is a sub clause in a sentence that mentions that Surface RT with Windows RT "utilizes an ARM-based chip"."</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372212811006</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372212953576-205</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to sell set to box Internet TV this year</Title><Username>khitchdumb</Username><Timestamp>1372212808695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:13:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The company hopes to build a customer base on par with satellite services, Free said. DirecTV had 20.1 million customers at year end, while Dish Network had 14.1 million, according to company reports. Intel hasn’t provided pricing details yet. Consumers increasingly view TV on their own schedule, wherever they are, Free said. They would prefer an experience at home where they don’t have to wade through hundreds of channels and can purchase and view shows based on their interests, he said. “One of the places where innovation really hasn’t happened, at least not at the pace of your phone, your tablet or your laptop, is really within the pay-TV stack,” Free said. With its own set-top box, Intel is betting it can create a flexible service that gives subscribers more choices over the channels they receive and better ways to navigate content, Erik Huggers, general manager of Intel Media, said in February. Intel plans to offer live channels and on-demand programming. Time Warner Cable and other pay-TV operators are offering incentives to media companies to withhold content from Web-based entertainment services such as the one Intel is pursuing, people with knowledge of the matter said this month. The incentives can take the form of higher payments, or they can include threats to drop programming, the people said then. Networks such as Time Warner’s CNN, NBC Universal’s USA Network and Viacom’s MTV would give Intel critical mass to offer consumers an alternative to established pay-TV services.</Msg><Username>khitchdumb</Username><Timestamp>1372212953576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:15:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372213029995-206</Id><Topic><Title>BYOD Enterprise trending forward</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1372210561912</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 21:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read the article on AnandTech: "Ask AnandTech: Tablets at Work, What are Your Experiences?" A very interesting piece by Anand Shimpi. He asks his readers to comment on their experiences and opinions on using tablets at work. Most of the comments seem to indicate that the tablet is not an ideal form-factor at work. If used it would have to be docked and used with external monitor/keyboard/mouse. Others talk about using tablets when it is part of a hybrid form-factor. The Surface Pro was mentioned quite often. I also got the sense that most prefer to use Windows 8 in the work environment. Also, quite a bit of readers mentioned that have been waiting on Haswell.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372213029995</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372214186092-207</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to sell set to box Internet TV this year</Title><Username>khitchdumb</Username><Timestamp>1372212808695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:13:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Barron's article: "WITHOUT GIVING TOO MUCH AWAY, the user interface seemed to hover beautifully above the currently playing show. An elegant simple menu made it easy to switch between channels or to pick and rent a recent film. It was light years from the cumbersome garbage that takes up most of the screen when using a standard cable-channel picker. There was a wide array of popular channels to choose from that would be familiar to any couch potato, though the final lineup is still being formulated. Equally important, when you hit the button on the remote, the TV seemed to jump to the next channel faster than is typical on cable. There also is a time-shifting aspect that goes beyond DVR, allowing you to go back through recent episodes." One wonders: Why hasn't TV always been this way? Others who've viewed the project are enthusiastic, too. "The No. 1 thing I noticed was speed," says Patrick Moorhead of Moor Insights &amp; Strategy. Intel's horsepower in the set-top is partially responsible for this, but multiple data centers that Intel is building to serve video also were a factor. "A lot of the value comes from what they've done on the back end," says Moorhead. "They have the highest-performance Intel servers and video-encoding technology." And he notes, "This is live television," unlike other over-the-top offerings, like those from the TV network consortium Hulu, Apple's (AAPL) AppleTV, Netflix (NFLX), or closely held Roku, which merely provide on-demand content from a back catalog. "It's something I've never experienced before" in an Internet offering, Moorhead adds.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372214186092</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:36:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372216789458-208</Id><Topic><Title>BYOD Enterprise trending forward</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1372210561912</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 21:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BYOD is mostly iPads, iPhones. Enterprises usage wise are quite narrow. They can also afford a full custom app. iPhone and iPad app apps are the trend for this.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1372216789458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 23:19:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372217009819-209</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confident It Will Obtain Programs for Internet TV Service</Title><Username>maxactionjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372180645386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here, here. the Wallis Weaver show coming to a set top box near you, the sure way to fame and fortune, pump INTC at 24 in 2010 on it's way to 17, hold on, what else can a pumper do, soar to 29. too early to take profits, good for 30, drop to 26, no problem, the elevator back up will take it back to new highs,drop to 19 instead, no problem, then soars to 21.70, before a drop back to 20, back to 26 at a market peak, no problem, drop back under 24.00, the markets stupid. Years and years of nonstop pumping and getting nowhere fast. But never fear, there will never be a bear market ever again, buy all the cyclical chip stocks you can and never ever sell.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372217009819</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 23:23:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372217106804-210</Id><Topic><Title>BYOD Enterprise trending forward</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1372210561912</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 21:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, the trend is towards Hybrid devices running Windows 8 that is compatible with all current company software. Intel has a lock on this trend.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372217106804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 23:25:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372218315582-211</Id><Title>Catalyst for tomorrow.. Microsoft will unveil Windows 8.1 for testing.</Title><Msg>Just being ahead of Mr Weaver here.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372218315582</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 23:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>