<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-26"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361855561322-1</Id><Title>ALTR @ MS 2/25 12:45,,,So we gain quite a bit of competitive advantage doing that.</Title><Msg>check it out Ronald J. Pasek - Chief Financial Officer, Principal Accounting Officer and Senior Vice President No, in fact, because we're -- the significance of being 3 nodes ahead is when you compare the size of us currently say a 28-nanometer FPGA to a 90-nanometer ASIC, they're almost identical in size. So we don't have a cost disadvantage anymore. When we're 4 nodes ahead, the size of a, say 20-nanometer FPGA to a 90-nanometer ASIC, the size of the FPGA would actually be smaller so we'd have a cost advantage. And because it's smaller we'd even have -- further mitigate the power disadvantage still being a general-purpose device. Okay. So you asked me questions and this just happened to work out this way. So we just had a press announcement about 5 minutes ago. Honestly, we didn't plan it this way. I knew I'd be onstage but only until -- only last week. So we had a major announcement today that we'll be building our next generation high-performance FPGA at 14 nanometers with Intel. So obviously, we're going to be at breakthrough levels of performance and power efficiencies. Intel's product at 14 uses their tri-gate technology, which is their second generation of FinFET technology. So we gain quite a bit of competitive advantage doing that. We still are going to be building a 20-nanometer plainer device with TSMC, but we will also have this 14-nanometer device.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361855561322</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 00:12:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361856174942-2</Id><Topic><Title>ALTR @ MS 2/25 12:45,,,So we gain quite a bit of competitive advantage doing that.</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361855561322</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 00:12:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously they don't want to #$%$ off TSMC but that's pretty blunt - and high end FPGA are NOT low margin business So obviously, we're going to be at breakthrough levels of performance and power efficiencies. Intel's product at 14 uses their tri-gate technology, which is their second generation of FinFET technology. So we gain quite a bit of competitive advantage doing that. We still are going to be building a 20-nanometer plainer device with TSMC, but we will also have this 14-nanometer device.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361856174942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 00:22:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361857083805-3</Id><Title>INTC to foundry biggest fish in ponds only</Title><Msg>Intel signs exclusive deal with Altera who is biggest in FPGA. Next up Cisco...then Apple or Google. Whoever signs will have distinct advantage.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361857083805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 00:38:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361857469455-4</Id><Title>TSMC/Samsung?Glofo 16/14nm FinFet + 20nm chip</Title><Msg>Couple weeks ago East was raving about Samsung taping out 14nm FinFet and noe of thge spread sheet monkeys/analysts questioned him or pointed out it is a 20nm chip - they just don't know... The analysts buy it but ALTR (and other chipmakers) know better Well, the most obvious reason is it's, obviously, a smaller nanometer, 14 versus 20, even though 16 is called, 16 FF, it's actually 20 nanometers. But the real key, as you get to these smaller and smaller geometries, is the need for essentially FinFET or technology that prevents transistors from arcing. And Intel's had that technology at 22 and obviously, we'll have that at 14, and it becomes increasingly important as you move down the nodes and that's the biggest reason. TSMC will have it. We feel that this was a -- those of you that talked to me before, you know that we do a constant evaluation of foundry capability, weighing a number of factors, been really open about that and at this point, we just decided this made the most sense. Keep in mind TSMC still is building all of our products and so they're still a very, very important partner to us.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361857469455</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 00:44:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361862295056-5</Id><Title>BIG day of news for INTC</Title><Msg>- LTE 4G shipping first half of 2013 - 7" Asus Fonepad announced - Altera deal The availability of the XMM 7160 is big news. We will see LTE 4G Intel-inside phones and tablets in US market this year. CloverTrail+ already far outperforms ARM right now (Antutu of around ~24000) and Merrifield by holiday season will double performance, which will far outperform even Tegra 4. For sure Intel will be inside either Apple's next iPhones and iPads...or Motorola's next generation phones and tablets. Lenovo and Asus will carry Intel-inside products for Asian market.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361862295056</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 02:04:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361862734721-6</Id><Topic><Title>Key to Intel's Web TV set-top box is WiDi</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361575496389</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 18:24:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's a big difference between Intel's WiMAX efforts and their Web TV with Widi. With WiMAX, there was no industry-wide support for the standard. Intel/Goog and Sprint wanted to be first to market with 4G, but industry did not support and went with LTE standard. Had industry gone with WiMax, Sprint would be ahead of Verizon right now. With WiDi, there is industry support for the standard. Google WiFi Alliance's Miracast, which recently announced support for WiDi. As well, Intel has recently announced that WiDi will support MiraCast in the future.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361862734721</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 02:12:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361867064452-7</Id><Topic><Title>BIG day of news for INTC</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361862295056</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 02:04:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CloverTrail+ already far outperforms ARM right now (Antutu of around ~24000) and Merrifield by holiday season will double performance, which will far outperform even Tegra 4 ---- As you can see from the benchmarks below, even Merrifield will struggle to beat Tegra 4 across all benchmarks (Not reliable sources) anandtechDOTcom/show/6787/nvidia-tegra-4-architecture-deep-dive-plus-tegra-4i-phoenix-hands-on/6 blogDOTgsmarenaDOTcom/lenovo-k900-hands-on-impressions-and-synthetic-benchmarks/ K900 (Clovertrail+) AnTuTu: 25154 Quadrant: 5248 Sunspider: 962 (lower is better) Tegra 4 AnTuTu: 36127 Quadrant: 16449 Sunspider: 506 (lower is better)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1361867064452</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 03:24:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361867880714-8</Id><Topic><Title>BIG day of news for INTC</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361862295056</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 02:04:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see that you are referencing Antutu, now that it suits your argument. As I said, Merrifield will double in performance. We will see how Tegra 4 compares to it. I'm thinking Antutu for Merrifield will be well over 40,000.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361867880714</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 03:38:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361870984557-9</Id><Topic><Title>BIG day of news for INTC</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361862295056</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 02:04:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see that you are referencing Antutu, now that it suits your argument. As I said, Merrifield will double in performance. We will see how Tegra 4 compares to it. I'm thinking Antutu for Merrifield will be well over 40,000. ---- I listed 3 benchmarks, not just Antutu. I didn't choose those benchmarks, they are the common ones from both articles.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1361870984557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 04:29:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361872021896-10</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Up 20 Cents AH</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361849998314</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 22:39:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bid shows $20.08 at yahoo.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1361872021896</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 04:47:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361876881586-11</Id><Topic><Title>BIG day of news for INTC</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361862295056</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 02:04:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think he meant Bay Trail not Merrifield as that will be the first new Atom implementation and Intel have already said it will have double CT+ performance so I don't think it will do any struggling ;-). Also what was tested above was a Tegra 4 tablet test platform which obviously does not have to be tuned power wise to be a usable tablet and which might slug those numbers you gave in a real world design. Also A15's Sunspider numbers have been all over the place depending on o/s and browser so are they under the same conditions ? It's obvious A15 can be a powerful mobile processor at times but has that come at the expense of too much power ? CT+ is a very efficient performance/power design, let's see how A15 compares in a real world phone for battery usage when it is asked to work hard for long periods of time.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1361876881586</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 06:08:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361879067166-12</Id><Topic><Title>Getandid61 wet dream</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361831712322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 17:35:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MIPS64 chips found their niche in broadband/network chips. I have a lot of time and respect for what MIPS has done in the computing industry from the early very high ipc 64-bit SGI implementations to the later many-core many-thread implementations by Netlogic, Broadcom, Cavium etc. These guys just quietly work in the background without hype and bragging and just let their chips do the talking. This to me is a more dangerous and advanced architecture competitor to Intel than ARM is but I am beginning to think the only real reason MIPS was not chosen over ARM for consumer mobile was because of the strong Chinese MIPS connection and maybe Western companies just don't want to make China even stronger so they would rather reinvent the 64-bit wheel with ARM.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1361879067166</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 06:44:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361880029121-13</Id><Topic><Title>Getandid61 wet dream</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361831712322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 17:35:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This to me is a more dangerous and advanced architecture competitor to Intel than ARM is but I am beginning to think the only real reason MIPS was not chosen over ARM for consumer mobile was because of the strong Chinese MIPS connection and maybe Western companies just don't want to make China even stronger so they would rather reinvent the 64-bit wheel with ARM ------ MIPS didn't have the right cores at the right time (ie, 32 bit core). As a side, until recently MIPS didn't have it's own 64 bit cores (other than the ones from a decade ago), so all the cores from Netlogic, Broadcom, Cavium are their own designs to the MIPS ISA. On paper, MIPS do have a higher performance (IPC for equivalent family) but have been let down by mismanagement and sales hype for many, many years. The ARM64 bit ISA is very similar to the MIPS ISA, so will be easier to scale for raw performance going forward.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1361880029121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:00:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361881090095-14</Id><Topic><Title>Getandid61 wet dream</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361831712322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 17:35:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'The ARM64 bit ISA is very similar to the MIPS ISA, so will be easier to scale for raw performance going forward.' It will not get the best raw performance throughput without multi-threading and absolutely nobody in the ARM world is even attempting it ! So much for world support, seems they can't find a serious micro-architectural brain cell amongst them ;-). MIPS chips (like PowerPC and Sparc) can actually have more than 2 threads per core which just shows you how advanced all the other Riscs are in it. MIPS baseband chips won sockets based on transaction throughput so the theoretical advantage has been proven in the real world no matter how many excuses East trots out for his ARM chip's deficiencies.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1361881090095</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:18:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361881854328-15</Id><Topic><Title>Getandid61 wet dream</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361831712322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 17:35:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Riscs have been promising to take x86 (and that other great Cisc, IBM Mainframes) down for over 30 years now and still x86 (and IBM Mainframes) march on ;-). You are basically wishing and hoping on a star here without giving a single valid reason why ARM will succeed where much better quality Riscs have tried and failed and don't give me that cheap ubiquitous nonsense because Intel will price all of you out of business with its cheap skus considering it holds the high asp ground and is bankrolled by its top skus. You know, it really only has to keep AMD alive to satisfy monopoly concerns not ARM ;-) ---- much better quality Riscs eh? Like who?:) The ARM (32bit) ISA is one of those things, you love it or hate it, but it's great for embedded programming which is one of the key reasons why it's so popular. The ARM64 bit ISA is new and is not for hand crafted assembly of the tiny embedded world. It shares many of the features that come from other big RISC family's over the years, but with little of the crud that can be built up by additions to the ISA over time. Without going into technical reasons, as I see it, there are three advantages of ARM64 over any of the previous 'big' RISC family's: Multiple designs from different firms (ARM, Applied Micro, Broadcom, Cavium, Nvidia etc) SoC based design (IO fabrics, GPU's on die etc) Open OS support (unlike the proprietary OS's Solaris, AIX &amp; HPUX of the day) ARM64 will succeed, for no other reason that it'll be used in deeply embedded applications (from Broadcom, Cavium and others). Will anyone build a high performance ARM64 core that could take on Intel or other big iron providers in CPU heavy workloads? The ISA does make it 'easy' to build for performance, but so far, other than the mythical project Denver at Nvidia, all the designs I've seen announced are low power (and low performance/low cost) designs. Intel's core server business is safe:) The ARM (32bit) ISA is one of those things, you love it or hate it, but it's great for embedded programming which is one of the key reasons why it's so popular. The ARM64 bit ISA is new and is not for hand crafted assembly writing and as such shares many of the features that come from other big RISC family's over the years, but with little of the crud that can be built up by additions to the ISA over time.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1361881854328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:30:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361882240330-16</Id><Title>Intel revolution had started yesterday</Title><Msg>With this bunch of the great news released past 24H, INTC will fill the gap between 27.5$ to 27.74$ range very fast! INTC competitors are toast!</Msg><Username>gainerys</Username><Timestamp>1361882240330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:37:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361882667707-17</Id><Title>WALLIS-</Title><Msg>What is it that you don't understand about the FACTS that PCS are dead INTC missed the mobile boat the Ultrabook failed INTC stack has been unchanged for more than 10 years.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1361882667707</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:44:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361882688059-18</Id><Topic><Title>Getandid61 wet dream</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361831712322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 17:35:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You overstate the importance of multi-threading at the chip level:) In MIPS case, it's threaded designs weren't big licence winners as they really only had an impact on certain work loads (such as heavy IO bound workloads [such as network packet processing]). Intel are dropping multi-threading in their phone based SoC's at 22nm for the same reason why ARM haven't including it - it uses power. It's cheaper from a power perceptive to have 2 cores rather than 1 core/1 hyper threaded as you can turn one core totally off, while in the threaded core you have to keep more of the chip active to maintain those 2 (hardware) threads. It's a balancing act between performance, power and die size, and it seems that Intel agrees with ARM (in the phone SoC space at least) :)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1361882688059</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:44:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361882703050-19</Id><Topic><Title>Intel revolution had started yesterday</Title><Username>gainerys</Username><Timestamp>1361882240330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>elaborate pleae? tegra 4 is still getting kudos over Clover Trail + (but as Mars says, the Tegra benchmarks are on a test stand, while you can see CT+ live on the Lenovo youtube video). LTE still does not exist in smartphones. And, Altera gross revenues are under $2 Billion (and declining), which can't mean significant R for INTC in this deal. So, tell me what has dramatically changed? I am long INTC and looking for explosive upside, but I don't see it yet.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1361882703050</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:45:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361883197097-20</Id><Topic><Title>Intel revolution had started yesterday</Title><Username>gainerys</Username><Timestamp>1361882240330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't understand why anyone would be selling here. Fab business is a big deal. Intel can make lots of money renting out state of the art fabs. Chip makers who want a 2 year jump on the competition can dial up Intel and get it. Now Intel pushing deep into the mobile space with Clover Trail +. This is only the beginning by Christmas Intel will have a mobile chip that will demolish the competition.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361883197097</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:53:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361883563775-21</Id><Topic><Title>WALLIS-</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1361882667707</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:44:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is it that you don't understand about the FACTS that PCS are dead INTC missed the mobile boat the Ultrabook failed INTC stack has been unchanged for more than 10 years. ---------------------------------------------------------------------------- PC's are dead? Mine isn't. Use it everyday. Take it to Asia and Europe often..plan on buying another, and another, and another... INTC missed the Mobile boat? I think you mean "bus", and there's another bus coming along every 15 minutes. Clover Trail + is on it, with LTE, and I just wish I was Chinese so I could own a Lenovo smartphone. Most of the market is NOT USA, but China, India, etc..(I suppose you never get out of New Jersey, so you wouldn't know these things). INTC has cleverly targeted them, since AAPL doesn't have the strong foothold there. But, a smartphone bus to the USA will be along in another 15 minutes. Ultrabook failed? Gosh, the ones I tried at B-buy were all working, really well, and I had to fight a crowd to touch them...no one at the AAPL display.. My next PC will be an Ultrabook. INTC stack? What's that? Flat stock, but Divvy is WAY WAY up!!! I like buying cheap and getting a BIG DIVVY! Sort of like taking candy from idiots. You really aren't so funny, Tooofunny...but you are tooooostupid.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1361883563775</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:59:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361885358256-22</Id><Title>Considerable Upgrade for INTC. Read Now!</Title><Msg>If or when you are looking for information concerning the stock market, then you might as well take a look at this.. winningstocksDOTorg/-INTC</Msg><Username>charleslouie274</Username><Timestamp>1361885358256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 08:29:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361885541469-23</Id><Topic><Title>Getandid61 wet dream</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361831712322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 17:35:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Intel are dropping multi-threading in their phone based SoC's at 22nm for the same reason why ARM haven't including it - it uses power. ' You have made a lot of assumptions based on one slide. Firstly Bay Trail is a tablet design not a phone design and secondly I don't believe Android yet supports 8 core threads all working at the same time which maybe why HT is switched off in quad-core Bay Trail for the moment but may be present in single and dual-core Merrifield. 'It's cheaper from a power perceptive to have 2 cores rather than 1 core/1 hyper threaded as you can turn one core totally off, while in the threaded core you have to keep more of the chip active to maintain those 2 (hardware) threads.' Disagree. The RAZRi vs RAZRm comparisons clearly showed 1 hyper threaded Atom core was more power efficient than two async Krait cores. Having hyper-threading allows you the option to run at lower voltage when multi-threading as the core hardware can run at lower clock speeds and voltages when multi-tasking using its existing resources more efficiently. Intel definitely do not agree with you ... theinquirerDOTnet/inquirer/news/2182710/intel-claims-android-ready-multi-core-processors " CHIPMAKER Intel has claimed that system-on-chip (SoC) vendors have not done enough to optimise Android for multi-core processors. Intel's single-core Medfield Atom processor enters the market at time when almost all of the big hitting ARM vendors are focusing efforts on dual-core and quad-core processors. However Intel said that chip firms should do more to optimise Android for multi-core processors as it does not effectively make use of multiple cores. Although Intel's Medfield Atom processor does have pseudo multi-threading capability thanks to the firm's Hyperthreading technology, Intel still needs to defend Medfield against the obvious question of how it can compete with quad-core processors from ARM chip designers Nvidia, Qualcomm and Samsung. According to Mike Bell, GM of Intel's Mobile and Communications Group, the firm's defence is that Android's thread scheduler simply isn't ready for multi-core processors. Bell said, "If you are in a non-power constrained case, I think multiple cores make a lot of sense because you can run the cores full out, you can actually heavily load them and/or if the operating system has a good thread scheduler. A lot of stuff we are dealing with, thread scheduling and thread affinity, isn't there yet and on top of that, largely when the operating system goes to do a single task, a lot of other stuff stops. So as we move to multiple cores, we're actually putting a lot of investment into software to fix the scheduler and fix the threading so if we do multi-core products it actually takes advantage of it." Bell also claimed that Intel's internal testing had shown multi-core implementations running slower than single core, however he did not finger any particular chip. "If you take a look a lot of handsets on the market, when you turn on the second core or having the second core there [on die], the [current] leakage is high enough and their power threshold is low enough because of the size of the case that it isn't entirely clear you get much of a benefit to turning the second core on. We ran our own numbers and [in] some of the use cases we've seen, having a second core is actually a detriment, because of the way some of the people have not implemented their thread scheduling." Later Bell said that for some chip vendors he isn't certain what advantage they get from sticking multiple cores on a die. "I've taken a look at the multiple core implementations in the market, and frankly, in a thermal and/or power constrained environment - what has been implemented - it isn't obvious to me you really get the advantage for the size and the cost of what's going into that part," said Bell. Finally Bell claimed that Android doesn't make use of multi-core processors, something he thought other chip firms should work on sorting out alongside Intel. "The way it's implemented right now, Android does not make as effective use of multiple cores as it could, and I think - frankly - some of this work could be done by the vendors who create the SoCs, but they just haven't bothered to do it." Bell ended with a parting shot at other chip vendors, saying that their lack of work to improve Android's multi-threading support is what's holding performance back. "Right now the lack of software effort by some of the folks who have done their hardware implementation is a bigger disadvantage than anything else," said Bell. Bell wouldn't give a date, or even a year when Intel will bring out multi-core Atom processors, but given that he said Intel is working on Android's thread scheduling and handling, it is safe to say that there will be a multi-core Atom chip sooner rather than later. µ"</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1361885541469</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 08:32:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361886281595-24</Id><Topic><Title>Intel revolution had started yesterday</Title><Username>gainerys</Username><Timestamp>1361882240330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra 4 is nothing compare to the 22nm next Atom generation, this is obvious Intel is not far behind like it was year ago but start competition with the high end mobile chips, next 22nm phase will be smasher for competitors, load the boat as long Intel is with this low price.</Msg><Username>gainerys</Username><Timestamp>1361886281595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 08:44:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361886842663-25</Id><Topic><Title>Key to Intel's Web TV set-top box is WiDi</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361575496389</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 18:24:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WiDi may be a standard but its inclusion in Intel's Web TV is not particularly important to the service the device is intended to deliver - which is delivering video content from the box to the TV or other devices. WiDi is short range and intended to be used for devices in the same room, as a potential cable replacement. However, HDMI performs superbly, is built-in to every video device today and doesn't have WiDi's latency problems. WiDi is also not a solution to distributing video material to other parts of the house. WiDi adapters for TV have been available for some time now but virtually no one buys them. WiDi is included because its technology baked into Intel's chipsets, it's just along for the ride.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1361886842663</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 08:54:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361886897169-26</Id><Topic><Title>Intel revolution had started yesterday</Title><Username>gainerys</Username><Timestamp>1361882240330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Intel decided to get into the foundry business for 1 main reason, but the side benefit is equally compelling: (1) The main reason is that Intel needed to advance its process technologies rapidly at huge capex. It needed to make sure that there is enough demand (its own x86 combined with other chips) for its huge factories. (2) The side benefit is that it will take cut off the air supply from the current foundries (especially TSMC) who have been helping Intel competitors make ARM-based chips without huge capex budgets. Especially as they move towards 22/20nm and beyond, capex is huge - with fewer large customers fabbing at their foundries, there will be increased pressure on the current foundries to slow down their capex or spread it amongst their customers. Both of which will hit the current foundries and fabless companies hard. IMO, both these reasons advanced Intel's move into the foundry business. There is really no downside for Intel in doing so.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1361886897169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 08:54:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361887155692-27</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>referancesdelores</Username><Timestamp>1361794083482</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 07:08:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job. Informational article.</Msg><Username>nedyelestela</Username><Timestamp>1361887155692</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 08:59:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361887288878-28</Id><Topic><Title>Intel revolution had started yesterday</Title><Username>gainerys</Username><Timestamp>1361882240330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another indirect benefit of the foundry relationships is that it creates a huge ecosystem of companies aligned with Intel and making products that compliment Intel's products. The message it sends is that you will either be "with them [the Intel ecosystem], or against them" and the "with them" crowd will have the world's best technology.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1361887288878</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:01:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361887323574-29</Id><Topic><Title>WALLIS-</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1361882667707</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:44:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at poor DWEEB Lucy still trying to convince Wally to go negative on Intel. Hey buddy, you're a NOBODY. What an idiot.</Msg><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1361887323574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:02:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361887912409-30</Id><Topic><Title>Getandid61 wet dream</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361831712322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 17:35:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have made a lot of assumptions based on one slide. Firstly Bay Trail is a tablet design not a phone design and secondly I don't believe Android yet supports 8 core threads all working at the same time which maybe why HT is switched off in quad-core Bay Trail for the moment but may be present in single and dual-core Merrifield. ---- Yes, was a single slide, and from memory I thought it was the phone SoC. I could be wrong on that score. The kernel of Android is Linux, and has no problem with 8 (running) threads. Thread scheduling issue's aside. The real problem is a lack of workloads that would use 8 threads (let alone 4 threads). ---- Disagree. The RAZRi vs RAZRm comparisons clearly showed 1 hyper threaded Atom core was more power efficient than two async Krait cores. Having hyper-threading allows you the option to run at lower voltage when multi-threading as the core hardware can run at lower clock speeds and voltages when multi-tasking using its existing resources more efficiently ---- I disagree on your on the RAZRi vs RAZRm comparisons:) but my point was not about running multi-threaded code, but single threaded code. If you had two identical SoC's, one with 2 real cores and 1 real/hyper threaded (with the same CPU Arch [ie, x86] and revision), then when running single threaded code, the 2 core SoC solution would use less power as it's lighting up fewer transistors as code flows through the CPU (assuming the second core can be turn totally off and the threaded logic can be turned off). The 2 core SoC (would be larger) and use more power when running 2 threads but it would also be more performant than the 1/1 core SoC in this situation. It's all about balance and the workload being run.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1361887912409</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:11:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361887979618-31</Id><Topic><Title>Gutless Alexander exposed</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361850475880</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 22:47:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gutless hypocrite skunk. Shake my head.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1361887979618</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:12:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361888574972-32</Id><Topic><Title>Breakout on INTC</Title><Username>barbourticiara81</Username><Timestamp>1361545250780</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:00:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let me try this.</Msg><Username>psavoydailey40</Username><Timestamp>1361888574972</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:22:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361888583376-33</Id><Topic><Title>Altera first to use TSMC 20nm - 9/14/2012 ...mmh</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361830259273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 17:10:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read it again and think "sarcasm" and "dumb analysts making up stupid, ignorant junk". Sorry. I thought it was sort of obvious.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1361888583376</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:23:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361888788870-34</Id><Topic><Title>Altera first to use TSMC 20nm - 9/14/2012 ...mmh</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361830259273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 17:10:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FAIL</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1361888788870</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:26:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361889038675-35</Id><Title>Subject</Title><Msg>Type message</Msg><Username>goldfinder843</Username><Timestamp>1361889038675</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:30:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361889057481-36</Id><Title>ILNS - to give presentation at BIOEUROPE in Barcelona March 11-13</Title><Msg>mover!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>goldfinder843</Username><Timestamp>1361889057481</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:30:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361889134058-37</Id><Topic><Title>Getandid61 wet dream</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361831712322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 17:35:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was a Bay Trail slide and that is the tablet SoC, Merrifield will be the phone SoC. I see what you are saying now about single-thread but even that may not be true as another core will still have significant leakage current even when switched 'off' and the thermal penalty for having an unused 2nd thread facility on a core is not high as it is the actual execution of the 2nd thread which burns the power.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1361889134058</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:32:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361889284844-38</Id><Topic><Title>Gutless Alexander exposed</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361850475880</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 22:47:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure what you are talking about. If you are referring to my sarcastic post about FPGA's and analysts making up ignorant stuff, then you are just waiting to cast your insults for the wrong reason. I thought my sarcasm was extreme enough that it was obvious. Obviously, I was wrong. 1. I am not a Saint and want people to verify what I say. I make mistakes. 2. I am long Intel shares in my account, IRA and kids accounts. 3. I am short Intel put options and rolling them out. 4. I am long ARM put options for July $40. 5. I think that Intel is a great company and has made many contributions. 6. I think has made some mistakes but will recover (see #2 &amp; #3)</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1361889284844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:34:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361890533523-39</Id><Topic><Title>Read this now -Intel Corporation(INTC)</Title><Username>brooksterrell60</Username><Timestamp>1361890111890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:48:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>best out there</Msg><Username>sneeddavid381</Username><Timestamp>1361890533523</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:55:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361890572162-40</Id><Title>INTEL UPGRADED FROM SELL TO HOLD WITH A TARGET OF $22</Title><Msg>THAT IS TOOOOOOOOOO TOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!!! NO MENTION OF "GOOD FOR $30" OR "INTC IS A $40 STOCK" HI=HO WEAVERINO!!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1361890572162</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:56:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361890598431-41</Id><Topic><Title>Gutless Alexander exposed</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361850475880</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 22:47:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh so you hurling sarcastic insults at analysts is ok but I'm a lesser person when I hurl insults. Got it... the liberal way. Preach what you practice rather than practicing what you preach.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1361890598431</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:56:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361890660315-42</Id><Topic><Title>Read this now -Intel Corporation(INTC)</Title><Username>brooksterrell60</Username><Timestamp>1361890111890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:48:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fantastic info on report</Msg><Username>frederick.casarez</Username><Timestamp>1361890660315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:57:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361891185730-43</Id><Topic><Title>Read this now -Intel Corporation(INTC)</Title><Username>brooksterrell60</Username><Timestamp>1361890111890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:48:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looking good</Msg><Username>bakerluis14</Username><Timestamp>1361891185730</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:06:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361891706356-44</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL UPGRADED FROM SELL TO HOLD WITH A TARGET OF $22</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1361890572162</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:56:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ANALyst went all out on that upgrade. It's really hard to admit when you are wrong, but 22 is a start.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1361891706356</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:15:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361891801513-45</Id><Topic><Title>Read this now -Intel Corporation(INTC)</Title><Username>brooksterrell60</Username><Timestamp>1361890111890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:48:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good potential</Msg><Username>jstamperq</Username><Timestamp>1361891801513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:16:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361891922244-46</Id><Topic><Title>Considerable Upgrade for INTC. Read Now!</Title><Username>charleslouie274</Username><Timestamp>1361885358256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 08:29:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes it is</Msg><Username>royjonathon</Username><Timestamp>1361891922244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:18:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361892106060-47</Id><Topic><Title>Altera first to use TSMC 20nm - 9/14/2012 ...mmh</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361830259273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 17:10:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trouble is that TSMC promises but Intel delivers. People badly underestimate Intel manufacturing prowess when evaluating Intel as a long term investment. There is not a better chip fab company in the world.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361892106060</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:21:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361892108036-48</Id><Topic><Title>= = Analyst Predicts Decline to 17.07 =SEE REPORT=</Title><Username>blackscott588</Username><Timestamp>1361404069367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good update.</Msg><Username>crisreed414</Username><Timestamp>1361892108036</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:21:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361892246490-49</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (INTC)</Title><Username>frankbryant786</Username><Timestamp>1361483522525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:52:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good update.</Msg><Username>crisreed414</Username><Timestamp>1361892246490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:24:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361892265544-50</Id><Title>Intel and Cisco priced the same !</Title><Msg>I think I'll trade Intel for Cisco, watch Intel go to 29 as I ride Cisco to 13, lose my mind and hurl insults on the Intel board for the rest of my wasted life. Hi Ho, TooooooooooooooFunkio !</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1361892265544</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:24:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361892412784-51</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL UPGRADED FROM SELL TO HOLD WITH A TARGET OF $22</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1361890572162</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:56:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess WW is a hero and you're toast Nuff (as usual). Better cover your short worm.</Msg><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1361892412784</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:26:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361892590432-52</Id><Topic><Title>Read this now -Intel Corporation(INTC)</Title><Username>brooksterrell60</Username><Timestamp>1361890111890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:48:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yea im in</Msg><Username>markweatherby27</Username><Timestamp>1361892590432</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:29:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361892896657-53</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL UPGRADED FROM SELL TO HOLD WITH A TARGET OF $22</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1361890572162</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:56:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel should be a $30 stock. Selling Intel down below 21 the stock is an absolute steal. No way you would get me to part with any of my shares at 22. I will be enjoying my nice divy check at the end of the week. :-)</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361892896657</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:34:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361893304121-54</Id><Title>Bought another 10K shares at $20.25 yesterday afternoon</Title><Msg>The foundry deal is huge. Intel know has a recurring revenue stream like all the other high tech "service" companies.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361893304121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:41:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361893384612-55</Id><Topic><Title>Gutless Alexander exposed</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361850475880</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 22:47:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't determine whether you are a lesser person or not. You determine your worth to yourself. You determine your worth to others by your thoughts translated into actions. You are very quick to hurl insults. The political ones are just off topic, complex and being oversimplified. I usually just add more information to "today's outrage" that you share. Notice ... no name calling or insults on my part. You will rarely (IF EVER) see me do that. I don't know you. I just know what persona you present here on this board by the words you type. By also what appears to be your aliases or others who think similarly. I think my comments about financial analysts on the Intel finance board are "OK". I think that anyone's comments on Intel finance related issues on the Intel finanace board are "OK". Including yours. "READY, FIRE, AIM."</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1361893384612</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:43:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361893388183-56</Id><Topic><Title>Gutless Alexander exposed</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361850475880</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 22:47:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gutless hypocrite skunk. Shake my head. att4glte are you already drunk like a skunk yelling at people ? High end FPGA are very good business - you did not know?</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361893388183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:43:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361893407605-57</Id><Topic><Title>Read this now -Intel Corporation(INTC)</Title><Username>brooksterrell60</Username><Timestamp>1361890111890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:48:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>listen to the masters</Msg><Username>jonesvern846</Username><Timestamp>1361893407605</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:43:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361893972964-58</Id><Title>Bottomed The Past Few days?</Title><Msg>Looks like the short squeeze has begun.</Msg><Username>vincent90157</Username><Timestamp>1361893972964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:52:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361894008303-59</Id><Title>Looks like my 21 calls might be executed...</Title><Msg>Was hoping to use them to average down, but I make money either way so it's all good...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1361894008303</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:53:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361894035563-60</Id><Topic><Title>Bought another 10K shares at $20.25 yesterday afternoon</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361893304121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:41:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you have any idea how much of a joke you have become? Get back to class, top of the hour is coming and so is your study hall more than likely.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1361894035563</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:53:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361894163968-61</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like my 21 calls might be executed...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1361894008303</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:53:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like it may have bottomed and the shorts are covering. Maybe value guys have come in the past few days. I think $21 may get touched today but holding above??</Msg><Username>vincent90157</Username><Timestamp>1361894163968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:56:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361894189242-62</Id><Topic><Title>Intel revolution had started yesterday</Title><Username>gainerys</Username><Timestamp>1361882240330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree...taking it a concrete step forward, perhaps, the foundry offering may be a very effective carrot to to transition some of the erstwhile ARM-core (or using other core) companies to transition over to x86-core - even those that are clearly not in the radar like Apple. The more offerings with x86 core, the better for Intel. Chip-heads (and I mean that as a compliment!) can perhaps comment as to value of the foundry in creating an Intel ecosystem with x86 core across a multitude of offerings - and the type of chip companies this can attract.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1361894189242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:56:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361894715658-63</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like my 21 calls might be executed...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1361894008303</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:53:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I sold March 13 calls, so they have till the 16th.... I imagine we'll be deep in the $21s by then...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1361894715658</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:05:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361895155402-64</Id><Topic><Title>Intel revolution had started yesterday</Title><Username>gainerys</Username><Timestamp>1361882240330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 07:37:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, Intel is just getting going. Clover Trail was not designed to take on the best. It was a stop gap till Bay Trail comes out. The fact that Intel in a year was able to take an aging off the shelf chip and make it competitive with most chips out there say alot about what Intel is going to do going forward. One only has to go over to AMD and ask them competitive Intel is when they decide to be. So in one year Intel is producing competitive chips in the mobile space. In another year they are producing some of the best chips out there. In 3-5 years Intel has relegated ARM to a second tier product.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361895155402</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:12:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361895480383-65</Id><Title>TSM stock does not like the news</Title><Msg>ALTR said that even in case TSMC gets FinFet working Intel/ALTR would still have a die size (shrink) advantage compared to TSMC/XLNX. Intel will have great cost advantage relative to TSMC/Samsung/Glofo FinFets because Intel seems to be able to shrink (indirectly indicated by ALTR) . Do the analysts figure this one out?</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361895480383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:18:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361895488142-66</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like my 21 calls might be executed...</Title><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1361894008303</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:53:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>13 March $21 Call contracts ... right? If so, you can roll them up at a credit and keep the shares. This AM someone is buying March $21 and selling March $22 calls. So far they have bought 7k $21 and sold 33k of the $22. They seem to be doing the same for Apr. Buying the $21 and selling the $22. Appears to be a BULL CALL SPREAD for Mar and Apr.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1361895488142</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:18:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361895699671-67</Id><Title>Ignition...</Title><Msg>Let's hope this is a lift-off.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1361895699671</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:21:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361895960356-68</Id><Topic><Title>REDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDD!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1361825616578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 15:53:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL @ the desperate little putz.</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1361895960356</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:26:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361895977766-69</Id><Topic><Title>Ignition...</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1361895699671</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:21:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dream on, smegma breath. TOOOOO FUNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1361895977766</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:26:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361896236732-70</Id><Title>So, Analysts were worried about the CAPEX ??</Title><Msg>Hmmmmmmm</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1361896236732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:30:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361896409724-71</Id><Topic><Title>REDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDD!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1361825616578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 15:53:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>same old, same old. _________ Yeah, same old same old since you bought CSCO in 2011. 2011! LOL!!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1361896409724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:33:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361896687083-72</Id><Topic><Title>I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1293550442000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-12-28 10:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My bad, it was 2010 when you bought Cisco at the same price that it's at today. 2010 ROFL @ U.</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1361896687083</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:38:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361896756809-73</Id><Topic><Title>REDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDD!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1361825616578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 15:53:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction, it was 2010 that you bought the same old Cisco shares as they are today. ROFL @ U ! 2010 ! Was Star Wars playing then?</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1361896756809</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:39:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361897226333-74</Id><Topic><Title>So, Analysts were worried about the CAPEX ??</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1361896236732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:30:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I remember the conference call distinctly. The question came up in the conference call about CAPEX. Intel answered it and analysts drew their own conclusions. The jest of the analysts conclusion is that Intel is spending money on Fabs that it didn't need. Intel said in the conference call flatly that they will need that capacity. So now we are learning the rest of the story.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361897226333</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:47:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361898276660-75</Id><Topic><Title>I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1293550442000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-12-28 10:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How's that trade treated you since 2010?</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1361898276660</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:04:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361898606710-76</Id><Topic><Title>So, Analysts were worried about the CAPEX ??</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1361896236732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:30:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not only did the analysts criticize the spending they were hyperventilating over it and promptly downgraded Intel's shares becaue they didn't understand the strategy. But this just underscores that analysts see the world as a spreadsheet isolated from the reality of competing in the real world. Don't expect to see those analysts admit their ignorance now though.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1361898606710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:10:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361898611833-77</Id><Topic><Title>= = Analyst Predicts Decline to 17.07 =SEE REPORT=</Title><Username>blackscott588</Username><Timestamp>1361404069367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very good report. thank you.</Msg><Username>mickgray446</Username><Timestamp>1361898611833</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:10:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361898796880-78</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (INTC)</Title><Username>frankbryant786</Username><Timestamp>1361483522525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:52:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very good report. thank you.</Msg><Username>mickgray446</Username><Timestamp>1361898796880</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:13:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361899242351-79</Id><Topic><Title>Bottomed The Past Few days?</Title><Username>vincent90157</Username><Timestamp>1361893972964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:52:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you referring to the vxx?</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1361899242351</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:20:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361899993429-80</Id><Topic><Title>Bottomed The Past Few days?</Title><Username>vincent90157</Username><Timestamp>1361893972964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 10:52:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Following Intel's announcement about increasing Capex during the CC, the analysts came out negative. Until we get to the next earnings CC, I doubt that there will be any short squeeze unless Intel bags a large deal as a smart phone supplier</Msg><Username>typea1948</Username><Timestamp>1361899993429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:33:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361900032443-81</Id><Topic><Title>So, Analysts were worried about the CAPEX ??</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1361896236732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:30:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's a good reason why analysts are analysts and not running companies. Intel has been doing exactly the things they need to do to take over mobility and, in fact, all of processor manufacturing. They made a bold and risky investment in FinFET that is now totally changing the competitive landscape. The ARM world went with the decidedly not bold fabless concept, thinking it to be the safe route. It turns out that it wasn't safe at all and as a result they have conceded the future to Intel. So, Intel now is putting in place huge manufacturing capability with a two process node lead. It is no surprise that companies are starting to queue up to be a part of this very significant competitive advantage. And the analysts, instead of complementing Intel for the foresight, intelligence and guts, has offered nothing but criticism. They weren't just wrong, they were screamingly wrong. And now the results start to speak for themselves. Hats off to Intel's management and their bold moves...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361900032443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:33:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361900295558-82</Id><Topic><Title>TSM stock does not like the news</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361895480383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:18:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not convinced that TSMC will easily get FinFet working. Intel played with FinFet but it has structural issues as you shrink. TSMC is right now engaged in a very risky catch up game with Intel by trying to push a die shrink before they have completely tested it. Even if they manage to get it working I doubt that they will get the yields they want. TSMC thinks they will have 14nm process by 2015 but Intel will be mass producing by 2014. So even by TSMC overly optimistic projections they are still a year behind.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361900295558</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:38:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361900326940-83</Id><Title>Don't Worry Shorts!!!</Title><Msg>There will be better and better and better opportunities for you to give your money back as the year goes on. And we know you really want to give ALL of those profits back. Otherwise why would you still be here when the stock bottomed last November. Thanks for hanging in there and don't give up yet!!! Not until your profits dwindle into the beer money category...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361900326940</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:38:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361900385942-84</Id><Title>Altera bumps it a buck, Cisco will bump it 2 bucks</Title><Msg>Mama Say Mama Saw Moo Maw Coo Saw.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1361900385942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:39:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361900423965-85</Id><Title>I don't think there will be a short squeeze on INTC, there's only a SMALL % short...</Title><Msg>If there was 10% or more short, then yeah, that be big, but less than 1% short isn't much...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1361900423965</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:40:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361900476738-86</Id><Topic><Title>TSM stock does not like the news</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361895480383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:18:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel put ten years into developing FinFET. The idea that the ARM foundries are just going to crank it out are really pretty silly - especially given how much trouble they have had with just planar on recent nodes...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361900476738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:41:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361900558256-87</Id><Topic><Title>Read this now -Intel Corporation(INTC)</Title><Username>brooksterrell60</Username><Timestamp>1361890111890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:48:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one. Subscribed just now.</Msg><Username>salvador.gertz</Username><Timestamp>1361900558256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:42:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361900847350-88</Id><Topic><Title>TSM stock does not like the news</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361895480383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:18:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Otelini said they'd never figure out FinFet, didn't he?</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1361900847350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:47:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361901043037-89</Id><Topic><Title>Don't Worry Shorts!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361900326940</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:38:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what a classic Waldo, talks about shorts giving up profits on a stock over 8.00 below it's peak last year, and still below the don't worry you'll be fine 24's..</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1361901043037</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:50:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361901212444-90</Id><Topic><Title>Don't Worry Shorts!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361900326940</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:38:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watching Wally remain postive until his final day on this earth while you chase him around the internet to no avail is even more CLASSIC.</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1361901212444</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:53:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361901872990-91</Id><Topic><Title>Don't Worry Shorts!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361900326940</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:38:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder if their are stalking laws for chat boards.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1361901872990</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:04:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361903561154-92</Id><Title>FNHC - EPS up 180%, .7book, PE 8 insiders buying heavily, trading at 50% of target price.</Title><Msg>This is a turnaround story just starting and they just reinstated dividend after 4-straigt quarters of profits and are not ramping up book of business again. They have paid a nice 8% dividend, so we have some nice raises ahead and nice stock moves on each news release. Earnings date should be coming out soon, which will also give the stock a boost. It is a very safe place for some cash with a good chance of a double or more, which is still under the target price target. All good all true, take a look.</Msg><Username>daveparker0808</Username><Timestamp>1361903561154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:32:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361904528579-93</Id><Title>Adoption of ARM big.LITTLE Technology Accelerates</Title><Msg>ARM today unveiled that its big.LITTLE processing technology has been adopted by many of the world’s leading mobile chip manufacturers. Samsung and Renesas Mobile have already announced their plans, and subsequent implementations will be revealed during 2013 by five more companies including CSR, Fujitsu Semiconductor and MediaTek. ARM big.LITTLE technology saves up to 70 percent of processor energy consumption in common mobile workload tasks, essential as the performance of the smartphone has jumped by 60x since 2000 and 12x since 2008, causing a massive increase in both content generation and consumption. With tablets and smartphones out-shipping PCs and some 1 billion smartphones expected to ship in 2013, there is an explosive growth in smart mobile devices. Users now want a richer mobile experience, and it is low-power technologies like big.LITTLE that are making previously impossible experiences possible - such as instantaneous browsing, console-quality gaming and days, rather than hours, of battery life. ARM big.LITTLE processing technology addresses the challenge of creating a system-on-chip (SoC) that meets the diverse needs of smartphones and other mobile devices. These conflicting demands require a smartphone to deliver high-performance when needed, while also extending the battery life. ARM big.LITTLE technology increases the dynamic performance range and energy efficiency of the mobile device while being completely transparent to the extensive range of applications available today for ARM processor-based platforms. The big.LITTLE solution pairs the industry’s highest performance Cortex™-A15 processor, delivering up to 2x more performance than today’s smartphones, with the ultra-efficient Cortex-A7 processor and the ARM CoreLink™ Cache Coherent Interconnect (CCI-400), which together enable devices to seamlessly use the right processor for the right task based on performance requirements to deliver the best user experience and optimal energy usage. Future implementations may also pair the Cortex-A53 and Cortex-A57 processors. This is complemented by ARM system-wide IP including: POP™ IP – core-hardening acceleration technology to streamline the implementation of big.LITTLE technology SoCs at advanced process technology nodes; Development Studio 5 (DS-5™) debug and analysis tools, and Active Assist design services. “big.LITTLE processor technology builds on ARM low-power leadership and sets a new standard for high performance and energy-efficient processing. By reducing processor energy consumption by up to 70 percent on common workloads, big.LITTLE technology enables users to do more with their smartphones for longer,” said Simon Segars, president, ARM. “As smartphones and tablets continue to evolve into users' primary compute device, our partners are increasingly looking to ARM for innovations to help them deliver performance as well as the always-on, always-connected service their customers expect." “In addition to being suitable for smartphones and mobile computing devices, ARM big.LITTLE technology enables the development of powerful, yet low power consumption SoC for a broad range of embedded applications,” said Mitsugu Naito, executive vice president, Advanced Products BU, Fujitsu Semiconductor Limited. “Our SoC development expertise coupled with ARM big.LITTLE processing technology will provide the market with the combined performance and low power required for the next generation of innovative embedded products.” “big.LITTLE processing is the next logical extension after symmetric multi-processing to increase performance in a mobile device within the same power budget,” said Johan Lodenius, chief marketing officer, MediaTek. “We look forward to extending the capabilities of our extremely successful multi-core chipsets through the use of big.LITTLE processing, bringing new experiences to smartphones.” “The mobile device market is demanding ever increasing performance and Renesas Mobile is well placed to deliver world-beating smartphone platforms based on highly integrated communications processors and application processors to meet this need,” commented Shinichi Yoshioka, senior executive vice president &amp; chief operating officer, Renesas Mobile. “Our smart design approach and ARM’s big.LITTLE processing will provide the mobile device market with the combined performance and battery life it needs to satisfy the growth in mobile computing.” “In an era when smartphones and tablets are evolving into the user’s primary compute device, Samsung’s Exynos 5 Octa, as the industry-first big.LITTLE enabled application processor, will drive innovation to bring outstanding user experience by handling diverse mobile workloads while also being optimized for power consumption,” said Tae-Hoon Kim, vice president of System LSI marketing, Device Solutions, Samsung Electronics. “Data usage is dramatically increasing as the mobile internet becomes more accessible for customers. As such we’re seeing the consumption of HD content and multimedia services increase and new connected experiences emerge,” said Yves Maitre, senior vice president, Mobile Multimedia and Devices, Orange. “To make the most of the advances in high-speed mobile networks, operators and device manufacturers need to have high-performance, energy-efficient processing power, such as ARM Cortex processors and big.LITTLE technology, to continue the growth in the connected device market and create new experiences.” “Battery consumption is an important factor with the use of smartphones, especially with the exponential growth of data use that we are seeing today. ARM Cortex processors and big.LITTLE processing have great potential to help increase smartphone performance and energy efficiency,” commented Von McConnell, Director at Sprint.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361904528579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:48:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361904842437-94</Id><Title>Intel launches latest platform for crunching Big Data</Title><Msg>Intel launched a new software platform for number-crunching on a massive scale, its latest offering in a growing field that it hopes will boost sales of its powerful server chips. The Santa Clara, California-based chipmaker is one of a growing number of technology companies that want to help organizations find value in Big Data -- the analysis of vast troves of information that can be culled from social media, Web searches, financial records, and other mountains of digital facts and figures. Intel unveiled its third customized version of Hadoop, the open-source software that aggregates results from large sets of data and is widely used in Big Data analysis. Intel's tweaks to Hadoop optimize it to work better with solid-state drives as well as other improvements, Boyd Davis, vice president of Intel's architecture group and general manager of the datacenter software division, said at a news event on Tuesday. Intel hopes that developing software to encourage more companies to leap into Big Data analysis will lead to higher sales of its high-end Xeon server processors. "One of our biggest motivators is to drive faster growth of the data center itself," Davis said. Intel plans to distribute its version of Hadoop through vendors and service providers and will also sell its own technical support services.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361904842437</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:54:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361905167780-95</Id><Topic><Title>Adoption of ARM big.LITTLE Technology Accelerates</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361904528579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:48:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sam Mobile Posted by DannyD on 23 February 2013 at 10:01 BREAKING: Samsung ditches own AMOLED and EXYNOS inside new Galaxy S IV Yes you just read the title of this message right. Our insider just gave us the first official “unconfirmed” specifications of the next generation Galaxy S, the Galaxy S IV. The Galaxy S IV will no longer use the Samsung EXYNOS processor and according to the latest rumours this processor has overheating issues. Today we can confirm Samsung will use the Snapdragon 600 and it is clocked at 1.9 Ghz which is 0.2 Ghz higher than the HTC One. The Galaxy S IV will have 2 GB of RAM and will come in three variants 16, 32 or 64 GB. As the rumours earlier reported Samsung is going to use a Full HD display. The Galaxy S IV uses a 4,99″ Full-HD SoLux Display we have no information if this is based on LCD3 like the HTC One. But a couple of months ago we posted the first hint regarding Samsung’s LCD factory is ready to produce Full HD panels from early 2013. And we also know Samsung’s AMOLED factory does have many problems with the production of full HD AMOLED screens. "OVERHEATING ISSUES" HA HA HA HA HA !!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1361905167780</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:59:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361905737726-96</Id><Topic><Title>Adoption of ARM big.LITTLE Technology Accelerates</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361904528579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:48:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big-little is what you do when you don't have access to state-or-the-art fabrication. So, of course, it's going to expand in the ARM world - they don't have any other choices. It's not a sign of progress for ARM, it's a sign that the apocalypse is upon them...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361905737726</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:08:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361905878218-97</Id><Topic><Title>TSM stock does not like the news</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361895480383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:18:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course Walliweaver. I remember the pain Intel went through when they came up with tri-gate. Tri gate has its roots in FinFet but the implementation of it is so different that Intel refuses to call their Tri gate process FinFet. Going 3D raises the complication to a whole new level. I remember all the hecklers when Intel was struggling with tri gate. Now I am going to watch TSMC squirm.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361905878218</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:11:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361905927360-98</Id><Topic><Title>Don't Worry Shorts!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361900326940</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 12:38:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey toooostupid, today would be a marvelous day to double up your short. Go for it!</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1361905927360</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:12:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361905973503-99</Id><Title>Intel says you can build a Bay Trail tablet that’s just about 8mm (0.3 inches) thick</Title><Msg>Intel may be busy launching a new dual-core Clover Trail+ processor for smartphones, but the company’s already looking ahead to next-generation Atom chips for smartphones and tablets. The companys’s 32nm Clover Trail+ will eventually be replaced by 22nm “Merrifield” processors designed to offer better performance and longer battery life. Meanwhile the company’s confirming that the upcoming Atom “Bay Trail” chips should start shipping later this year, which means you may be able to pick up a tablet with a 22nm Atom processor in time for the 2013 holiday season. Bay Trail chips are expected to offer twice the performance of the Clover Trail processors powering Windows 8 tablets today, while offering lower power consumption (and heat generation). That means we should see tablets with longer battery life and thinner cases — Intel says you can build a Bay Trail tablet that’s just about 8mm (0.3 inches) thick. Intel is partnering with device makers including Quanta, Pegraton, ECS, and Wistron to build Bay Trail tablets. You may have noticed that all the news about Atom chips recently has concerned tablets and smartphones. While the Intel Atom chips of yesteryear were primarily used in low-cost netbook computers, Intel is positioning future versions of its low power processors as chips for mobile devices. From liliputing</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361905973503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:12:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361906123294-100</Id><Topic><Title>Read this now -Intel Corporation(INTC)</Title><Username>brooksterrell60</Username><Timestamp>1361890111890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:48:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they are amazing fact</Msg><Username>malonecbobby</Username><Timestamp>1361906123294</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:15:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361906476206-101</Id><Title>Gosh, this is excting!!!</Title><Msg>This is it, boys and girls, the moment you have all been waiting for! There are countless board rooms and strategy sessions going on at this very moment in the big boy banks, and the little boy funds wondering...how much scratch do we have to throw at Intel??? This is an ignition, but not in the sense of your uncle olaf's volvo, rather it's an H-bomb, which starts with ignition of a tetrahedron of A-bombs. A - for Altera? AAPL?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1361906476206</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:21:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361906773378-102</Id><Topic><Title>Adoption of ARM big.LITTLE Technology Accelerates</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361904528579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:48:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is truly the last gasp of RISC architecture. So we can't build a powerful efficient chip so we are going to marry a power hog to a whimpy chip. When we need to save power we use the whimpy chip. LOL.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361906773378</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:26:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361906892256-103</Id><Topic><Title>Adoption of ARM big.LITTLE Technology Accelerates</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361904528579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:48:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the last gasp of RISC architecture." repeat: Adoption of ARM big.LITTLE Technology Accelerates</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361906892256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:28:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361906972219-104</Id><Topic><Title>TSM stock does not like the news</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361895480383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:18:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am sure the have so smart people at TSMC so I am not going to say Otellini is right but Intel has a little secret about making FinFet work and TSMC has a nasty suprise waiting for them when they try to make FinFet go into production.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361906972219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:29:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361906995120-105</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>blacknick671</Username><Timestamp>1361906263256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:17:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice fart</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1361906995120</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:29:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361907328472-106</Id><Title>Twelve Year Deal with Altera</Title><Msg>[Apparently Altera got a 12-year exclusive deal. Bet the exclusive part of that cost some coin. Bump for Intel...] "Well, how long that lasts – and how long rival Xilinx remains outside of Intel's fabs – is an open question. Intel surely wants all three FPGA makers to keep the wafer bakers warm and cover some of the billions of dollars that Chipzilla invests in foundries. Right? Wrong. The terms of the deal cut between Intel and Altera were not disclosed, but apparently Intel did not keep its options open with the deal it cut with Altera. According to a report in the Wall Street Journal, Intel agreed to a twelve-year deal with Altera and said that the other major suppliers of FPGAs – that is mainly Xilinx – would not be given access to Chipzilla's fabs." From The Register</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361907328472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:35:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361907338147-107</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>blacknick671</Username><Timestamp>1361906263256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:17:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spam</Msg><Username>typea1948</Username><Timestamp>1361907338147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:35:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361907399405-108</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>referancesdelores</Username><Timestamp>1361794083482</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 07:08:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you and please keep it coming.</Msg><Username>revachenell</Username><Timestamp>1361907399405</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:36:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361907523712-109</Id><Topic><Title>Twelve Year Deal with Altera</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361907328472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:35:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you dumb that down for me a bit... I'm not quite sure if that was a positive for the stock price or a negative for the stock price...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1361907523712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:38:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361907575177-110</Id><Topic><Title>TSM stock does not like the news</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361895480383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:18:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Otellini did seem pretty confident. He didn't say it would take the ARM foundries a long time - he said they would never have FinFET. Well, if they can't do it in three years, it might as well be never. Given Intel is going to have a two node lead for several years, it looks doubtful that the ARM foundries can move to FinFET soon enough to save themselves...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361907575177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:39:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361907809922-111</Id><Topic><Title>Twelve Year Deal with Altera</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361907328472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:35:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see it as a positive for the stock price for the following reasons: 1.) Intel isn't going to give Altera a 12-year exclusive unless the price is right. 2.) Intel isn't going to lock others (like Xilinx) out of a contract unless they are confident in filling capacity from other sources. 3.) A 12-year deal with Intel means ARM won't have this business for over a decade.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361907809922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:43:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361908033037-112</Id><Topic><Title>Adoption of ARM big.LITTLE Technology Accelerates</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361904528579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:48:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok getanid61, you have been reading too much ARM propaganda so I will spell it out for you. An inherernt weakness of RISC is that as the chips become more powerful and increase in complexity they require more power. Much more. RISC chips excel at areas where the task isn't overly complex. In those cases it has a distinct power efficency advantage. They don't scale very well performance wise. As soon as you scale them they become very inefficent. Intel who uses CISC has been talking about this problem and giving this as the reason it never went the RISC route. Little big is just a way with ARM trying to cope with the limit of RISC. RISC has reached its limitation.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361908033037</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:47:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361908196758-113</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>blacknick671</Username><Timestamp>1361906263256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:17:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pc market down 8% every year in the future! Tsm is strong advancing technology. See qcom and apple and samsumg all use tsm product.</Msg><Username>lkelongchow</Username><Timestamp>1361908196758</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:49:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361908391186-114</Id><Topic><Title>Adoption of ARM big.LITTLE Technology Accelerates</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361904528579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:48:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I will spell it out for you. An inherernt weakness of RISC is that as the chips become more powerful and increase in complexity they require more power. " IF they are powerful &amp; complex... are they still RISC... "They don't scale very well performance wise. As soon as you scale them they become very inefficent. " clear as mud... please do tell...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361908391186</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:53:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361908629716-115</Id><Topic><Title>Twelve Year Deal with Altera</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361907328472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:35:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pluses for Intel on the Altera deal: Increases Intel's ability to deliver silicon convergence, integrate hardware and software programmability...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361908629716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:57:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361909892547-116</Id><Title>FBR destroyed PC stocks today with their research note</Title><Msg>Says 1Q PC shipments tracking well below seasonality (down 15%). INTC started dropping around the same time their note became public. Not good.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361909892547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:18:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361910438234-117</Id><Title>First Tegra 4i phones come in late 2013</Title><Msg>Design cycle of 18 months to blame Nvidia has a working prototype of Phoenix, its first reference phone design based on its first LTE chip. The chip codenamed Grey is now known as Tegra 4i. Nvidia not only has a working chip, it also has phone prototypes that it was showing around at MWC. The bad thing for end users is that Grey, Nvidia Tegra 4i phones are not going to hit the market before late 2013, probably sometime in Q4 2013 at the earliest. You can blame the slow phone design cycle that usually takes 18 month. Tegra 4i will probably live through a good part of 2014. By 2014 Nvidia is expected to have its first high end chip with LTE codename Logan that can easily end up with Tegra 5 branding. It turns out that Nvidia will get Grey Tegra 4i phones faster to market than the usual 18 months, the usual time it takes to design and build a smartphone. Then again Tegra 4i phones are still more than six months away. Tegra 4i is a big step for Nvidia as having LTE integrated on the chip saves some battery power, saves the design cost, saves a space on the phone motherboard and it becomes mandatory for many phone manufacturers. Nvidia is making a lot of noise at the Mobile World Congress, especially touting the good performance of Tegra 4 against the competition but again there is a bitter aftertaste that things could have been much better for Nvidia had this chip been ready in late Q4 2012, as it was originally planned. From Fudzilla [Wow, doesn't the ARM world know what an opportunity 6 and 12-month delays give Intel? Doesn't Nvidia know what kind of competition Intel is going to bring by the end of 2013. Given all of Nvidia's problems, not having a phone out until the end of the year seems like a complete disaster...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361910438234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:27:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361910615905-118</Id><Topic><Title>FBR destroyed PC stocks today with their research note</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361909892547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:18:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really sucks for you since you own 11 million shares, per your post history.</Msg><Username>backstreetboy_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361910615905</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:30:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361910618411-119</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>blacknick671</Username><Timestamp>1361906263256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:17:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Tsm is strong advancing technology." [LOL, you obviously haven't seen their fabrication roadmap. Or lack thereof...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361910618411</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:30:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361910684608-120</Id><Title>Here's my hope</Title><Msg>Intel will start a new trend as of today and people like who are short like Nuff will be wiped out over time. As a result, he will disappear and we will no longer have to hear his azznine comments.</Msg><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1361910684608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:31:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361911066821-121</Id><Topic><Title>Here's my hope</Title><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1361910684608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:31:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who cares about Nuff? I have about two dozen idiots on ignore, and that pretty much wipes out nuff. What I hope is that Wall Street finally get's a brain. The scarecrow got one, why can't Wall Street?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1361911066821</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:37:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361911231162-122</Id><Topic><Title>Here's my hope</Title><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1361910684608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:31:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Won't happen. When Intel reached 29, he said he was glad Intel was the cornerstone of his portfolio. Life kicked him in the teeth and he takes his vengence (sp?) out here.</Msg><Username>backstreetboy_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361911231162</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:40:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361911236390-123</Id><Topic><Title>Adoption of ARM big.LITTLE Technology Accelerates</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361904528579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:48:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Generally they use more power the more complex but Intel is building Haswell which uses about half the power of Ivy bridge which is less complex. As you scale a CISC chip performance wise the power use goes up but when you scale the performance of a RISC chip the power usage goes up a lot. ARM will lose the power efficiency battle with INTEL. ARM's highest performance chips are power hogs and that is why they came up with Little-big. It is a little like saying my caddy v8 is a big power hog so I am going to put a little engine in there with it so I can save money on gas. Little big is stupid and ARM's weak answer to Intel core efficiency.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361911236390</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:40:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361911240382-124</Id><Topic><Title>Here's my hope</Title><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1361910684608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:31:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once the big boys cover their 200mm short positions we will start the accent. If INTC gets a brain and increases the buy back at these low prices, we will be at 30 in no time.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1361911240382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:40:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361911289811-125</Id><Topic><Title>First Tegra 4i phones come in late 2013</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361910438234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:27:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well, we know one thing, Wallis...Wall Street cannot project anything into the future. They are clueless, living only in the present..for today...that's what happens when you do a few ounces of cocaine per week....you live only for the momentary thrill...no memory of the past, not notions about the future. There's a theorem in computing that such a machine can't compute anything. That's wall street, my friend.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1361911289811</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:41:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361911464509-126</Id><Topic><Title>= = Analyst Predicts Decline to 17.07 =SEE REPORT=</Title><Username>blackscott588</Username><Timestamp>1361404069367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job mate. Thank you!</Msg><Username>smithjoseph529</Username><Timestamp>1361911464509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:44:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361911474075-127</Id><Title>LOL at Lucy AKA Tooofunnny buying Ciso in 2010 at same price it is today</Title><Msg>lucy_nuff•Dec 28, 2010 10:34 AM I Just Sold All of My INTC and Bought CSCO CSCO will outperform INTC in 2011.</Msg><Username>backstreetboy_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361911474075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:44:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361911502474-128</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>blacknick671</Username><Timestamp>1361906263256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:17:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job mate. Thank you!</Msg><Username>smithjoseph529</Username><Timestamp>1361911502474</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:45:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361911529014-129</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>blacknick671</Username><Timestamp>1361906263256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:17:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ LINK IS TO NASTY PORN!!!! ████████████...</Msg><Username>zion_will_up_huge</Username><Timestamp>1361911529014</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:45:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361911673425-130</Id><Topic><Title>FBR destroyed PC stocks today with their research note</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361909892547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:18:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more buying opportunities in the weeks ahead..buy low &amp; live off the dividends....</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361911673425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:47:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361911842009-131</Id><Topic><Title>FBR destroyed PC stocks today with their research note</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361909892547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:18:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would appear that only INTC shorters got the report. HPQ is up over 4.2% and climbing.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1361911842009</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:50:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361911873458-132</Id><Topic><Title>LOL at Lucy AKA Tooofunnny buying Ciso in 2010 at same price it is today</Title><Username>backstreetboy_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361911474075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:44:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CSCO went from 20.25 to 14.93 just 4 months after he bought it. LOLOLOLO.................................L</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361911873458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:51:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361912028732-133</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (INTC)</Title><Username>frankbryant786</Username><Timestamp>1361483522525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:52:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job mate. Thank you!</Msg><Username>smithjoseph529</Username><Timestamp>1361912028732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:53:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361912424627-134</Id><Topic><Title>Adoption of ARM big.LITTLE Technology Accelerates</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361904528579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:48:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ARM camp is just beginning to realize that power efficiency doesn't scale linearly as one moves up the performance curve. Intel has known this a long time. big.Little is a bandaid but they don't really have an alternative. The folly of big.Little strategy will become obvious as Intel moves forward on its roadmap.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1361912424627</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:00:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361912502872-135</Id><Topic><Title>TSM stock does not like the news</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1361895480383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 11:18:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, I agree if they "can't do it in 3 years it might as well be never." TSMC stubbornly clung to 2D too long. Intel chose to bite the bullet early and deal with it. Now they have reached the wall without 3D and have to embrace FinFET. Now Intel struggled and it took them 6 month longer then they thought and TSMC thinks it can get it done by 2015? Not gonna happen in my opinion. It is game over for TSMC. They will be forever be a 2nd teir foundry.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361912502872</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:01:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361912806623-136</Id><Topic><Title>= = Analyst Predicts Decline to 17.07 =SEE REPORT=</Title><Username>blackscott588</Username><Timestamp>1361404069367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please stop posting your child and animal porn here. It's disgusting.</Msg><Username>drensber</Username><Timestamp>1361912806623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:06:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361912854904-137</Id><Topic><Title>FBR destroyed PC stocks today with their research note</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361909892547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:18:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nah...now is the time of the quarter for the bear Intel analysts to come out &amp; bash PCs &amp; Intel because they know Intel leadership is too weak to respond &amp; refute. Otellini is asleep at the wheel, as he has been for the past 8 years.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361912854904</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:07:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361913733715-138</Id><Topic><Title>FBR destroyed PC stocks today with their research note</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361909892547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:18:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sure it isn't the 6 week quiet period? Thats when the real bashing starts. Back when we had mid qtr. updates, the only had 3 weeks to bash unabated.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1361913733715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:22:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361914146966-139</Id><Title>Can Intel's Dividend go up 7% per year for the next five years?</Title><Msg>That would put us at 1.26/share.</Msg><Username>smokinghotblitch</Username><Timestamp>1361914146966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:29:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361914243860-140</Id><Title>With no one else able to fab at 22nm and below, Intel will have to do it for everyone.</Title><Msg>Intel seems pretty confident that TSM and others won't be able to copy their technology by opening it up to Altera and Cisco. End of fabless is getting nearer.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361914243860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:30:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361914389013-141</Id><Title>Could Intel open things say Qualcom exclusively?</Title><Msg>Say they do just Qualcom. That would be HUGE for both companies. And if Qualcom got the exclusive, they would pay mega bucks. Why wouldn't 'this be great for both companies if they worked exclusively?</Msg><Username>smokinghotblitch</Username><Timestamp>1361914389013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:33:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361915135771-142</Id><Topic><Title>With no one else able to fab at 22nm and below, Intel will have to do it for everyone.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361914243860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:30:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's an upper limit on how much a mobile device maker will pay for a CPU/SOC for use in their phones/tablets/whatever. And that price of that chip will likely be less than the price of INTC low end CPU's. The question then is even if INTC wins the majority of these future chip manufacturing contracts, will this translate to higher earnings? The answer is far from obvious.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1361915135771</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:45:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361915416381-143</Id><Topic><Title>With no one else able to fab at 22nm and below, Intel will have to do it for everyone.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361914243860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:30:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel won't manufacture CPU's for others.. Anything that is a direct threat to Intel won't be manufactured. 2nd and 3rd tier chips will still be manufactured by TSMC.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361915416381</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:50:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361915873854-144</Id><Topic><Title>With no one else able to fab at 22nm and below, Intel will have to do it for everyone.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361914243860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:30:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That may very well be true, but even if they sell x86-SOC to mobile device makers, the price INTC sells those chips for will have to be cheaper than most of INTC CPU products.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1361915873854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:57:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361916542707-145</Id><Topic><Title>With no one else able to fab at 22nm and below, Intel will have to do it for everyone.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361914243860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:30:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still more margin than Intel would get just fabbing chips for others.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1361916542707</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 17:09:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361916567198-146</Id><Topic><Title>Could Intel open things say Qualcom exclusively?</Title><Username>smokinghotblitch</Username><Timestamp>1361914389013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:33:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uh...no.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1361916567198</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 17:09:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361916572849-147</Id><Topic><Title>With no one else able to fab at 22nm and below, Intel will have to do it for everyone.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361914243860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:30:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The external fab customers will generate incremental revenue, will help Intel achieve greater utilization of its assets and lower Intel's overall cost. That is a lot of upside.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1361916572849</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 17:09:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361917175090-148</Id><Topic><Title>Could Intel open things say Qualcom exclusively?</Title><Username>smokinghotblitch</Username><Timestamp>1361914389013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:33:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not only could they get a great premium, but it would put every other phone maker 1 to 2 generations permenatly behind. That could be the almighty game changer.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1361917175090</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 17:19:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361917265905-149</Id><Topic><Title>With no one else able to fab at 22nm and below, Intel will have to do it for everyone.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361914243860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:30:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another much cheaper way to achieve greater utilization and lower cost is to build fewer fabs. Why go through the hassle of foundry work if that's not your modus operandi?</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1361917265905</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 17:21:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361917382587-150</Id><Title>Intel is Good for $23.02</Title><Msg>777777777777777</Msg><Username>wilder_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1361917382587</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 17:23:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361917501907-151</Id><Topic><Title>With no one else able to fab at 22nm and below, Intel will have to do it for everyone.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361914243860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:30:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True, but why not instead simply reduce leading edge capacity additions to match internal requirements? If you want to boost utilization of depreciated trailing edge fabs by doing foundry work great, but these contracts don;t do that..</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1361917501907</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 17:25:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361917740340-152</Id><Topic><Title>With no one else able to fab at 22nm and below, Intel will have to do it for everyone.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361914243860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:30:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only way Intel can be attractive to some of the companies they'd like as cusotmers is to have the capacity to serve them. Intel has removed capacity as an obstacle, while others are struggling to meet demand for leading edge product. At the same time Intel has positioned itself to produce very high quality product in very high volume. That's an enviable place to be as competition gets tougher.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1361917740340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 17:29:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361918177440-153</Id><Topic><Title>With no one else able to fab at 22nm and below, Intel will have to do it for everyone.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361914243860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:30:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But why build capacity, especially expensive lead edge capacity, to attract customers who, because of the end-market cost restrictions (mobile devices), can't pay prices like those INTC gets for it's own CPU's in those same fabs? Why settle for lower margins? Something just doesn't jive.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1361918177440</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 17:36:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361918335734-154</Id><Topic><Title>With no one else able to fab at 22nm and below, Intel will have to do it for everyone.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361914243860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:30:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Short answer is they intend to bury the competition. With leading edge tech, the can decide who the winners and losers are, the rest go by way of the dodo bird. This insures INTC gets the cream and the people buying leading edge tech for INTC let them have it. 2 gen behind in tablets and cell phones can pretty well assure you will never be a contender.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1361918335734</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 17:38:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361918865878-155</Id><Topic><Title>= = Analyst Predicts Decline to 17.07 =SEE REPORT=</Title><Username>blackscott588</Username><Timestamp>1361404069367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good info.thank you.</Msg><Username>smithdaniel122</Username><Timestamp>1361918865878</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 17:47:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361918924296-156</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>blacknick671</Username><Timestamp>1361906263256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:17:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting report.</Msg><Username>smithdaniel122</Username><Timestamp>1361918924296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 17:48:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361919040020-157</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (INTC)</Title><Username>frankbryant786</Username><Timestamp>1361483522525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:52:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting report.</Msg><Username>smithdaniel122</Username><Timestamp>1361919040020</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 17:50:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361919765946-158</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (INTC)</Title><Username>frankbryant786</Username><Timestamp>1361483522525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:52:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very interesting information. thank you.</Msg><Username>whitejohn397</Username><Timestamp>1361919765946</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 18:02:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361919919278-159</Id><Topic><Title>With no one else able to fab at 22nm and below, Intel will have to do it for everyone.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1361914243860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:30:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But why build capacity, especially expensive lead edge capacity, to attract customers who, because of the end-market cost restrictions (mobile devices), can't pay prices like those INTC gets for it's own CPU's in those same fabs? Why settle for lower margins? Something just doesn't jive." [You are apparently confused about the economics. Intel builds new fab nodes because the economics are better not worse. Intel can offer competitive prices in mobility. And it doesn't really matter what the margins are as long as they are positive. Because it's a brand new market and because the huge volume will offset a smaller margin. It's really all about the profit dollar volume and not the margins. Intel can do this business, they can do it economically, they can make a ton of money doing it, and state-of-the-art is how they get there. ARM's fab economics and ramps are fading while Intel's remain quite robust. These dynamics have produced the tipping point we are now seeing as strongly evidenced by the Altera deal...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361919919278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 18:05:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361920503103-160</Id><Title>Apple Intel soon to announce</Title><Msg>40 soon.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1361920503103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 18:15:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361921786897-161</Id><Topic><Title>Adoption of ARM big.LITTLE Technology Accelerates</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361904528579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:48:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" As you scale a CISC chip performance wise the power use goes up but when you scale the performance of a RISC chip the power usage goes up a lot." OK, why is that... or again will you evade an answer... Kinda obvious you can't explain something you don't understand... " Little big is stupid and ARM's weak answer " Meanwhile, Big/little adoption is accelerating...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361921786897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 18:36:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361923257752-162</Id><Topic><Title>Adoption of ARM big.LITTLE Technology Accelerates</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361904528579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:48:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Extreme tech did a wonderful piece on ARM's attempt to out power INTC with one of their chips the CORTEX A-15. "Atom vs. Cortex-A15.." Cortex will chew threw 4-8 watts and Clovertrail burns 2 watts. Bay trail will produce the same output at 1 watt. Thems the facts. As you can see. ARM is becoming the power hog at they try to build high performance chips.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361923257752</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 19:00:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361924910100-163</Id><Topic><Title>Adoption of ARM big.LITTLE Technology Accelerates</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361904528579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:48:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude, Are you changing from RISC to strictly A15 now ?? an A15 on Samsung's process will draw some power... but Tegra 4 power numbers will be telling... but do check on the non-ARMH designed cores... Done wonders for Apple, Qualcomm, etc... OH yeah, check on the MIPS64 power draw... another pesky RISC ISA It's faster than anything from ARMH too...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361924910100</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 19:28:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361924973031-164</Id><Topic><Title>Adoption of ARM big.LITTLE Technology Accelerates</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361904528579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:48:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Meanwhile, Big/little adoption is accelerating..." [Yes, big/little adoption is accelerating amongst those companies that don't have access to state-of-the-art fabrication, i.e. all of the ARM shops...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361924973031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 19:29:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361928137555-165</Id><Topic><Title>FBR destroyed PC stocks today with their research note</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361909892547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:18:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who knows? Intel has not been transparent about this &amp; every quarter around this time, the bashers come out &amp; put out very negative "forecasts" based on "their un-named checks". Lets hope the new CEO has much more shareholder-friendly policies.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361928137555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 20:22:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361928321559-166</Id><Topic><Title>Can Intel's Dividend go up 7% per year for the next five years?</Title><Username>smokinghotblitch</Username><Timestamp>1361914146966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:29:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC's dividend has gone up 43 percent in 3 years time. I expect it to go to 1.00 by this time next year. In five years I am projecting 1.50 or better. I bought it to lock it up for a dividend for my retirement income. Much better then owning a government bond.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361928321559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 20:25:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361928848074-167</Id><Topic><Title>FBR destroyed PC stocks today with their research note</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1361909892547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 15:18:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amen</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1361928848074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 20:34:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361930003974-168</Id><Title>First Tablet designed for gamers available March 1st (Intel inside)</Title><Msg>Razer Edge tablet available for pre-order from March 1 By Samantha Loveridge 26 February 2013 Razer has announced that the award-winning Razer Edge tablet will be available to pre-order from March 1, with units set to ship later that month. Due to be released in two versions, the Razer Edge will offer an Intel i5 processor and 64GB SSD, whilst the Razer Edge Pro will play host to an Intel i7 processor and the option of 128GB or 256GB SSD. The basic model will cost $999 (£569) and the Razer Edge Pro will set you back $1,299 (£857) and $1,499 (£989) for the different storage options. “The Razer Edge combines the features of full-functioning PCs, touch-enabled tablets and gaming consoles into one incredible, portable form factor,” said Min-Liang Tan, co-founder, CEO and Creative Director at Razer. “Furthermore, the Razer Edge’s powerful chipset, unique among all tablet computers, ensures that you can take advantage of the world’s most sophisticated games, programs and apps on these multiple platforms anytime.” Razer Edge Features The Razer Edge claims to be the first tablet designed for PC gamers, complete with 10.1-inch HD multi-touch display and Nvidia GeForce graphics. Running Windows 8, the Razer Edge is a fully fledged mobile gaming PC in tablet form, and gives users access to a large library of games. A versatile tablet, the Razer Edge can change into different devices based on the user’s needs. The tablet mode offers a 10.1-inch Windows 8 tablet, but when partnered with the Keyboard Dock the Razer Edge converts to a notebook style PC. Attaching the Gamepad Controller allows the Razer Edge to offer console-style gaming on the go with full PC game support and vibration feedback. Finally the home console mode Docking Station means the Razer Edge can connect to a desktop display and support multiple gamepad controllers. All of the Razer Edge peripherals will be available to pre-order alongside the tablet come March 1. Offering a 10.1-inch IPS display with 1366 x 768 HD resolution, the Razer Edge also sports stereo speakers with Dolby Home Theatre v4 audio technology, a front-facing 2-megapixel webcam, an array of microphones and a USB 3.0 port. The basic model will ship with an Intel i5 processor with 64GB SSD. The Razer Edge Pro will provide an Intel i7 processor with 128GB or 256GB SSD options available. Are you impressed by the Razer Edge PC gaming tablet? Will you be saving your pennies to pre-order one in March? Give us your thoughts at the TrustedReviews Facebook and Twitter feeds or the comments section below.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361930003974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 20:53:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361930218274-169</Id><Title>Intel unveils new Software weapon for Big Data</Title><Msg>Intel unveils new software weapon for 'Big Data' By Noel Randewich Reuters Posted: 02/26/2013 10:51:05 AM PST Updated: 02/26/2013 11:04:36 AM PST More Intel coverage Latest news More about CEO Paul Otellini Market update: INTC SEC filings Company profile SAN FRANCISCO -- Intel (INTC) launched a new software platform for number-crunching on a massive scale, its latest offering in a growing field that it hopes will boost sales of its powerful server chips. The Santa Clara-based chipmaker is one of a growing number of technology companies that want to help organizations find value in "Big Data" -- the analysis of vast troves of information that can be culled from social media, Web searches, financial records, and other mountains of digital facts and figures. Intel unveiled its third customized version of Hadoop, the Showgoers visit the Intel booth on the first day of the Consumer Electronics Show (CES) in Las Vegas January 8, 2013. REUTERS/Rick Wilking (RICK WILKING) open-source software that aggregates results from large sets of data and is widely used in Big Data analysis. Intel's tweaks to Hadoop optimize it to work better with solid-state drives as well as other improvements, Boyd Davis, vice president of Intel's architecture group and general manager of the datacenter software division, said at a news event on Tuesday. Intel hopes that developing software to encourage more companies to leap into Big Data analysis will lead to higher sales of its high-end Xeon server processors. "One of our biggest motivators is to drive faster growth of the data center itself," Davis said.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361930218274</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 20:56:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361930265727-170</Id><Topic><Title>Could Intel open things say Qualcom exclusively?</Title><Username>smokinghotblitch</Username><Timestamp>1361914389013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:33:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Won't happen.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361930265727</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 20:57:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361930841090-171</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel soon to announce</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1361920503103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 18:15:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never know - Tommorrow is AAPL stockholders meeting.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1361930841090</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:07:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361933531952-172</Id><Topic><Title>Could Intel open things say Qualcom exclusively?</Title><Username>smokinghotblitch</Username><Timestamp>1361914389013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 16:33:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will not happen, Qualcomm is the most direct competitor to Intel now.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1361933531952</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:52:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361934240267-173</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel soon to announce</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1361920503103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 18:15:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple is not ready to give up their own designs and Intel will not fab an arm design. Apple needs a global LTE, so the just annouced modem may be possible. Intel is shipping the modem the end of the first half this year, Qualcomm will ship theirs 2nd half</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1361934240267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:04:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361934577324-174</Id><Title>Does Intel's LTE roadmap address this article regarding Apple?</Title><Msg>Can Intel Save Apple From the LTE Mess? Sascha Segan By Sascha Segan September 15, 2012 11:30am EST 33 Comments Google 9 Share 62 Tweet 53 Submit 603 Share 3 Pin It 0 Email Print iPhone 4 vs. iPhone 4S vs. iPhone 5 VIEW ALL PHOTOS IN GALLERY Apple couldn't engineer itself out of the global LTE mess, but maybe Intel can. The new iPhone 5 features 4G LTE, which is going to dramatically improve Internet speeds for AT&amp;T and Verizon iPhone owners. (Sprint subscribers are left waiting for LTE to arrive where they live.) But globally, the iPhone LTE picture is a disaster. There are two different iPhone models. The AT&amp;T iPhone will work on LTE on T-Mobile USA and in Canada, but not in the rest of the world. The Verizon/Sprint iPhone will work in some European and Asian countries. No iPhone will work on the existing LTE networks in Austria, Brazil, Columbia, Denmark, Norway, Russia, Saudi Arabia, and Switzerland, as iMore points out. The phones will still roam where they can't get LTE; they'll be on 3G, which isn't fatal, but it's a night-and-day difference in terms of speeds. The incompatibility is because there are way too many frequency bands being used for mobile phone networks right now. Apple's a popularizer and refiner of technologies; they're not introducing any radical new RF breakthroughs here, so they're stuck in the same LTE band whirlwind that everyone else is. Between Apple's two models, it's already supporting seven different LTE bands, known as band 1, 3, 4, 5, 13, 17 and 25. But European operators have three more bands they use: 7, 20 and 38. They may also use band 8 in the future. Some Asian operators appear to be on Band 40. Here at home, Sprint also plans to use band 26, and some smaller US carriers have band 12. It's a mess. It means phone makers have to put together lots of different models for different countries, and those units will have trouble roaming well in other countries if they travel. It also means small carriers on obscure LTE bands, like 12, have trouble getting phones that work well with their networks because there are no huge carriers placing large orders for them. Can Intel Fix Apple's Problems? Fortunately, across the street from the iPhone event, I saw a potential solution. Intel's Developer Forum was going on just across the street from Apple this week. Up on the second floor, the company was showing off the four relatively lackluster Intel phones so far, as well as a modem technology that could really change things. Intel's XMM6260 modem, which has been in the market for a while, uses a single power amplifier for multiple bands, and it can be extended in software to support as many bands as necessary. It doesn't support LTE or CDMA, which is part of why we haven't seen it in many U.S. products. But the point here, an Intel engineer told me, is that the company will be able to put an unlimited number of bands on a single LTE modem, possibly as soon as late next year. Intel's modems will be able to mate with processors from Samsung, Nvidia, TI, and others. Apple used its modems up until 2010, when it switched over to Qualcomm in part to get Verizon and Sprint compatibility. Modems are only half of the solution, though. Dermot O'Shea, co-founder of antenna firm Taoglas, said antenna design gets difficult when you're covering such a wide range of frequencies. Active antennas for smartphones, which have just started to hit the market this year, can adapt to different bands without being huge, although they add to the cost and complexity of smartphones. We're likely to see more of them next year. Between active antennas and multi-frequency power amplifiers, it looks like phone makers are starting to get their hands around the riot of LTE frequencies; they're just not there yet. Maybe we'll see them in the iPhone 7.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361934577324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:09:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361935742087-175</Id><Title>Samsung abandoning their Exynos (A15) chips for their next Galaxy products could mean exit from SoC design business</Title><Msg>Samsung abandoning their Exynos (A15) chips (due to overheating and power issues) for their next Galaxy products could mean exit from SoC design business. Could mean the end of their fabs too. Samsung may decide to go with Intel chips in the the future.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361935742087</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:29:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361936027875-176</Id><Title>I-Mate have phone that run FULL Windows 8 Pro OS</Title><Msg>Phones turning into computers is already here. We could see this product and many more with launch of Bay Trail in the next few months.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361936027875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:33:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361936229808-177</Id><Topic><Title>I-Mate have phone that run FULL Windows 8 Pro OS</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361936027875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:33:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>-Mate Phone Runs On Windows 8 Pro, not Windows Phone 8 By Andrew Grush, February 26, 2013 @ 10:44am Windows Phone 8? We don’t need no stinking Windows Phone 8. That’s i-Mate’s take on things apparently, as the company is skipping Microsoft’s phone OS with their new smartphone and jumping right to Windows 8. For those that don’t know (or remember) i-Mate, they were once well known for their rugged Windows Mobile handset that was designed to handle just about anything you could possibly throw at it and yet somehow still survive the mayhem and destruction brought down on it. So what kind of hardware is this Windows 8-based smartphone planning to arrive with? The phone will have a 4.7-inch display, an Atom processor, 2GB RAM, 64GB storage, HSPA+, LTE support and will run on the Pro version of Windows 8. The Windows 8 Phone will also have an optional docking station that includes a wired handset for making calls over the net, and more. The “HUB” package will also come with a 23-inch display, keyboard and mouse. In short, you can make this phone your desktop PC as well. Not enough options for you? There is also an auxilary 10.1-inch wireless tablet in the works. As you can probably guess, this will not exactly be a cheap buy. The phone buy itself is a stagerring $750. The “hub” with the phone, dock and monitor package comes in at $1,600. The wireless tablet is seperate, not sure on the costs though. While not a popular brand in the US, i-Mate is actually rather well known in the United Kingdom and Dubai. This might not be for everyone, but it is certainly a unique niche item. You have to wonder what they were thinking with a 4.7-inch display. Although I personally like displays of this size, going into the desktop to change settings and other options won’t exactly be a cakewalk with such a tiny display – 5.5-inches or so would have been a better fit. For those wondering, since this runs on Windows 8 and an Intel processor, it can also handle full desktop apps, though the Atom processor certainly won’t be strong enough for anything too intense. What do you think of the concept, could this have potential or is the idea of putting a full desktop OS onto a phone just too impractical at this point?</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361936229808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:37:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361936364710-178</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung abandoning their Exynos (A15) chips for their next Galaxy products could mean exit from SoC design business</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361935742087</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:29:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Man this is significant. I cannot see Samsung wanting their fate in the hands of TSMC or the other foundries. Intel and Samsung would make me much happier than Intel and Apple.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361936364710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:39:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361936717682-179</Id><Title>Why Intel's Web TV service will work</Title><Msg>To support Live TV and Cloud-based DVR you need a massive Data centers and networking equipment. These would normally cost ALOT of money. Intel can build and maintain these data center at cost since equipment will all run Intel chips.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361936717682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:45:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361936737852-180</Id><Title>Samsung and Intel unveil Tizen at MWC</Title><Msg>This plus Samsung not using Exynos in their next phone has me thinking that Intel and Samsung are about to get together in a BIG way. Samsung And Intel Unveil Tizen OS To The World At MWC First Posted: Feb 26, 2013 05:09 PM EST Samsung and Intel took to the Mobile World Congress stage to unveil Tizen, the open-source, Linux-based mobile operating system the two tech giants created. Tizen will appear on smartphones initially, but it was also designed to easily run on tablets, smart TVs and in-vehicle infotainment (IVI) devices. Tizen is designed to offer a consistent user experience from device to device and is a truly open-sourced platform that allows developers to easily create HTML5 applications for any device running Tizen. Tizen has become the elephant in the room between Samsung and Google. It is believed that Samsung partnered with Intel to create the mobile operating system to lessen its dependence on Google's Android OS, which is found on the majority of Samsung's smartphones. Google is reportedly uneasy about Samsung's meteoric success with Android, and this unveiling doesn't seem like it's going to give Google any reassurance that Samsung will continue to give Android nearly as much attention as it's been used to. Samsung has already officially announced that it will ship a Tizen OS smartphone this year through a partnership with NTT Docomo. The smartphone is expected to ship in July or August. Samsung and Intel have recently secured a partnership with smartphone maker Huawei, who just joined the steering committee of the Tizen Association. It's not just smartphone makers who have committed to supporting devices running Tizen. European wireless carrier Orange has announced it will begin selling Samsung and Huawei smartphones running Tizen this year. In the U.S., wireless carrier Sprint has also pledged full support for Tizen devices. Google has every right to be nervous about the future of Samsung and Tizen, since Google makes more money off Samsung than any of its other Android partners. Samsung reportedly sells 40 percent of all devices running Android. Is Tizen just another way of Samsung diversifying its choice of OS on smartphones and tablets, or is it a big hint to Google that it needs Samsung much more than Samsung needs Google?</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361936737852</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:45:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361936853173-181</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung and Intel unveil Tizen at MWC</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361936737852</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:45:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beginning of a beautiful friendship</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361936853173</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:47:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361936949511-182</Id><Title>Everyone wants to be INTC's new BFF</Title><Msg>Anyone that signs with Intel will have distinct competitive advantage.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361936949511</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:49:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361936984976-183</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung and Intel unveil Tizen at MWC</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361936737852</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:45:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure looks to me like Intel is going to have more places to put chips than it can keep up with. I've lost count on how many new devices have come out the last few months running on Intel chips. This is nuts.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361936984976</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:49:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361937692902-184</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung and Intel unveil Tizen at MWC</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361936737852</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:45:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can it use Google map?</Msg><Username>pc_addicte</Username><Timestamp>1361937692902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 23:01:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361937879165-185</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung and Intel unveil Tizen at MWC</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1361936737852</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:45:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At some point their is going to be a serious shakeup in the industry. Intel with its x86 chip can run a Windows OS and they can taylor their chips to run almost anything. Many vendors are starting to realize that the ARM chip is running into serious power/performance issues and Android is controlled too much by Google to their benefit. The Android/ARM setup is very limiting for a lot of vendors. Microsoft and Intel are determined to push into the mobile space. Google needs to fear Microsoft and ARM needs to lookout for Intel.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361937879165</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 23:04:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361937936062-186</Id><Topic><Title>Adoption of ARM big.LITTLE Technology Accelerates</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1361904528579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 13:48:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why pay for silicon that is not fully utilized? duh</Msg><Username>optermoron</Username><Timestamp>1361937936062</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 23:05:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361938712546-187</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung abandoning their Exynos (A15) chips for their next Galaxy products could mean exit from SoC design business</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361935742087</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:29:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exynos is a "big-little" endeavor that a previous poster hyped. It is going to be a big failure. Samsung "temporarily" abandoned it because it has issues. So they are using another vendors chipset. Nvidia took a different and better approach to solve the power/performance problem with ARM chip designs. While I don't see Samsung getting out of the fab business it is possible that they leave the high performance chips designs to someone else. Samsung really is really geared more toward the storage market.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1361938712546</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 23:18:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361939069585-188</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel's Web TV service will work</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1361936717682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 22:45:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMG. INTC sells chips to itself for no profit and enters a fifty year old industry known for razor thin margins. Brilliant.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1361939069585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 23:24:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361939682875-189</Id><Title>ARM vendors have shown all their cards</Title><Msg>Except for the new Nvidia which jury is still out, none of their CPU could come close to the Clover Trail+. When the quad-core BayTrails hit the mass later this year, the ARM camp has nothing to response in both power, performance, and integration.</Msg><Username>six_packers</Username><Timestamp>1361939682875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 23:34:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>