<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-15"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363320598555-1</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung's S4 looks like S3.. with a lot of features that nobody will use.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363306506416</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 20:15:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Overall I agree with that assessment. Thinner and lighter is good, a slightly larger display in the same physical length &amp; width is a also positive, but the most promoted features such as eye tracking and gesture control is somewhat gimmicky. These type of features often sound cool but rarely work well in actual usage. Reminds me of the front facing camera and facial recognition to unlock a phone. It looked like it was going to be useful but then you discover it has problems in different lighting conditions and just isn't that reliable. After a while one just turns it off and goes back to a password or swipe. I like Samsung's build quality but this release doesn't advance the state of smartphones in any meaningful way.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1363320598555</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 00:09:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363323884919-2</Id><Title>I wonder what</Title><Msg>...Paul Ryan thinks about the new pope ... another socialist wet bag ....</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363323884919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:04:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363323932767-3</Id><Topic><Title>Intel releases Android Dual bootable on Windows 8</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363299836151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:23:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I posted this yesterday but not too many people seem to gasped the significance of this. This news means ALL future PCs (especially PC hybrid) can run Android! So, for a PC hybrid, this means that in laptop mode, you can do your PC work in Windows and in tablet mode, you can run Android and be able to use all current Android apps! This will allow for new breed of products such as the Asus PadFone. There was also news yesterday from Google that Andy Rubin, head of Android has stepped down to be replaced by the head of Chrome OS. This sounds like Google plans to merge Chrome OS with Android. It won't be long before Apple merges their iOS with MacOS. Intel is in very good position here because it can support all 4 major OS's (Windows, MacOS, Chrome and Linux).</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363323932767</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:05:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363324225607-4</Id><Topic><Title>I wonder what</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363323884919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:04:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the records the former pope - native German shook hands with Fidel.... I suppose Cuban Cigars are still contra band - part of US is still fighting the cold war - pathetic</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363324225607</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363324487099-5</Id><Topic><Title>Intel releases Android Dual bootable on Windows 8</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363299836151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:23:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Also want Ubuntu Touch and Tizen!" [I second that emotion...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363324487099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:14:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363324600411-6</Id><Title>Samsung S4 is further proof that that A15 is a power hog</Title><Msg>The Exynos 5 Octa has 4 A7 running at 1.6GHz while the 4 A15 are only running at a pathetic 1.2GHz so it does not overheat. In the end, the Octa is not performing any better than the Snapdragon 600. Early Antutu benchmarks show the Octa competitive with the 600. Intel's CloverTrail+ still beat them both.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363324600411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:16:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363324924495-7</Id><Topic><Title>I wonder what</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363323884919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:04:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney also went on a mission to Paris .. to convert Mr. Mojo Rising ..while dodging the draft way to go</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363324924495</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:22:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363325572737-8</Id><Title>Why Apple will sign with Intel</Title><Msg>Devastating news out today that TSMC may only be at tape out stage for Apple's A7. This means Apple would not be able to have any new products with the A7 for this year's holiday shopping season if they stick with TSMC. There's only one way to salvage this situation and that is to sign with Intel who have already stated they will have their next-generation quad-core Atom SoC (“Bay Trail”) on 22nm available by this holiday season.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363325572737</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:32:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363325598833-9</Id><Topic><Title>How Does Websters Spell TURD- I-N-T-E-L</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363290618490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I took a wallisweaver a couple of hours ago and had to use the damned plunger to get the sucker to flush... It stunk to high heaven and so do you dude. My comments might resemble another watcher of Insmell because the stock has underperformed for 14 years... Yet, it is gone up and down in small trading channels but who has the crystal ball to know what quarter will be up and which will be down.. Otellini is on the way out and so are you... The local water treatment plant will take care of both of you.... LOL</Msg><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363325598833</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:33:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363326410166-10</Id><Topic><Title>How Does Websters Spell TURD- I-N-T-E-L</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363290618490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tsk, Tsk, Tsk. Potty humor? Really? You're a therapist's dream, DanaLucy...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363326410166</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:46:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363326581187-11</Id><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro sales hit 400K in a hurry</Title><Msg>Microsoft has sold 400,000 Surface Pros since launch, according to a Bloomberg report. That's not a bad start for a very pricey tablet -- starting at $899 -- considering that the Windows 8-based Pro launched only about a month ago. "That's a respectable number and it leads me to believe that Surface Pro will end up outselling Surface RT," Bob O'Donnell, an analyst at IDC, said in a phone interview. O'Donnell is referring to the RT version of Surface, which is less expensive, starting at $499, but it is not compatible with older Windows software. "It's something that we've predicated all along because of the compatibility that Surface Pro offers," he said. From Brooke Crothers</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363326581187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363328006288-12</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro sales hit 400K in a hurry</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363326581187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>+The sales numbers have spoken. It looks like Microsoft has a veritable hit on their hands. With the intro of Haswell, some of the criticism around this PC will get addressed. Also, this leads the way for core series chips to be put to use in tablets which is probably a win for core series sales volumes. If I was Qualcomm or NVidia, I would be very scared about competition for tablet chips in this form which neither has a chance of competing with at least on the performance front. Windows 8 it seems is set to take off as a touch OS albeit a little slowly contrary to earlier reports.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1363328006288</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 02:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363331808814-13</Id><Title>Here's what I see happening with Apple, Intel and TSMC.</Title><Msg>Apple will fab their ARM chips for the Iphone 5 and Iphone 4 at TSMC's 28nm. Apple will use Intel Atom 22nm chips for their new Iphones. The Iphone 5 and Iphone 4's will be the low end, yesterdays product (Free with 2 yr contract). Apple still has to sell these, as they can't just stop selling ARM products the next day. The New Iphones and Ipads will have Intel chips and will be the high end Phones and Ipads. So Digitimes may be RIGHT in a way with Apples production split between Intel and TSMC. Apple may also not dump Samsung immediately, but will Phase them out over a year or so. Mark this Post. You heard it here first.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363331808814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 03:16:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363337936115-14</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro sales hit 400K in a hurry</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363326581187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the Cheat Sheet: The chip analyst JoAnne Feeney at Longbow Research reported that her conversations with vendors of components for personal computers imply to her that the second half is shaping up worse than expected, and might cause problems for PC-related names like Intel, Advanced Micro Devices, Nvidia, and Intersil Corporation (NASDAQ:ISIL). Feeney maintains Neutrals on all four names, commenting that “contacts now see desktop units down 5 to 10 percent for the year vs. our forecast for INTC DT segment to be down 4 percent year-over-year in 2013. Look for a slow Haswell ramp as last year’s inventory build, following a surprisingly weak second half, leads the industry to stick with the safer Ivy Bridge platform (socket compatible with Sandy Bridge, unlike Haswell) and for Haswell to make up less than 50 percent of desktop CPU shipments even in the fourth quarter.”</Msg><Username>aye_corumba</Username><Timestamp>1363337936115</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 04:58:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363340296486-15</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro sales hit 400K in a hurry</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363326581187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That makes sense and is not a surprise to me. Not only is socket 1155 compatible with Sandy Bridge but is is also compatible with Ivy Bridge 22nm. The Haswell socket 1150 supports the Haswell on chip VTR and will likely have most value when coupled with an OS that can take advantage of its power conservation features. Those are not exactly "desktop CPU" features. Power conservation will be an issue for laptop sysems. Socket 1155 motherboards are not only "safe" but they are very cheap since there are many suppliers. A neutral rating and a target price that yields a 5% dividend is pretty safe. That is how she selected the $18 target. $18 = 5%. If Intel declared a dividend incease when they declare next week, she will raise her target.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363340296486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 05:38:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363342027977-16</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung S4 is further proof that that A15 is a power hog</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363324600411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:16:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Exynos 5 Octa has 4 A7 running at 1.6GHz while the 4 A15 are only running at a pathetic 1.2GHz so it does not overheat. In the end, the Octa is not performing any better than the Snapdragon 600. --- You've got it the wrong way round, the A7@1.2 and the A15@1.6. She will perform better than the 600:) Wait until real benchmarks arrive before making any assumptions.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1363342027977</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 06:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363345299471-17</Id><Topic><Title>Secret INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>timothy.maldonaldo</Username><Timestamp>1363184916481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very helpful report , thanks !</Msg><Username>ballerano</Username><Timestamp>1363345299471</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:01:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363346131162-18</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro sales hit 400K in a hurry</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363326581187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This rear view analysis is waste of time and stupid at best. Who doesn't know that desktop days are numbered. Honestly, how many desktops are you buying these days. Laptops are powerful and can carry the same tasks as a desktop machine plus provides mobility. So the transition is obvious. The analysis should be more like how many people have shelved notebook buying plans and switched to mobile phones (which I think is 0%) or switched to tablet devices like ipads etc., ipads/android tablets is where Intel has been bleeding until end of last year losing 90+ business to ARM. But Intel has woke up to this call, the future will be bright for Intel in this space as well as they will be bring same power and performance to even mobile phones. This game is not new to Intel. They were challenged like during notebook transition also. Google around for companies Transmeta etc., Where are they now? ARM will have the same future? The answer depends...I will leave it at that argument will take a couple of pages...</Msg><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1363346131162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:15:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363347067954-19</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>An overextended market always has a mean reversion. It may not be tomorrow but it won't be very far away. There is probably a lot of pressure on those who are underinvested but I would probably wait for a pullback to buy in. Also, while sticking with the uptrend, it is a good idea to get some hedges for the next one or two months as VIX (11.30) dropped to another multiyear low. The major indexes continue to move in the same pattern as they did in 2012 when the market topped in late March and then spent April and May in a correction.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1363347067954</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:31:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363347398545-20</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro sales hit 400K in a hurry</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363326581187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, how much does Intel make off of that? Gross $100/unit, so all of $40 million, about 0.1% of revenues for a month's work? Could be a per cent or two of total revenues annualized. Not too shabby.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363347398545</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363347617314-21</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro sales hit 400K in a hurry</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363326581187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm going to miss the desktop era. Sort of reminds me of steam locomotives, etc. I think this "analysis" reflects a delayed replacement cycle.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363347617314</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:40:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363347755229-22</Id><Topic><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1363347067954</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:31:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As if there were "laws of physics" governing market moves. What you're saying is, "markets sort of go up and down sometimes" and "I can't predict what and when." Sort of like getanid's peri-menopausal mood swings.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363347755229</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 07:42:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363349088151-23</Id><Title>A post from Khitchdees other personality regarding Surface Pro</Title><Msg>khitchdee•5 hours ago . +The sales numbers have spoken. It looks like Microsoft has a veritable hit on their hands. With the intro of Haswell, some of the criticism around this PC will get addressed. Also, this leads the way for core series chips to be put to use in tablets which is probably a win for core series sales volumes. If I was Qualcomm or NVidia, I would be very scared about competition for tablet chips in this form which neither has a chance of competing with at least on the performance front. Windows 8 it seems is set to take off as a touch OS albeit a little slowly contrary to earlier reports</Msg><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1363349088151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 08:04:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363349901728-24</Id><Title>Intel price targets of 16 and 18</Title><Msg>The people placing these targets WANT TO BUY Intel at that price, so why not try to help get it there? Remember Romit Shah? I haven't heard a word from him since he got his second chance to buy Intel at 19. Not a peep.</Msg><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1363349901728</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 08:18:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363350508544-25</Id><Topic><Title>Intel price targets of 16 and 18</Title><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1363349901728</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 08:18:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>160 to 180, you forgot the 0</Msg><Username>jayl1961</Username><Timestamp>1363350508544</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 08:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363351632601-26</Id><Topic><Title>I wonder what</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363323884919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:04:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You couldn't dodge the draft simply by going abroad. His number either came up or it didn't.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1363351632601</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 08:47:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363351854359-27</Id><Topic><Title>Intel price targets of 16 and 18</Title><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1363349901728</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 08:18:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How are board posters able to drive down the price? Message people have a measly amount of shares to short. (and there are some people, like Nuff, who don't own any. Maybe he could short his aliases.)</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363351854359</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 08:50:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363352068891-28</Id><Topic><Title>Intel price targets of 16 and 18</Title><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1363349901728</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 08:18:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm talking about Analysts that have the national stage, sir. Not board poster. Jeez.</Msg><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1363352068891</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 08:54:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363352907275-29</Id><Title>Just for Fun, Wally and Ashraf should look at ARM's chart today</Title><Msg>You guys are an embarrassment and COMPLETE amateurs.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363352907275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363352985301-30</Id><Topic><Title>Just for Fun</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363294257303</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Care to run that chart again, amateur hour boy? ARM up 4 percent pre-market.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363352985301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:09:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363353093607-31</Id><Title>When someone post "look at this report" your best option is to look for the IGNORE button...</Title><Msg>Cleans out a a lot of garbage...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1363353093607</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363353281114-32</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH 50 DMA breached</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363176408900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 08:06:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much is it down today?</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353281114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:14:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363353287507-33</Id><Topic><Title>Importan info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>seanlacroix518</Username><Timestamp>1363042083166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 18:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report</Msg><Username>john.freeman14</Username><Timestamp>1363353287507</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:14:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363353355662-34</Id><Topic><Title>ARM AH</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363209284288</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:14:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please advise as to the current status of this post. Bwah ahah! AMATEUR.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353355662</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363353378687-35</Id><Topic><Title>Another Bad Day for the ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363113635637</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 14:40:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol.....</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353378687</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:16:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363353494063-36</Id><Title>Hey Wallisweaver</Title><Msg>Intel up 2 pennies, ARMH up almost 2 dollars. Will you come out today to address the peasents that follow your amazing Stock Market Knowledge or will you just FABRICATE some more lies. Bwah-ah-ah !!!!!!</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353494063</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:18:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363353560340-37</Id><Topic><Title>Intel price targets of 16 and 18</Title><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1363349901728</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 08:18:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can undertand the $18 target. With a dividend at 22.5 cents, $18 results in a 5% yield. The GS $16 target is a 5.6% dividend yield. That seems extreme. The short interest has increased about 1m shares per day (except 1 two week period recently) and those shorting that many shares know how to punch through the share repurchase program rule restrictions.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363353560340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:19:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363353648068-38</Id><Topic><Title>Just for Fun, Wally and Ashraf should look at ARM's chart today</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363352907275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see the rise today as an opportunity to re-short the block that I covered the other day. The SGS IV hype is probably driving ARM up, but it is inevitable that Intel and Imagination Tech (MIPS) will start to significantly pressure ARM's monopoly.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363353648068</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363353735207-39</Id><Title>Wally and Ashraf, please come lecture us on the ARM Bubble again</Title><Msg>....and while you are at it, tell us how responsible it is to short stocks. We'd like to teach our children how to be as wreckless as you. Then again, you have no short position and are only saying you do so as to pump Intel. You are both degenerates.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353735207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:22:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363353763284-40</Id><Topic><Title>Just for Fun, Wally and Ashraf should look at ARM's chart today</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363352907275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You aren't short anything. You are a lying litle weasel.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353763284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:22:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363354709057-41</Id><Topic><Title>How Does Websters Spell TURD- I-N-T-E-L</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363290618490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude, If you think I am someone else simply ping my IP address.... I don't know who the fugg you are talking about. What I do know is that every semiconductor on my board was up yesterday except for Insmell.. Why do you defend this turd? Are you a paid columnist for the advertising department of what? I don't care what you do with your career, but this stock is stealing people's money and has been in the crapper forever... When Microsoft, CSCO and Insmell Move you know that every other stock in the market must be way overvalued..</Msg><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363354709057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:38:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363354953205-42</Id><Topic><Title>Just for Fun, Wally and Ashraf should look at ARM's chart today</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363352907275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$44 Call writers trying to save their investment ... http://finance.yahoo.com/news/traders-bet-arm-muscle-higher-082307402.html</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1363354953205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:42:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363354955169-43</Id><Topic><Title>How Does Websters Spell TURD- I-N-T-E-L</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363290618490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 15:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What the H do you care? jerkoff get lost!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1363354955169</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:42:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363355092932-44</Id><Topic><Title>Just for Fun, Wally and Ashraf should look at ARM's chart today</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363352907275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imagination Tech (MIPS) will start to significantly pressure ARM's monopoly ---- MIPS has been after ARM's phone market for years and near the end they where practically giving their cores away for free. What do you think Imagination can bring to the table? As a side, ARM has an ISA monopoly, not a core monopoly. Very different things.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1363355092932</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:44:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363355151785-45</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Ashraf, please come lecture us on the ARM Bubble again</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353735207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is a megacap company. Sorry, but you can't really "pump" a $100B+ company.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363355151785</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:45:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363355271947-46</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353494063</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:18:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, wait til financial results for Intel start showing the margin hit they are going be experiencing in this mobile chip area. Wallis is gonna take a perpetual dump. The chips coming into the server space are coming, no matter how much all these guys say they won't be accepted.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1363355271947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:47:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363355417015-47</Id><Title>INTC down on considerbly high volume for 20 minutes.</Title><Msg>This stock is too much a money maker for options market makers.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1363355417015</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:50:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363355469713-48</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro sales hit 400K in a hurry</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363326581187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haswell improves the Surface Pro by a wide margin. A Core tablet that runs full W8, will probably support multi-boot with Android and other OSs, and have the power of an Ultrabook is very compelling. It won't be cheapest tablet around but it will be the tablet power users will buy.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1363355469713</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363355564116-49</Id><Topic><Title>INTC down on considerbly high volume for 20 minutes.</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1363355417015</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly.... the kill the options buyers... worked good for me today though as I bought back my $21 calls at a discount...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1363355564116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:52:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363355618110-50</Id><Title>painful eliminations</Title><Msg>Intel takes a none stop dump. Never need to wipe.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1363355618110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:53:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363355631049-51</Id><Topic><Title>INTC down on considerbly high volume for 20 minutes.</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1363355417015</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>12m shares traded in the first minute likely as a couple large blocks. INTC opened at $21.61, finished the first minute at $21.58. Otherwise, Intel is trading about 100,000 shares a minute like it usually does.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363355631049</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363355774554-52</Id><Title>This dog has fleas all of a sudden.......</Title><Msg>So much for irrational exuberance......</Msg><Username>waltertobley2000</Username><Timestamp>1363355774554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363355842013-53</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Ashraf, please come lecture us on the ARM Bubble again</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353735207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARMH stock goes up and you act like you've won the war. It was down as the stock market was on a record run and you said nothing. Count your good days. You'll need something to remember.</Msg><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1363355842013</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363356161751-54</Id><Topic><Title>Just for Fun</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363294257303</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wally you are so very confused, ignorance is bliss.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1363356161751</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363356558009-55</Id><Title>Plop Plop Fizz Fizz</Title><Msg>Every morning when I get up and look in the toilet bowl there is a little man swimming around.. His name is Paul Otellini.. He is standing on a brown log ship with the name Insmell inscribed on his sleuth... Every morning I see this, and every morning I do the same thing.. I flush the damn toilet and watch him go down the drain.. After awhile the smell goes away and the sun comes out and the day gets brighter...</Msg><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363356558009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:09:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363356568654-56</Id><Topic><Title>Why Apple will sign with Intel</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363325572737</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:32:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow shorts out in full force today</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363356568654</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:09:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363356589590-57</Id><Title>Max pain</Title><Msg>Option expiry today - max ain = 21</Msg><Username>mrpoorguy</Username><Timestamp>1363356589590</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:09:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363356723788-58</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Ashraf, please come lecture us on the ARM Bubble again</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353735207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf is still in school... with ZERO industry experience Wally et al, too many ids... still lives with his mom... both give their expertise to those fools in industry...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363356723788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:12:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363356851848-59</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung S4 is further proof that that A15 is a power hog</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363324600411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:16:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still no real good explanation why a smart phone needs a quadcore processor with a baby core. The Tegra 3 didn't do such a wonderful job on economizing the power. I suspect some consumers will leave certain apps running in the background that will keep all four cores running and draining the phone's power. They will complain about short battery life. I 'm anxious to see if all this power will be something consumers will appreciate and demand. I think Apple may be right about not making such a big deal about the processor. Consumers really only appreciate only a certain amount of raw processing power then the rest enters the law of diminishing returns. It's hard to defend needing four cores when there isn't many apps that are mufti threaded.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1363356851848</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:14:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363356889129-60</Id><Topic><Title>Latest Intel Buzz</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363025357492</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 14:09:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice post</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363356889129</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:14:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363356938331-61</Id><Topic><Title>Importan info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>seanlacroix518</Username><Timestamp>1363042083166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 18:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>excellent work</Msg><Username>hortonpreston</Username><Timestamp>1363356938331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:15:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363356967631-62</Id><Topic><Title>New Windows-powered tablets threaten iPad's enterprise dominance, claims analyst</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1363300522868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:35:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good post</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363356967631</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:16:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363357038842-63</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell release date ahead of Computex?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363209075387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:11:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good info</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363357038842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:17:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363357072138-64</Id><Topic><Title>Intel has mobile under control</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363142809673</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 22:46:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yup agreed</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363357072138</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:17:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363357159572-65</Id><Topic><Title>ARM, Intel Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362629054994</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 23:04:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good info</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363357159572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:19:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363357360873-66</Id><Topic><Title>Wall St Analysts are SLOW.. They'll figure out TSMC's 20nm in another 6 months.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363307761265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 20:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good post</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363357360873</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363357384448-67</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE will incorporate ALL upcoming smartphones with Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363201680264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 15:08:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good post</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363357384448</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:23:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363357402726-68</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Seeks Additional Professionals for Custom Foundry Division</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362806991974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:29:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good post</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363357402726</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:23:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363357484679-69</Id><Topic><Title>Apple/Intel Deal will happen</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1362678402542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 12:46:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good post</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363357484679</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:24:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363357523218-70</Id><Topic><Title>Build it and they will come</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1362635329952</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 00:48:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good post</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363357523218</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:25:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363357992045-71</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Ashraf, please come lecture us on the ARM Bubble again</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353735207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People have lost more money listening to Nuff. He is truly an embarrassment.</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363357992045</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:33:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363358173342-72</Id><Topic><Title>Just for Fun</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363294257303</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 16:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good Info.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363358173342</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363358207511-73</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Wallisweaver</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353494063</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:18:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363358207511</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:36:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363358246729-74</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Ashraf, please come lecture us on the ARM Bubble again</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353735207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great post.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363358246729</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:37:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363358332359-75</Id><Topic><Title>Another Bad Day for the ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363113635637</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 14:40:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallisweaver never admits he's wrong as rain.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363358332359</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:38:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363358373715-76</Id><Topic><Title>Nice to See</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363286848076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 14:47:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. You gonna apologize for this post? Didn't think so.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363358373715</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:39:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363358710920-77</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Ashraf, please come lecture us on the ARM Bubble again</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353735207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure, just the other day Ashraf informed us that the ARM 64 ISA can't support multi-threading... Hey, He read it on the internet... but then ran away when others informed him he was wrong again...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363358710920</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363359055924-78</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung S4 is further proof that that A15 is a power hog</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363324600411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:16:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still no real good explanation why a smart phone needs a quadcore processor with a baby core. The Tegra 3 didn't do such a wonderful job on economizing the power. I suspect some consumers will leave certain apps running in the background that will keep all four cores running and draining the phone's power. They will complain about short battery life. ---- To be honest there is very little point in having a quadcore processor in a phone fullstop. Very few apps would use that many threads - except benchmarks:) The baby core (in the Tegra 3/4) as you put it, is a core optimized for low power (in it's layout) but it is the same design as the full power core (A9 in Tegra 3 and A15 in the Tegra 4). Basically, when the SoC is doing very little, this baby core runs thus saving power. In the Exynos 5 Octa, a different approach is taken where 1 quad cluster is one processor type (A7) and the other cluster (A15) is a different type. The idea is similar, you use the A7 cluster when doing very little, then power up the A15's when doing heavy work. As the A7 is very small and uses less power than even the A9, so on paper at least you can save a lot of power.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1363359055924</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:50:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363359489772-79</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung S4 is further proof that that A15 is a power hog</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363324600411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:16:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra has 5 cores, and usually only the low-power core is active... Some Games can use 4 cores... fyi, NVidia's next gen phone SOC Tegra 4i has only 2 A9 cores...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363359489772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363359582744-80</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Ashraf, please come lecture us on the ARM Bubble again</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353735207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not perfect, and I, like everyone else, can make mistakes, getanid61 ;)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363359582744</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:59:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363359628378-81</Id><Title>Samsung has over 70% of the smart phone markert and they don't use INTC inside. Thats not good for INTC</Title><Msg>Samsung has over 70% of the smart phone markert and they don't use INTC inside. Thats not good for INTC</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363359628378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363359673085-82</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung has over 70% of the smart phone markert and they don't use INTC inside. Thats not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363359628378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung, like Apple before it will give up market share to the hordes of other players that will enter the market. Many of the new entrants like Lenovo and ZTE will have INTC inside.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363359673085</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:01:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363359688993-83</Id><Title>According to the "experts" this stock should be flying high......</Title><Msg>Across the board.......the worst is a neutral......with several "buy" recommendations...... Why do I always lose on these "great" stocks.......</Msg><Username>waltertobley2000</Username><Timestamp>1363359688993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:01:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363359852819-84</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung has over 70% of the smart phone markert and they don't use INTC inside. Thats not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363359628378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't think so , INTC is in big trouble</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363359852819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:04:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363360429901-85</Id><Topic><Title>According to the "experts" this stock should be flying high......</Title><Username>waltertobley2000</Username><Timestamp>1363359688993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:01:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess that's the case when one lives on a chat board &amp; has a one day time frame.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1363360429901</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:13:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363360712419-86</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Ashraf, please come lecture us on the ARM Bubble again</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353735207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Me too... but you've singled me out to throw any edge you can at me.. not sure why... evidence dictates I've been correct... yet you stick it to me... maybe writing web articles makes you view thing differently...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363360712419</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363360839203-87</Id><Topic><Title>Secret INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>timothy.maldonaldo</Username><Timestamp>1363184916481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks !!</Msg><Username>dale.hollen</Username><Timestamp>1363360839203</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:20:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363360878860-88</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung has over 70% of the smart phone markert and they don't use INTC inside. Thats not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363359628378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no, just reverified. Ashraf is right. Sorry Nuff. INTC will soon soar like an eagle. Everyone is buying here. In fact, no sellers today. Hard to believe but true.</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363360878860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363360954155-89</Id><Title>bubida is faster and more reliable</Title><Msg>Search it out guys. You'll like it.</Msg><Username>alammuha</Username><Timestamp>1363360954155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:22:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363361111574-90</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Ashraf, please come lecture us on the ARM Bubble again</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353735207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>getanid61, I really have nothing against you; I'm sure you're a decent person, and I certainly don't think that things should get "personal" over the stock market. That being said, spamming the INTC boards with "ZOMG ARMH AT 52-WEEK HIGH" is just a little unnecessary -- we are all aware that ARMH is a momentum darling and that INTC is quite hated. Anyway, if I come off as uncivil in the future, feel free to call me out on it. It's not my intention to be so.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363361111574</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:25:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363361167731-91</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung has over 70% of the smart phone markert and they don't use INTC inside. Thats not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363359628378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not with that volume, get ready for the next wave of selling because its coming</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363361167731</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:26:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363361353026-92</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Ashraf, please come lecture us on the ARM Bubble again</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353735207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry Ash, I've had too much fun with ARMH on the INTC board... I do it for the naive who think it's all about the fabs... No matter what you say, what evidence you point them too, it's the same... They view ARMH as they do AMD... and INtel is coming out with something next year...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363361353026</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:29:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363361540008-93</Id><Topic><Title>Plop Plop Fizz Fizz</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363356558009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:09:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For anyone reading this little ditty.. you know it is damn funny... As in the Broadway musical "Annie," Insmells theme song is, "The Sun will come out tomorrow, bet your bottom dollar that tomorrow, there'll be sun." When will that day come Insmell investors? When? When?</Msg><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363361540008</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:32:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363361940839-94</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Ashraf, please come lecture us on the ARM Bubble again</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353735207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>getanid61, You're right; it's not all about the fabs. I have to head out now, but I'd be happy to discuss with you further the headwinds that I see for ARM. Fabs are part of the equation, but not really the deal-breaker. My "main" points are: - As Qualcomm/Nvidia take market share, that's less potential Mali royalties for ARM - Imagination Technologies is not sitting still and will likely be a competitor to ARM and will serve, if anything, to keep ARM's royalty rates in check - Intel gaining market share is also a problem as Intel designs its own cores as well as graphics. Bay Trail uses Intel graphics, and I wouldn't be surprised if Merrifield (22nm phone SoC) did too. - Smartphone market itself is showing signs of slowing growth, and that's where ARM makes the big bucks - ARM in servers is not likely to gain traction; AMD was compatible with INTC and even it could not gain any meaningful market share long term And then of course, there's valuation. At $15-$20, I would be a buyer of ARMH in expectation of steady dividend growth, but at $42, it's just hyped up beyond all reasonable expectations.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363361940839</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363361977925-95</Id><Topic><Title>Secret INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>timothy.maldonaldo</Username><Timestamp>1363184916481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAMMER !!</Msg><Username>daxwang</Username><Timestamp>1363361977925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:39:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363362400641-96</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung has over 70% of the smart phone markert and they don't use INTC inside. Thats not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363359628378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC has been and is still in big trouble, Missed the Cell phone and tablet market way behind and might not ever catch on NOT GOOD</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363362400641</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:46:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363362504953-97</Id><Title>I would not be supprised to see INTC at $15 with a dividend cut</Title><Msg>I would not be supprised to see INTC at $15 with a dividend cut</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363362504953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:48:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363362887283-98</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung has over 70% of the smart phone markert and they don't use INTC inside. Thats not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363359628378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung’s smartphone market share increased from 23% in the December 2011 quarter to 29% in the Decemeber 2012 quarter. Where do you get your 70% number?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363362887283</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363362900049-99</Id><Topic><Title>I would not be supprised to see INTC at $15 with a dividend cut</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363362504953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IMHO that is where she is going. Search some of the latest mutterings that Samsung is saying about Windows devices....pretty negative. I think Sammy has some software surprises coming.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1363362900049</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:55:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363362986389-100</Id><Topic><Title>I would not be supprised to see INTC at $15 with a dividend cut</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363362504953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC might go lower if they eliminate the dividend. INTC price will really drop if they declare bankruptcy. Probability of any of those happening? zero</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363362986389</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:56:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363363028573-101</Id><Topic><Title>I would not be supprised to see INTC at $15 with a dividend cut</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363362504953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>any chance it could go even lower? What about $8 ? What about bankruptcy Nuff? You seem to have a handle on every aspect of this co. You should be an anal- yst :)</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363363028573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:57:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363363111042-102</Id><Topic><Title>Plop Plop Fizz Fizz</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363356558009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:09:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What goes around comes around one day you won't be able to cower behind Troll IDs anymore &amp; you will get your moron Troll head pinched off.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1363363111042</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:58:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363363241662-103</Id><Topic><Title>Wally and Ashraf, please come lecture us on the ARM Bubble again</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363353735207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 09:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"As Qualcomm/Nvidia take market share, that's less potential Mali royalties for ARM" but more market share means more royalties for ARMH, whether it's an ARMH core or proprietary ARM ISA CPU "Imagination Technologies is not sitting still and will likely be a competitor to ARM and will serve, if anything, to keep ARM's royalty rates in check" ARM will still get the CPU royalty, and gonna get more of it... "Intel gaining market share is also a problem" Only if you view this as a ZERO SUM GAME... which it's not... "Smartphone market itself is showing signs of slowing growth, and that's where ARM makes the big bucks" still growing, and there will be new products... "ARM in servers is not likely to gain traction" IT hasn't even started... No ARM64 yet to speak of... and don't be naive and expect the first introductions of ARM64 CPUs to be in all SKUs... LOTS of growth thru the decade... tell you again, don't miss it... "AMD was compatible with INTC and even it could not gain any meaningful market share long term" As I said, BIGGEST most naive mistake is that you compare AMD to ARMH... ARMH is a rubber stamp...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363363241662</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:00:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363364052573-104</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung S4 is further proof that that A15 is a power hog</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363324600411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:16:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anand claims (see his twitter feed) Samsung told him 1.2 GHz for A15 and 1.6 GHz for A7 and the Antutu score of 25K implies that is correct anandtechDOTcom/show/6832/samsungs-galaxy-s-4-introduction-hands-on investorshubDOTadvfnDOTcom/boards/read_msg.aspx?message_id=85700214</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1363364052573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:14:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363364083855-105</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung has over 70% of the smart phone markert and they don't use INTC inside. Thats not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363359628378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would love to be in the trouble intc is in. They are a money making machine and i am happy to be a shareholder. Go intc.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1363364083855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:14:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363364109028-106</Id><Topic><Title>I would not be supprised to see INTC at $15 with a dividend cut</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363362504953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With earnings and margins dropping how likely is it that INTC cuts the dividend 75-100%</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363364109028</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:15:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363364247656-107</Id><Topic><Title>According to the "experts" this stock should be flying high......</Title><Username>waltertobley2000</Username><Timestamp>1363359688993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:01:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One day? You live some mightly long days......... And I live in a cardboard box.......thank you very much..... Try Fiber One......it will help with that congestion.........</Msg><Username>waltertobley2000</Username><Timestamp>1363364247656</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:17:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363364324464-108</Id><Topic><Title>I would not be supprised to see INTC at $15 with a dividend cut</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363362504953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a rumor that the div will be cut over a 100%. What this means is that shareholders will have to pay Intel. It is called a negative dividend reversal of fortune. Uncommon but it does happen.</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363364324464</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:18:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363364528285-109</Id><Title>The problem with buying dividend payers is when they cut the dividend, You lose big time always</Title><Msg>The problem with buying dividend payers is when they cut the dividend, You lose big time always</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363364528285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363364628730-110</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung S4 is further proof that that A15 is a power hog</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363324600411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:16:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sooo to get this Octafrankenstein chip to fit into a phone they overclocked the low power low performance chip to get decent enough base performance and underclocked the high power high performance chip to get not much more performance while still not burning the phone users ;-). 8 cores and the user end result will probably be slightly worse than the dual-core (with HT) Clovertrail+ ! Samsung and ARM are both amateurs in serious performance chip design and it's now showing for all the world to see. 22nm Atom will eat this chip alive.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1363364628730</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363364639522-111</Id><Topic><Title>I would not be supprised to see INTC at $15 with a dividend cut</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363362504953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dividend will not be cut. There is zero change of a cut.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363364639522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:23:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363364731999-112</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with buying dividend payers is when they cut the dividend, You lose big time always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363364528285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:22:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very true. But zero chance of it happening to Intel.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363364731999</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:25:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363364934649-113</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with buying dividend payers is when they cut the dividend, You lose big time always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363364528285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:22:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not with earnings and margins dropping as fast as they are. Good chance I would say</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363364934649</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:28:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363365025655-114</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with buying dividend payers is when they cut the dividend, You lose big time always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363364528285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:22:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My uncle (di)(ck) reads your posts and has the utmost respect for you. You just scared him and he sold all his shares at a huge loss.</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363365025655</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363365394072-115</Id><Topic><Title>According to the "experts" this stock should be flying high......</Title><Username>waltertobley2000</Username><Timestamp>1363359688993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:01:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good question. I think that the general public is told over and over such sound bytes as "PC is Dead," which you read every time you look at Motley Fool posts (which I am avoiding assiduously these days) , and hear from the vaulted analysts at the great crock-houses, like GS's Covello, etc., and they simply act accordingly...they don't buy INTC and the idiots actually short it. And, PC's have been and may continue to be weak. The only thing that will change this is something like AAPL announcing INTC is fabbing for them. Neve rmind that such a deal is only worth a few percent to topline, it will drive the stock up a few bucks. Give us a streak of such announcements, and maybe the fiends on WS will change their tunes. And maybe getanid will be absorbed back into the heaping pile of sh^^^t from whence he came into the world.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363365394072</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:36:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363365455959-116</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung has over 70% of the smart phone markert and they don't use INTC inside. Thats not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363359628378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung is a quality smartphone maker and a desireable customer for Intel. That being said, Samsung's share and influence will decline as other vendors grow, particularly China's Lenovo. Further, Samsung is on a path to migrate off Android to Tizen and Intel is one of the supporters of Tizen. Tizen will get optimized for x86 and have a good shot at Samsung's business.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1363365455959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:37:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363365468640-117</Id><Title>More Bad ARM Technicals</Title><Msg>ARM has now dropped a buck thirty from the pre-open level. Attempts to pump air back into the stock are just not working...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363365468640</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:37:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363365799451-118</Id><Title>Samsung EYETRACKING - will this work when you wear sunglasses ??</Title><Msg>any idea ???</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1363365799451</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:43:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363365833627-119</Id><Topic><Title>More Bad ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363365468640</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:37:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please give it a rest old man....you don't know what the hell you're talking about. Stick with what you know even if it's not much.</Msg><Username>tuoithin</Username><Timestamp>1363365833627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:43:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363366130665-120</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung EYETRACKING - will this work when you wear sunglasses ??</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1363365799451</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:43:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, but you have to bump your head against the screen.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363366130665</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:48:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363367283626-121</Id><Title>Baristas Submits Formal Application for NASDAQ Listing-- news release</Title><Msg>huge$</Msg><Username>goosehunt393</Username><Timestamp>1363367283626</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:08:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363367475007-122</Id><Title>Baristas Submits Formal Application for NASDAQ Listing-- news release</Title><Msg>facts</Msg><Username>goosehunt393</Username><Timestamp>1363367475007</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:11:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363367542781-123</Id><Topic><Title>According to the "experts" this stock should be flying high......</Title><Username>waltertobley2000</Username><Timestamp>1363359688993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:01:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said it.........the fiends on WS.......they should all be hanged.......starting with the criminals at JPM.......</Msg><Username>waltertobley2000</Username><Timestamp>1363367542781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:12:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363367701627-124</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with buying dividend payers is when they cut the dividend, You lose big time always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363364528285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:22:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Other than Q4 when Intel wrote off excess capacity charges, they are fine. ZERO CHANCE since dividend coverage was 40% (the Intel target) even at these low levels. GROSS MARGINS Dec. 31, 2012 58.00% Sept. 30, 2012 63.28% June 30, 2012 63.36% March 31, 2012 64.04% Dec. 31, 2011 64.46% Sept. 30, 2011 63.36% June 30, 2011 60.64% March 31, 2011 61.38% Dec. 31, 2010 64.64% Sept. 30, 2010 65.94% June 30, 2010 67.21% PROFIT MARGINS Dec. 31, 2012 18.31% Sept. 30, 2012 22.09% June 30, 2012 20.94% March 31, 2012 21.21% Dec. 31, 2011 24.20% Sept. 30, 2011 24.37% June 30, 2011 22.67% March 31, 2011 24.60% Dec. 31, 2010 27.76% Sept. 30, 2010 26.62% June 30, 2010 26.82%</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363367701627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:15:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363368079698-125</Id><Title>The benefit with buying dividend payers is when they continually increase the dividend, Investors WIN big time</Title><Msg>and pundits like coinmaker77 crawl back into their holes wondering why they didn't listen to good advice.</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1363368079698</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363368382742-126</Id><Topic><Title>The benefit with buying dividend payers is when they continually increase the dividend, Investors WIN big time</Title><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1363368079698</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>coinmaker isn't even a pundit. He is a 70 yr old man that makes reckless statements to annoy everyone. He states that he is neither long nor short but apparently has an axe to grind. He was embarrassed/bitter over a trade he made awhile back where he took a huge loss on Intel and overpaid on CSCO. Also, he has a feud going with W. Weaver. If Weaver were to state that he hated Intel, Nuff would be touting it.</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363368382742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:26:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363368480495-127</Id><Topic><Title>Importan info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>seanlacroix518</Username><Timestamp>1363042083166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 18:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>superb</Msg><Username>danielyoung215</Username><Timestamp>1363368480495</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363368536312-128</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with buying dividend payers is when they cut the dividend, You lose big time always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363364528285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:22:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good proof that profits and margins are going lower and last Q should have been INTC best Q and it was NO, Get ready for a dividend cut</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363368536312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363368907985-129</Id><Topic><Title>Take a look at this report before you loose your $</Title><Username>caden.campbell</Username><Timestamp>1363298519439</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:01:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Important info</Msg><Username>blakecruz82</Username><Timestamp>1363368907985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:35:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363369031861-130</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung S4 is further proof that that A15 is a power hog</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363324600411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:16:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the clarification on that Blue. I did watch the news videos this morning and there a few neat features, not really certain what the quad core brings to the party. This looks like the defacto Android phone to get for the next year as long as the battery life is decent. I'm still of the opinion that the processor improvements are significant on paper and in benchmarks but for the real world other OS features are more important. The tilt screen to scroll feature may become the next big thing for all smart phones in the next couple of years. Still, it's not that significant of a feature. A 13MP camera on a smartpone? I can speak to that, it's starting to get into a range where the optics will start to matter especially in low light situations. I never say "you don't need all those megapixels" because it's just space on a microsd card or hard drive. More is always better.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1363369031861</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:37:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363369519915-131</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with buying dividend payers is when they cut the dividend, You lose big time always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363364528285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:22:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No dividend cut. zero chance.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363369519915</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363370045297-132</Id><Topic><Title>Plop Plop Fizz Fizz</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363356558009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:09:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is all this #$%$ with doubting my screen name.. I do not use any other names to post.. I started posting on this piece of #$%$ stock over the past few weeks out of sheer boredom and frustration at it's movement and valuation.. The dividend does not help if the stock keeps going down.. Ya know... Stop hatin on a playa... Ya'll just turds anyway and got no skin in da game...</Msg><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363370045297</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 13:54:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363370550616-133</Id><Title>EUROPE is STARTING TO COLLAPSE AGAIN...all bailout $ spent</Title><Msg>Everyone is in. GET OUT!</Msg><Username>sulit_pantel</Username><Timestamp>1363370550616</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:02:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363370656260-134</Id><Title>Interesting Developments</Title><Msg>1.) Hedge fund advisory firm CR Intrinsic fined $600 million. Maybe they'll have time to investigate James Covello next. 2.) Investors Give Samsung Galaxy S4 a Thumbs Down. Headline from CNBC. Doesn't make sense. 3.) Apple up on announcement of Galazy S4. Doesn't make sense. 4.) ARM way up before markets open. Doesn't make sense. Drops significantly during day. Makes sense. 5.) ARM having trouble holding $42. Makes sense. 5.) Intel down. Makes no sense.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363370656260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:04:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363370670070-135</Id><Topic><Title>Secret INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>timothy.maldonaldo</Username><Timestamp>1363184916481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome info , thanks !</Msg><Username>reese.donna</Username><Timestamp>1363370670070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:04:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363370938191-136</Id><Topic><Title>Plop Plop Fizz Fizz</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363356558009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:09:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What is all this #$%$ with doubting my screen name.." [You rub yourself in excrement on a daily basis just like DanaLucy. What does it matter if you're not - your behavior is identical. You say the stock is going down but it's up over 2 bucks since November. So exactly how can you be frustrated over the past few weeks? It's all bs, DanaLucy. Everyone knows...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363370938191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:08:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363371071176-137</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Developments</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363370656260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:04:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You make NO SENSE!!!</Msg><Username>tuoithin</Username><Timestamp>1363371071176</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:11:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363371445099-138</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung S4 is further proof that that A15 is a power hog</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363324600411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:16:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anand, heard wrong, or was told wrong, or tweeted wrong:) It's the other way around (1.2 for the A7, 1.6 for the A15).</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1363371445099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:17:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363371620795-139</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with buying dividend payers is when they cut the dividend, You lose big time always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363364528285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:22:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They always say that every time just before its cut</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363371620795</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:20:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363371643674-140</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung S4 is further proof that that A15 is a power hog</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363324600411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 01:16:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>8 cores and the user end result will probably be slightly worse than the dual-core (with HT) Clovertrail+ ! Samsung and ARM are both amateurs in serious performance chip design and it's now showing for all the world to see. 22nm Atom will eat this chip alive. ---- :) I would put money on it that this chip will beat Atom@22nm in all known benchmarks (except Javacript). I suspect that Clovertrail+ will struggle against even the A9. We shall soon see when the real benchmarks start to arrive...:)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1363371643674</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:20:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363371900898-141</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with buying dividend payers is when they cut the dividend, You lose big time always</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363364528285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:22:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They also say that every time the dividend is NOT CUT too. "dividend cut" is a very minority opinion and it is OK if you share that opinion. "dividend NOT cut" is a very majority opinion and I am part of that group. Dividend coverage supports me. One bad quarter, made worse by Intel writing off idle fab supports you.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363371900898</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:25:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363372252134-142</Id><Topic><Title>Plop Plop Fizz Fizz</Title><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363356558009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:09:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and it's down since the lofty heights of 23.00 on the last earnings report spike. guess that's better than being down from 29 eh waldo?</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1363372252134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:30:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363372435960-143</Id><Title>WOW now forecasting earnings to be down over 21%, Big fall off NOT GOOD</Title><Msg>WOW now forecasting earnings to be down over 21%, Big fall off NOT GOOD</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363372435960</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:33:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363372518026-144</Id><Topic><Title>WOW now forecasting earnings to be down over 21%, Big fall off NOT GOOD</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363372435960</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW next Q is going to be really really BAD</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363372518026</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363372728824-145</Id><Topic><Title>WOW now forecasting earnings to be down over 21%, Big fall off NOT GOOD</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363372435960</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seriously Nuff, if you were in close proximity, I would $hit on a newspaper and have you eat every morsel.</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363372728824</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:38:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363373365146-146</Id><Topic><Title>WOW now forecasting earnings to be down over 21%, Big fall off NOT GOOD</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363372435960</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are you talking about? Earlier you gave 70% of the smartphone market to Samsung. Are you sure you are on the right board? You are not being very careful</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363373365146</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363374409353-147</Id><Title>ARM Giving Up</Title><Msg>ARM has given up an amazing buck fifty from the pre-open high. Investors are exhausted. Pull up the one-day chart if you want to see a truly impressive fade...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363374409353</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363374437025-148</Id><Topic><Title>WOW now forecasting earnings to be down over 21%, Big fall off NOT GOOD</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363372435960</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am sure INTC earnings are going to be down the 21% maybe more</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363374437025</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363375172805-149</Id><Title>TSMC looks weak</Title><Msg>Apple to follow ALTR - no way Apple is going to gamble in particular after ALTR announcement. They already need to concern themself with 450mm In other words, while Samsung may go on supplying A6 processors made using 32-nm/28-nm CMOS to Apple for some time, TSMC looks set to be the incumbent at 20-nm but it may have been made clear to the foundry that Apple is already working with Intel aiming at the 14-nm and 10-nm FinFET as a potential alternative to TSMC's 16-nm FinFET roadmap. There are major hurdles to overcome in regards to ltho - issues like overlay. Not just the fins Just read what ASML has to say...</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363375172805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363375372499-150</Id><Topic><Title>Importan info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>seanlacroix518</Username><Timestamp>1363042083166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 18:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>helt.joseph</Username><Timestamp>1363375372499</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:22:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363375409292-151</Id><Topic><Title>WOW now forecasting earnings to be down over 21%, Big fall off NOT GOOD</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363372435960</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh. So YOU are forecasting the earnings results. Good. I thought you might have a credible source that I had missed.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363375409292</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:23:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363375594377-152</Id><Title>stock will make lots of cash next week (YTRV) 55 MILLION SHARES TRADED</Title><Msg>ANOTHER BIG RUN NEXT WEEK</Msg><Username>pauladaytona500</Username><Timestamp>1363375594377</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:26:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363376149962-153</Id><Title>Guys BCCI Baristas Coffee Company Inc. @ 0.06 BCCI will be listed in Nasdaq under the symbol BAPI . Last chance to buy cheap shares</Title><Msg>Look @ sbux gmcr jva and remember PEET's coffee. Last chance to buy cheap. BCCI will fly @ the open on Monday morning.</Msg><Username>johnjohn5200</Username><Timestamp>1363376149962</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363376176560-154</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Giving Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363374409353</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hate to say it, Wally, but INTC looks weak to me today.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363376176560</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:36:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363376423626-155</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Giving Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363374409353</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor fool. Intel shredded since you called it a strong buy at 29, and you spend every day of your lfie bashing a stock that's up almost ONE HUNDRED PERCENT since you recommended Intel at 29. I mean WHISKEY TANGO FOXTROT is your major malfunction ??? THIS is the definition of madness.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1363376423626</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:40:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363376467997-156</Id><Topic><Title>WOW now forecasting earnings to be down over 21%, Big fall off NOT GOOD</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363372435960</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You better sell before earnings, Big drop coming</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363376467997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:41:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363376868680-157</Id><Topic><Title>WOW now forecasting earnings to be down over 21%, Big fall off NOT GOOD</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363372435960</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 14:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Possible huge cut in div, horrible earnings, big drop in price. Does Intel have any redeeming qualities? My plan is to sell per your recommendation and then hang myself. Appreciate your input.</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363376868680</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:47:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363377137564-158</Id><Topic><Title>Secret INTC Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>timothy.maldonaldo</Username><Timestamp>1363184916481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report</Msg><Username>d.daviesdonnell</Username><Timestamp>1363377137564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:52:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363377438020-159</Id><Title>AMSC receives Tender Offer, review by board</Title><Msg>Acquisition may be approved next week.</Msg><Username>csivomni10</Username><Timestamp>1363377438020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363378891036-160</Id><Title>INTC is a pig and will always be a pig. Wall St hates this pig</Title><Msg>and will take it down every chance it gets.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363378891036</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 16:21:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363379042920-161</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Giving Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363374409353</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well put! I think Wallis is living in denial. Everything that comes from INTC is great even though it's a slow-growth company.</Msg><Username>tuoithin</Username><Timestamp>1363379042920</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 16:24:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363379124041-162</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is a pig and will always be a pig. Wall St hates this pig</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363378891036</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 16:21:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not all .... Signal With 71% Accuracy Says This Tech Icon is a Long-Term 'Buy' Many traders try to make decisions using short-term charts, some looking at charts using bars that update every minute or less. These time frames can be useful but individual traders should normally use longer-term charts. Wall Street powerhouses are competing against high-frequency trading firms for the intraday profits that are available and individual traders probably can't match their advantages. Daily charts could be more useful for individuals, but weekly and monthly charts should also be considered. Recommended Trade Setups: -- Buy INTC at $22 or less -- Set stop-loss at $19 -- Set price target at $25.20 for a potential 22% gain in 21 months, assuming dividend payments remain unchanged -- Buy INTC Jan 2015 20 Calls at $3.50 or less -- Set stop-loss at $1.50 (in dollar terms, the risk is less than the risk of buying the stock) -- Set price target at $5.20 for a potential 49% gain in 22 months</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363379124041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 16:25:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363379281843-163</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is a pig and will always be a pig. Wall St hates this pig</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1363378891036</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 16:21:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poll of the Day Why does will_amd_yu post completely contrary messages? 1.) Bi-polar 2.) DanaLucyVinnieLucifer forgets which ID he is using 3.) Excessive drug and alcohol consumption 4.) Totally nuts 5.) All of the above</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363379281843</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 16:28:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363379915257-164</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Giving Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363374409353</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you day trading? I don't really worry about the day to day stuff. It was prolly the Samsung effect. The new product looks good. ARM is in its hay day so this is not unexpected. But ARM is also topping the hill and it's a long way down from here. Intel is building strength and the sky is the limit. So, this was just another day and another day closer to Haswell which will be much sooner than expected, another day closer to Intel 14nm FinFET volume production and another day closer to another big Intel deal. I'm thinking the Cisco shoe will drop next. And I'm looking forward to more Intel releases in countries that the shills can mock, like the Philippines, which is the fastest growing smartphone market in Asia. Pretty soon the shills will be mocking Intel by saying, "Intel is in 57 small countries!!!" And on the large side, Intel will be in all future ZTE smartphones and ZTE is number 4 or 5 in unit sales in the world. Things are shaping up nicely...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363379915257</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 16:38:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363380056514-165</Id><Title>ARM Showing Strength</Title><Msg>The ARM stock price recovered 3 cents at the end of the day after having dropped a buck fifty in a straight slide down during the day. Fanbois rejoice!!!</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363380056514</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 16:40:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363380366959-166</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Giving Up</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363374409353</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 15:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM is in its hay day -------- hay day/heyday HI-HO WEAVERINO! TOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1363380366959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 16:46:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363380809104-167</Id><Topic><Title>Importan info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>seanlacroix518</Username><Timestamp>1363042083166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 18:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>love it</Msg><Username>miguelnelson69</Username><Timestamp>1363380809104</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 16:53:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363380822336-168</Id><Title>CSCO ROOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOLZ!!!</Title><Msg>INTEL IS FOR TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOZ and FOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOLZ! Who's your Daddy, Wallazzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz?</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1363380822336</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 16:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363380905006-169</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO ROOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOLZ!!!</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1363380822336</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 16:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOLZ</Msg><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1363380905006</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 16:55:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363383375954-170</Id><Title>Poor Lucy_Nuff, Intel bagholder</Title><Msg>He watches every tick because he's an underwater long. He posts pro-Intel digitimes articles under his Will_amd_you alias and then responds to that same thread saying that digi times articles are BS. LOL! He's crazier than those that he calls crazy. Check his post history. He used to say Intel would not go up until Mr. Weaver #$%$ his pants. He said it over and over until he morphed into Lucy_nuff, a guy, in yet another weak moment, claimed how happy he was that Intel was the cornerstone of his portolio at 29. Wally and Lucy, two crusty old farts pillow fighting every day. Ever seen a senior citizen thug? ROFL!</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363383375954</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 17:36:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363385369969-171</Id><Topic><Title>Importan info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>seanlacroix518</Username><Timestamp>1363042083166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 18:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great job</Msg><Username>efrain.mercer</Username><Timestamp>1363385369969</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 18:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363388999974-172</Id><Title>market go lower now till they pass bill white house buy it after that my veiw</Title><Msg>ok</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1363388999974</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 19:09:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363389794351-173</Id><Topic><Title>Get latest Information in INTC</Title><Username>josephgray404</Username><Timestamp>1363381440673</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 17:04:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAMMER !!</Msg><Username>daxwang</Username><Timestamp>1363389794351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 19:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363390225254-174</Id><Topic><Title>Take a look at this report before you loose your $</Title><Username>caden.campbell</Username><Timestamp>1363298519439</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:01:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAMMER !!</Msg><Username>daxwang</Username><Timestamp>1363390225254</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 19:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363393980925-175</Id><Title>New Atom will rock!</Title><Msg>CloverTrail+ already beat the soon-to-be-released snapdragons and exynos in performance and power. New redesigned Quad-core Atom on 22nm tri-gate will have twice the performance and power will put snap and exynos to shame. The new Atom will appear in devices for holiday shopping season!</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363393980925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 20:33:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363394318187-176</Id><Title>DUAL FORM-FACTOR, DUAL OS</Title><Msg>Intel has announced that with patch for Android 4.2.2, you'll be able to dual boot Android with systems running Windows 8! Imagine getting a hybrid PC like a Lenovo Yoga or a Surface Pro that can also run Android and all Android apps!</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363394318187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 20:38:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363394910519-177</Id><Title>PCs will be making a come back this year</Title><Msg>Look at what Intel has set up: - Haswell launch in June - Quad-core Atom around September - Web TV service and set-top box around September (my guess) - Dual boot option for Android and Windows 8 - LTE availability for in first half of this year When you add it all together you have one compelling case to get a new Hybrid PC. With the Hybrid PC you get the following: - Use both as a PC and a tablet - 10 hours of battery life - ability to run Windows 8 apps and games which you cannot do with RT - ability to dual boot and run Android and enjoy all android apps and games - will support WiDi and so allows you to stream videos on your TV if you have the set-top box - can watch live TV if you sign up with Intel's TV service - will support LTE when you need data connection on the go</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363394910519</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 20:48:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363396135923-178</Id><Title>With a new Atom chip, Intel’s smartphone BFF is ZTE</Title><Msg>After years of trying to crack the mobile market there are still relatively few smartphones with the “Intel Inside” branding. Last year was a bit of a breakthrough, however, as Intel silicon powered the Motorola Razr i handset. Yet few other handset makers have followed suit, leaving Intel with few places to put a mobile foothold. The situation could be changing. On Tuesday, Chinese handset maker ZTE announced a strategic collaboration with Intel on the chipmaker’s latest Atom processor. The Intel Atom Z2580, announced at last month’s Mobile World Congress event, is the focus of the strategy. More important is the fact that ZTE is a fast growing handset maker, currently the No. 4 seller of mobile phones in the world. That data point alone is good news for Intel because it’s not likely the company will get its chips inside devices made by Samsung, Apple, Nokia — although that would be an interesting WinTel mobile play — or many of the other household name mobile device makers. Even better for Intel is ZTE’s base of China: The handset maker’s home country is expected to see big growth in smartphone sales thanks to its large population, improving mobile broadband networks and current lack of smartphone penetration compared to the U.S. and Europe. As a result, depending on how many smartphones come from this agreement, Intel has a key hardware partner in an important mobile market. From gigaoam</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363396135923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 21:08:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363398250608-179</Id><Title>Intel and Google are teaming up to circumvent Windows</Title><Msg>Microsoft really p*ssed Intel off my partnering with arm. Now it's pay back time! Three significant piece of news recently: 1) Intel has announced that with Android 4.2.2 you will be able to dual-boot it with systems running Windows 8 2) Google introduced their own branded Chromebook PC (the Pixel) running a Core i5 processor 3) Andy Rubin stepped down as Android head, to be replaced by current head of Chrome OS First, by making Android available on Windows machines, what is the point of using Windows 8 apps on the Metro UI? Developers will probably ask the same question. Second, with the Pixel, you have to ask yourself why you would need a Core i5 to run such a simple OS such as Chrome. The Pixel is surely meant to run Windows 8 as well. We will soon see a dual boot option or some sort of software that will allow the Chrome OS to run on top of Windows 8. Third, with Any Rubin stepping down, it really signals Chrome OS will be merging with Android. There you have it. Google gets into PCs and slowly build out the web/office tools that will slowly be embrace by corporations and consumers alike.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363398250608</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 21:44:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363399548320-180</Id><Topic><Title>Intel and Google are teaming up to circumvent Windows</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363398250608</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 21:44:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the way, with Intel helping Google get into the PCs, don't you think Google will return the favor and help Intel get into phones (even though Intel doesn't really need it). Expect the much anticipated Google X Phone to carry Intel inside.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363399548320</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 22:05:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363400351561-181</Id><Topic><Title>With a new Atom chip, Intel’s smartphone BFF is ZTE</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363396135923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 21:08:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Smart Phone Market Share in China by sales in 2012 Samsung 18% Lenovo 13.2% Apple 11% Huawei 9.8% CoolPad 9.7% Nokia 3.7% Others 34.5%</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1363400351561</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 22:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363400658120-182</Id><Topic><Title>With a new Atom chip, Intel’s smartphone BFF is ZTE</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363396135923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 21:08:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Between Lenovo and ZTE that's a HUGE chunk of change headed Intel's way. Make no mistake, Intel is a stock you buy at these levels and hold for a LONG LONG time. Also, Intel knows that by increasing the dividend, the "low" PPS will increase. One day, after several more Dividend increases, when Intel is priced at 25, it will be paying a 5% Dividend. Everybody wins when Intel increases the Dividend, including Intel.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363400658120</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 22:24:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363400732222-183</Id><Topic><Title>PCs will be making a come back this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363394910519</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 20:48:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you just used your Paul.Otelini alias to post all this ? Embarassed by your Intel 3.00 EPS call last year?</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1363400732222</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 22:25:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363401493720-184</Id><Title>Crazy Big DELL 18 inch Windows Tablet</Title><Msg>Dell Reveals Crazy Big 18-inch Windows 8 Tablet/AIO 2:00 PM - March 15, 2013 by Kevin Parrish - source: Dell Is it a super-huge tablet, a super-slim AIO PC, or a cool hybrid? Ok, so maybe it's not a tablet but rather a super-thin AIO PC called the Dell XPS 18. Slated to launch here in the United States on April 16 starting at USD 899.99, it will sport an 18.4-inch capacitive touch Full HD display -- nearly twice that of Apple's iPad -- but have an overall weight of 4.85 pounds. That said, should it be characterized as a super-huge tablet or as a super-light AIO? You be the judge. "It features much of the power you would expect from an AIO while still being surprisingly portable, so you can use it in many different rooms in the house," said Dell chief blogger Lionel Menchaca. "It works well as a streaming media device in the living room, viewing recipes or cooking videos in the kitchen, or as a homework machine in the kids' room." While the specs aren't available online, the device will be sold with a Bluetooth mouse and keyboard, with custom flip-out feet to convert the device from a tablet to a desktop. The "starting" model will reportedly include a dual-core Pentium ULV processor and a 320 GB HDD. Higher-end models are said to include a third-generation Intel Core i7 CPU, 8 GB of RAM and a 512 GB SSD. The battery will offer around five hours of life on a single charge. "It features an aluminum back with soft grip for traction and comfort," Menchaca said. "Overall craftsmanship and flexibility were two key focuses for our design team. You can use it in a number of ways: on an adjustable powered stand so it can be used with a wireless keyboard and mouse, on a desk or surface with flip-out feet so it can be set to a comfortable viewing angle, totally flat for collaborating or browsing, or even like a newspaper for reading."</Msg><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1363401493720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 22:38:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363401736289-185</Id><Title>Intel and Qualcom to speak</Title><Msg>Intel, Qualcomm will speak on mobile chip development Mike Rogoway, The Oregonian By Mike Rogoway, The Oregonian on March 15, 2013 at 11:55 AM Few companies illustrate the impact of the mobile computing revolution better than Qualcomm and Intel. Qualcomm has enjoyed a surge of business as electronics demand shifts from the PC to mobile devices, with wireless capabilities tightly integrated with microprocessors. Sales leaped nearly 30 percent last year despite an overall poor year for the chip industry. With a market capitalization topping $110 billion, and its stock near its highest point since the XXXXX era, Qualcomm surpassed Intel last year as the world's most valuable semiconductor company. Intel's sales are more than double Qualcomm's, but those revenues -- and its share price -- are stagnant. Reliant on the slumbering PC industry, Intel has been unable to gain traction in the mobile market. Another big difference: Intel makes its own chips, and bears the cost of all its technology upgrades. Qualcomm contracts that work out. Over time, Intel's manufacturing prowess may give it an advantage -- but that's a long game. The contrasting visions will be on stark display May 1 at a breakfast forum organized by SEMI, a trade group of chip industry suppliers. The event pairs Qualcomm director of business development Samir Kumar with Rohit Vidwans, director of products for Atom -- Intel's mobile chip. The May 1 event, at Intel's Ronler Acres campus in Hillsboro, begins at 8 a.m. Advance tickets are $55 for SEMI members, or $75 for nonmembers. (Prices go up $20 after April 17.)</Msg><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1363401736289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 22:42:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363401894889-186</Id><Topic><Title>PCs will be making a come back this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363394910519</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 20:48:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I take it you don't agree that PCs will make a comeback this year? All I can say is, there's big difference between laptops from last year and hybrid laptops from this year. This year you will be seeing hybrids that are thinner, lighter and have 10 hours battery life. Look up 'North cape' for what a Haswell hybrid will look like. When the new quad-core Atom (bay trail) comes out, you will see hybrids that are thinner and lighter than the HP Envy 2 or Samsung Ativ Smart PC and have much much more power. I expect hybrids to start cannibalizing tablets since people like the idea of having a tablet and PC in one device.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363401894889</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 22:44:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363403912173-187</Id><Topic><Title>PCs will be making a come back this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363394910519</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 20:48:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is the rancid att4glte, and god knows who else..the most disgusting (sub)-human on this board. He has a severe personality disorder, probably having been multiply abused as a child by his drunken father, and emotionally abandoned by his mother, and constant bullying in the schoolyard for his small stature and obesity. Pathetic, but best to put him on perma-ignore.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363403912173</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 23:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>