<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-12"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357970660255-1</Id><Title>Wallis, did you read the barron's piece on ARM CEO interview.</Title><Msg>The headline was "ARM CEO East Says Phooey to the ‘Transistor Cliff’ " Your thoughts??</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357970660255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:04:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357973924552-2</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, did you read the barron's piece on ARM CEO interview.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357970660255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:04:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What else can you say when you can't control the ability to get your technology manufactured at the the advanced process that your competitor can (and pulling away). You dismiss it. And he keeps using the power advantage argument.</Msg><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1357973924552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:58:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357977979914-3</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH new 52-week high today AGAIN !!!</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357948456120</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 18:54:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Poor, poor NVDA " Indeed.... "Remember how you belittled Intel TriGate " Been hearing for years the term FinFET... "telling everybody TriGate was (only) specifically applicable to CPU manufacturing" Have NO CLUE what you're referring to... I see all advanced geometries moving to FinFETs... "My semi equips doing very well because I know the ARM ecosystem is going to buy a lot of goodies." I've done well with ASML &amp; CYMI too... "And there's always a faster gun" ARMH had a new 52-week high today... how fast a gun is INTC...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357977979914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 03:06:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357978535973-4</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, did you read the barron's piece on ARM CEO interview.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357970660255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:04:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://blogs.barrons.com/techtraderdaily/2013/01/11/arm-ceo-east-says-phooey-to-the-transistor-cliff/?mod=yahoobarrons More gems of stupidity ... 'When I propose to East that ARM's taking a larger share of the traditional WinTel notebook chip market would be a psychological victory of some sort, he brushes aside the suggestion. “It doesn't matter because it's already evident to most people that these kinds of ARM-based systems are eventually going to take over” the large bulk of traditional computing.' 'In the Intel worldview, a kind of “Transistor Cliff,” if you will, is one very possible end game. To East, it is nonsense. He offers that the things that sell individual chips are “How much does the chip cost, how fast does it go, and how much power does it consume,” considered in concert. If chips can do that in any existing technology, “Why even move to the next node?” “The only benefit of a new geometry is to get more chips out of a wafer,” adds East. But if wafers end up costing twice as much because double patterning — the application of multiple additional “mask layers” — is needed to get to smaller geometries, than the additional cost may outweigh any benefits. When I reply that a transistor cliff would imply some companies wouldn't be able to progress at all, he replies, “I'm not sure I buy the notion of a transistor cliff; I think there's a lot of marketing fluff in that.”'</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357978535973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 03:15:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357978934391-5</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, did you read the barron's piece on ARM CEO interview.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357970660255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:04:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“The only benefit of a new geometry is to get more chips out of a wafer,” "But if wafers end up costing twice as much because double patterning — the application of multiple additional “mask layers” — is needed to get to smaller geometries, than the additional cost may outweigh any benefits." ------------------------------------------------------------------------- Can only repeat: ARMH is a rubber stamp...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357978934391</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 03:22:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357981532662-6</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, did you read the barron's piece on ARM CEO interview.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357970660255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:04:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'ARMH is a rubber stamp...' That means nothing if the product is not competitive e.g. Windows RT. Customers will not be railroaded into products they don't want to buy no matter how many vendors try.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357981532662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 04:05:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357983182048-7</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, did you read the barron's piece on ARM CEO interview.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357970660255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:04:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'ARMH is a rubber stamp...' That means nothing if the product is not competitive e.g. Windows RT. Customers will not be railroaded into products they don't want to buy no matter how many vendors try. ------------------------------------------------------------- It meant that if the products are competitive, it won't be due to ARMH... their customers do the heavy lifting...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1357983182048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 04:33:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357998201986-8</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo ThinkPad X1: Amazon Price and Release Date Details</Title><Username>tiderunner3</Username><Timestamp>1304772583000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2011-05-07 08:49:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really free??? let me check...</Msg><Username>j.ivans</Username><Timestamp>1357998201986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:43:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357999400043-9</Id><Topic><Title>Ballmer was right</Title><Username>dtmstran</Username><Timestamp>1357956798258</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 21:13:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ha, ha, ha...and MS needs to keep buying their own RT tablets too. There was an article prior to Surface release that they bought about 150,000 of these Surface/Windows RT tablets for free distribution to their employees, remember? MS can keep making Surface/Windows RT tablets for their own internal use and tout some garbage volume data till they actually kill Windows RT.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1357999400043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:03:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357999460863-10</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, did you read the barron's piece on ARM CEO interview.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357970660255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:04:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can only repeat: ARMH is a rubber stamp... ----------------------------------------------------------- ARMH is not a rubber stamp. Wrong analogy. ARMH is a PIMP, shopping the girls around the city. Providing them protection. ARMH BIG.little is the kind of monster you get after a failed attempt to self-abort. TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYYY</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1357999460863</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:04:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358001847830-11</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis: RE: shorting ARMH</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357957796585</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 21:29:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You'd rather see Arm shares fail than see Intel shares succeed. You are a certifiable crackpot! HI-HO WEAVERINO!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358001847830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:44:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358002401995-12</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, did you read the barron's piece on ARM CEO interview.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357970660255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:04:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Earlier East used the power advantage argument but now that that is mostly gone he's moved to the next line of defense which is the size of the ARM ecosystem and ARM's marketshare. Intel is giving East no good entry point for servers and ARM was just thrown out of the Samsung's Windows tablet. One by one, Intel is dismantling ARM's defenses along with East's grandiose claims.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1358002401995</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:53:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358004800855-13</Id><Title>ARM's a rubber stamp and transistors don't matter</Title><Msg>LMAO.....</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1358004800855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:33:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358007379002-14</Id><Title>The writing's on the Haswell</Title><Msg>The writing on the laptop: What Intel’s Haswell reference Ultrabook tells us about tomorrow January 11, 2013 By Matt Smith Intel’s new Haswell architecture will release in mid-2013. We piece together information revealed during and before CES 2013 to learn what it will offer. Intel only spent a few minutes talking about its upcoming GPU architecture, Haswell, at CES 2012. That’s probably because the company didn’t have anything new to say. Still, CES provides a once-a-year chance to check out everything a company is doing. We spent some time putting together the pieces of the Haswell puzzle by examining Intel’s announcement, the reference Ultrabook, and the company’s in-booth demos. There’s one number from the press conference on Monday that keeps coming back to us – 13. That’s the battery life Intel claims a Haswell Ultrabook will provide. Claims like this are exaggerated as a rule, but adjusting for that still brings us to an estimated endurance of between eight to 10 hours. Current Ultrabooks and laptops based on 3rd-gen Intel Core processors (aka Ivy Bridge) usually last five to seven hours in our tests. It seems Haswell will offer a gigantic boost. Efficiency improvements that increase endurance often allow for smaller, lighter systems. Haswell will be no exception. Intel’s convertible Ultrabook reference design is 17mm thick with keyboard attach and shrinks to 10mm when the keyboard is removed. Also displayed was NEC’s LaVie X, a conventional laptop powered by Haswell that’s 12.8mm thin. Graphics performance is a focus of the new architecture. It includes a revised integrated graphics component, code-named “GT3,” which Intel claims is on par with current mid-range graphics. To prove this the company used a demo that pit a Haswell CPU with GT3 integrated graphics against an Nvidia GT 650M in Dirt 3: Showdown playing at 1080p. There’s no easily discernible difference between them. It’s worth noting that Intel has almost certainly optimized its drivers for this specific demo and, in addition, we don’t know the details of the graphics settings used (though Intel says it used the same graphics settings on both systems). Still, this demo shows significant improvement over the current HD 4000 IGP. There was another interesting video technology on display, though only briefly – Smart Frame. It is meant to address the fact that laptops and tablets work best with different bezel sizes. On a laptop a small bezel is desirable, but a moderate bezel is required on a tablet to provide a grip-able surface. Smart Frame resolves this by using driver trickery to automatically switch between a 13.3-inch and 11.6-inch effective display size. We suspect the technology simply under-scans the display and ignores touch at the display’s borders, but Intel has so far remained secretive about Smart Frame’s specifics. Other features shown by the Haswell reference Ultrabook have less to do with technology than they do with business. Intel has mandated that 4th-generation Ultrabooks must have a touchscreen to earn the moniker – so it was no surprise to see that the reference design shown this year was a convertible rather than a clamshell. Also mandatory is Intel Wireless Display, an existing technology that lets users extend a laptop’s picture to a monitor or HDTV via an HDMI doggle. Making this a requirement will encourage the development of convertibles and premium laptops but may also prevent prices from falling too far. Intel proudly stated that it wants touchscreen models to sell for $599, which is about $200 less than today’s cheapest touchscreen models – but not any less than today’s entry-level Ultrabooks. Haswell won’t be out until mid-year. When it does arrive, however, we’ll see a wave of 4th-gen ultrabooks that expand on current strengths. Many models will be convertibles that offer thickness and battery life to rival ARM-powered tablets. Overall performance will improve, as well, mostly notable in graphics - an important extra. Intel HD4000 is adequate for many games, but only at 720p, and most ultrabooks are moving on to 1600×900 or 1080p displays. And while the Ultrabooks sold later this year may not be cheaper, they should offer more of everything for the same price.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358007379002</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:16:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358007412743-15</Id><Title>Forget the 7W debate....13 hour batter life is what consumers care about</Title><Msg>Thanks.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358007412743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:16:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358008803936-16</Id><Topic><Title>Forget the 7W debate....13 hour batter life is what consumers care about</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358007412743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:16:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For Windows devices they want to run all their apps and connect to their networks without problems. They want good performance for their applications and graphics. They don't care about TDP or how the CPU maker achieves it, they are just concerned how long it lasts. This is why the Y Ivy Bridge has has virtually overnight forced manufacturers to abandon the ARM based RT tablet and build new x86 designs. x86 is where all the action will be this year for Windows tablets. And since x86 also runs Android and other forms of Linux there's is a very good possibility that users can run multiple OS'es on the same device.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1358008803936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:40:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358011214409-17</Id><Title>They finally figure it out - ...is about to hit the fan</Title><Msg>But if wafers end up costing twice as much because double patterning — the application of multiple additional “mask layers” — is needed to get to smaller geometries, than the additional cost may outweigh any benefits. They finally figure it out - for a long time I predicted margins for fabless will come down the ...is about to hit the fan East sems to be completely disconnected to what the foundries are doing - couple months ago East said Intel has no advantage in process technology for mobile ICs, says ARM CEOIntel ....BUT "We’re supporting all the independent foundries," says East. That includes 20nm planar bulk CMOS and 16nm finfet at TSMC; 20nm planar bulk CMOS and 14nm finfet at Samsung and 20nm planar bulk CMOS, 20nm FD-SOI and 14nm finfet at Globalfoundries. What a dork “The only benefit of a new geometry is to get more chips out of a wafer,” adds East. Just google DDR4 for example - what are the benefits of DDR4 for example for data centers? 20% reduction in power requirements NVDA calls for 450mm wafers and they (TSMC, Samsung) all follow Intel investing in ASML/litho - I suppose GF is out of spare cash</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358011214409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:20:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358011314711-18</Id><Topic><Title>The writing's on the Haswell</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358007379002</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:16:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A $599 13 hour powerful thin light 13.3" laptop. Hmmm, seems to me the laptop form factor will get a new lease of life in 2013. Another thing to note is that Q4 PC sales were still actually up a couple of per cent over Q3.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358011314711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:21:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358011527361-19</Id><Topic><Title>Forget the 7W debate....13 hour batter life is what consumers care about</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358007412743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:16:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Clovertrail is what killed WindowsRT but the 7W Ivy bridges and 13 hour Haswells will probably turn some Android tablet users back to Windows. So Defense turns to Offense as in all good football plays ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358011527361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:25:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358014528670-20</Id><Title>Samsung not crazy about Windows RT at all.</Title><Msg>CNET reports that Samsung took a number of factors into consideration. First off, feedback from retail partners showed that there was a certain lack of interest in Windows RT devices. Combined with the fact that there's a lot of consumer confusion about the platform, Samsung felt that there was "a lot of heavy lifting we still needed to do to educate the customer on what Windows RT was." And, by "heavy lifting," Samsung exec Mike Abary meant it was going to take a bunch of money that the company didn't feel was worth investing. That's especially true because Microsoft hasn't exactly been carrying its own weight in the education department, and it should have been doing most of the heavy lifting, anyway. Just weeks before the launch of Windows 8 and Windows RT, Microsoft sales reps still weren't adequately trained on how to explain the differences to potential buyers. The Verge went on the Microsoft Store website pretending to be an average consumer, and chatted up numerous reps who failed to properly explain how different the platforms truly are. The Verge: What's the difference between Windows 8 and Windows RT, or are they the same thing? Microsoft rep: They're pretty much the same thing, there is no real huge difference beside the RT is more touch friendly. This was just days before launch, and even sales reps at Microsoft retail stores didn't fare much better. Needless to say, they're not pretty much the same thing, and there is a huge difference. Microsoft has a page buried on its website outlining the differences, but how many people will unearth it, compared to how many stroll into a physical Microsoft Store? Wait and see Abary also said that Samsung was going to have to make certain trade-offs to keep its Windows RT tablets competitive -- trade-offs it didn't want to make. Windows RT devices cost less, in part because ARM chips cost less than Intel processors; but all tablets are inevitably compared to Apple's iPad that starts at $499 for the newest models. Abary added, "We didn't necessarily attain the price point that we hoped to attain." That's not Microsoft's fault, according to Samsung, but it is what it is. It's a little ironic that Steve Ballmer was displaying a Samsung-built Windows RT device with a Snapdragon just this week when he made a surprise appearance at Qualcomm's CES keynote. Samsung's not scrapping the devices altogether, and it didn't specify its plans for outside of the U.S., but it wants to wait and see where the RT market goes before jumping in. Winners and losers Intel is a clear winner here, because it will continue to maintain its hegemony within the Windows PC market (which is shrinking). Microsoft's Surface Pro, which runs on an Intel chip, is due out later this month starting at $900. It's a tough break for Qualcomm, as Windows RT has been its best shot at tapping the tablet market, while it has little to no traction in Google Android tablets. Other ARM-chip makers may similarly be disappointed if the broader Windows RT market fails to develop. That would include NVIDIA, whose Tegra 3 is in Microsoft's current Surface RT, which had a "modest start." Windows RT was the ARM army's hope at cracking into PCs, but it doesn't look like they're going to have much of a chance.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358014528670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:15:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358015501726-21</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis: RE: shorting ARMH</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357957796585</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 21:29:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Waldo, always bullish on INTC and has been trashing ARMH for quite some time as it reaches an all time high. Fails to realize that his beloved INTC is almost as overbght as ARMH.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1358015501726</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:31:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358017113238-22</Id><Topic><Title>SMART MONEY GUYS DALIO AND COHEN DUMP INTEL SHARES</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1355500108992</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:48:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SMART MONEY GUYS DALIO AND COHEN DUMP INTEL AT THE BOTTOM Hi Hi Too funnio!</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1358017113238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:58:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358017170160-23</Id><Topic><Title>An INTEL WARNING IS IMMINENT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1354739684483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 15:34:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HI HO TOO FUNNNNNIO !!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1358017170160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:59:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358017311296-24</Id><Topic><Title>FORBES COMMENT</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1353790506880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:55:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FORBES: Intel Surprise Winner at CES. HI-HO TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNIO! Intel is Surprise Winner at CES Full story: Forbes</Msg><Username>tooofunnky</Username><Timestamp>1358017311296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:01:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358018621157-25</Id><Topic><Title>Who will be the next to dump RT.. My guess is Asus.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1357949739826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 19:15:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably right. The writing is on the wall. RT is terminal for Windows. Companies with RT projects are diverting resources away from producing what consumers and businesses want - x86 devices that delivers better performance and runs real Windows and all they software they have invested years learning to use. It won't take long for Asus and others to reach this conclusion.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1358018621157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:23:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358018915123-26</Id><Title>Acer wisely shelve "Rubber Stamp" tablets</Title><Msg>Bet it never sees the light of day.... Acer Wisely Shelves Windows RT Tablet Launch Until Q2 2013 Matt Burns Tuesday, October 30th, 2012 Hope you weren’t waiting for an Acer Windows RT tablet. The company is not releasing its offering until later next year. Originally, Acer was going to launch Windows RT tablets in the first quarter of 2013, but the company is wisely going to sit on the sidelines a bit and watch the market’s reaction to other WinRT tabs — most notably the Microsoft Surface. Acer President Jim Wong told Reuters today that his company is going to be more cautious because of the Surface. Acer was one of the first companies to speak out against Microsoft’s sudden move in the hardware business. Per Jim Wong, Acer, as the No. 4 PC maker worldwide, was going to follow “a very aggressive plan” with Windows RT tablets. Samsung, Dell, and Lenovo have Windows RT tablets in the pipeline, but they will not ship until later this year. Digitimes reports that shipments of Windows RT tablets are expected to be fewer than 50,000 units each. HP, Sony, and Toshiba scrapped plans for Windows RT tablets — HP and Toshiba did so specifically in response to the MS Surface. Microsoft beat most hardware makers to market with the Surface RT. The Asus Vivo Tab is the only other major WinRT tab on the market right now. The Vivo Tab is a virtual clone of the Surface with similar specs (not to mention the optional keyboard accessory) but with a slightly smaller screen. Combined with Windows RT’s limited capabilities and slim hardware selection, the future of Windows RT is questionable. Windows RT is not Windows 8. They operate similarly, but Windows RT requires special applications that can only be installed through Microsoft’s application store. This greatly limits the capability of the tablet and will likely be confusing to the general consumer. I found the Surface RT to be incomplete and rather disappointing because of its limited capability. “I don’t know what’s next, what Microsoft will do,” Wong told Reuters. “We are watching how Surface is doing … How is RT accepted by customers, how Microsoft is aggressive on RT and on Surface, we don’t know… We want to see.”</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1358018915123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:28:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358019146653-27</Id><Title>CNET Hands-on: 'Microsoft Surface Pro lives up to hype'</Title><Msg>reviewsDOTcnetDOTcom/microsoft-surface-pro</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358019146653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:32:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358020420075-28</Id><Topic><Title>CNET Hands-on: 'Microsoft Surface Pro lives up to hype'</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358019146653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:32:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Surface Pro will compete with those devices and others. But, based on how good that Type Cover is and how good the Surface Pro's screen feels -- not to mention its small size -- the Surface Pro seems well-positioned to rise to the top of the pack. From the moment the Surface was announced, the real killer feature was the Type Cover. To me, the success or failure of the Surface hinges on the ability of that cover to be comfortable and productive. And I think it is. It also draws power from the tablet, never needs recharging, and has a grip strong enough to hold the whole Surface tablet from the cover alone. Can a tablet comfortably be your full PC? So far, when it comes to my limited time with Surface Pro, the answer seems to be yes. And that could, in the long run, be the most impactful development in PCs in years.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1358020420075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:53:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358022221316-29</Id><Topic><Title>Acer wisely shelve "Rubber Stamp" tablets</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1358018915123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:28:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Windows RT is not Windows 8. They operate similarly, but Windows RT requires special applications that can only be installed through Microsoft’s application store. This greatly limits the capability of the tablet and will likely be confusing to the general consumer. I found the Surface RT to be incomplete and rather disappointing because of its limited capability." [CES told us that Windows RT has no competitive edge. Stick a fork in the ARM RT. It's done...] [ARM CEO East will soon have something else on which to say "Phooey" in addition to his bubble trouble and fabrication crisis...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358022221316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 15:23:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358022579707-30</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, did you read the barron's piece on ARM CEO interview.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357970660255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:04:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft hasn't helped with the "heavy lifting" on RT and now look what's happening....1 by 1 the OEMs are abandoning it because consumers are confused and/or aren't buying it. I wouldn't want to be in a position, as a company, where i'm relying on someone to dictate my success. INTC got complacent in a similar situation and now are having to be proactive in trying to create their opportunities by pushing innovation in their OEMs' products (Intel Ultrabook fund, reference designs, etc.), i.e. helping in heavy lifting.</Msg><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1358022579707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 15:29:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358026158576-31</Id><Title>Intel's '7W' Ivy Bridge chips are partly a marketing sleight-of-hand</Title><Msg>CHIP INDUSTRY WATCHERS were somewhat stunned earlier this week when Intel revealed at its CES press conference on Monday that it has begun fabbing Ivy Bridge processors that draw only 7W of power and is shipping them to device makers for use in smartphones and tablets. However, further investigation has found that Intel's claim to have developed 7W Ivy Bridge chips at least partly rests on some marketing sleight-of-hand, and it remains to be seen how well these processors will actually perform, that is, whether Intel will get away with this clever marketing ploy in the highly competitive mobile device markets. Technology website Ars Technica looked into Intel's 7W chip announcement and discovered that its Y series CPUs are significantly downclocked versions of its Core i3 and Core i5 processors that have been favoured with a supplementary power rating that Intel calls "Scenario Design Power", or SDP, in addition to its traditional Thermal Design Power, or TDP rating. There's one Pentium 2129Y chip that's clocked at 1.1GHz, with a TDP rating of 10W and an SDP rating of 7W, and there's also a Core i3 3229Y chip clocked at 1.4GHz with a TDP of 13W and also an SDP of 7W. Neither of these processors has Turbo Mode and only the Core i3 processor has support for Hyperthreading. These are likely destined to be sold as low-end budget processors, but it's interesting that while they have TDP ratings that differ by 3W, they both have the same SDP rating of 7W. Ars Technica compared two "roughly analogous" Core i5 processors and found that the Core i5 3339Y chip is clocked at 1.5GHz and 2GHz in Turbo Mode with a TDP of 13W and an SDP of again 7W, while the Core i5 3317U chip is clocked at 1.7GHz and 2.6GHz in Turbo Mode with a TDP of 17W. Note that the Y series chip with 7W SDP is downclocked by 200MHz base frequency and by 600MHz in Turbo Mode, which explains why its TDP is 4W lower than the TDP of the similar U series chip. That's almost 12 percent slower base frequency and 23 percent slower in Turbo Boost. All of the Y series CPUs have integrated Intel HD 4000 graphics cores like their faster U series siblings, but those are limited to 850MHz maximum speed, whereas the U series graphics cores can run at up to 1,050MHz. That's 19 percent lower maximum graphics processing speed in the Y series chips compared to the U series chips. Thus, we can expect tablet PCs that feature Intel's '7W' Ivy Bridge processors to be at least 12 percent to 23 percent slower than similar laptops, and to be up to 19 percent slower displaying complex graphics. Whether these performance differences will show up in commonly used benchmark tests is something that will be discovered as these chips are used in smartphones and, most likely, tablets, and benchmark tests are conducted. I'm willing to bet that these differences will be noticable, but it is possible that device usage patterns are such that they will not be noticable by users in their web surfing, emailing, tweeting and so on, and I suspect that is exactly what Intel's marketing department is counting on. I'd expect that Intel did some testing of typical smartphone and tablet usage patterns and demands on CPU and graphics processing resources, and discovered that, at most, users of those devices stress the processor and graphics core at about 50 percent utilisation. Thus perhaps, it set its new Scenario Design Power level at 7W/13W, or just shy of 54 percent. Decades ago, it was found that computer users were not so bothered by mediocre response times as they were by response times that varied widely. Then, users of mainframe based computer systems, such as bank tellers for example, wouldn't complain if response time was typically two seconds versus one second, but they would protest if an average two second response time was punctuated by occasional four second or longer response times. With its Scenario Design Power rating marketing ploy, Intel might be relying on a similar set of psychological expectations to develop among mobile device users, and that they will be happy if their shiny smartphones and tablets are consistent, as opposed to really fast.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358026158576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:29:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358027300956-32</Id><Topic><Title>They finally figure it out - ...is about to hit the fan</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358011214409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:20:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And once Wall Street figures it out (better late than never I suppose), the bubble will burst. I don't envy East - he has bubble trouble, fading fabrication and no solutions to either...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358027300956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:48:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358028340808-33</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's '7W' Ivy Bridge chips are partly a marketing sleight-of-hand</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358026158576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:29:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Ars Technica compared two "roughly analogous" Core i5 processors and found that the Core i5 3339Y chip is clocked at 1.5GHz and 2GHz in Turbo Mode with a TDP of 13W and an SDP of again 7W, while the Core i5 3317U chip is clocked at 1.7GHz and 2.6GHz in Turbo Mode with a TDP of 17W. Note that the Y series chip with 7W SDP is downclocked by 200MHz base frequency and by 600MHz in Turbo Mode, which explains why its TDP is 4W lower than the TDP of the similar U series chip. That's almost 12 percent slower base frequency and 23 percent slower in Turbo Boost.' The better comparison would be with the best Y sku which is the i7-3689Y which has a base clock of 1.5 GHz and turbo of 2.6 GHz at 13W so you get the same peak performance as the 3317U at about 25% less power which is kind of what you would expect from a good die harvesting exercise. All skus here ... xbitlabsDOTcom/cms/include/image.php?src=/images/news/2012-12/intel_ulp_specs_24.png&amp;width=550&amp;height=382&amp;cache=1&amp;quality=88&amp;aspect=0&amp;format=png Even the 1.1 GHz 10W Pentium 2129Y though would beat the 1.7 GHz 8W ARM A15 in Exynos 5 in most benchmarks and by a greater amount than its power differential, i.e. it has greater performance/power. Not bad for simply testing a few dies on a high performance 22nm process ;-). BTW can you point me to any ARM vendors that give out official TDP, SDP, datasheets like Intel ? I will save you the trouble ...NONE. Once again lower standards get a free pass in the sensationalist press for your rubber stamp boys.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358028340808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:05:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358028583720-34</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, did you read the barron's piece on ARM CEO interview.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1357970660255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:04:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When I propose to East that ARM's taking a larger share of the traditional WinTel notebook chip market would be a psychological victory of some sort, he brushes aside the suggestion. “It doesn't matter because it's already evident to most people that these kinds of ARM-based systems are eventually going to take over” the large bulk of traditional computing." [When Intel chips are the market leaders in performance and power efficiency and competitive in price, why would anyone assume that ARM would take over the bulk of traditional computing? The guy acts as if fabrication will be frozen today and never advance. Well, that's pretty much true of ARM but certainly not Intel. But, hey - what's the guy going to say? That given the trend in fabrication, Intel will turn ARM into AMD in three years? He's not going to say it but that's what is going to happen. We got solid proof of that at CES...] "When I reply that a transistor cliff would imply some companies wouldn't be able to progress at all, he replies, “I'm not sure I buy the notion of a transistor cliff; I think there's a lot of marketing fluff in that.”" [Intel is closing the power efficiency gap with ARM faster than anyone thought possible and they are doing it substantially but not entirely with superior fabrication. Let's see what Mr. East has to say when Intel's 14nm products hit the streets and the deals start falling Intel's way. Maybe then he will admit that ARM has gone over the edge of the transistor cliff...] [It doesn't really matter what Mr. East says. ARM will be at 28nm for a very, very long time, 20nm planar will be significantly problematic and 14nm FinFET non-existent for ARM for years and years. Intel will continue to move the node process every two years. To say that will not effect ARMs ability to compete is just not true. It changes everything...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358028583720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:09:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358028841038-35</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's '7W' Ivy Bridge chips are partly a marketing sleight-of-hand</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358026158576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:29:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is the TDP of any Snapdragon chip? What is the TDP of any Tegra chip? I wanted to compare their TDP with those of Intel chips but I could not find any TDP for them.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358028841038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:14:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358029018670-36</Id><Title>Getanid61 reduced to driveby hit and run messages on the Intel board</Title><Msg>DESPERATION for the rubber duckey guy!</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358029018670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:16:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358029169209-37</Id><Topic><Title>Getanid61 reduced to driveby hit and run messages on the Intel board</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358029018670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:16:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much time did Microsoft waste by, as GETANID61 would say.......porting to ARM.. ROFL! Samsung sure aint porting to ARM. GETANID61 used to say the whole world was porting to ARM.........he doesn't say it anymore (lmao).</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1358029169209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:19:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358029497281-38</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's '7W' Ivy Bridge chips are partly a marketing sleight-of-hand</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358026158576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:29:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"BTW can you point me to any ARM vendors that give out official TDP, SDP, datasheets like Intel ? I will save you the trouble ...NONE. Once again lower standards get a free pass in the sensationalist press for your rubber stamp boys." I hit the refresh button and saw you had discovered the same thing about lack of ARMH OEM transparancy. Guess why Intel has made such rapid reduction in power and has became competitive in battery life. You can make a very, very low power ARMH chip but when you add cache, memory buffer drivers and other logic, the power consumption skyrockets.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358029497281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:24:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358029684971-39</Id><Topic><Title>Getanid61 reduced to driveby hit and run messages on the Intel board</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358029018670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:16:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol....</Msg><Username>rtsuxwang61</Username><Timestamp>1358029684971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:28:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358029791550-40</Id><Title>Pin this to the top of the Intel board, forever</Title><Msg>Guess that's why Intel has made such rapid reduction in power and has became competitive in battery life. You can make a very, very low power ARMH chip but when you add cache, memory buffer drivers and other logic, the power consumption skyrockets.</Msg><Username>rtsuxwang61</Username><Timestamp>1358029791550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:29:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358030451993-41</Id><Title>Some follow up on GF's $10 billion "annoucement"</Title><Msg>The idea Intel could simply build chips for Apple ( AAPL) or Qualcomm ( QCOM) seems to Mosemann not an answer: “Does it make sense for Intel to build $10 billion shiny new fabs for foundry work? We think not for 45-50% gross margins, and ask IBM how the foundry investment turned out.” Me thinks ARM weasels are getting cornered - they start contradict each other - I mean heavy duty.. Neither East nor clown Hans seem to be up to date what the foundries are doing. In particular East seems to be clueless but he works "closely" with all the independent foundries. TSMC Breaks Ground to Build 16nm FinFET Fab - X-bit labs Looks like the ARM mantra of (cheap) manufacturing playing third fiddle is melting away Mosesmann writes that the recent announcement Intel CEO Paul Otellini will step down next May was “spit-my-coffee-on-my-PC alarming” and a “big deal.” Why? Because Mosesmann thinks Intel needs to change its culture of simply building bigger fabs (not: NVDA is suggesting 450mm fabs!). At issue is what Mosesmann sees as the potential for a “gross margin disaster” as rival ARM Holdings ( ARMH) gains ground and Intel’s gains against Advanced Micro Devices ( AMD) fade amidst a sluggish PC market: We believe the 62%-65% gross margins seen over the last three years were the exception to the rule. Over that time, Intel gained share vs. AMD in both PCs &amp; servers and benefited from the last real Windows enterprise upgrade cycle. With these benefits abating, Intel has a number of new challenges in the form commoditization of x86 (by ARM), price competition in both PC and data center markets (also ARM) and an increasing capex burden (with little to no growth). We believe mid 50% (and potentially low 50% over time) gross margins are an increasing reality as opposed to a downside scenario, and investors should brace for lower estimates. With ARM-apps processor pricing at 15-20% of x86 vs. Intel on recently launched Surface platforms, we believe a gross margin baseline below 55% should not be surprising. The data center assault from ARM will be next, and that could prove even more damaging as this is the only area where Intel has posted op. profit growth in 2012. The idea Intel could simply build chips for Apple ( AAPL) or Qualcomm ( QCOM) seems to Mosemann not an answer: “Does it make sense for Intel to build $10 billion shiny new fabs for foundry work? We think not for 45-50% gross margins, and ask IBM how the foundry investment turned out.” May 19, 2011 – Others have called this structure a FinFET for several years, but FinFETs ... to 32nm planar transistors) while increasing wafer cost by 2% to 3%. What about Intel not only matching but actually undercutting TSMC et al...</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358030451993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:40:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358030704303-42</Id><Title>Microsoft exec doesn't rule out Intel-based Windows Phones</Title><Msg>"We have nothing to announce at this time," about Windows Phone running on Intel, Greg Sullivan, a senior product manager for Windows Phone told Computerworld at CES. Still, he left a wide opening for alternatives to Qualcomm's Snapdragon, which is widely deployed on phones by many manufacturers. "Our architecture is such that it's hardware independent. For the same reason that Windows 8 [tablets] could run on 'Wintel', right now Windows Phone is on Qualcomm. We have a portable OS architecture."</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1358030704303</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:45:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358030911843-43</Id><Title>Microsoft rumored to be considering an Xbox tablet and phone</Title><Msg>With new xbox expected to show up for holiday season and Intel's Bay Trail also expected to show by holiday season, there's a good chance we see Bay Trail, with integrated HD Graphics 4000, inside both these MS devices.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1358030911843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:48:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358031755493-44</Id><Title>Intel's North Cape Haswell detachable reference design video</Title><Msg>youtubeDOTcom/watch?v=nG8CPaX1PxQ</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1358031755493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:02:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358032693209-45</Id><Topic><Title>Some follow up on GF's $10 billion "annoucement"</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358030451993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:40:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"With ARM-apps processor pricing at 15-20% of x86 vs. Intel on recently launched Surface platforms, we believe a gross margin baseline below 55% should not be surprising. The data center assault from ARM will be next, and that could prove even more damaging as this is the only area where Intel has posted op. profit growth in 2012." [This analyst cites pricing as a huge advantage for ARM on the Surface platform. Um, the results speak otherwise as it appears that they can't price the ARM Surface RT cheap enough to get it to sell. This is the kind of clueless analysis that is driving Wall Street...] [As far as the data center assault, I have to ask, "What data center assault?" He says it will be more damaging than the Surface RT. LOL The Surface RT has come and gone without a ripple. As will the data center assault...] [ARM has BTFF (bubble trouble coupled with fabrication fade). A bad combination. Often fatal...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358032693209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:18:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358032890230-46</Id><Topic><Title>Some follow up on GF's $10 billion "annoucement"</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358030451993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:40:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mosesmann is the absolute worst analyst commenting on the semi industry, everything he said above is blatant nonsense just like his price forecasts e.g. NVDA to $40 ! How he is still in a job just amazes me as he is totally incompetent and stupid.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358032890230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:21:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358033177243-47</Id><Title>The Countdown Has Begun: 168 Days Left</Title><Msg>TSMC has until June 30 to produce volume production on 20nm planar or will suffer the rather dramatic competitive consequences. Picture Apple waving buh-bye. I wonder if anyone thinks they will make it...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358033177243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:26:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358034228751-48</Id><Title>Even Microsoft Creative Fiction Isn't Helping ARM's RT</Title><Msg>From an Interview: The Verge: What's the difference between Windows 8 and Windows RT, or are they the same thing? Microsoft rep: They're pretty much the same thing, there is no real huge difference beside the RT is more touch friendly. *** "This was just days before launch, and even sales reps at Microsoft retail stores didn't fare much better. Needless to say, they're not pretty much the same thing, and there is a huge difference. Microsoft has a page buried on its website outlining the differences, but how many people will unearth it, compared to how many stroll into a physical Microsoft Store?" From: Is Microsoft Windows RT About to Lose a Key Partner? By Evan Niu, CFA</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358034228751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:43:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358036471067-49</Id><Title>Apple will move its tablets to X86 too. ARM just doesn't cut the mustard</Title><Msg>in power/performance/cost. By the end of 2013, Intel will OWN the tablet market.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358036471067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:21:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358038670526-50</Id><Topic><Title>Is Anyone Making Money WIth INTC?</Title><Username>newtontodd714</Username><Timestamp>1358014743482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:19:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome</Msg><Username>jackcaleb839</Username><Timestamp>1358038670526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:57:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358039838048-51</Id><Topic><Title>Apple will move its tablets to X86 too. ARM just doesn't cut the mustard</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358036471067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:21:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Apple does go x86, then I would buy some AAPL stocks :)</Msg><Username>clemsyn</Username><Timestamp>1358039838048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:17:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358042640529-52</Id><Topic><Title>The Countdown Has Begun: 168 Days Left</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358033177243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:26:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are attempting it (A6X) on 28nm HKMG planar so it is less of a stretch but still has to be proven. Remember Apple is currently on 32nm so 28nm will be an improvement for them especially as TSMC has 3 different flavors of HKMG to choose from (HP, HPM, HPL). theinquirerDOTnet/inquirer/news/2233481/apple-reportedly-taps-tsmcs-28nm-process-node-for-a6x-chip Meanwhile TSMC 20nm is looking late and apparently won't be ready for Nvidia in early 2014 ... semiaccurateDOTcom/2012/12/06/nvidias-maxwell-process-choice/</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358042640529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:04:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358043166553-53</Id><Title>Haswell</Title><Msg>Among other things, Intel hailed the architecture as the "largest generation-to-generation battery life increase in the history of Intel" and the first CPU architecture designed "from the ground up" for Ultrabooks and tablets, rather than being retrofitted for those form factors after the fact. From: Intel at CES: More performance, less power, and x86 everywhere</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358043166553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:12:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358043800187-54</Id><Title>Intel to move on earnings this week</Title><Msg>Intel has a history of meeting or beating analysts' estimates. I see a nice move up this week, after a terrible last 5 months price action. I like the Jan 20 and 21 Calls for leverage on INTC.</Msg><Username>garyg474</Username><Timestamp>1358043800187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:23:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358044198167-55</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to move on earnings this week</Title><Username>garyg474</Username><Timestamp>1358043800187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:23:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The news we've been getting on the PC market has been mixed. Windows 8 sales seem to have picked up, but the overall PC market seems to have shrunk a few percent since last year. Hard to predict which way Intel's PC revenues will go.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1358044198167</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:29:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358044392122-56</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358043166553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:12:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even Intel is reducing the performance of its processors to fit within the laptop power budget. Soon, performance will have to start playing a secondary role to other factors since it does't do much for the average user that influences the buying decisions of 90% of the market. Intel will have to tone down its performance rhetoric in the face of conflicting signals from PC makers.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1358044392122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:33:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358045543368-57</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358043166553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:12:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Err no, Haswell will be appreciably better performing than Ivy Bridge but still at lower power. This processor is a work of semiconductor art.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358045543368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:52:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358045896413-58</Id><Title>Early previewers go nuts over the Lenovo K900</Title><Msg>They really love the slim design, specs and potential performance. Intel could have itself a superphone sales winner this year ! Unlike the foundries and thanks to Sandy Bridge building a couple FABs there is no shortage of 32nm wafers too to build as many as the customers want ;-). gizmodoDOTcom/5974392/lenovo-k900-hands+on-this-tall-skinny-hottie-needs-to-get-in-my-pants auDOTibtimesDOTcom/articles/423015/20130111/samsung-galaxy-note-2-vs-lenovo-k900.htm digitaltrendsDOTcom/ces-videos/hands-on-lenovo-k900-intel-atom-clover-trail-smartphone/ androidcentralDOTcom/lenovo-k900-hands engadgetDOTcom/2013/01/08/lenovo-k900-intel-clover-trail/</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358045896413</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:58:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358046627151-59</Id><Title>INTC should be trading near its 52-wk high right now</Title><Msg>ARM has proven to be a bust with regards to "replacing" the PC or servers. See Surface RT. They are no threat to Intel.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1358046627151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:10:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358047946105-60</Id><Topic><Title>Early previewers go nuts over the Lenovo K900</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358045896413</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:58:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a technical reason why it can be so slim : dual-core Clovertrail+ has a ~2W TDP. To get equivalent performance from the ARM world you would need a ~2W dual-core Apple A6, a ~3W quad-core Qualcomm S4 Pro or a 4W quad-core ARM A9 or 4W dual-core A15. Yes, Intel and Apple have made the best mobile processors of 2013 ! Who would have thought it a year ago before Medfield was released ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358047946105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:32:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358048558339-61</Id><Topic><Title>First benchmark results of Intel-powered Lenovo K900 are off the charts!</Title><Username>rehsab33</Username><Timestamp>1357906104116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 07:08:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome!</Msg><Username>pluscard_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1358048558339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:42:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358049259206-62</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358043166553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:12:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>marsavian Intel haters will be Intel haters. Just let them wallow in their ignorance as they believe ARM Holdings or any one of its many scattered licensees can hurt Intel in any significant way.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358049259206</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:54:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358049959830-63</Id><Topic><Title>First benchmark results of Intel-powered Lenovo K900 are off the charts!</Title><Username>rehsab33</Username><Timestamp>1357906104116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 07:08:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Now however we’re starting to form an idea, and we’ll tell you this – it’s beyond our wildest dreams and ARM’s darkest nightmares." I like this quote.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358049959830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:05:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358051366980-64</Id><Topic><Title>First benchmark results of Intel-powered Lenovo K900 are off the charts!</Title><Username>rehsab33</Username><Timestamp>1357906104116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 07:08:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It seems like the score for RAM in K900 is pretty impressive looking at the antutu scores ;)</Msg><Username>clemsyn</Username><Timestamp>1358051366980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:29:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358052523704-65</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358043166553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:12:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They seem to have already forgotten the fact that TXN is planning to exit the ARM based processor business. TXN doesn't want to make OMAP processors anymore. They figured it out that there is not much differentiation between one ARM processor builder over another, when most are made by the same manufacturer. Or in other words, design doesn't mean much when the manufacturing capabilities are very limited. Or going further, Intel is eventually going to kick everyones behind from here to England.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358052523704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:48:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>