<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360214619461-1</Id><Topic><Title>Intel selling at 1997 level, that 16 yrs ago!!!!</Title><Username>jettfuellllll</Username><Timestamp>1360208877381</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 22:47:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you sure? Maybe in 2029 same price @ same share denomination?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360214619461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 00:23:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360217407177-2</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis Beaver is a schill- AVOID</Title><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1360206879407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 22:14:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nuff is just some old shut in F that stalks people on chat boards,a real meaningful way to live.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1360217407177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 01:10:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360232593407-3</Id><Topic><Title>East on Windows RT</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360103456454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"our expectation was really satisfied that Microsoft proved they could bring a Windows operating system up on ARM technology" Wasn't is supposed to be a two way street? Microsoft could prove to ARM that they could bring Windows to ARM and in return ARM would let Microsoft into it's world of mobile? What, it was only a one way street? Here's how I see ARMH. They had a dozen years of just being out there in the market. They had very mild success going in PDA's and the emerging feature phone market. They hit astronomical success with the invention of the iPhone. They had further success with the wanna bee Android market that eventually caught up to iPhone. And as Steve Jobs last benevolent act he invented the tablet market. What's the next driver for ARMH? Windows! While we're on it, why haven't the prices of the ARM based products dropped? Shouldn't the iPad Mini be under $150? Instead it's over $300? There isn't the consumer cost savings with the increased acceptance in the market. Are the ARM products getting all that much better? No, I'm not talking dweebs spewing benchmark scores, I'm talking something noticeable by teenage girls. ARMH has no realistic drivers for new technology sales this year ( data centers and 4K TV still years off) No exceptional cost savings for consumers, and no superior performance over previous generations that consumers can understand and demand. With Windows RT is was assumed that ARM would get 20% market share within the first year of the windows market. That would be 60 million units. It's still struggling with it's first million. I'm thinking that it won't hit 3 million before it's killed off by Microsoft. Keep in mind RT was going to drive ARMH through the roof. Now what? ARM64? Yes, Microsoft can't wait for another flavor of failure. Emperor East has no clothes!</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1360232593407</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 05:23:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360234152862-4</Id><Topic><Title>East on Windows RT</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360103456454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft is a new entrant in phones and tablets. It had no choice but to support ARM based tablets through Windows RT because there's already a lot of Android and iOS based ARM tablets out there. As is evident, ARM chips enable thinner and lighter form factors that have set the precedent for tablets. Since it is so late, even with its huge market presence through all its OEMs and its brand recognition, it will be hard for it to make a dent in the tablet market. Chances are it will become a niche player in tablets just the way the Mac was compared to PCs in the old days. ARMs growth in mobile is not dependent on Microsoft's success in any way. It's pervasive in the market without Microsoft, and the market is growing, at least for now.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360234152862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 05:49:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360235735072-5</Id><Topic><Title>East on Windows RT</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360103456454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While we're on it, why haven't the prices of the ARM based products dropped? Shouldn't the iPad Mini be under $150? Instead it's over $300? There isn't the consumer cost savings with the increased acceptance in the market. Are the ARM products getting all that much better? No, I'm not talking dweebs spewing benchmark scores, I'm talking something noticeable by teenage girls. ----- Do a google for 'BOM ipad'. The bill of materials for the Ipad mini is $188, the ARM SoC is $13, while the display/touchscreen is $80 alone. It's a similar story for phones, the higher end phones have higher bom's typically driven by the screen and other high cost items. The cost of the ARM app processor is usually way down the list of items. ---- ARMH has no realistic drivers for new technology sales this year ( data centers and 4K TV still years off) No exceptional cost savings for consumers, and no superior performance over previous generations that consumers can understand and demand. ---- ? The bulk of the growth isn't SoC's for phones/tablets, it's the dull, boring stuff (microcontrollers and other deeply embedded gear). As for TV's, unless the iTV actually arrives ARM wont see a big revenue jump in this area, but as most smart TV's now have an ARM CPU (and many a mali GPU) they will see revenue increases in this sector as more models move over to the newer 'smart' chipsets.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1360235735072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:15:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360244592805-6</Id><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro destroys all other Tablets in performance</Title><Msg>Actually it more like annihilate lol ! wwwDOTanandtechDOTcom/print/6695 p.s. what will low voltage Haswells do !!</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360244592805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:43:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360246305807-7</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>sampiyonlugumaureen</Username><Timestamp>1360162258793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 09:50:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was really looking for some great news. Now I found it.</Msg><Username>laurelvialexis</Username><Timestamp>1360246305807</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:11:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360246332302-8</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>sampiyonlugumaureen</Username><Timestamp>1360162258793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 09:50:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am waiting for. Thanks for giving out this article for free.</Msg><Username>laurelvialexis</Username><Timestamp>1360246332302</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:12:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360246346398-9</Id><Topic><Title>People crave Windows 8 tablets at work more than iPads</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360198579021</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:56:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>otherwise known as 'geeks", hardly a majority</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1360246346398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:12:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360246522842-10</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro destroys all other Tablets in performance</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360244592805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:43:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Final Words Surface Pro is about as well executed as Microsoft could have made it given the currently available hardware. Its performance is outstanding for a tablet - it’s truly in a class of its own. If I sit down and use Surface Pro as I would an iPad or Android tablet, it delivers an appreciably quicker user experience. Apple does get fairly close in some cases on far slower hardware, which should concern Microsoft quite a bit should Apple ever choose to go ahead and build a tablet/notebook convergence device of its own. But overall, there’s just not a faster tablet on the market. It’s really the combination of a very fast CPU and very fast storage that enable such great performance out of Surface Pro. The beauty of Surface was in its flexibility. The ability to quickly switch between tablet and notebook usage modes, between content consumption and production. Surface Pro really takes that to the next level. It can quickly switch between operating modes just like its predecessor, but it can also double as a full blown notebook or desktop PC. There’s tremendous potential in what Microsoft is trying to do here with Surface Pro. The inclusion of a Wacom powered digital pen is interesting for the creative professionals out there. My only complaint there is the lack of mouse tracking for the pen, it can only be used in pen mode, but if that’s something you’re ok with then I can see the pen being a good solution to consolidating tablet, notebook and Wacom tablet into a single device for use on the road.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360246522842</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:15:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360246607841-11</Id><Title>Let s see how many times shut-in Tooofunny sticks his nose up Wally's #$%$ today</Title><Msg>The over under is set at 11.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360246607841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:16:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360248015702-12</Id><Title>Whats next</Title><Msg>AMD LYG AKS</Msg><Username>maker.stock</Username><Timestamp>1360248015702</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:40:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360248387985-13</Id><Topic><Title>East on Windows RT</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360103456454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"As is evident, ARM chips enable thinner and lighter form factors that have set the precedent for tablets." Under 7mm is "thinner" today. The thinnest that I could find was an HTC phone at 6.45mm. The HTC was the only phone thinner than the Lenovo K900 Atom Lexington leaked last month is 6.9mm. MSFT has been under pressure from Linux variants for 20 years. "ARM" and "Android" are nothing new. There is nothing special about ARM today that enables "thinner" designs.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360248387985</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:46:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360248407726-14</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro destroys all other Tablets in performance</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360244592805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:43:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Anandtech review is very thorough and yes the numerous benchmarks shows Pro to be the most powerful tablet available while supporting the world's largest software ecosystem. There are some valid criticisms. While some aren't too pleased about the extra half pound weight it carries versus the iPad, most of the criticism centers around thickness and battery life. Interestingly both of these issues could be improved with low power Ivy Bridge processors Intel already has but were not used for this product. There is another feature which makes Pro unique among tablets. The user has full access to the BIOS and Microsoft's Secure Boot (which is of debatable value anyway) can be disabled and this device will boot any OS the user wants to run. This answers one of the open questions some had about users being able to boot multiple OSes and the answer is YES - and no hacking is required to do it. This also gives superior security options than is available for Android or iPad. As the very first full powered tablet on the market there is a lot to like, and some features not so likeable, but what is exciting is that processors Intel already ships, and will be shipping before the holidays, have the ability to improve this product quickly. Pro will still compete with convertibles coming on the market but its very encouraging to see a tablet-first product in this performance class.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360248407726</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:46:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360248708088-15</Id><Title>Why doesn't the sstock go up?</Title><Msg>If this is such a great company why doesn#$%$ stock go up?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360248708088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:51:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360249109803-16</Id><Topic><Title>getanid61 &amp; Marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360090860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That ~43.64 ARMH resistance is holding and the stock is down more than the general market which is another sign. The last thing to look for is when the 50 Day MA arrives at the current price, will it support the stock or will it then turn into resistance. If the latter then that will be a clear sign that a peak in the stock, which may prove to be permanent, has been reached.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360249109803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:58:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360249161260-17</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesn't the sstock go up?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360248708088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:51:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like a dog today....................................</Msg><Username>cmi_or_die</Username><Timestamp>1360249161260</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:59:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360249213809-18</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro destroys all other Tablets in performance</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360244592805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:43:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To me, the following is going to be a crucial factor in deciding between detachables and convertibles (swivel or flip screen). ==================== Microsoft integrated 4GB of DDR3-1600 memory (dual-channel, soldered on-board) and a full 64GB or 128GB SATA based SSD into Surface Pro. ==================== Detachables and Tablets are going to have soldered on-board DRAM. I am pretty sure this means that the DRAM cannot be increased or upgraded. Convertibles will probably win hands-down for users who need such upgrades. Yes, we might have to carry some extra weight around even when you use the device as a Tablet, but that beats being locked-in to a specific set of hardware with no upgrade potential. Unless, of course, some OEMs come up with a detachable device that has 2 processors - one on the detachable screen (low-end Atom) to use as a Tablet - and another one under the keyboard (Core i3 to i7) to use as a laptop. Hope some OEM comes out with such a device.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1360249213809</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:00:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360249395359-19</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is a coiled spring</Title><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1360169214342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:46:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The cretin Wallis may or not notice that just as my expert writing indicated, the low today is $20.85 --( Hit it to the penny, thus far) As a qualified imbecile, Wallis knows as much about sardonic musings as the moron knows about INTC..Nothing ! Imbeciles like Wallis seem to revel in their own stupidity.."Ignore" the fool..</Msg><Username>pentomic</Username><Timestamp>1360249395359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:03:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360249534367-20</Id><Topic><Title>getanid61 &amp; Marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360090860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC underperfoming armh again today</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1360249534367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:05:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360250167380-21</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro destroys all other Tablets in performance</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360244592805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:43:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for all your interesting observations guys. It's pretty clear to me that ARM has had its 15mins of fame and that all the leading future performance/price and performance/power improvements are going to come from Intel for the foreseeable future.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360250167380</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:16:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360250427334-22</Id><Topic><Title>getanid61 &amp; Marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360090860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>finviz has a nice SP500 heat map that will show you visually all the stocks that are outperforming INTC. It doesn't show ARMH on that heat map because ARMH is not part of the SP500, QQQ, or any of the other US indices that influence the direction of INTC. Almost 50% of the INTC volume comes from index ETF and those trades will track the market. A better company to compare would QCOM (except large IP revenue component), NVDA, .... rather than ARMH which is a pure IP company. Interesting that QCOM and INTC are both down 0.49% as I just look. I always chuckle when people compare ARMH to INTC.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360250427334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:20:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360250477155-23</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesn't the sstock go up?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360248708088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:51:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy the drops sell the pops, hold when it gets close to the dividend. 1 of 2 things will happen with INTC. Either A: the economy will tank, and INTC along with it, in which case we're all shoed anyway... or B: it will get back to its $30 level before 3rd part of the year... In the short term.. yes, nothing is happening and it is a hold.</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1360250477155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:21:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360250645624-24</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesn't the sstock go up?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360248708088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:51:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Traders are looking for dip below 20 then you should see some price action. Look at the two year chart</Msg><Username>healthyrisk</Username><Timestamp>1360250645624</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:24:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360250849338-25</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesn't the sstock go up?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360248708088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:51:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Presently, the stock is not liked or respected..(Sort of like the majority of know- nothing posters on this board),,The stock is a hold. And as I have said countless times, it is a hold and a buy @ $19-$20.</Msg><Username>pentomic</Username><Timestamp>1360250849338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:27:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360252158333-26</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro destroys all other Tablets in performance</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360244592805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:43:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would think that for Pro to succeed as a tablet-first device and distinguish it from a number of very compelling convertibles, it must get thinner, lighter and have better battery life. If that means a fixed qauntity of DRAM that's probably acceptable if it makes it more competitive against iPad and ARM tablets. As you point out, DRAM expandability will be one of the factors that will help users decide which form factor is the better fit.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360252158333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:49:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360252394122-27</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesn't the sstock go up?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360248708088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:51:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would it be a hold in a market that may just have started correcting? Aand if you anticipate a drop further down in any event? it was overbght the day it reported when Waldo was all giddy when it hit 23.00. Talk about giving up gains</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1360252394122</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:53:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360252445988-28</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesn't the sstock go up?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360248708088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:51:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too much negative news flow. Bears can bring up "PC is dead", "Intel missed mobile" whenever they want to bring the stock down. They know Intel will never defend themselves in a PR war. We never see Intel on TV pounding the table to pump up their stock. The company doesnt care about its shareholders.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1360252445988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:54:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360252550248-29</Id><Title>Critical support broken..We go below $20 soon</Title><Msg>Horrible short-term indicators with this stock.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1360252550248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:55:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360252644852-30</Id><Title>But EVERYONE wants a SURFACE PRO, eh Wallus?</Title><Msg>After all, it's novel.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1360252644852</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:57:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360252758207-31</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro destroys all other Tablets in performance</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360244592805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:43:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It takes $ hi tt y pictures</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360252758207</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:59:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360252938362-32</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesn't the sstock go up?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360248708088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:51:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Too much negative news flow. Bears can bring up "PC is dead", "Intel missed mobile" whenever they want to bring the stock down." True. "They know Intel will never defend themselves in a PR war" True also. Intel is smart enough to know trying to convince the audiences of the analysts that they are right and the analysts are wrong is a dumb idea. The analysts simply say that "Intel does not know what is going on". The analysts simply dismiss Intel as "deluded". "We never see Intel on TV pounding the table to pump up their stock." I hope not. That is a stupid idea and a behavior that easily dismissed as "desperate" and confirms the analysts position. "The company doesnt care about its shareholders." Silly.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360252938362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:02:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360253435498-33</Id><Topic><Title>Is INTC ready to break out?</Title><Username>english.mary73</Username><Timestamp>1360251490604</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:38:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Men and women these people happen to be right with their last recommendations, please</Msg><Username>barbara.grissom24</Username><Timestamp>1360253435498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:10:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360253801539-34</Id><Title>OH WALDO, OH CEEEESCO!</Title><Msg>csco 21.10 intc 20.79 HI-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360253801539</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:16:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360253948845-35</Id><Title>Answer for why INTC is not going up?</Title><Msg>1) It generally always goes down after div. paid. (usually for 3 weeks after) 2) Currently market overextended and pulling it down 3) Low earnings and revenue growth 4) Intel is not a buy and hold stock unless you have a humongous time horizon.</Msg><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1360253948845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:19:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360253990013-36</Id><Topic><Title>Critical support broken..We go below $20 soon</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1360252550248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:55:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep bashing backbay. It's working. Go. Go. The only thing better than a cheap stock is a stupid cheap stock.</Msg><Username>thuddite</Username><Timestamp>1360253990013</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:19:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360254010168-37</Id><Title>Forrester predicts 200 million workers will lineup for Windows tablet</Title><Msg>CNET The research company predicts that 200 million workers will be lining up for a Windows tablet, such as the Surface Pro.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360254010168</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:20:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360254088169-38</Id><Topic><Title>Answer for why INTC is not going up?</Title><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1360253948845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:19:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well Wally probably plans on working another 30 years. by then the semiconductor chip will probably be useless</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1360254088169</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:21:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360254593661-39</Id><Topic><Title>Answer for why INTC is not going up?</Title><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1360253948845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:19:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well Said-Buy low -sell high!</Msg><Username>michaelsbill51</Username><Timestamp>1360254593661</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:29:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360255284692-40</Id><Title>To the two females: Meg and Carly. Please don't break HP up, just let it waste away and go</Title><Msg>to zero....</Msg><Username>dc10050</Username><Timestamp>1360255284692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:41:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360256689339-41</Id><Topic><Title>But EVERYONE wants a SURFACE PRO, eh Wallus?</Title><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1360252644852</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:57:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lucy Nuff/Tooofunny inserting his nose directly in between Wally's #$%$ cheeks. Let's see how many times and aliases he uses to run around the internet like a psychopath chasing Wallly today. The count is now at one post and one alias used.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360256689339</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:04:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360256775732-42</Id><Title>Game changing report</Title><Msg>With the Unusual market maker activity on TERX. This company just recently had a ticker change and has one hell of a story behind it. 52 week highs could get crushed.</Msg><Username>marshalltse34828</Username><Timestamp>1360256775732</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:06:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360256914666-43</Id><Title>DoesAsus have an Ace up its sleeve for Mobile World Congress?</Title><Msg>Asus to wow us at Mobile World Congress with an Intel-powered tablet/phone all-in-one? By Andy Boxall — February 7, 2013 Asus has scheduled a press conference for February 25 at Mobile World Congress, and while it’s not the first to announce an event, and certainly won’t be the last; it is one we’ve been expecting. At CES 2013, Asus gave us a few cool new toys, including the Transformer AIO, but a spokesperson said the best was yet to come and that it would, “wow” us at MWC. At the time we had very little to go on, with rumors circulating around an Asus-branded Nexus 7 challenger and not much else. However, while MWC likes its tablet announcements, it’s more about smartphones. Asus has a single smartphone in its line-up, which is part of its PadFone 2 hybrid device, so could it be planning a standalone phone? That would be a little ordinary for Asus, a firm which loves to inject some quirk into its hardware, which makes the latest rumor from Digitimes sound more plausible than it would if it was about any other company. The report says Asus is going to reveal the Fonepad, which as you can probably tell from the name is a tablet with which one can make calls. It continues to give us a rundown of the spec, which throws up another surprise in the shape of an Intel processor. Asus has a strong relationship with Intel, using the chips to power devices including the Taichi, VivoBook and Transformer Book. The company also uses the In Search of Incredible tagline in relation to its other Intel-powered hardware, linking the rumor nicely with the event promo seen above. Asus Stylus HeadsetIntel Atom Lexington power The Atom chip in question is the Z2420, or Lexington as it’s also known, and rather than a Tegra 3 or Snapdragon S4 Pro challenger, Lexington chips are supposedly destined for budget devices such as the Acer Liquid C1. If this information is correct, it could mean the Fonepad may not make it to the U.S. or Europe. The Fonepad may also have a 7-inch screen, a 1280 x 800 resolution, Android 4.1 Jelly Bean, a 3-megapixel camera and 16GB of storage memory. Adding weight to the Digitimes report is the appearance of the Fonepad, this time with the model number of K004, on Indonesia’s communication regulator’s website. It even included the same spec printed by Digitimes. So, could there be any truth to it? Silly name aside (let’s hope that’s a codename), Asus has already toyed with incorporating phone functionality into its tablets, particularly with its Stylus Headset, an accessory which doubles as both a tablet stylus and a Bluetooth headset. Plus its PadFone and PadFone 2 provide the best of both worlds, but in two separate devices. Looked at this way, an Asus tablet/phone all-in-one isn’t much of a stretch. Will the Fonepad wow us at MWC? There’s only a few weeks to go before we find out.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360256914666</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:08:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360256935030-44</Id><Title>OH NO down INTC goes. WHY OH WHY are all the insiders selling?</Title><Msg>OH NO down INTC goes. WHY OH WHY are all the insiders selling?</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360256935030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:08:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360257093524-45</Id><Topic><Title>DoesAsus have an Ace up its sleeve for Mobile World Congress?</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360256914666</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:08:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another know nothing pumper. hint short armh for a trade, hedge those INTC losses</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1360257093524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:11:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360257832527-46</Id><Topic><Title>East on Windows RT</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360103456454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do a google for 'BOM ipad'. The bill of materials for the Ipad mini is $188, the ARM SoC is $13 The continued use of the legacy A5 chip may not come as a surprise to most, as Apple was said to be keeping component costs down in order to offer the mini at a relatively inexpensive price point. Chip analysis firm Chipworks took a closer look at the iPad mini's processor to see if Apple moved to an updated process as it did with the incremental iPad 2 revision in May, which saw a process change from 45nm to 32nm. The firm noted in its report that Apple quietly changed the process in the A5 chip when it introduced the New iPad and its touted A5X SoC. "Apple (likely) plays it this way because they don’t want people evaluating their products based on 'commodity' technical specifications, but based on the overall experience with the device," Chipworks wrote. Based on the company's generational process changes, some speculated that the iPad mini would carry a third-generation A5 chip even more efficient than the 32nm version found in the iPad 2 and Apple TV. Chipworks discovered, however, that the tablet's SoC is the same 32nm component found in the most recent iPod touch. "Basically, we put our device in for a cross section and the images show the same contacted gate pitch and the same high-k metal gates, so we are comfortable with this conclusion," the firm said, referring to Samsung's 32nm process. The continued use of the legacy A5 chip may not come as a surprise to most, as Apple was said to be keeping component costs down in order to offer the mini at a relatively inexpensive price point.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360257832527</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:23:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360257856995-47</Id><Topic><Title>DoesAsus have an Ace up its sleeve for Mobile World Congress?</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360256914666</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:08:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow!!! GEE!!! A computer that's also a fone!!!??? Wow!!! I'm gonna call my friends right now on skype from my 2010 Dell Inspiron laptop (on its 3rd hard drive, weighs about 120 lbs, and incinerates your thighs) and tell them about this cool new high-tech development. What will they think of next?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360257856995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:24:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360257915257-48</Id><Title>INTC is starting to stink up the place</Title><Msg>Like a dog that wipes itself on the carpet.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360257915257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:25:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360257943707-49</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Want A Stock That's Going Nowhere or One Headed To New Highs?</Title><Username>druggy52</Username><Timestamp>1359132851598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:54:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm</Msg><Username>permit2084</Username><Timestamp>1360257943707</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:25:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360258093180-50</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Want A Stock That's Going Nowhere or One Headed To New Highs?</Title><Username>druggy52</Username><Timestamp>1359132851598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:54:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep watching it sink....you bought a round trip ticket back to $19.66.</Msg><Username>permit2084</Username><Timestamp>1360258093180</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:28:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360258951249-51</Id><Topic><Title>We're Good for 30</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1327420596000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-01-24 10:56:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more than one year has passed since the original "good for 30" post and still NO 30! HI-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360258951249</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:42:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360259858177-52</Id><Title>Baig: Microsoft Surface Pro packs a punch</Title><Msg>[Bottom line: Not a perfect product but pretty good and a world better than the hugely flawed ARM RT version. And it's going to get much, much better...] ["At the time of my review of Surface RT I indicated that I'd consider it more of a hotshot if it could run older Windows software. Well, Surface Pro obviously can do that, so I'll stick to my word and call it a hotshot. It's blistering fast. The screen is beautiful. It's a solid hybrid between tablet and laptop..."] It was hardly flawless, but I found much to admire in the Surface RT tablet computer that Microsoft started selling in October. The very first personal computer that Microsoft produced itself, it was light, sturdy and, as I wrote at the time, an impressive piece of engineering. It was Microsoft's premier showpiece for its radical new tile-based touch-friendly Windows 8 operating system, a machine that could possibly bridge the narrowing divide between tablet computers and traditional laptops. Except that wasn't entirely the case. Surface RT actually runs a Windows 8 variant known as Windows RT, which means it was incompatible with all of the Windows PC software that came before it. Sure, Surface RT was preloaded with complete versions of Microsoft Office programs Word, Excel, OneNote and PowerPoint (but not Outlook). And other apps were available through an online Windows Store. But for the many people (including me) who might consider Surface as a Windows notebook substitute, the inability to run old programs was for RT a probable deal-breaker. It meant waiting instead for the Surface Pro tablet that goes on sale Saturday, which does make nice with older software. The time is near. I've been testing Surface Pro and like it very much, though it, too, is by no means perfect. On the, um, surface, Surface Pro and Surface RT are not identical twins, though you can't help but notice the strong family resemblance. Both have (not overly loud) stereo speakers and front and rear high-definition (720p) video cameras. Both are solidly built tablets encased in a magnesium alloy, with convenient kickstands that enable you to prop them on a desk. Alas, the lack of a hinge attached to the Surface display means you cannot adjust the angle of the screen when it is propped up. Surface Pro and RT can accommodate clever Microsoft-branded keyboard/cover accessories that add versatility if you want to go into work mode. There's something reassuring about the clicking sound — and which Microsoft highlights in TV spots — when you snap on these keyboards. They come in different colors and there are two main versions: a thin Touch Cover ($119.99) that lets you touch-type passably but without any give on the keys and a somewhat thicker (but still pretty thin) Type Cover ($129.99) that I used to write this column in Word. You'll find the Type Cover experience reasonably close — if not quite as good — as typing on a decent regular laptop keyboard. And you will have difficulty typing with it on your lap. Of course, Windows 8 lets you summon an onscreen touch keyboard. And the touch environment is what makes the new operating system, and Surface itself, feel fresh and modern. But the very schizophrenic nature of Windows 8 means you're likely to spend a fair amount of time going back and forth between handling the screen with your fingers and reverting to the more traditional mouse/trackpad and keyboard worlds in which you've comfortably lived for years. I adapted quickly but expect it will drive some of people crazy. (I tried Microsoft's optional pocket-size $69.95 Wedge Touch Mouse Surface Edition during my review.) Surface Pro, unlike RT, also comes with a pen that you can use to draw or write, such as when jotting things down in OneNote. You can magnetically adhere the pen to the tablet by connecting it to the same port where you connect the power charger. I figure it's only a matter of time before the pen goes AWOL. Surface is smart enough to pick up whatever you're writing with the pen while ignoring the movements of your finger that may be simultaneously touching the screen. The tablet is just over a half-inch thick, compared with a little over one-third of an inch on RT. And at 2 pounds, Pro is heavier than its 1.5-pound sibling but not to the point where it bothered me. Where you do feel the extra weight is in your wallet. Pro versions start at $899, compared with a $499 starting price for Surface RT. The entry-level Pro unit comes with a mere 64 gigabytes of storage, a sum that is far stingier after you factor in the operating system and other built-in software. Microsoft says tests on final production units show about 30 GB of storage are left for installing your own software and files. (Published reports said the available storage was even lower, but Microsoft claims that was for pre-production models.) The push nowadays may be toward cloud storage — in this case through Microsoft's SkyDrive — but I still like having a decent amount of on-board storage. For $999, you can buy Surface Pro with 128 GB, though, again, the available storage — roughly 90 GB — is considerably less. You can bolster storage through a microSD expansion. Surface Pro also comes up short on battery life. In my harsh test with the brightness cranked to the max and a movie streaming over Wi-Fi, I got just 3½ hours of juice. That's extremely skimpy for a tablet and not great for a laptop either. In a similar test, Surface RT got six hours. (Neither comes close to the battery life on an iPad.) Expect somewhat better battery performance under less-trying conditions. So why then do I like Surface Pro so much? For starters, this machine packs a punch. It's got an Intel Core i5 processor inside, compared with an Nvidia Tegra 3 in RT, and it smokes. You appreciate the difference in speed when you run the same apps side by side. The 10.6-inch full-high-definition display (resolution 1920x1080 pixels) is terrific, with wide viewing angles. I didn't mind the same-size but otherwise lower-resolution display on Surface RT, but it doesn't hold a candle to Surface Pro. Surface doesn't have a built-in DVD/CD drive, so to install older software that resided on disks, I had to borrow such a drive from a friend. I connected it to Surface via the tablet's lone built-in USB port; a second USB port is on the power connector, letting you, say, charge a cellphone while you're plugged in working. Incidentally, Surface Pro uses a faster version of USB than Surface RT. I successfully loaded older versions of Family Tree Maker software, Adobe Premiere Elements and Quicken, some dating back to the Windows XP era. Of course, I imagine most folks will load more of the recent stuff they may have on a Windows 7 PC. I downloaded Firefox, iTunes and Office, and they worked fine, though depending on the software, you may not be able to exploit the machine's full touch capabilities. In iTunes, for example, I could tap the screen to make things happen but couldn't always flick to scroll. Microsoft won't say exactly how many apps are available in the Windows Store. On Surface Pro, Microsoft includes its own apps for Internet Explorer, Bing, Xbox Music and more. It does say that the number has quadrupled since the grand opening back on Oct. 26 and that there have been 100 million app downloads overall. Suffice to say the thousands that are available are a small fraction compared with the tablet apps available for the iPad, still the envy of the tablet universe. Pardon the pun, though, but Surface vs. the iPad doesn't exactly represent an apples-to-apples comparison. Especially if you factor in the accessory touch cover keyboards, Surface has as much in common with regular laptops as it does with tablets. The ability to run Office alone suggests it is very likely to show up in the workplace. At the time of my review of Surface RT I indicated that I'd consider it more of a hotshot if it could run older Windows software. Well, Surface Pro obviously can do that, so I'll stick to my word and call it a hotshot. It's blistering fast. The screen is beautiful. It's a solid hybrid between tablet and laptop. But you still have to take to the radically different Windows 8 operating system. And I wish it were cheaper, had more available apps and storage and longer battery life.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360259858177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:57:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360259954368-53</Id><Topic><Title>DoesAsus have an Ace up its sleeve for Mobile World Congress?</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360256914666</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:08:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WDBLAWGROW, the man that comes out AFTER a stock has made a big move and taunts people for not buying it (Facebook) or selling it (Intel). What a hero.......he can't predict stock moves AFTER they've been made. What an internet HERO.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360259954368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:59:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360259963440-54</Id><Topic><Title>OH NO down INTC goes. WHY OH WHY are all the insiders selling?</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360256935030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:08:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holt sold 25,000 shares and still owns 30k shares Plummer sold 10,000 shares and still owns 6k shares 4 others sold between 1k and 5k shares. Holt is selling to pay college tuition. Plummer is putting in a pool. The 3 of the others are doing minor rennovation to their homes. One bought a new car.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360259963440</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:59:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360259974052-55</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Want A Stock That's Going Nowhere or One Headed To New Highs?</Title><Username>druggy52</Username><Timestamp>1359132851598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:54:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$1.70 to $2.15 trumps your measly gain.</Msg><Username>permit2084</Username><Timestamp>1360259974052</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:59:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360259988650-56</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is starting to stink up the place</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360257915257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:25:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're starting to sound like backbay. Give the whining a break and stop watching the daily ups and downs. We're just really waiting on the big breakout in the second half of the year. It will happen sooner if we get some big news and there are lots of possibilities for that...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360259988650</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:59:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360260073465-57</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Want A Stock That's Going Nowhere or One Headed To New Highs?</Title><Username>druggy52</Username><Timestamp>1359132851598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:54:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>or you can spin your wheels with a stock going nowhere.</Msg><Username>permit2084</Username><Timestamp>1360260073465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:01:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360260286848-58</Id><Topic><Title>Is INTC ready to break out?</Title><Username>english.mary73</Username><Timestamp>1360251490604</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:38:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you wanna get the next Bull Exchange/APS stock pick half hour EARLY before the crowd then check this out for FREE.</Msg><Username>claudias.ayala72</Username><Timestamp>1360260286848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:04:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360260349896-59</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is starting to stink up the place</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360257915257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:25:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Turn your device off,pull your head out &amp; go for a nice long hike every day.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1360260349896</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:05:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360261083853-60</Id><Topic><Title>OH NO down INTC goes. WHY OH WHY are all the insiders selling?</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360256935030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:08:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They just sold again and again</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360261083853</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:18:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360261159981-61</Id><Title>You ask me to take INTC down so you could buy the shares real cheap</Title><Msg>That why the share price is down today. Time to buy before the share price goes back up. I casn't keep the share price down anymore.</Msg><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1360261159981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:19:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360261258022-62</Id><Topic><Title>OH NO down INTC goes. WHY OH WHY are all the insiders selling?</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360256935030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:08:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Insiders have sold 2.4 million share almost 50% of there holdings and they are still selling</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360261258022</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:20:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360261352575-63</Id><Title>Forrester predicts that 200 million workers will be lining up for a Windows tablet.</Title><Msg>newsDOTcnetDOTcom/8301-13579_3-57567743-37/is-there-an-ipad-pro-in-apples-future/ Is there an iPad Pro in Apple's future? Forrester predicts that 200 million workers will be lining up for a Windows tablet. Apple may want to take a bite out of that market with an iPad "Pro." by Dan Farber | February 7, 2013 6:54 AM PST Microsoft's Surface Pro is apparently just what businesses want in what was formerly known as the desktop computer. If that's the case, Apple's brain trust may want to revisit the space where the Mac and the iPad intersect. According to Forrester Research's annual survey of nearly 10,000 people around the world who use a computer to do their jobs an hour or more a day, 32 percent said they would prefer Windows over Apple or Android for their next work tablet. Currently, about 2 percent are using a Windows tablet for their work Forrester predicts that Apple will continue to be a smartphone maker of choice for business users, but the research company predicts that 200 million workers will be lining up for a Windows tablet, such as the Surface Pro. It could be that those business users just want their Microsoft Office and other Windows features on a tablet. Still, 26 percent of those surveyed preferred an iPad compared the 32 percent who wanted a Windows tablet. Despite what Forrester says, Apple portrays the iPad as taking the enterprise by storm. "With more than 120 million iPads sold, it's clear that customers around the world love their iPads, and everyday they are finding more great reasons to work, learn and play on their iPads rather than their old PCs," Philip Schiller, Apple's senior vice president of worldwide marketing, said in a press release introducing the new 128GB iPad. "With twice the storage capacity and an unparalleled selection of over 300,000 native iPad apps, enterprises, educators and artists have even more reasons to use iPad for all their business and personal needs." Schiller added that "virtually all of the Fortune 500 and over 85 percent of the Global 500 [are] currently deploying or testing iPad" for applications such as film editing, music composition, training videos, architectural projects and medical diagnostics. iPad apps are generally single-purpose. For example, professional sports teams are buying iPads to run apps, such as GamePlan, that replace paper playbooks, game film, schedules and guidelines for players and coaches. The app is not part of a more complex workflow involving several apps. The reality is that people like the iPad, or just tablets in general, and that's helping to fuel a post-PC wave that is eclipsing sales of PCs. "Post-PC," as Steve Jobs put it, means devices that are easier to use and more intuitive than a PC. But the new 128GB, $799 Wi-Fi-only iPad in its post-PCness doesn't satisfy users who want multitasking, multiuser access and other "PC" features. It's the difference between what you can do with Mac OS and Apple's mobile iOS. Some users will want the best of both, and that is what Microsoft is attempting to do with Windows 8 and the hybrid Surface Pro. Apple CEO Tim Cook has described the Surface as "fairly compromised, confusing product," and compared it to designing a car that flies and floats. "I don't think it would do all of those things very well," he said. The $999, battery-life deprived Surface PC-laptop-tablet might be off to a slow start, but as ZDNet's Ed Bott wrote in his evaluation of the machine, "this is a great product for anyone who's already committed to a Microsoft-centric work environment. It isn't likely to inspire many iPad owners to switch, unless those Apple tablets are in the hands of someone who has been eagerly awaiting an excuse to execute the iTunes ecosystem." Jean Louis Gassée, a former Apple executive, founder of Be Inc. and venture capitalist, sums up Apple's "pro" problem in his attempt to use an iPad to write his recent Monday Note column: Once I start writing, I want to look through the research material I've compiled. On a Mac, I simply open an Evernote window, side-by-side with my Pages document: select, drag, drop. I take some partial screenshots, annotate graphs (such as the iPad Pro prices above), convert images to the .png format used to put the Monday Note on the Web....On the iPad, these tasks are complicated and cumbersome. For starters -- and to belabor the obvious -- I can't open multiple windows. iOS uses the "one thing at a time" model. I can't select/drag/drop, I have to switch from Pages to Evernote or Safari, select and copy a quote, and then switch back to the document and paste....Adding a hyperlink is even more tortuous and, at times, confusing....and things get worse for graphics. Gassée speculates Apple might want to expand the iPad into "authentically Pro territory." He concluded, "The more complex the task, the more our beloved 30-year-old personal computer is up to it. But there is now room above the enforced simplicity that made the iPad's success for UI changes allowing a modicum of real-world "Pro" workflow on iPads." If the Surface Pro becomes more successful as it evolves, Cook and design chief Jony Ive will have to think about designing a no-compromise iPad that can fly and float, or fly and drive, and do both very well.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1360261352575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:22:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360261391256-64</Id><Topic><Title>Answer for why INTC is not going up?</Title><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1360253948845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:19:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reason is I am the controller of the share price and I am making the stockholders sell today. They are all under my control so I can buy the shares real cheap. I using my mind machine to get the stockholders to sell. So remember buy low and sell high</Msg><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1360261391256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:23:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360261520958-65</Id><Topic><Title>You ask me to take INTC down so you could buy the shares real cheap</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1360261159981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:19:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take it down to 14-15 $ that were is going</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360261520958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:25:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360261912027-66</Id><Topic><Title>You ask me to take INTC down so you could buy the shares real cheap</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1360261159981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:19:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>take armh down, new 52 week high today</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1360261912027</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:31:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360262099748-67</Id><Topic><Title>We're Good for 30</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1327420596000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-01-24 10:56:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But if you bght at 24 will you be fine in six months?</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1360262099748</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:34:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360262113613-68</Id><Title>Intel microserver leaves door open for ARM</Title><Msg>SANTA CLARA, Calif.--Intel’s first microserver processor is less power efficient than its existing Xeon chips, leaving a significant opportunity for alternative SoCs, according to Linley Gwennap, principal of the Linley Group. Intel released last year the Atom S1000, also known as Centerton, a dual core chip meant to fend off mainly ARM-based server SoCs from a growing group of vendors. While it reduced power consumption to 6.3W, it does not support Ethernet, Serial ATA or USB controllers or multithreading. “According to data Intel provided, this chip is less power efficient than its Xeon, so it seems like we are going in the wrong direction,” Gwennap said. “It’s not really a system on a chip yet, it has significantly lower performance and only uses 32-nm process technology,” he said at the Linley Data Center Conference here. Gwennap characterized the chip as a placeholder for Avoton, a 22-nm CPU with a new Atom core. “They haven’t announced what it is yet, and it will not be in production until the second half of the year,” he added. Linley Group recently released a report that projects alternative server SoCs will compete for an available market of $2.5 billion by 2016. That’s about 30 percent of a server processor market that the report estimated is edging toward $10 billion a year. The forecast assumes Microsoft will not have a version of Windows Server for ARM during that period. Both sides have their challenges, Gwennap noted. ARM server SoCs need to port x86 server software, they won’t support 64-bit addressing until later this year and they have a lower single-thread performance than the x86, he said. In addition, Intel has a process edge and will use it to roll 14-nm chips in 2014. On the other hand, the x86 architecture was designed for best single-thread performance. As such it is encumbered by complexities such as an ability to manage up to 168 instructions simultaneously in flight in the latest chips and up to 192 in the next-generation Haswell. “There’s a lot of logic just moving data around without doing useful computations,” Gwennap said.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360262113613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360262607874-69</Id><Topic><Title>Intel microserver leaves door open for ARM</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360262113613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Linley Group is an ARM shill organization. You can't expect anything independent from them. Go ahead - find an independent source that backs them up, fanboi...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360262607874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:43:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360262973926-70</Id><Title>New INTC CEO...</Title><Msg>Maybe INTC should recruit a former employee, AMAT CEO and BOD Chairman Michael Splinter, for the new position at INTC. He had such an impressive career at INTC and obviously knows sales/marketing and manufacturing inside-out. -------- Splinter worked for nearly 20 years at Intel Corporation, where most recently, he was executive vice president and director of the Sales and Marketing Group. He previously held various executive positions at Intel, including executive vice president and general manager of the Technology and Manufacturing Group.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360262973926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:49:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263207124-71</Id><Topic><Title>Forrester predicts that 200 million workers will be lining up for a Windows tablet.</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1360261352575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:22:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forrester can't predict their way out of a paper bag. And JL Gasse, chief architect of the BeOS failure, is telling AAPL to make a Pro iPad. What a joke...</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360263207124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:53:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360263290384-72</Id><Title>Surface Pro will allow Microsoft to redeem itself for its previous RT device</Title><Msg>It seems like just yesterday when Microsoft introduced the Surface Windows 8 tablet in October 2012, causing consumers to be wracked with both anticipation and plenty of confusion. This touch-friendly tablet was the first early showcase for Windows 8 and is also the first computer that Microsoft developed completely on its own. The initial Windows 8 tablet was running Windows RT at the time, which was a variant of the Windows 8 software that came with complete, specialized versions of Microsoft Word, Excel, OneNote and PowerPoint along with various integrated apps. It also featured some drawbacks as the device was not yet compatible with any of the programs that could be run on an older Windows system, which proved to be a major turnoff for many people who were otherwise in the market for an impressively engineered tablet. However, Microsoft has finally announced that the Microsoft Surface Pro will be released within the United States and Canada on February 9, 2013. This iteration has all of the added benefits that many of the turned-off consumers have longed for the last three months. This new tablet will be sold through the retail Microsoft stores, Best Buy and Staples, as well as the online Microsoft store. New Microsoft Tablet on the Way A 64GB model will be available for $899 or there will be 128GB of storage for $999. The high definition screen measures 10.6 inches and comes with 1920 x 1080 touchscreen capability. As an added bonus, it is possible to drive an external monitor to jump the resolution up to 2560 x 1440. In addition, the tablet ships with a Surface Pen, which is the Pro's version of a stylus, and it stores easily by magnetically snapping into the side. In addition, the Pro comes with Palm Block technology to prevent accidentally making inputs when writing on the screen. Microsoft can use the Surface Pro as an opportunity to recover from the poor reception that the Surface RT had, and it may even stop the iPad from continuing to infiltrate the market of enterprises looking to incorporate tablets into the workplace. If they succeed, it will also prove that Microsoft knows how to put together a touch- and tablet-friendly interface that can also integrate with a desktop experience in Windows 8. Microsoft designed its operating system so that it can be versatile, working on standard desktop computers along with tablets. This line of thinking is how the Surface came to be, though the approach does have its fair share of risks. For instance, Apple has a different approach with its own line of devices, keeping the iOS and OS X systems separate. Like the RT, the Pro will allow consumers to get outer cases that can actually double as keyboards that are surprisingly durable and usable. These upcoming so-called Touch Covers, which will be available in red, magenta and cyan, will be priced at about $130 each. Additionally, one other option is a $70 touch mouse with four-way scrolling. Tablet fans are eagerly awaiting the February 9 release of the Surface Pro, which will hopefully allow Microsoft to redeem itself for its previous RT device.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360263290384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:54:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263364360-73</Id><Topic><Title>Forrester predicts that 200 million workers will be lining up for a Windows tablet.</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1360261352575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:22:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Forrester can't predict their way out of a paper bag." [Then you two should really get along, BuzzBoy...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360263364360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:56:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263369834-74</Id><Topic><Title>Intel microserver leaves door open for ARM</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360262113613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If ever there were a shill that shill would be you, goatbanger. Only a shill or a fool would beat this dead horse, Intel, 24 x 7 for years.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360263369834</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:56:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263625384-75</Id><Topic><Title>New INTC CEO...</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360262973926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think we'll pass on this one: lost etch business to Lam lost out in implant business to Varian and bought Varian (me ex Varian shareholder :-) actually it was not Splinter - it was the business model introduced by Morgan AMAT total solution lost against Best of Breed LRCX stock was always discounted in the past rellative to AMAT because stupid WS analysts thought it was One horse company - Best of Breed beat total solutions AMAT was notorious for bundling business in order to undercut competitors that's why it was named the evil empire</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360263625384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:00:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360263767634-76</Id><Title>Tipping Point for ARM is June 30</Title><Msg>ARM has until the middle of the year. Intel fully believes that it's significant fabrication advantage will be fully visible by then. So visible that even a Wall Street analyst will be able to see it. ARM has until then to demonstrate volume 20nm planar production - just to stay in the race. There is no possibility of this, of course. By the middle of the year, Intel's 14nm production plan and roadmap will take center stage. The ARM over-inflated bubble and bloated P/E ratio therefore have no chance of surviving the year. In the meantime we get to see if any of the big Intel deals will break early. If so, we won't have to wait until June 30th for the big bang...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360263767634</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:02:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263868694-77</Id><Topic><Title>Intel microserver leaves door open for ARM</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360262113613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correct me if I am wrong but The article refers to the micro server market?</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360263868694</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:04:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360264333483-78</Id><Topic><Title>Important Report About INTC!</Title><Username>riveraandres435</Username><Timestamp>1360257318814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:15:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>helpful report.</Msg><Username>diegofisher522</Username><Timestamp>1360264333483</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:12:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360264738249-79</Id><Topic><Title>New INTC CEO...</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360262973926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow you obviously didn't detect the sarcasm in my post. And Splinter ruined AMAT through the disastrous business expansion into flat panel / solar equipment markets and related loss of focus on their bread and butter silicon biz.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360264738249</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:18:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360264903641-80</Id><Title>Surface Pro Signals Start of Intel Tablet Traction</Title><Msg>With the introduction of the Surface Pro, Intel now marks entry into both the enterprise tablet market and the consumer tablet market although non-Microsoft offerings in the home market will probably be stronger. With new iterations and improvements on Intel's roadmap as far as the eye can see, their competitiveness in the tablet arena appears ready to gain serious traction...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360264903641</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:21:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360265019027-81</Id><Topic><Title>New INTC CEO...</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360262973926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Wow you obviously didn't detect the sarcasm in my post." [Why would we think that you would engage in anything other than character assassination and nastiness where Intel is the subject?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360265019027</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:23:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360265399449-82</Id><Topic><Title>getanid61 &amp; Marsavian</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360090860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The last thing to look for [on the ARM turn] is when the 50 Day MA arrives at the current price, will it support the stock or will it then turn into resistance. If the latter then that will be a clear sign that a peak in the stock, which may prove to be permanent, has been reached." [We definitely don't want to miss the turn. Can't be long now until the big bang of bubble deflation...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360265399449</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:29:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360265608125-83</Id><Topic><Title>Intel microserver leaves door open for ARM</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360262113613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Linley Group recently released a report that projects alternative server SoCs will compete for an available market of $2.5 billion by 2016. Intel should be @10nm Manufacturing cost will force many small and medium ARM players out of the market - No more cheap ARM SoCs!</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360265608125</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:33:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360265648619-84</Id><Topic><Title>New INTC CEO...</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360262973926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Waldo, same old garbage. Pumping INTC in 2010 at 24 on the way to 17 and trashing ARMH then as well. well over 2 years and not a penny gained holding INTC. during all that time.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1360265648619</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:34:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360265977413-85</Id><Topic><Title>New INTC CEO...</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360262973926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you seem to be obsessed with Waldo - do you have night mares about waldo . consult with a shrink</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360265977413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:39:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360266070751-86</Id><Title>Down, down, down</Title><Msg>Market up YTD. Not INTC. This stock is below 50 and 200 DMA, and appears to be headed only in one direction. Market is rocking ytd, and this stock can not get any traction. What will happen when the market has it's inevitable pullback. If today is any indication, the market is down about 1/2% and INTC is down over double that.</Msg><Username>asheepshdplayr</Username><Timestamp>1360266070751</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:41:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360266537098-87</Id><Topic><Title>New INTC CEO...</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360262973926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe because I am actually considering to open long position?</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360266537098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:48:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360266679857-88</Id><Title>With all the federal employee furlough coming in MARCH they are pulling money out of the TSP and moving back to G fund. There will be a lot less money going into stock funds</Title><Msg>With all the federal employee furlough coming in MARCH they are pulling money out of the TSP and moving back to G fund. There will be a lot less money going into stock funds</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360266679857</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:51:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360266723885-89</Id><Topic><Title>New INTC CEO...</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360262973926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would be an ironic twist (and a poor reflection on INTC BOD) if they did hire him back though.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360266723885</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:52:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360266849010-90</Id><Topic><Title>Is INTC ready to break out?</Title><Username>english.mary73</Username><Timestamp>1360251490604</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:38:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This news letter truly comprehend how the stock trading runs.</Msg><Username>brooks.paige34</Username><Timestamp>1360266849010</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:54:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360266915902-91</Id><Topic><Title>New INTC CEO...</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360262973926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unlike you (the INTC head cheerleader) I am only cautiously optimistic about INTC's prospects to grow earnings.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360266915902</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:55:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360267179426-92</Id><Topic><Title>New INTC CEO...</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360262973926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC Solar Commercial-size Modules (1.09 Square Meters) Set 15.1% Efficiency RecordPR Newswire(Thu, Jan 31) Probably using Varian (now AMAT) implanters</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360267179426</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:59:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360267304185-93</Id><Topic><Title>New INTC CEO...</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360262973926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Unlike you (the INTC head cheerleader) I am only cautiously optimistic about INTC's prospects to grow earnings." [That's because of your inability to properly evaluate Intel's significant fabrication superiority and the effects it will have on mobility market share. If you knew anything about FinFET and 14nm production, then you would be a cheerleader too...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360267304185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:01:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360267508164-94</Id><Topic><Title>Down, down, down</Title><Username>asheepshdplayr</Username><Timestamp>1360266070751</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:41:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Market up YTD. Not INTC. This stock is below 50 and 200 DMA, and appears to be headed only in one direction. Market is rocking ytd, and this stock can not get any traction. What will happen when the market has it's inevitable pullback. If today is any indication, the market is down about 1/2% and INTC is down over double that." [You have a 4-page message history full of nothing but short sentiments. Not exactly a source of analysis or independent thinking...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360267508164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:05:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360267962535-95</Id><Topic><Title>Down, down, down</Title><Username>asheepshdplayr</Username><Timestamp>1360266070751</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:41:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have a 4-page message history full of nothing but short sentiments. Not exactly a source of analysis or independent thinking...] ------------------------- And you, goatbanger, have a message history of 100s of pages and thousands of messages of nothing but long sentiments. Not exactly a source of analysis or independent thinking... HI-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360267962535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:12:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360267981237-96</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro Signals Start of Intel Tablet Traction</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360264903641</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:21:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thus far analysts have valued Intel as having zero participation in tablets or smartphones. With new products like Lenovo's K900, Surface Pro, Asus Fonepad and many other Intel-based convertibles, tablets and smartphones arriving in the market, one would expect a new perspective from analysts that recognizes the industry change. Surface Pro may not be perfect, but there's no question it's at the top of the tablet food chain for performance and everything we know about Intel's roadmap suggests this device category can improve very quickly.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360267981237</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:13:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360268049158-97</Id><Topic><Title>Down, down, down</Title><Username>asheepshdplayr</Username><Timestamp>1360266070751</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:41:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you've been pumping INTC nonstop ad infinitum. and all you're geek speak has gotten you exactly no where.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1360268049158</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:14:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360268172035-98</Id><Topic><Title>New INTC CEO...</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360262973926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis, Stop being so smug. I'll bet I know a lot more about process technology than you ever will. I am fully aware of INTC's fabrication superiority. The effect it will have on mobility market share is also slowly becoming clearer. The effect all of this will have on what really matters though, earnings growth, if far from evident.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360268172035</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:16:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360268339263-99</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy Nuff fell in love with Intel and is BITTER! ROFL!</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1360196791916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:26:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at Lucy/Tooofunny defending Intel like it was his own relative. LOL! Priceless!</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360268339263</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:18:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360268448593-100</Id><Topic><Title>OH WALDO, OH CEEEESCO!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360253801539</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:16:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what's even worse, back in June 2010 when waldo was pumping INTC at 24.00, ARMH which he disliked even then was just starting it's rise from $5.00. But alas, Waldo settles for INTC and earns nothing in approaching 3 years</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1360268448593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:20:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360268449528-101</Id><Title>DIRECT quote from the nasty mouth of Lucy_Nuff/Tooofunnny ROFL!!!</Title><Msg>"This company has a virtual franchise on the future of technology in the world and will be the first to benefit from a a recovery and renewed IT spending."</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360268449528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:20:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360268758241-102</Id><Topic><Title>Inturd Seems to Be Stuck in the Pipe Between the Toilet and the Septic Tank</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358976631507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 16:30:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Smelltel is backing up the toilet and stinking up portfolios.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360268758241</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:25:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360269361487-103</Id><Topic><Title>New INTC CEO...</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360262973926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll bet I know a lot more about process technology than you ever will. -------------------------------------- I'll betcha you don't know more about cutting and pasting than Wallis does.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360269361487</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:36:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360269635434-104</Id><Topic><Title>Answer for why INTC is not going up?</Title><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1360253948845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:19:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Answer for why INTC is not going up? ----------------------- Because turds sink.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1360269635434</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:40:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360270089862-105</Id><Topic><Title>Answer for why INTC is not going up?</Title><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1360253948845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:19:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not necessarily. Have you ever heard the expression- " I'm going to float a log'" ?</Msg><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1360270089862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:48:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360270594203-106</Id><Title>Here Here!</Title><Msg>Hate it or love it, Intel's on top and we gonna shinnne homey til our heart stop.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360270594203</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:56:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360270649907-107</Id><Topic><Title>DIRECT quote from the nasty mouth of Lucy_Nuff/Tooofunnny ROFL!!!</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360268449528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:20:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dagger</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1360270649907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:57:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360270863296-108</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro Signals Start of Intel Tablet Traction</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360264903641</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:21:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>one would expect a new perspective from analysts that recognizes the industry change. good luck with this one! Mercedes Benz versus Yugo The Benchmark Company‘s semiconductor analyst Gary Mobley, who covers ARM Holdings (ARMH), and rates its shares Hold, with a $44 price target, today writes that tablet computers based on the chips using ARM technology, such as parts from Nvidia (NVDA), are “far more power efficient” than Microsoft‘s (MSFT) “Surface Pro” tablet that runs Intel’s (INTC) microprocessors. Surface Pro goes on sale February 9th, joining the Surface RT model based on Nvidia’s chip, which went on sale October 26th. You can check Microsoft’s site for buying information. Despite the appeal of being able to run fully fledged Windows 8 applications on the Surface Pro, Mobley thinks the device has some notable drawbacks, citing both the review from Anandtech this week and one from The Wall Street Journal’s Walt Mossberg: When the Intel processor is not in power savings mode, the clock speed of the Intel processor is better than an ARM-based processor. On the negative side, and these are big negatives, the Surface Pro costs about $200 more than ARM-based tablets (with equivalent flash storage capacity). The higher cost of the Surface Pro can be attributable to the fact that Intel processor costs approximately 10.0x as much as an ARM-based mobile application processor ($225 [according to Anandtech] vs. ~$20 of NVIDIA Tegra III). Additionally, unless you dim the screen and turn off all connectivity features, the Surface Pro may run out of batteries before you can finish watching Gone With the Wind (if that’s your thing). According to Walt Mossberg’s review of the Surface Pro, battery life is only four to five hours (click link for WSJ article). That’s about half the battery life for an ARM-based tablet (see recent Engadget article by clicking link). Last, the Surface Pro is considerably heavier and thicker than ARM-based tablets; however, this may have to do more with the screen technology used and available i/o features such as USB ports. Some supporters of Intel claim that a more power- sensitive processor is around the corner. Last month (January) Intel introduced its Ivy Bridge Y chips with a 13W TDP (7W SDP) power specification, saying it has over a dozen wins already for these chips, including Lenovo’s IdeaPad Yoga 11S Ultrabook and a future detachable Ultrabook from Acer. The thing to keep in mind, however, is that ARM licensees are continuously improving clock speed while minimizing power budgets. This tradeoff between power and performance should be further enhanced with use of ARM’s big.LITTLE technology. Samsung, for example, in two weeks will be showing off an 8-core mobile application processor utilizing big.LITTLE.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360270863296</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:01:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360271630775-109</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy Nuff fell in love with Intel and is BITTER! ROFL!</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1360196791916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:26:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dagger</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1360271630775</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:13:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360272729928-110</Id><Title>Sales &amp; Marketing Conference ??</Title><Msg>Any News ??</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1360272729928</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:32:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360272890690-111</Id><Topic><Title>Answer for why INTC is not going up?</Title><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1360253948845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:19:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If one examined Intel over the past 13 years it would be easy to conclude a very long term horizon would be needed. For the majority of Intel's history this was not the case. However, around year 2000 and shortly after several events occurred that put Intel's growth on simmer. First was the dotcom bust that took the wind out of almost everything tech. Following that Intel's primary competitor AMD managed to upstage Intel's flagship processors with the 64 bit Athalon and a range of great performing server chips. For the next five years AMD hammered at Intel's marketshare in both PC's and servers and for the first time captured the major OEM's as customers. By the time AMD had peaked they may have reached near 40% market share in servers. Intel's stock languished and deservedly so. But around 2006 Intel launched the Conroe design and since then AMD has been looking at Intel's exhaust ever since. Today, AMD is a beaten company with very little prospects and Intel has the greatest share of every PC category it has had in many years. However, while Intel was busy retaking the lead in everything x86, the mobile industry quietly crept up on Intel and created this booming mobile market, and analysts again hammered Intel for not being part of it. So where does Intel stand today? For all practical purposes Intel put the AMD threat to rest. It dominates virtually every segment of the x86 market and it may also reclaim all of its x86 intellectual property if AMD becomes insolvent as some predict. Analysts should have already rewarded Intel for reclaiming such a lead in everything x86 but they haven't because they see mobile (right or wrong) as the new threat. But now Intel is very well positioned to make its assault on mobile and the result of their work is just now starting to be seen in the new smartphone, tablets and convertible market. For those familiar with Intel's product and process roadmap they are aware that Intel is about to put the semiconductor and mobile industry on a roller-coaster ride of innovation like they've never seen. Not only will Intel have slayed the AMD dragon and be the undisputed king of its traditional markets, it will have also taken the volume graphics market from both Nvidia and AMD and captured a meaningful part of mobile, the embedded market, and the Internet-of-Things. The time horizon looks to be roughly 24-36 months. There sure are a lot of reasons to be optimistic about Intel during this time.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360272890690</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:34:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360274099651-112</Id><Title>CVU - Ready to Rally!</Title><Msg>Breakout!</Msg><Username>weinstein_s</Username><Timestamp>1360274099651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:54:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360274381225-113</Id><Topic><Title>Answer for why INTC is not going up?</Title><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1360253948845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:19:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5) Because it is neither going up nor remaining unchanged. 6) Because Wallus &amp; Mux are loooooooooooooooooooooooosers, and until they capitulate, there is no change for a sustained rise in INTC.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1360274381225</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:59:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360275128941-114</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro Signals Start of Intel Tablet Traction</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360264903641</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:21:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mobley's comments show how analysts become captured by their own investment advice and the extent they will go to justify their opinion. Mobley says, "an ARM based tablet is far more "power efficient" than the [Core i5 based] Pro". That's like saying a Prius gets better mileage than a Lamborghini. It may be a true statement but so what? No one expected anything different. CPU efficiency and performance do not scale linearly as the ARM camp is beginning to learn as they attempt to make faster processors to compete with Intel's CPU's. The rest of Mobley's comments re thickness, weight is just more rehashed negativity. Surface Pro reminds me of making pancakes. The first one is rarely good, but the following one's are delicious.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360275128941</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:12:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360275331534-115</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro Signals Start of Intel Tablet Traction</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360264903641</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:21:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The thing is a boat anchor.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1360275331534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:15:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360275437778-116</Id><Title>Surface Pro and Core tablets are created for Business. Reviewers don't understand this.</Title><Msg>Anyway, Business purchases are done by the IT department, and they evaluate the product based on its usefulness to get work done.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360275437778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:17:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360275931943-117</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro and Core tablets are created for Business. Reviewers don't understand this.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360275437778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:17:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought you guys all said ULTRABOOKS were going to make INTC stock go to the moon? How did that work out? About the same as GOOGLETV, eh? Oh, and yesterday you boneheads were predicting a big rise in INTC because Dell is going private. In fact, Wallis was saying Robert Noyce was going to lead the buyout bid.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1360275931943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:25:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360276221196-118</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro and Core tablets are created for Business. Reviewers don't understand this.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360275437778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:17:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the most part Anandtech did a very thorough review of Pro's strengths and weaknesses. But then not surprisingly Wall St. analysts beholden to ARMH jumped in with their pseudo analysis/spin in an attempt to do damage control.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360276221196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:30:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360278102686-119</Id><Title>New generation of analysts---grads of american "high" schools</Title><Msg>him and me are gunna to shoots um hoops</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360278102686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:01:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360278407000-120</Id><Title>INTC is a great buy.Looking for the share price tol go over 24.00 this year</Title><Msg>In a recent article I singled out three companies that will perform favorably in 2013 due to their exposure to international markets. I would like to add a fourth company to this list, Intel. One of the reasons for Intel's poor performance in 2012 was the lack of growth in PC units within emerging markets, but the prospect for 2013 is strong. I believe that many emerging markets such as China, Brazil, Indonesia and Russia are reaching a tipping point to mass penetration to PCs. Population growth and the desire for connectivity to the internet are main factors that should drive growth for the company, as the PC remains the dominant device for internet access. For FY 2013, revenue from emerging markets should account for 19% of overall sales, and this figure should grow 13% year over year with a target of 40% by 2016. PC growth is directly correlated to GDP growth, which should rise by 5.6% in 2013.</Msg><Username>smithdon827</Username><Timestamp>1360278407000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:06:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360278979428-121</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is a great buy.Looking for the share price tol go over 24.00 this year</Title><Username>smithdon827</Username><Timestamp>1360278407000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:06:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What utter drivel.</Msg><Username>harlan_titusville</Username><Timestamp>1360278979428</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:16:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360279134450-122</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro Signals Start of Intel Tablet Traction</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360264903641</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:21:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>--- The rest of Mobley's comments re thickness, weight is just more rehashed negativity. --- Weight is a huge problem for tablet designs. All the units available on the market (including iPads) are veritable bricks. A key reason to use a tablet instead of a laptop is to be able to operate it while holding it comfortably in your hand for extended periods. The tablet revolution will only truly happen when the weight of tablets approaches that of today's e-ink based ereaders while offering a battery life of at least 8 hours (a typical workshift).</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360279134450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:18:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360279649860-123</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro Signals Start of Intel Tablet Traction</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360264903641</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:21:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why not comparing to surface RT? And who watches "gone with the wind" in high resolution on a tablet anyway... Surface Pro versus MacBook Microsoft has been absolutely pummeled in the press and in reader comments this week by pundits and customers alike. They feel cheated by the amount of free storage space available to them on the new line of Surface Pro devices. But is that criticism fair or even valid? If it were valid, then surely Apple would have been scrutinized carefully over its 11.6-inch MacBook Air 128, which has specs that are reasonably similar to the Surface Pro 128. They’re both ultraportable devices that run full-strength operating systems. Both use similar CPUs, offer similar amounts of RAM, and advertise 128 GB of storage. The Surface Pro has touch capabilities and can be used as a tablet, but at its heart it is a full-strength PC designed for extreme mobility. Unlike the Surface RT, which is a tablet that does a few PC-like things, Surface Pro is a real, no-compromises PC. It can power a 2560x1600 30-inch display, it runs Windows 8 Pro, it supports Hyper-V virtualization, you can run PhotoShop and AutoCAD on it. It deserves to be compared head to head with another full PC like the MacBook Air... zdnetdotcom/surface-pro-versus-macbook-air-whos-being-dishonest-with-storage-space-7000011009/</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360279649860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:27:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360280154135-124</Id><Title>Apple responds to critics &amp; stock jumps today</Title><Msg>Meanwhile, Intel management keeps their hands over their ears &amp; lets the stock get manipulated...Worst management team I've ever seen, starting with the CEO.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1360280154135</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:35:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360280676220-125</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro Signals Start of Intel Tablet Traction</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360264903641</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:21:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would rather pay extra $200 to get a full power tablet and use it as a computer for high power needs than have an ARM based tablet and a seperate compute.</Msg><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1360280676220</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:44:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360281059990-126</Id><Topic><Title>Apple responds to critics &amp; stock jumps today</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1360280154135</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:35:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple responded to a lawsuit that was filed against them. They did the exact same thing that Intel has done several times.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360281059990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:50:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360281900590-127</Id><Title>Lucy Nuff, butt-burtt Intel Long's main aliases these days</Title><Msg>ToooFunnny backbay_bstn will_amd_yu Harlan_Titusville Wdblawgrow wallis_weener</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1360281900590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:05:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360282034797-128</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy Nuff, butt-burtt Intel Long's main aliases these days</Title><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1360281900590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:05:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>butt-hurt? I agree.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360282034797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:07:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360283307448-129</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy Nuff fell in love with Intel and is BITTER! ROFL!</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1360196791916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:26:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yhoo needs to get it's act together &amp; chop nuff's pathetic nuts off so that serial IDIOT abuser can't post anymore IMO.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1360283307448</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:28:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360284970937-130</Id><Title>ARM rates FDSOI process as 'good technology'</Title><Msg>Some observers have argued that 20-nm bulk planar CMOS will not produce significant power savings while being hard to manufacture. The FinFET processes, where transistors are created in fins standing proud of the silicon surface, could be even more complicated to make and harder to yield.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360284970937</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:56:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360285040726-131</Id><Topic><Title>ARM rates FDSOI process as 'good technology'</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360284970937</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:56:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When was the last time anyone saw any of the shills post a message with content or substance?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360285040726</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:57:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360285519549-132</Id><Title>Catalysts and Potential Catalysts to Pop the ARM Bubble</Title><Msg>[Just looking for one good catalyst or big deal to pop the ARM bubble. Only takes one. It will happen...] Windows Surface Pro Release: February 9th On Friday, Feb. 8, Microsoft will be holding an exclusive event for select guests to commemorate the Surface Pro’s launch. After this reception, the formal launch will take place just before midnight at the Best Buy in New York City’s Union Square. Mobile World Congress 2013: February 25th Intel has announced that it will showcase Android devices running a new dual core, dual graphics platform at the Mobile World Congress in Barcelona from February 25 to 28. “Specifically, Intel will showcase its latest smartphone technologies and devices running the Android* platform, including a new dual core, dual graphics platform, as well as OEM- and service provider-supported devices based on the company’s new Intel® AtomTM Z2420 platform targeted at emerging markets,” the company said in a release. Tizen "In fact, Google's biggest and most profitable Android partner, Samsung, is supporting a new platform called Tizen. (Intel is also a backer.) If Samsung switched from Android to Tizen, the phone platform scene would be transformed overnight. The first Tizen devices are expected within three months." Cisco Announcement iWatch Announcement; This would be big if it happens Intel Web TV: A la carte TV. Let's really hope this happens Smartphone Announcements: We know we'll get these Tablet Announcements: Lots of these too. Lots of enterprise potential Windows 8 Growth: Starting slow but should have steady growth</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360285519549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:05:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360285783005-133</Id><Title>Asustek Computer to unveil the biggest supersized smartphone yet at 2013 Mobile World Congress</Title><Msg>I used to belong to the school of thought that large-screen smartphones were a gimmick that Apple could safely ignore and most iPhone users would never miss. I’ve changed my mind. Strong and growing sales of so-called phablets have convinced me that there is user demand for the jumbo-sized smartphone, and I agree with Apple-watching Bear-Stearns analyst Shaw Wu that Apple is leaving money ( and market share) on the proverbial table by not having one to offer. In a note to investors cited by Appleinsider, Mr. Wu observes: “We believe AAPL is leaving money on the table by not participating in larger touchscreen form factors. But more importantly, we believe AAPL needs to reclaim high-end leadership as that is what brand is about. Sure, iOS, iTunes and the App Store are great, but it is clear that many customers want larger screens. “ Digitimes’ Monica Chen and Joseph Tsai, reported Wednesday that Asustek Computer may unveil the biggest supersized smartphone yet at the 2013 Mobile World Congress (MWC) in Barcelona, Spain, February 25-28. The Asus Fonepad is rumored to be a 7-inch Android 4.1 tablet (Asus makes the Nexus 7 tablet for Google) equipped with telephony functions and powered by an Intel Atom Z242 processor, Other purported specs include a 1280 x 800 IPS touchscreen, 16GB RAM and 1GB ROM, a 3-megapixel rear camera, support for 3G, Wi-Fi, Bluetooth and GPS, and an expected selling price of US$271-$305 according to unnamed insider sources in the Asian upstream supply chain. As we’ve noted here before, Apple could quite easily and quickly make a super-phablet that could do battle with the Asus Fonepad, by adding a telephony chip to the 4G iPad mini, just as the mini itself has answered the Nexus 7 (et al.) challenge. I’m skeptical that they will do that. From: iphone5newsblog</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360285783005</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:09:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360286782634-134</Id><Topic><Title>Intel microserver leaves door open for ARM</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360262113613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Linley Gwennap has already proven himself to be totally clueless with respect to future server predictions. In 1999 he published a one grand book report on Itanium in which he boldly claimed ... 'With all of this backing, IA-64 is likely to grab at least 60% of the server market by 2003, according to a new report “Intel's Itanium and IA-64” from MicroDesign Resources.' wwwDOTipst-infoDOTnet/download/LinuxJournal/LJ/074/4019.html Itanium was your rubber stamp in those days and a fat lot of good it did ! More nonsense from him here ... eetimesDOTcom/electronics-news/4042174/Itanium-era-dawns 'I expect Itanium to replace Xeon, but not until 2003, when McKinley and its successors open a performance gap over Xeon. Changes in servers never happen fast. But with Itanium now a reality, Intel's dominance is only a matter of time.'</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360286782634</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:26:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360287215119-135</Id><Topic><Title>Catalysts and Potential Catalysts to Pop the ARM Bubble</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360285519549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:05:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If this is your best shot at defining catalysts, Intel is pretty dead in 2013. I guess we'll have to wait till 2014 when Otellini's plan to light a fire under Apple and Samsung with his accelerated 14nm LP roll-out takes shape :-)</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360287215119</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:33:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360287315801-136</Id><Title>How hard is it for intel to start another architecture?</Title><Msg>I am trying to understand the possibilities available to intel here given its vast resources and cash availability vs some small opponent like ARM. How hard is it for intel to keep improving its own core architecture but at the same time research the possibility of designing a completely new architecture similar to eg risc of ARM or at least in a direction other than x86 that will strike aRM at its own area and eliminate the need for people to licence from ARM and instead see in intel a new threat alternative at all levels both the mobile and the PC /server. Intel must make sure it recognizes that ARM is not the problem. The real problem is allowing some other companies like say QCOM to grow enough earnings that they then become able to attack intel in other areas. To do that it needs to challenge those companies directly where it hurts by outdoing the ARM+others architecture game with its own alternative that can be superior. Is that direction considered? Why do we need to worry about the mobile transition or adapting x86 to it and not try to not only defeat them at their own game since we can fund research there to outperform their designs but also to move the market into directions of new applications of PCs that will require super massive computing power that mobile devices will never be able to provide forcing the server and cloud markets to rely insanely more on the traditional intel architecture. You need to corner the market in many levels. I would imagine intel with the economy of scale can launch such multiple wars and win them all if it wanted. Who can finance such efforts better than intel? However if this is not done pretty soon this will be indeed some other company not ARM etc but the big players that are now relying on ARM and growing their earnings on their designs... In fact if intel wants to completely kill everyone they need to consider a particular architecture and hardware direction that will prove very expensive and complicated and yet very efficient for nobody else to be able to chase them there and the applications to depend on it. If you develop technology that takes dozens of billion to build factories for, nobody will be able to chase them there but they will be able to chase them there and better if intel doesnt take the market in that direction very soon.</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1360287315801</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:35:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360288337642-137</Id><Topic><Title>Intel microserver leaves door open for ARM</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360262113613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Having already proven in an earlier post that Linley Gwennap has no historical credibility (e.g. wildly optimistic Itanium predictions over a decade ago) let's analyze his latest piece of nonsense ... 'Linley Group recently released a report that projects alternative server SoCs will compete for an available market of $2.5 billion by 2016. That’s about 30 percent of a server processor market that the report estimated is edging toward $10 billion a year. The forecast assumes Microsoft will not have a version of Windows Server for ARM during that period.' No way in hell is the microserver market going to be 30% in 2016 or most likely ever. Atom/ARM 64-bit products will just not be developed or attractive enough against low voltage Xeons. A 10% figure, like HPC is, of the general server market is a more realistic long term target although I think it will be more like 5-10% and that's assuming they can actually eventually beat LV Xeons on performance/power which is still in doubt. 'According to data Intel provided, this chip is less power efficient than its Xeon' There's your big giant cluestock Dumbo and you missed it. Once you add all the other elements that comprise a server any performance/power advantage a low power chip may have is gone swamped by all the other fixed power constants like memory, I-O lanes and drive storage. The point about micro-servers like Centerton is that they maximize memory/I-O bandwidth per cpu performance but that is always going to be a niche market otherwise Vector chips would already have inherited the computing world. Centerton was also designed before they got the Atom SoC design right with Clovertrail but Avoton will not be so encumbered. Centerton also has multi-threading so he was wrong on that score too. arkDOTintelDOTcom/compare/71269,71268,71267</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360288337642</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:52:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360288519931-138</Id><Topic><Title>Intel microserver leaves door open for ARM</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360262113613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The recent article references micro servers. Linley's article on Itanium was a swing and miss. One reason would be that Gwennap worked at HP on PA RISC which became the foundation of Itanium. What Linley overlooked was cache improvements made in the Core i (Nehalem) family. Nehalem 64-bit performamce beat that of Itanium by a wide margin. "Linley Gwennap is the president and principal analyst of The Linley Group. One of the most respected analysts in the microprocessor industry, he has followed the industry for more than 15 years. Starting as a processor designer at Hewlett-Packard, Linley later worked in PA-RISC marketing and then became editor-in-chief of Microprocessor Report and vice president of MicroDesign Resources before founding The Linley Group in 1999."</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360288519931</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:55:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360288928974-139</Id><Title>Windows xp is going away next year, resuling in a massive upgrade cycle late 2013.</Title><Msg>Just in time for Haswell, with longer battery life, and thinner and lighter convertibles. 2014 will be the year for PC's. The stock may move in anticipation of this, when the Wall St crooks start pumping it up.. But one never knows with these crooks, when they'll start the pump.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360288928974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:02:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360289110714-140</Id><Topic><Title>How hard is it for intel to start another architecture?</Title><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1360287315801</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:35:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps you should pose a different question: how hard is it for you to pick a different stock? Apparently VERY difficult as you are wedded to failure.</Msg><Username>longtalltxn</Username><Timestamp>1360289110714</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:05:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360289192914-141</Id><Topic><Title>Windows xp is going away next year, resuling in a massive upgrade cycle late 2013.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360288928974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:02:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will smoke start pouring out of those machines running Windows XP on the day extended support ends?</Msg><Username>longtalltxn</Username><Timestamp>1360289192914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:06:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360289260565-142</Id><Title>Michael Dell is no dummy. He knows the PC upgrade cycle will be massive</Title><Msg>after Win XP goes away. He is going to make a TON of $$ from taking Dell private.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360289260565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:07:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360289408247-143</Id><Topic><Title>Intel microserver leaves door open for ARM</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360262113613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nehalem did not come on the server scene until about 6-7 years after Itanium's introduction so that does not explain its poor adoption before then. Fundamentally Itanium was a niche processor with poor legacy server software support. Does that sound familiar to what another architecture is attempting to do now ? Even when the McKinley version of Itanium 2 was released and it was amongst the most powerful of chips along with Alpha EV7 it made no sales difference. I don't care how many vendors try to bring out ARM servers, if they perform like the current mobile chips (+ 30-50%) they will be ignored by the buying public. They need to show double something over x86 in some important metric to the server buying public to get anyone's attention but it will be more like half something compared to x86 which just won't cut it. p.s Nehalem had significant core improvements too over its Pentium ancestors.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360289408247</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:10:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360289683763-144</Id><Topic><Title>Intel microserver leaves door open for ARM</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360262113613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That other architecture is a lot cheaper, a lot more power efficient and from the stand-point of its customers, well supported in software. It's targeted at the sweet-spot of the market in terms of volumes. Big high-performance chips are today what main-frames were yesterday. They don't have a bright tomorrow.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360289683763</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:14:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360289907674-145</Id><Topic><Title>Intel microserver leaves door open for ARM</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360262113613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They need to show double something over x86 in some important metric ..." Perhaps that metric will be in performance per dollar (when measured both in terms of initial deployment and recurring cost of energy to run). Also, the world wants more than one supplier, because Intel played very dirty for years (which is what happens when there aren't enough suppliers). For the world, the stranglehold of x86 being broken is a good thing. The "server software" issue you raise is a nonstarter; it went away with virtualization. And as for the "server buying public", no such entity exists. The public is not in the habit of buying servers at all, and the companies which are in the habit will evaluate what is available and decide accordingly. They won't make their decisions on some perverted sense of loyalty like some of the diehard losers on this board have done by marrying a stock that does absolutely nothing for them.</Msg><Username>longtalltxn</Username><Timestamp>1360289907674</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:18:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360289948758-146</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy Nuff, butt-burtt Intel Long's main aliases these days</Title><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1360281900590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:05:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>longtalltxn is another one. He crucifies Wally for always being here........yet he's always here as well. We know he hates himself because he's everything that he rants against. Hilarious !</Msg><Username>lucy_alert</Username><Timestamp>1360289948758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:19:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360290123916-147</Id><Topic><Title>Intel microserver leaves door open for ARM</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360262113613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not server software, frankly even MIPS has some legacy server software support unlike ARM which currently has zero server production software support. ' It's targeted at the sweet-spot of the market in terms of volumes.' The sweet spot of the server market in terms of volumes is currently occupied by Xeons, your toy processors have zero chance of displacing them. 'Big high-performance chips are today what main-frames were yesterday. They don't have a bright tomorrow.' LOL, Mainframes were sold basically on I-O throughput not cpu performance which is currently the angle the ARM guys are fishing with. You fancy Mainframe volumes ? LOL</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360290123916</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:22:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360290317150-148</Id><Topic><Title>Windows xp is going away next year, resuling in a massive upgrade cycle late 2013.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360288928974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:02:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they will be expose to easy hacking and also xp takes a while to boot unlike WIN8 which is 10 sec boot time.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1360290317150</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:25:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360290336234-149</Id><Topic><Title>Intel microserver leaves door open for ARM</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360262113613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The cpu cost of a server is around 10% and is basically noise. ARM is also less power efficient doing real work, I already posted linux benchmarks that showed high end Core chips beating clusters of A9s in performance/power.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360290336234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:25:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360290624709-150</Id><Topic><Title>Intel microserver leaves door open for ARM</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360262113613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM has NO advantage when it comes to power savings vs Haswell/Broadwell based Xeons. That kills it right there. Just because the world likes an alternative to Intel, doesn't mean they are going to buy an INFERIOR product at a higher price. Enterprises are very slow to move, and are very reluctant to change a reliable vendor like Intel. 50% of their computers are still Windows XP for christsake!! Linley Gwnepp lives in the 90's. Its a completely different world. Other than message board readers, I don't know of anyone who gives a hoot what he says. Theres that other dude of microprocessor report too.. They should just RETIRE now.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360290624709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:30:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360290729465-151</Id><Topic><Title>The truth behind the numbers and trading</Title><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1334749038000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-04-18 07:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel will top 30 eventually this year and then some. Intel to 100 eventually and then some. And you will be afraid that on the way to 100 you have some stupid gaps" --- maximum_probability, April 18, 2012 ----------------------------------------------------- No wonder he's mad.</Msg><Username>longtalltxn</Username><Timestamp>1360290729465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:32:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360291501956-152</Id><Topic><Title>Intel microserver leaves door open for ARM</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1360262113613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:35:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Door is always open. Why taking too long to enter?</Msg><Username>nofumble</Username><Timestamp>1360291501956</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:45:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360292132854-153</Id><Topic><Title>The truth behind the numbers and trading</Title><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1334749038000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-04-18 07:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dead money until earnings begin to accelerate. It's THAT simple with this stock and all stocks. Seen it a million times. I accumulated Oracle shares in the teens years ago when it was dead money, waited and waited and sold at 30. Intel will rise again. Look at this as an extended opportunity to accumulate more shares Via the Dividend as well as cash you have on-hand.</Msg><Username>fitfunactive2002</Username><Timestamp>1360292132854</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:55:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360292389865-154</Id><Topic><Title>Even ARMH's new partner, AMD admits ARM servers might be worthless</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351636998519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:43:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1360292389865</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:59:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360292557692-155</Id><Title>Another day closer to 14 nm fab 42 opening day ceramony.</Title><Msg>The whole game changes at 14 nm.Then 10 then 7.Who said intc is not a long term hold. I will collect the dividend for the next twenty years if I live that long.I like the way they buy back shares and raise the dividend.So if the stock rises 6% per year with the div of 4% thats 10% per year with no increase of the dividend.Like I said who said this is not a buy and hold stock.</Msg><Username>kravcleve</Username><Timestamp>1360292557692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:02:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360292684296-156</Id><Title>Lenovo Yoga's got the Surface Pro's back....</Title><Msg>Windows 8 tablet alternatives to Microsoft's Surface Pro Samsung, Acer, Asus and Lenovo are selling Windows 8 alternatives to Microsoft's upcoming Surface Pro tablet By Agam Shah February 7, 2013 03:05 PM ET . IDG News Service - Microsoft's Surface Pro tablet with the Windows 8 OS is due to ship on Feb. 9, starting at $899. The tablet will have a 10.6-inch screen and come in models with 64GB and 128GB of storage. Surface Pro's early reviews have been mixed, and there are many Windows 8 alternatives already available from Samsung, Acer, Lenovo and Hewlett-Packard. The tablets come with touchscreens and Intel's Core processors, and a keyboard attachment turns the tablets into full Windows 8 laptops. The tablets mostly come with 128GB of storage. Microsoft's Surface Windows 8 Pro tablet Microsoft's Surface Windows 8 Pro tablet But the Core processor demands a lot of power, so these tablets won't offer the battery life of Microsoft's Surface RT or Android tablets, or even Windows 8 tablets running on Intel's tablet-specific Atom chip code-named Clover Trail. Windows RT devices cannot run existing Windows applications, however, so Surface Pro alternatives could appeal to buyers looking for a PC and tablet in one. "I would absolutely love a product that could double as a tablet for easy carrying," said Catherine Chang, who is master instructor at Chang's Taekwondo America in Methuen, Mass. She already uses laptops at home and school, and uses Apple's iPhone 4 often for tasks such as email and Web browsing. But she is looking to buy a new laptop and has considered a tablet, and a device that combines the best of both is attractive, Chang said. Lenovo has coined the term "multimode" for devices that merge tablet and laptop functionality. The Chinese PC maker is selling Yoga 13 starting at $1,049 with a 13.3-inch touchscreen. The device turns into a tablet by folding the screen, which leaves the keyboard exposed. It can feel uneasy using Yoga 13 in tablet mode with the fingers flitting over the non-functioning keys at the back of the device, but that hasn't stopped people from buying the popular device. Yoga 13 comes with Intel's Core i3 processor and is available on Lenovo's website. The Yoga 13 has a 13.3-inch screen, weighs 1.5 kilograms and offers eight hours of battery life, which is comparable to laptops. The screen displays images at a 1600-by-900-pixel resolution, and the device has a webcam. A less expensive option would be the ThinkPad Twist, which has a classic convertible laptop design and starts at $829. Lenovo sells the ThinkPad Tablet 2 with Windows 8 starting at $629, but the device runs on Intel's Atom tablet processor. A smaller version of the Yoga 13, the Yoga 11, with Windows RT and an ARM processor, starts at $749.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1360292684296</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:04:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360292825061-157</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo Yoga's got the Surface Pro's back....</Title><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1360292684296</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:04:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>8 hour battery life with Lenovo Yoga and Intel inside and we aren't even getting started yet ! Haswell will change the world.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1360292825061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:07:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360292974895-158</Id><Topic><Title>Another day closer to 14 nm fab 42 opening day ceramony.</Title><Username>kravcleve</Username><Timestamp>1360292557692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:02:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anybody bashing the stock can't buy at this amazing price and hold it that long, let alone hold it for a week. OR they are so old (Lucy, Wdblawgrow, etc) that they are jealous of anyone that can buy here and hold longterm so they scream and yell here all day, every day. They've thrown their lives away as they couldn't resist envy/jealousy/bashing Intel. Think about that! How MISERABLE!</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1360292974895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:09:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360293043844-159</Id><Topic><Title>Even ARMH's new partner, AMD admits ARM servers might be worthless</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1351636998519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:43:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM's own server partner is rolling their eyes at the ARM server revolution. hahahahahahahahahahahahahahaa</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1360293043844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:10:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360294926502-160</Id><Topic><Title>How hard is it for intel to start another architecture?</Title><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1360287315801</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:35:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats kind a bs cheap gutless answer buddy. I can and do make money with intel even in flat or down markets by selling puts and buying leaps at -2sd and then selling the leaps at +2sd covering puts or letting expire or getting exercised and selling calls until taken away indefinitely eg sold leaps before earnings and then rebuying them 50% cheaper like say near here that we are now and so on. I would of course make more if the stock started a move to 40 or 100 that i am very confident eventually will happen when all the bs clears. But until then i am ok with making 5%-10% per trade cycle here and there rather than having up 30-40% up months which will be the case if an uptrend begins. The problem with finding new stocks is that their derivatives are insanely priced and have massive spreads and they are mostly overvalued bubbles ready to crash. The only other stock i like long here is apple at these PE levels. And of course i would enter only in severe down days and only by shorting puts on it as well. I am not going to switch the core of the trading portfolio out of intel the most undervalued company in the universe and into some 2x the PE type stock like TXN or ARMH or QCOM lol . I am patient enough to wait until intel and the idiot analysts get it right at the same time. The harder you train to make money the easier the money will come when the bs ends and the uptrend starts. A tough stock that you know is better than some casino garbage. with uptrend about to crash. If you are so happy to trash intel and not answer my question then please offer the other stocks that you like better.</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1360294926502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:42:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360294991528-161</Id><Topic><Title>Another day closer to 14 nm fab 42 opening day ceramony.</Title><Username>kravcleve</Username><Timestamp>1360292557692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:02:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How MISERABLE! psychopaths - definition of psychopath by the Free Online Dictionary ... A person with an antisocial personality disorder, manifested in aggressive, perverted, criminal, or amoral behavior without empathy or remorse.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360294991528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:43:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360295822032-162</Id><Topic><Title>How hard is it for intel to start another architecture?</Title><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1360287315801</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:35:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are so happy to trash intel and not answer my question then please offer the other stocks that you like better. ++++++++++++++++++ He loved Cisco from 20 down to 13 and back. lol</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360295822032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:57:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360297472983-163</Id><Topic><Title>East on Windows RT</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1360103456454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Blue, good seeing you again, thanks for your reply. It's interesting that the BOM is still so high for an iPad mini. It sounds like there will be no driver to bring down the cost much more than it is now without subsidizing the device from the manufacture. If anybody was capable of doing exactly this it would be Microsoft. But so far they haven't and I don't think they ever will. When it comes to ARMH I really don't care what the stock sells for. If people think it's worth $100 a share, more power to them. They have a bright future selling processors for refrigerators and TV sets and of course embedded applications. It's the rest of the story I take issue with. The ARM processor hasn't proven itself to be a suitable Intel processor replacement. This was the market they were going after. Quad core Tegra 3 processors are great, on paper. The consumer perhaps hasn't identified the need for faster more elaborate ARM processors. This is how I see things right now for the computer side of the ARM business. Windows RT can be considered a "niche' market. Or as I see it, somewhere between failure and disaster. But to ARMH's credit, Microsoft couldn't wait to get into bed with them. Phones and tablets based on ARM processors are having a problem getting consumers excited enough to dispose their old ARM based device and upgrade to their higher end models. There is nothing that can drive the BOM down on ARM based products in the near future. The pipe dream of the $100 iPad mini may never come true. Intel can cut into the higher end of the ARM market $100 at a time. ARMH has really nothing to respond with that consumers can appreciate.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1360297472983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 23:24:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360298900966-164</Id><Title>turn in a pos this stock intc need big time buy back to push back to 22,00</Title><Msg>ok</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1360298900966</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 23:48:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>