<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-16"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358312805915-1</Id><Title>AAPL is doomed. Tim Cook is a failure...next big thing</Title><Msg>is the realization that everything computer is INTC. It's a $100 stock, easily.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358312805915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 00:06:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358313752938-2</Id><Topic><Title>2 more reasons to dump MSFT</Title><Username>eshjg</Username><Timestamp>1358294856661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:07:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The PC client business is Intel's largest cah cow. That market segment is going down taking both Microsoft and Intel with it so you should be sayiong Intel should be doing as bad as Microsoft, because Microsoft is learly on its way down." [Do you ever say anything that makes any sense? Intel makes processors. You think processors are going away? Who dresses and feeds you? You don't have the brains god give a rubber duck...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358313752938</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 00:22:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358313954594-3</Id><Topic><Title>2 more reasons to dump MSFT</Title><Username>eshjg</Username><Timestamp>1358294856661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 19:07:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, my fault, I should have spell-checked my post before I send it out. "learly" should be "clearly" in the last line. That's probably the reason for the mis-understanding.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1358313954594</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 00:25:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358316569500-4</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL is doomed. Tim Cook is a failure...next big thing</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358312805915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 00:06:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tim Cook's next big idea, the Mega iPad. GENIUS!</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358316569500</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 01:09:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358323159124-5</Id><Title>The one thing is MSFT can sell windows 8 without selling PC, WIndows 8 is now sold in smart phones , tablets and PC,</Title><Msg>The one thing is MSFT can sell windows 8 without selling PC's, WIndows 8 is now sold in smart phones , tablets and PC. Windows 8 is really taking off now, NOK sold 5 million windows 8 smart phones this Q and is taking share from aapl big time, NOK will sell 10-15 million next Q if they can ramp up production, NOK is sold out every were</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1358323159124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 02:59:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358323849634-6</Id><Title>Intel says chip vendors' TDP figures are not comparable</Title><Msg>Its Atom and Core TDPs can't be compared CHIPMAKER Intel has said that it is not willing to disclose the workload details used to set its scenario design power (SDP) metric because its competitors do not disclose how they calculate TDP. Intel courted controversy over Kirk Skaugen's CES 2013 presentation where he announced Ivy Bridge chips that hit 7W using Intel's SDP metric and compared them against Intel's more traditional TDP metric. The firm said that it won't publish the workload profile used to calculate SDP values, claiming that other chip vendors do not disclose how they calculate TDP. Intel's claims that TDP values are not comparable is big news as many of those who cried foul over the firm's initial mistake - intentional or not - based their arguments on the premise that the TDP metric is calculated to the same standards throughout the industry. Not only did Intel say that chip vendors calculate TDP differently but the firm told The INQUIRER that it calculates TDP differently between its own product ranges, citing its Atom and Core processors as examples. Adam King, Intel's director of notebook product marketing told The INQUIRER, "At this time we are not prepared to talk specifically [about] what workloads we are using. It is something we haven't disclosed publicly to date and so that would be a pretty big decision for us to do that and we are not prepared to do that today, mainly for competitive reasons. One of the key things about TDP is that there is not an industry standard definition for it. We're not actually quite sure what our competition uses. We know a lot of the phone silicon guys don't appear to specify it at all. So it tends to be a little bit of a trade secret from company to company." Not only did King say that TDP values are not transferable between chip vendors, he added that TDP figures cannot be compared between Atom and Core processors. He said, "You should note that the Atom processors use a different definition of TDP [than Core processors], one that is more oriented towards mainstream or consumption oriented workloads." AMD has confirmed that King's comments weren't just a ploy to deflect attention away from Intel's presentation omission. AMD told The INQUIRER that the formula it uses to calculate the TDP ratings of its processors is different from that of Intel, however it didn't disclose the formula. Given that AMD and Intel have both said that they calculate TDP differently from each other, it might be argued that TDP is equally as meaningless as Intel's SDP metric that it trotted out at CES. After all, neither firm has yet defined how it calculates TDP for its chips, in the same way that Intel is not willing to define how it calculates SDP for its Y series Ivy Bridge chips. All of this gives rise to the question of what power utilisation ratings consumers and small systems builders can rely on without needing expensive test facilities. Chip vendors should agree upon an open, well documented and reproducible method of measuring chip power utilisation.</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358323849634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 03:10:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358335819642-7</Id><Topic><Title>Intel says chip vendors' TDP figures are not comparable</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358323849634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 03:10:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does that son you say you have know that his Dad likes to try and make people feel bad on a dumb message board? Look in the mirror and you'll see a PATHETICALLY inadequate role model. Guys like you are why kids are so screwed up.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358335819642</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 06:30:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358335940800-8</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH new 52-week high today... AGAIN !!</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358216502409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 21:21:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, what an immature "rub it in" post. Does your son know that you are a mischievous message board dweller?</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358335940800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 06:32:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358336117266-9</Id><Title>ARM Holdings Cut to Neutral From Buy by UBS</Title><Msg>ARM Holdings Cut to Neutral From Buy by UBS Last update: 1/16/2013 1:49:15 AM (END) Dow Jones Newswires January 16, 2013 01:49 ET (06:49 GMT)</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1358336117266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 06:35:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358337921282-10</Id><Topic><Title>Why is ARMH stock outperforming INTC so badly??</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357838146159</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 12:15:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This analyst is talking about royalty rate, well this means ARM A7, A8, A9 and A15. How the hell is smartphone asp going to increase in 2013 when only A7 and A9 is appreciably increasing in smartphones with A15 MIA and A7 is cheap and the price of A9 is dropping sharply as it get obsolete ? ARM gets no royalty for Qualcomm's S4 or Apple's A6 only licensing revenue. ---- Yes, ARM do get royalty for Qualcomm's S4 or Apple's A6. I've seen various values mentioned. The royalty rate for smart phone SoC's is meant to double from around 1% to around 2% this is due to: Higher royalty on the more advanced cores More cores used (dual/quad) Mali GPU and other ARM IP being used At 28nm and below, more ARM physical IP is being used at the foundry level Clearly, none of this has anything to do with ASP. 1.8bn devices sold in 2016 sounds high to me, in the past I have seen device mean 'chip', so 1 chip for the baseband, 1 chip for the app etc.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1358337921282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 07:05:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358338091112-11</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Holdings Cut to Neutral From Buy by UBS</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1358336117266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 06:35:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When ARM hit resistance around 42 nasdaqDOTcom/symbol/armh/stock-consultant I wondered if the Analysts would use the opportunity to pounce to make some money on the Short side and so it has proved. The point is though that all of the ARM profit forecasts are still so unrealistic in their final numbers and assumptions that a decline was going to happen at some point but the Analysts may just have defined the top.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358338091112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 07:08:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358338955525-12</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Holdings Cut to Neutral From Buy by UBS</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1358336117266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 06:35:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The analysts spent a much greater effort to bring down INTC, but again they aren't done with ARMH yet. The problem will be that ARMH will see a decent profit and many goons will buy without concern for the bubble. It is time for ARMH to take a big whack. I believe analysts see the inevitable market share take by INTEL in the coming year/s. It may be a long and very hard downfall for ARMH.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1358338955525</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 07:22:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358341423060-13</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>marthaije606</Username><Timestamp>1357915910195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 09:51:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>checking the chart now</Msg><Username>vestalhhie90594</Username><Timestamp>1358341423060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:03:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358343843063-14</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Holdings Cut to Neutral From Buy by UBS</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1358336117266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 06:35:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A good detailed analysis of why ARMH is only a 10 dollar stock ... http://seekingalpha.com/article/851981-the-fish-rots-from-the-head-down-and-arm-holdings-is-starting-to-smell</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358343843063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:44:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358344058656-15</Id><Title>The world is porting to ARMH</Title><Msg>LMAO !!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1358344058656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:47:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358344058811-16</Id><Title>The world is porting to ARMH</Title><Msg>LMAO !!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1358344058811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:47:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358345068853-17</Id><Title>NO SEMICONDUCTOR COMPANY IS A BUY ANYMORE: AVOID THE SECTOR</Title><Msg>Energy and high dividend yield only the investment now massive crash some time inn 2013 and riots late in 2013/early 2014 is the prediction</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1358345068853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:04:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358347696982-18</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>marthaije606</Username><Timestamp>1357915910195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 09:51:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this one keeps me thinking</Msg><Username>nanette.montgomery646d</Username><Timestamp>1358347696982</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:48:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358350064157-19</Id><Topic><Title>optimistic analysis shows steady growth</Title><Username>bennettrichard453</Username><Timestamp>1358347303597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:41:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice report.</Msg><Username>stanford749</Username><Timestamp>1358350064157</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 10:27:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358350431571-20</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH new 52-week high today... AGAIN !!</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358216502409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 21:21:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Does your son know that you are a mischievous message board dweller?" Does your mom know that you are a mischievous message board dweller?</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358350431571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 10:33:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358351027914-21</Id><Topic><Title>Is Anyone Making Money WIth INTC?</Title><Username>newtontodd714</Username><Timestamp>1358014743482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:19:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take off to where? my friend bought some call contract but i think its going down.</Msg><Username>benefactorrr</Username><Timestamp>1358351027914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 10:43:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358353153360-22</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH new 52-week high today... AGAIN !!</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358216502409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 21:21:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Does your son know that you are a mischievous message board dweller?" Does your mom know that you are a mischievous message board dweller? ____________ I am indeed a kid. I bet I grow up though. Sad to see that you never did. Yikes...</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358353153360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:19:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358353300859-23</Id><Title>Johnny reb is melting down the GOP. Good old boys are a poison of IGNORANT trash.</Title><Msg>Now it is TWO times the House GOP have split along geography and voted with the DEM on a bill. First was the budget deal to over come the self set fiscal cliff--the NE Repubs in the house voted for it. Now it is the help for the NE Hurricane victims that flooded and destroyed so much. Naturally, the good old boys of the GOP south voted against helping the Yankees. Never mind that the Dems and the Northern GOP had voted to help Louisiana and Mississippi in 10 days and did not give a rats about the debt then but now, new York goes under water and they take 60 days and almost all of the Southern House members vote against the same bailout when it is for the Yankees. Funny---but those Yankee house members will remember and vote as independents often now giving Obummer the votes in the House to pass the gun laws and future laws. The GOP is infested with low life KKK Teaparty #$%$ and they are killing the party and I thank them for it.</Msg><Username>hothectors</Username><Timestamp>1358353300859</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:21:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358353563233-24</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH new 52-week high today... AGAIN !!</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358216502409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 21:21:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I am indeed a kid. I bet I grow up though. Sad to see that you never did." Separate the men from the boys... how's INTC done compared to ARMH... now run back to your mom...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358353563233</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:26:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358353961800-25</Id><Topic><Title>Is Anyone Making Money WIth INTC?</Title><Username>newtontodd714</Username><Timestamp>1358014743482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:19:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, just put in a bottom, and they are moving (finally) into the mobile chip market to compete with QCOM. Check out the Lenovo K900 phone that is awesome. Hoping they don't take a hit tomorrow on earnings, but they should have positive guidance which may make up any revenue shortfall, hopefully, and the dividend is secure.</Msg><Username>hoxstox</Username><Timestamp>1358353961800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:32:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358354126193-26</Id><Topic><Title>Is Anyone Making Money WIth INTC?</Title><Username>newtontodd714</Username><Timestamp>1358014743482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:19:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I made lots of cash just on their divs.....</Msg><Username>jravera</Username><Timestamp>1358354126193</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:35:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358354221633-27</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH new 52-week high today... AGAIN !!</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358216502409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 21:21:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My mom sold your mom Nvidia at 20. hahahahahaahahahahahahahah!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358354221633</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:37:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358354287611-28</Id><Title>The world is porting ARMH, says GETANID61</Title><Msg>Samsung to Windows RT: Never Mind The Korean giant's decision to forego a U.S. launch is a big blow Jan 15, 2013, 1:37 pm EST | By Brad Moon, InvestorPlace Contributor</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358354287611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:38:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358354732795-29</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH new 52-week high today... AGAIN !!</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358216502409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 21:21:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"My mom sold your mom Nvidia at 20." Too bad your mom bought INTC at 29... Too bad your inheritance that your mom didn't buy ARMH...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358354732795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:45:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358354750880-30</Id><Title>wish open 23.00 on friday</Title><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1358354750880</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:45:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358354970047-31</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH new 52-week high today... AGAIN !!</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358216502409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 21:21:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung to Windows RT: Never Mind The Korean giant's decision to forego a U.S. launch is a big blow Jan 15, 2013, 1:37 pm EST | By Brad Moon, InvestorPlace Contributor</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358354970047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:49:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358355118291-32</Id><Title>Obama has his kids protected by GUNS</Title><Msg>Ohhhhhhhhhhh the Hypocrisy!</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358355118291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:51:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358355443268-33</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has his kids protected by GUNS</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358355118291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:51:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hypocrisy? Not really. Anyone that gets 30 death threats per day would probably have armed protection. Don't you think?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358355443268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:57:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358355449799-34</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH new 52-week high today... AGAIN !!</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358216502409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 21:21:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"a big blow" big blow...??? ARMH still near its 52-week high... INTC still near its 52-week low...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358355449799</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:57:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358355517713-35</Id><Topic><Title>Can InPig Squeeeeeze Out a Dime Today?</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1320682941000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-11-07 11:22:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chicken feed trading</Msg><Username>s_p_r_i_t_z_e_r</Username><Timestamp>1358355517713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:58:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358355634956-36</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH new 52-week high today... AGAIN !!</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358216502409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 21:21:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting. The charts are going to form complementary sine waves.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358355634956</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:00:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358355719960-37</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>marthaije606</Username><Timestamp>1357915910195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 09:51:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whenever I see an email name followed by numbers, I just assume that they are spammers. Makes reading these posts easier.</Msg><Username>johnright47</Username><Timestamp>1358355719960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:01:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358355981674-38</Id><Title>26-28 within 2 weeks after Mobile Congress</Title><Msg>9999999999</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358355981674</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:06:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358356020302-39</Id><Topic><Title>Can InPig Squeeeeeze Out a Dime Today?</Title><Username>lucy_nuff</Username><Timestamp>1320682941000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-11-07 11:22:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Low beta, slow motion "trading". If you are looking for high beta moves, this is the wrong stock to follow. INTC (the stock) price moves are highly throttled by option traders ... especially the near expiration, at the money trades. The Jan $22.50 call option volumes are 20k to 40k per day and the open interest does not change.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358356020302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:07:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358356157610-40</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH new 52-week high today... AGAIN !!</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358216502409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 21:21:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't prove you own a single share.... so your posts are worthless.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358356157610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:09:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358356298787-41</Id><Title>INTEL TENDS TO ROCKET UP WITH EARNINGS</Title><Msg>LOAD UP</Msg><Username>kelly_tankor81</Username><Timestamp>1358356298787</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:11:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358356865936-42</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has his kids protected by GUNS</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358355118291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:51:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The folks who don't get any threats need protection too....which they can freely get at their local pharmacy....ha, ha, ha....</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1358356865936</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:21:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358357465985-43</Id><Topic><Title>optimistic analysis shows steady growth</Title><Username>bennettrichard453</Username><Timestamp>1358347303597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:41:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great and helpful report</Msg><Username>ericeric301</Username><Timestamp>1358357465985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:31:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358357696968-44</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has his kids protected by GUNS</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358355118291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:51:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We think it makes perfect sense to have armed police in shopping malls to protect the families shopping there yet some individuals completely dismiss the value of having the same protection for schools where children spend most of their day. Now that is hypocrisy.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1358357696968</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:34:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358358902265-45</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has his kids protected by GUNS</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358355118291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:51:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i don't recall ever seeing armed uniformed police officers working security in a shopping mall. unarmed civilian security is common, however.</Msg><Username>ramalamalongdong</Username><Timestamp>1358358902265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:55:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358359090004-46</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>marthaije606</Username><Timestamp>1357915910195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 09:51:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was really looking for some great news. Now I found it.</Msg><Username>eunice.griffith406l</Username><Timestamp>1358359090004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:58:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358360163151-47</Id><Topic><Title>NO SEMICONDUCTOR COMPANY IS A BUY ANYMORE: AVOID THE SECTOR</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1358345068853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:04:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the encouragement. Do you think Intel will hold at least zero or will we owe more money than our original investment?</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1358360163151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:16:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358361060951-48</Id><Topic><Title>NO SEMICONDUCTOR COMPANY IS A BUY ANYMORE: AVOID THE SECTOR</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1358345068853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:04:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL BACK TO $19 NEXT AGAIN..................... SINGLE DIGITS END OF 2013 ROAD MAP</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1358361060951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:31:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358361225355-49</Id><Title>who said no semi buy? AMD is a buy</Title><Msg>$$$$$$$$$$$$ :)</Msg><Username>trade_4_somegreen</Username><Timestamp>1358361225355</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:33:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358361726447-50</Id><Title>All these Getanid61 posts...I had to do some research</Title><Msg>I find it funny that back when ARM's stock price was down around 20, he was passionate about the company and said he could care less about the stock price, "didn't even look at it." Now, he's passionate about the stock price and says nothing about the company when there's a lot of bad RT news out. Funny stuff... Ignore that guy, people. He's your typical internet fantasy land poster where no matter what's going on in the market, he's right.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1358361726447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:42:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358362214320-51</Id><Title>Tomorrows report???</Title><Msg>Anyone know if it's before or after the close tomorrow??</Msg><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358362214320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:50:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358362264031-52</Id><Title>low power process coming :)</Title><Msg>$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>trade_4_somegreen</Username><Timestamp>1358362264031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:51:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358362361312-53</Id><Title>LSI Corp best in show</Title><Msg>The best company right now to handle the data deluge going on for mega datacenters and cloud computing comes from LSI Corp. Please check out the company. Not only to they have stat of the art technology but they are debt free and buying back shares. They report next wednesday. See for yourself. GO LSI!!!</Msg><Username>data_analyst_dude</Username><Timestamp>1358362361312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:52:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358362655838-54</Id><Title>Does anyone know.....</Title><Msg>if Intels earnings are coming before or after the close tomorrow????</Msg><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358362655838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:57:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358362702878-55</Id><Topic><Title>Tomorrows report???</Title><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358362214320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:50:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have them down as reporting after the bell tomorrow.</Msg><Username>stockdox</Username><Timestamp>1358362702878</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:58:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358362721494-56</Id><Topic><Title>Does anyone know.....</Title><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358362655838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:57:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's always a few mintutes after the bell. Always.</Msg><Username>boknowsintel</Username><Timestamp>1358362721494</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:58:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358362797360-57</Id><Topic><Title>Tomorrows report???</Title><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358362214320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:50:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358362797360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:59:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358362817297-58</Id><Topic><Title>Does anyone know.....</Title><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358362655838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:57:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358362817297</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:00:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358362917054-59</Id><Topic><Title>Tomorrows report???</Title><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358362214320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:50:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm short the Jan 20 puts that expire on friday...Not sure if I should close them out.... Any thoughts??</Msg><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358362917054</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:01:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358362991000-60</Id><Title>WHERE ELSE.....???</Title><Msg>Are you going to get 4% on your money GUARANTEED!!! Intel will continue to pay Dividends as long as they remain in Business, they SIT on a Load of $$$$ see if your Bank can match that Yield?</Msg><Username>foreverdonquijote</Username><Timestamp>1358362991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:03:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358363054207-61</Id><Topic><Title>All these Getanid61 posts...I had to do some research</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1358361726447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:42:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you did all the DD and brought up my record... When ARMH went down, I wasn't buying into it... When ARMH started up, I let you know... do you want my trade confirmations too...? What part about trading do you find hard to understand... Keeping track of all those aliases taxes your brain...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358363054207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:04:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358363346800-62</Id><Topic><Title>All these Getanid61 posts...I had to do some research</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1358361726447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:42:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny stuff.....I think all your lies have taxed YOUR brain. Back then you said you didn't even look at ARM's stock price.....I'll sit down and listen to how you trade a stock without knowing its price.....Humor us.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1358363346800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:09:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358363515842-63</Id><Topic><Title>Tomorrows report???</Title><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358362214320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:50:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure what you mean. Did you sell the put? Or did you buy the put and now you are short? If you are selling put then I think you close it out and buy and out of the money call it is safer. If you bought a put then you sell before you lose more money.</Msg><Username>stockdox</Username><Timestamp>1358363515842</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:11:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358363518988-64</Id><Topic><Title>All these Getanid61 posts...I had to do some research</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1358361726447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:42:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Funny stuff....." There's an old saying: "Laughing all the way to the bank..."</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358363518988</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:11:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358363671717-65</Id><Topic><Title>All these Getanid61 posts...I had to do some research</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1358361726447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:42:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for dodging the facts and admitting you aren't scared to lie. Everybody knows you didn't hold ARM up to 42 or even anywhere near that, but enjoy the life of a liar. Isn't that why your X tossed you in the can? I wonder if she knows you are daytrading her child support. LOL....cheers, chump.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1358363671717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:14:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358363850676-66</Id><Topic><Title>All these Getanid61 posts...I had to do some research</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1358361726447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:42:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Thanks for dodging the facts " SIGH.... You remain oblivious to them... ARMH near its 52-week high !!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358363850676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:17:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358364342137-67</Id><Title>LMAO!</Title><Msg>By: GETANID61, 2009 currently has a mkt cap of $10B with current share price of $18. $3 share price would put the mkt cap at $2B. NVidia already has 80% of that in cash. The Revenue stream is returning and will probably be $4B for 2010. THey have also returned to profitability... $100M last quarter, limited by suppy. Add on to that their intellectual capital and your numbers just don't add up. Heck, INtel spent $3B and they couldn't make an advanced GPU. NVidia's leadership is a generation ahead in SOC and discrete GPUs. YOu are brave to short this stock... especially now !!!!</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358364342137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:25:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358364519325-68</Id><Topic><Title>Arm vs Intel</Title><Username>cuda1971_1971</Username><Timestamp>1343705641000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 23:34:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>by getanid61.Jul 30, 2012 11:39 PM.PermalinkGo to topic . "Windows for ARM gave Microsoft an opportunity to do a new version of Windows without all of the backward compatibility requirements, so the code is streamlined. And we’re hearing from early tests that it runs Windows RT apps as much as 20% faster than apps running on Intel chips. Also, Microsoft is including a full version of Office on all Windows RT-based devices, so they come with a good set of productivity apps from the start." ...from the start "For 30 years, Intel basically had the market to itself and as a result, its chips were priced much higher than ARM chips. But ARM’s entry into Intel’s territory is a real threat to Intel’s dominance. First time in decades INtel has had competition !!!! "huge win for consumers" !!!!! ________________________________ How's that RT that you are so passionate about doing now? LOLOLOLOL........</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358364519325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:28:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358364541509-69</Id><Topic><Title>LMAO!</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358364342137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:25:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2009... You are DESPERATE for anything... LMAO !!!!! CHUMP !!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358364541509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:29:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358364712245-70</Id><Title>Sell INTC or HOLD</Title><Msg>Who thinks it will go down tomorrow? Or up? And why?</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1358364712245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:31:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358364756810-71</Id><Topic><Title>Arm vs Intel</Title><Username>cuda1971_1971</Username><Timestamp>1343705641000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 23:34:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How's that..." ARMH at its 52 week highs INTC near its 52-week lows LMAO !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358364756810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:32:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358365068895-72</Id><Topic><Title>Tomorrows report???</Title><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358362214320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:50:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So your bullish... that's good. my position is bullish as well... I sold 60 jan 20 puts for .50 cents each. I received $3,000 in premiums. Right now I can close out the position for $250... If the stock closes below $20 on friday then I'll have to buy 6000 shares. Don't really have a problem owning INTC at $20 which is why I sold the puts in the first place..but generally I'd rather have the puts expire worthless (which will happen if the stock closes above $20 on friday) and then sell another cycle.. So i guess I'm asking if we think INTC will close above or below $20 on friday For the record.....Never buy options... particularly calls... it's a suckers game.. 80% of options expire worthless.</Msg><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358365068895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:37:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358365085709-73</Id><Topic><Title>LTIsteve - What to do ???</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1322527179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-11-28 19:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GETANID61 sure looks like a slimeball to me after readinng this thread. LOL, what a deadbeat.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358365085709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:38:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358365169003-74</Id><Topic><Title>LTIsteve - What to do ???</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1322527179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-11-28 19:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No position in ARM, per Getanid61's own words. ;)</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358365169003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:39:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358365212275-75</Id><Topic><Title>Sell INTC or HOLD</Title><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1358364712245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:31:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sell and buy LSI</Msg><Username>data_analyst_dude</Username><Timestamp>1358365212275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:40:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358365232794-76</Id><Topic><Title>optimistic analysis shows steady growth</Title><Username>bennettrichard453</Username><Timestamp>1358347303597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:41:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big thanks !</Msg><Username>malik_david</Username><Timestamp>1358365232794</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:40:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358365249751-77</Id><Topic><Title>Tomorrows report???</Title><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358362214320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:50:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today is a down day, Intel is up, expectations are in the toilet and large cap tech is moving since they have great dividends and growth. That said, you really don't want to hold short term options through and earnings report. Maybe sell your position, take your profits and write a higher strike price for next month. I personally own the stock and have since 1995- I buy and sell but its always there. To me, it seems like the stock is headed for $28 some time this year. I am not great at trading Intel short term, that's my opinion.</Msg><Username>tazmo85048</Username><Timestamp>1358365249751</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:40:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358365271788-78</Id><Title>No position in ARM.. but now he suddenly is in ARM at 40</Title><Msg>ROFL! by getanid61.Nov 28, 2011 9:37 PM.Permalink Maximum_pro, My post was for Steve, not you, And it's done now... "Are you short INTC and long ARMH? " I am long INTC, NVDA, QCOM, ALTR Heavy positions in all I tell the folks on the board I'm long INTC, but no one accepts it. My view on ARMH is that ARM is the rubber stamp that will allow NVidia, QCOM, TI, Marvell, AMCC, TI, Calxeda, etc... to enter the CPU business... The winners will design their own ARM cores... I also view ARMH growth separate from ARMH's customers such as NVidia or Qualcomm. But the ARM ISA is gonna spread everywhere... regardless of ARMH valuation. Though ARM will grow in 2012, ARM's real growth will begin to start in a year from now... What so many refuse to understand is that it's not a zero sum game. INtel is gonna double, but the market will quaddruple Trying to view that if INtel wins, then ARM loses is naive... ARM is NOT AMD...</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358365271788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:41:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358365344997-79</Id><Topic><Title>LTIsteve - What to do ???</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1322527179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-11-28 19:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chump, You are obsessed with me... Look what you've been reduced to... btw ltisteve, how you been ?? Do you believe me now... :)</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358365344997</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:42:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358365431563-80</Id><Topic><Title>LTIsteve - What to do ???</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1322527179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-11-28 19:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bears repeating! GETAND61 bashes someone for aliases yet on his own time he researches and threatens to expose the true identity of someonfe fhe disagrees with. Who's thte reals degenerate here? lol.... GETANID61 sure looks like a slimeball to me after readinng this thread. LOL, what a deadbeat.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358365431563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:43:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358365578048-81</Id><Topic><Title>Tomorrows report???</Title><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358362214320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:50:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am virtually certain it will close above 20. I see downside risk to 21. A lot of bad news is in the stock. Upside to 24 on a good report. 2 pts upside and 1 pt downside looks like pretty good risk/reward profile to me. Good luck.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1358365578048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:46:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358365709288-82</Id><Topic><Title>No position in ARM.. but now he suddenly is in ARM at 40</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358365271788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:41:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, let's take a look at my quotes from Nov 28, 2011... "Though ARM will grow in 2012, ARM's real growth will begin to start in a year from now..." Now go look at ARMH's chart... ARMH's climb started in Nov 2012... exactly as I said it would... the rest of my post was correct too... free advice... you're not helping your cause...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358365709288</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:48:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358365773786-83</Id><Topic><Title>Tomorrows report???</Title><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358362214320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:50:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I appreciate it.. Not that good trying to trade them either.. thanks for the response</Msg><Username>makiswak</Username><Timestamp>1358365773786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:49:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358365831914-84</Id><Topic><Title>LTIsteve - What to do ???</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1322527179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-11-28 19:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, you played "God" with that guy, Getanid61. So sad. Wow.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358365831914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:50:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358365996608-85</Id><Topic><Title>LTIsteve - What to do ???</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1322527179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-11-28 19:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, you played "Chump" with me, Chump. So sad. Wow</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358365996608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:53:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358366568202-86</Id><Title>Are you Lucies enjoying the preearnings runup?</Title><Msg>This is going to be a lot of fun.</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1358366568202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:02:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358366622059-87</Id><Topic><Title>LTIsteve - What to do ???</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1322527179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-11-28 19:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>by maximum_probability.Nov 28, 2011 8:30 PM What is that some attempt to blackmail someone about releasing their name in order to take it easy with you ??? Dont you find this a bit underhanded and maybe even fictitious? __________________________ Basically, but that's how European degenerates roll.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358366622059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:03:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358366886816-88</Id><Topic><Title>How many trading days left until ...</Title><Username>jimbo_homegamed_u</Username><Timestamp>1302902388000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2011-04-15 17:19:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis Weaver Day? President Barry Obama has declared May 21 Wallis Weaver Day, a national day of rememberance: "In six months those who bought Intel at 24 will look just fine." Wallis Weaver, May 21, 2010 ======================================================================= That's a very good question Lucy. Can you even count? Do you even own a Conroe based computer?</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1358366886816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:08:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358366963479-89</Id><Topic><Title>blotter_blades long TXN at $75!</Title><Username>am_i_a_clueless_moron</Username><Timestamp>1154566144000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2006-08-02 20:49:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>from the TXN board: Coiled Spring! (Not rated) 23-Jun-00 05:19 pm Once the arb`s finish, this baby will jump like a coiled spring. I really thinks the shorts are beginning to get a little nervous. RTQ 75 3/4 ================================================================= blotter blades is just another Lucy.</Msg><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1358366963479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:09:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358367085209-90</Id><Topic><Title>LTIsteve - What to do ???</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1322527179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-11-28 19:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Honest, I don't get where you're going... but hey... posting stuff from yrs ago is the best you got... DESPERATE !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358367085209</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:11:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358369134852-91</Id><Title>Intel and Facebook collaborate on Future Data Center Tech.</Title><Msg>1:01PM Intel and Facebook (FB) collaborate on future data center rack technologies (INTC) 22.02 +0.14 : Co announced a collaboration with Facebook (FB) to define the next generation of rack technologies used to power the world's largest data centers. As part of the collaboration, the companies also unveiled a mechanical prototype built by Quanta Computer that includes Intel's new, innovative photonic rack architecture to show the total cost, design and reliability improvement potential of a disaggregated rack environment.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1358369134852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:45:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358369694623-92</Id><Topic><Title>Are you Lucies enjoying the preearnings runup?</Title><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1358366568202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:02:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what is the earnings date?</Msg><Username>mmpsolutionsinc</Username><Timestamp>1358369694623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:54:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358369773763-93</Id><Topic><Title>Are you Lucies enjoying the preearnings runup?</Title><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1358366568202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:02:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thursday 4:10ET Jan 17th tomorrow after close</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358369773763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:56:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358369842850-94</Id><Topic><Title>Are you Lucies enjoying the preearnings runup?</Title><Username>wallus_weener</Username><Timestamp>1358366568202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:02:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yahooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo back to $19 next again</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1358369842850</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:57:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358370587788-95</Id><Topic><Title>Would like to take a dump in a shoe box</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1358267715319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:35:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1358370587788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 16:09:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358373523466-96</Id><Title>$22.20 is a concrete ceiling</Title><Msg>We need to smash it.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1358373523466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 16:58:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358376391839-97</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think INTC is a BUY, SELL, or HOLD?</Title><Username>marthaije606</Username><Timestamp>1357915910195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 09:51:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>golly gee- more SPAM</Msg><Username>mikemclaug</Username><Timestamp>1358376391839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 17:46:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358378451369-98</Id><Topic><Title>Reply to 1929 crash prediction</Title><Username>IBDMAN15</Username><Timestamp>937166275000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 1999-09-12 15:57:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Genius</Msg><Username>maloneksm</Username><Timestamp>1358378451369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 18:20:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358380833812-99</Id><Topic><Title>$22.20 is a concrete ceiling</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1358373523466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 16:58:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's the 600 day moving average at 22.19. Break it and it will turn into strong support. stockchartsDOTcom/c-sc/sc?s=intc&amp;p=D&amp;yr=1&amp;mn=0&amp;dy=0&amp;i=t77909490371&amp;r=1358345946442</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358380833812</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 19:00:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358382929062-100</Id><Title>SELL ON SIGHT</Title><Msg>long you will cry soon</Msg><Username>bumptemp</Username><Timestamp>1358382929062</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 19:35:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358383340721-101</Id><Topic><Title>SELL ON SIGHT</Title><Username>bumptemp</Username><Timestamp>1358382929062</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 19:35:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should I sell in the after hours session based on your recommendation Nuff? I've noticed that for every negative comment you post, it moves the market price down by a few cents. You really are the great and clever a-wipe!</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1358383340721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 19:42:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358383734074-102</Id><Title>Timber!</Title><Msg>Max $22.60</Msg><Username>ibmsys</Username><Timestamp>1358383734074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 19:48:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358383748000-103</Id><Title>Intel will be around forever, do you want the staunch Dividend or not?</Title><Msg>Intel prepares to use lasers, light to shuffle data between computers Intel is readying silicon photonics for use at the motherboard level By Agam Shah Wed, January 16, 2013 . IDG News Service (New York Bureau) — Intel is taking the first steps to implement thin fiber optics that will use lasers and light as a faster way to move data inside computers, replacing the older and slower electrical wiring technology found in most computers today. Intel's silicon photonics technology will be implemented at the motherboard and rack levels and use light to move data between storage, networking and computing resources. Light is considered a much faster vehicle to move data than copper cables. The silicon photonics technology will be part of a new generation of servers that will need faster networking, storage and processing subsystems, said Justin Rattner, Intel's chief technology officer, during a keynote at the Open Compute Summit in Santa Clara, California, on Wednesday. At the conference, Intel and server maker Quanta Computer are showing a prototype server rack architecture that is capable of moving data using optical modules. The server uses an Intel silicon switch and supports the chip maker's Xeon and Atom server chips. The new rack architecture with silicon photonics is a result of more than a decade of research in Intel's laboratories, Rattner said. He said silicon photonics could enable communication at speeds of 100G bps (bits per second), and transfer data at high speeds while using lesser power compared to copper cables. The technology could also consolidate power supplies and fans in a data center, reducing component costs. Intel's research revolved around the production of devices needed to implement silicon photonics at the rack level, including modulators and detectors. The company is now producing silicon photonics modules that can transfer data at 100G bps, and is offering it to a few clients for testing. Silicon photonics could potentially redefine server designs, Rattner said. With the high-speed bandwidth, processing and storage units could be decoupled from servers and stored in separate boxes. Once the infrastructure with silicon photonics is in place, server designs could change even more, Rattner said. Intel is working with Facebook to define new server technologies that will lead to the decoupling of computing, networking and storage resources. The high-bandwidth connection offered by silicon photonics will be key in bringing the rack technologies to reality, and the processor, switch and other modules need to work together on power management, protocol support, load balancing and handshakes to make high-speed data transfers possible. Critical to this step is "the introduction of silicon photonics in not just the inter-rack fabric, but also the intra-rack fabric," Rattner said. Intel is already using fiber optics with its Thunderbolt connector technology, which like USB 3.0, shuffles data between host devices and peripherals. At last week's International CES show in Las Vegas, Corning announced Thunderbolt Optical Cables that can stretch up to 100 meters. Intel is being aggressive with pushing silicon photonics into the data center, said Jason Waxman, general manager of the cloud platforms group, in an interview. He said it could be in use in fewer than five years, but did not commit to a timeline. There are multiple protocols that could be supported for high-speed data transfers, including InfiniBand, Ethernet and PCI-Express, Waxman said. Intel said it will implement the InfiniBand networking technology inside its chips, which could enable faster data transfers. It is only a matter of time until copper wires are replaced by fiber optics, said Dean McCarron, principal analyst at Mercury Research. "Over time you will see the server communication infrastructure -- which includes switches -- to include photonics," McCarron said. High-speed communication networks use optical technology, and so far the bandwidth in servers was adequate, McCarron said. But with more data flowing through networks, there is a growing demand to crank up the speed over connections, which is where silicon photonics comes into play. "We're going to keep seeing continued demands for the interconnect. It is a forgone conclusion we will have to go to photonics," McCarron said. Initial implementations may be expensive, and there may be a need to introduce protocols that could enable high speed data transfers over fiber optics. "Eventually the signalling gets far too complex, and the move to photonics makes sense," McCarron said. "The motivation is how do you economically get to higher speeds."</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358383748000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 19:49:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358383965559-104</Id><Title>Shorts Give Back 15 Percent</Title><Msg>Since the low of 19.23 on November 21st, Intel shorts have given back 15 percent. Almost three bucks. They are determined to hang in and give it all back. All except the smart ones. Obviously that doesn't include any of the shills on this board. ARMs bubble trouble and fabrication fade continue...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358383965559</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 19:52:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358386217988-105</Id><Title>AMD accuses former employees of spying for Nvidia</Title><Msg>AMD is taking legal action against four former employees, including a former vice president and former managers accused of stealing sensitive documents and passing them on to Nvidia. AMD alleges that Robert Feldstein, Manoo Desai, Nicolas Kociuk and Richard Hagen downloaded over 100,000 files to external drives in the months leading up to their departure from the company and recruiting AMD employees after leaving for Nvidia. AMD said it examined computers used by former employees and found additional evidence that Desai and Kociuk conspired to misappropriate confidential information and trade secrets. The company also filed a restraining order against the former employees, ordering them to preserve all AMD property and preserve their computers so they can be used for forensic evaluation. We still don’t know what Nvidia learned by looking over AMD’s shoulder, but this is starting to look like an embarrassing episode for both companies. So far the four employees are facing civil lawsuits, no criminal charges yet. [When I saw this I thought the fanboi might be leaving us, but then I saw they were talking about executives and not the guys who take out the trash. Color me disappointed...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358386217988</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 20:30:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358386394649-106</Id><Title>Qualcomm CEO not a fan of wearable augmented reality</Title><Msg>Jacobs thinks smart watches are the way to go Qualcomm is the biggest player in the smartphone space and it is at the forefront of augmented reality technology, but CEO Paul Jacobs is not a huge fan of wearable augmented reality gear. [Maybe he can buy a nice Intel/Apple iWatch soon...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358386394649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 20:33:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358386701356-107</Id><Title>"Haswell will be a bar worth drinking at..."</Title><Msg>Intel dominated the start of this year's show, and for good reason. If we were in a purely practical frame of mind, we'd say that our next laptop purchase would most likely have Intel inside. Or, more precisely, Haswell. Or even more precisely, the 10-watt version of Haswell, which is destined to appear in hybrids and touch-enabled laptops by the fall. "Our next laptop purchase would most likely have Intel inside." By cutting down on the 17-watt consumption of current Ultrabooks and MacBook Airs, we could see a big leap in battery life -- potentially taking us over the 10-hour threshold that we've been burning people's ears about for so long. A 10-watt TDP could also mean a reduction in weight. Less need for cooling and ventilation increases the possibility of serious x86 computing in devices that weigh significantly less than two pounds (1kg) even including their keyboards -- although that's just optimistic speculation on our part. So long as performance stays broadly inline with, say, an existing Ivy Bridge Core i5 laptop, Haswell will be a bar worth drinking at. From Engadget</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358386701356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 20:38:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358386842230-108</Id><Title>Qualcomm Confusion</Title><Msg>While we're on the topic of category confusion, or actually just confusion in general, we may as well broach Qualcomm's keynote. A week later, it's still not clear what Big Bird, Guillermo del Toro, Desmond Tutu and Alice Eve (from Star Trek Into Darkness) really brought to the chip designer's live show, and frankly Steve Ballmer's appearance was awkward too. But the confusion runs even deeper than that. Qualcomm represents the cutting edge of ARM-based chip innovation, and not for a split second do we doubt the technical achievement of the new Snapdragon 800 and 600. These processors will take an already excellent chip -- the S4 Pro -- and give it as much as 75 percent more CPU grunt and 50 percent better graphics, in addition to a doubling of GPU compute. That's a recipe for almost guaranteed success, but at the same time there's a critical chapter missing from Qualcomm's narrative. "There's a critical chapter missing from Qualcomm's narrative." The void in Qualcomm's presentation is this: if the Snapdragon 800 is really as amazing as it looks, why isn't it being put forward as a chip for hard-nosed computing? From Engadget</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358386842230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 20:40:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358387919939-109</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcomm CEO not a fan of wearable augmented reality</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358386394649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 20:33:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People are never a fan of parties they aren't invited to. Funny stuff.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1358387919939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 20:58:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358392011324-110</Id><Topic><Title>Would like to take a dump in a shoe box</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1358267715319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:35:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wouldn't send that stupid bastid the time of day.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1358392011324</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 22:06:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358394366853-111</Id><Title>massive tech run till March</Title><Msg>INTC 28</Msg><Username>raygeo2003</Username><Timestamp>1358394366853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 22:46:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358396036005-112</Id><Topic><Title>Qualcomm Confusion</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358386842230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 20:40:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because hard-nosed computing is going away. No wants performance anymore when it makes no difference to the usefulness. This message is taken a long time to sink in, but it will eventually. Everyone else is headed to Los Angeles while Intel is headed to New York.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1358396036005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 23:13:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358397707388-113</Id><Topic><Title>AMD accuses former employees of spying for Nvidia</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358386217988</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 20:30:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This could be big trouble for NVDA if they accepted this info and failed to report the theft to AMD and the authorities. XQ</Msg><Username>xquestor</Username><Timestamp>1358397707388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 23:41:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358398627072-114</Id><Topic><Title>AMD accuses former employees of spying for Nvidia</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358386217988</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 20:30:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I backup my data all the time. I even have to save my data at a few places at work because IT are very smart and they keep crashing the system all the time. I even use Truecrypt so that my coworkers don't mess with my data.</Msg><Username>batmantran</Username><Timestamp>1358398627072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 23:57:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>