<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-26"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372221991571-1</Id><Title>Intel demos real-time code compression for die shrinkage, power saving</Title><Msg>google it, cannot paste here</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372221991571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 00:46:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372222237024-2</Id><Title>Intel doubles throughput, slashes power to stave off DATAPOCALYPSE</Title><Msg>With 750 gigabytes per second approaching, strong measures must be taken Research@Intel Intel researchers have developed a prototype interconnect that they say will both increase bandwidth and lower power requirements, whether used for simple CPU-to-CPU connections or scaled up to connect tens of thousands of CPUs in a data center. "Based on past trends, every four years the bandwidth requirements for systems is increasing by an order of magnitude," Intel senior research scientist Mozhgan Mansuri told The Reg at the annual Research@Intel dog and pony show in San Francisco on Tuesday. If this trend continues, she said, by 2020 bandwidth needs will be in the range of 750 gigabytes per second. And since today's most efficient interconnects require about 10 or 15 picojoules per bit, the juice required to power that bandwidth will be about 50 per cent of the whole system in 2020, "which is unacceptable." The solution that Mansouri and her colleagues have come up with is called, rather straightforwardly, "Scalable Energy Efficient I/O". Their setup consists of 64 bidirectional lanes controlled by a global clock – and it's that clock that is key to their system's efficiency, Mansouri said. The global clock takes advantage of the fact that although systems require more and more peak bandwidth, most of the time they're not running at that rate, but instead they're perhaps idling or running workloads that require only half that peak. If you want to conserve power in current implementations, she said, you simply turn off lanes that aren't needed, but keep the clock at the same rate – if you only need half the bandwidth, you turn off half the lanes. "So in that case, you just get the linear power saving – your bandwidth goes down by half, your power goes down by half." In Scalable Energy Efficient I/O, if you want to halve the bandwidth of the interconnect, instead of turning off half the lanes, you keep all the lanes running but drop the throughput of each of the lanes. By doi</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372222237024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 00:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372222328892-3</Id><Title>Hurry up and put a projector in my phone, Intel</Title><Msg>What if your mobile phone could project a screen of any size onto any surface? Intel has technology that could make that a reality very soon. For several years now, Intel has used its annual Research@Intel event to showcase an interactive projected display. The idea is that any surface can be turned into a space to flip through photos, watch videos and even compose documents. At today’s event in San Francisco, people crowded around a table to doodle and type messages with their fingers on a projected screen. It’s easy to see why the technology has wide appeal. Most people have made the leap from a physical keyboard to a touchscreen on their phone or tablet, and it doesn’t feel very different to type on a tabletop as opposed to a screen made of Gorilla Glass. It may even be easier, since a user can adjust a projected screen to be as small or large as they wish. An Intel expert raised a brilliant application: mobile phones. As the need and desire to interact with data while mobile has grown, a range of screen sizes have emerged for different types of personal use. We work on laptops with large screens and read on medium-sized iPads. But most of the time, we rely solely on a tiny phone screen to read our email, catch up on the news or share moments with friends. What if that phone could have any size screen? That’s the promise of an embedded projector. Suddenly, your Mailbox app becomes iPad-sized, laptop-sized, even wall-sized. If you get caught on a surprise deadline with just your cellphone, you don’t have to tap away on its tiny keypad. And you wouldn’t need extra accessories or a particularly smooth surface: You could even wear gloves.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372222328892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 00:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372222349907-4</Id><Topic><Title>Hurry up and put a projector in my phone, Intel</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372222328892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 00:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The projector demonstrated by Intel Tuesday is obviously still a prototype. It lagged at times, and at one point I was sent away for a few moments so Intel employees could reboot the system after it froze. The projector and camera that make the touch sensitivity possible will need to shrunk to a size that can fit comfortably inside a phone. But it was the only project at Research@Intel where people jumped in to test it already knowing what to do. We are ready, Intel. Hopefully you are too, soon.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372222349907</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 00:52:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372222454073-5</Id><Topic><Title>BYOD Enterprise trending forward</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1372210561912</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 21:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a marketing pitch not a market trend</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1372222454073</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 00:54:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372222838205-6</Id><Topic><Title>BYOD Enterprise trending forward</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1372210561912</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 21:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read the article. The trend is clear.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372222838205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:00:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372222885281-7</Id><Title>Intel's working on DIY programmable home automation, we go eyes-on with its proof-of-concept (video)</Title><Msg>The internet of things is growing, friends, and Intel knows it. From WiFi lightbulbs to smart thermostats and door locks, it seems that most everything in our homes will have some sort of connectivity in the not-so-distant future. That's why chipzilla's research arm has been working on a way to program all of those devices and make it easy enough so that any do-it-yourselfer can get her home working the way she wants it to. The key is getting all of these future devices to work together, and Intel's plan is to build a platform that'll talk to most any PCB (Arduino, Beagle Boards, etc.) over any wireless protocol (WiFi, Bluetooth, Zigbee, et al.). A layer of middleware lets the bits of hardware talk to each other on an ad-hoc basis, so that say, when a baby monitor hears a crying child, it can tell a nearby stereo to tee up some soothing tunes to put him back to sleep automagically. The system actions are crafted using an easy-to-use HTML 5 programming environment, and will be deposited in a software library of modules that can be accessed by end users. Then, home automators can utilize a simple GUI editor to tailor their system to their wishes. We got to see a proof-of-concept system in person today, so head on past the break for a full video explanation and a demo of it in action.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372222885281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:01:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372222952346-8</Id><Topic><Title>Coming Up Next!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372123462400</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 21:24:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>June 26: Windows 8.1 software preview release date June 26-28: Microsoft's Build Developer Conference - Rumors of next Surface Pro announcement The Surface Pro would complete the hat trick: 1.) Mac upgrades 2.) Samsung Samsung tablets 3.) New Surface Pro model(s)</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372222952346</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:02:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372223096788-9</Id><Topic><Title>BYOD Enterprise trending forward</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1372210561912</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 21:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anandtech is quite clearly Intel biased.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1372223096788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372223108947-10</Id><Title>Smart tech, big data top priorities at Intel Labs</Title><Msg>SAN FRANCISCO -- It's what inside that counts, posited Intel Chief Technology Officer Justin Rattner. Now, for a microprocessor giant, this tagline should be interpreted in multiple ways. The obvious reading being that, because it's coming from Intel, the company is touting its own hardware bits. But being that this is the theme of this year's Research@Intel summit on Tuesday, the line is also meant to promote what Intel Labs has been cooking up to improve people's lives and communities rather than to just play a numbers game of making devices more faster or efficient. This year, the processor giant's research showcase has been organized into the following four categories: enriching lives, intelligent "everything," the data society, and tech essentials. More specifically, some of the projects run the gamut from personalized shopping to connected vehicle safety to discovering relationships among data communities. For example, Rattner showed a demo of "smart headlights" technology integrated on a vehicle driving through snow, which is being pitched to top-tier automakers right now. Citing the 2010 National Highway Traffic Safety Report, Rattner posited that smart headlights could prevent up to 800,000 crashes, 200,000 injuries, and even 3,000 fatalities. Intel futurist and chief evangelist Steve Brown argued that "if we can do anything with technology," then the task is figuring out the best way to spend resources rather than just throwing them at anything and everything.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372223108947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:05:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372223145297-11</Id><Topic><Title>Smart tech, big data top priorities at Intel Labs</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372223108947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:05:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brown noted that Intel conducts approximately 250,000 interviews worldwide annually, asking people both what they need and what they want from life. Those responses have been compiled and analyzed, boiling down to these six categories: learning, entertainment, creativity, wellness, productivity, and feeling connected. Rattner said these categories represent the kind of research going on at both Intel Labs and around the world right now. While providing an overview of Intel's international research facilities, Rattner highlighted the sixth and newest center in China. Rattner said that "given the massive size of its communications infrastructure," China was deemed the "perfect place to do this research." Thus, promoting Intel's ongoing evolving mobility strategy, the ICRI for Mobile Networking and Computing specializes in development for telecommunications infrastructure, systems, and services. Naturally, figuring out what to do about big data is also on the docket at Intel Labs around the world. One such area is centered on graph analytics technologies, which is enabling analytics based upon sparse data. "This work is intended to make graph analytics technology ubiquitous and available to the industry at large," explained Rattner. The two principle tools are Intel's Graph Builder and the Graph Lab developed at the ISTC-Cloud Computing center. Pointing out that both of these products are open-source, Rattner continued that that these should be "rapidly embraced" by the technology community.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372223145297</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372223161676-12</Id><Topic><Title>Smart tech, big data top priorities at Intel Labs</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372223108947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:05:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Current users include Google, Facebook, Twitter, Netflix and Pandora, among others. But many of these technologies sprouting up and fueled by big data have also given way to media buzz topics such as "the rise of the sharing economy" and "collaborative consumption." While sometimes it seems like news feeds are so saturated with these topics that they lose value, that doesn't eliminate the opportunities that exist here. At Intel, research scientists said it is referred to as "the data society." "More than ever it's become not just acceptable but desirable to do things with people we don't know at all," remarked Intel Labs director Genevieve Bell, arguing that people are sleeping in the homes of people they don't know, borrowing the cars of strangers, and even video-streaming romantic dates to online viewers for feedback. "That seems useful," Bell said.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372223161676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:06:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372223328531-13</Id><Title>Intel explores brain scanning to make roads safer</Title><Msg>Researchers at Intel are hoping a little insight into the way drivers think as they hurtle down the highway can be harnessed to make roads safer. The company is using a brain scanning technique called functional near infrared spectroscopy to attempt to differentiate between those times when a driver is focused on the road ahead and when his or her thoughts are occupied with other things. "We're trying to understand people better, what they're thinking, what they're feeling," said Paul Crawford, a senior research scientist at Intel Labs who is working on the project at the company's Silicon Valley research center. He said the research builds on the sizeable amount of work that has already been done on how people interact with computers and machines such as cars. "We want to understand cognitive workload, how hard someone is having to work to do something," he said. In a demonstration in San Francisco on Tuesday, the company showed how it is measuring the brain activity of a driver sitting at a simulator. The driver is navigating a virtual Formula One car around a racetrack at 50 miles per hour in one test, and at more than 250 mph in another test. (See video of the demonstration on YouTube.) Infrared sensors fitted to a cap over the driver's head sensed activity in the outermost 2 centimeters of the driver's brain. By measuring differences between the two drives, researchers start to be able to tell the difference between intense concentration -- when the race car is being driven at top speed -- and the much-reduced amount needed at lower speeds. "When you're driving, sometimes you're looking at the road and paying attention, and sometimes you're looking at the road and you're not paying attention. There are some subtle differences there that I hope, and I hypothesize, we can tease out," said Crawford. That information could one day be fed into a car's computer, which might make adjustments to the environmental controls to keep the driver more alert, or give more or</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372223328531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:08:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372223410189-14</Id><Topic><Title>Intel explores brain scanning to make roads safer</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372223328531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:08:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That information could one day be fed into a car's computer, which might make adjustments to the environmental controls to keep the driver more alert, or give more or less control to safety features such as automatic braking or lane control. "With that information, we can say 'maybe they need some additional stimulation, maybe we [change the radio station], maybe we dial up or down the amount of control, maybe we pull you off the car in front of you a little bit," he said. Road-related injuries are the eighth-leading cause of death in the world and the number-one killer of people between 15 and 29 years of age, according to the World Health Organization. Road accidents killed about 1.24 million people in 2010, the latest year for which global figures are available. Intel's research is initially focused on cars, but it goes beyond the highway. "We're leading with cars because it's a well-controlled area that we can do some laboratory research around," said Crawford. "A lot of us get paid to work with our brains, and we want it to be as efficient as possible, so there's all sorts of enterprise-level applications of this, and some consumer-level applications." At the San Francisco event, Intel also showed a second research project that could help cut road accidents. That work, being done with the National Taiwan University, seeks to provide vehicle-to-vehicle communications using something already found on many vehicles: LED brake lights. The researchers are using a laptop computer to modulate the light from the rear lights so it can carry data about the state of the vehicle. Intel's demonstration used a pair of scooters, which are ubiquitous on the streets of Taiwan. The rear LED light of the front scooter carried an alert each time the brakes were applied or the turn indicators were switched on or off. In motion, the system can also transmit the current speed of the scooter. A rider on a rear scooter would see an alert on his or her dashboard when the scooter in fron</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372223410189</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372223427844-15</Id><Topic><Title>Intel explores brain scanning to make roads safer</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372223328531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:08:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A rider on a rear scooter would see an alert on his or her dashboard when the scooter in front is slowing down, speeding up, turning or stopping. In the demo, the modulated light signals were received by a camera mounted on the front of the bike and were displayed via a phone app. The idea, said Hao Min Lin, a Ph.D. student at the National Taiwan University and one of the team working on the project, is that the extra information would give riders a fraction of a second more time to react. By knowing the scooter in front is slowing, for example, riders would be able to begin adjusting their speed before the brake lights come on.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372223427844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:10:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372223580400-16</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's working on DIY programmable home automation, we go eyes-on with its proof-of-concept (video)</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372222885281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:01:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great find! This is exciting stuff. WiFi LED lightbulbs controlled by an Arduino board would be pretty slick. The IoT (Internet of Things) is going to be a network equal in size to the current cellular network. There will be an immense revenue stream attached to it. And Intel is going to be right there...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372223580400</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:13:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372223745891-17</Id><Topic><Title>Intel explores brain scanning to make roads safer</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372223328531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:08:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't wait for driverless cars to become affordable and accepted. It will save a lot of lives...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372223745891</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:15:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372228101425-18</Id><Topic><Title>One trade + $4,500 On the day..</Title><Username>rogerwalker513</Username><Timestamp>1371785363137</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 23:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>POHJ</Msg><Username>tryme877</Username><Timestamp>1372228101425</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 02:28:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372229763413-19</Id><Topic><Title>Intel explores brain scanning to make roads safer</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372223328531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 01:08:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haha. That's hilarious. The last thing Taiwan needs is people paying less attention to the road and more to a "dashboard". I live in Taiwan. Drivers here are the worst drivers, except for the drivers in China, in the 25+ countries I've been to. We need driverless cars. "Knowing" what the scooter in front of you is doing is only relevant if you "care" what the scooter in front of you is doing, or are even "aware." Sorry, personal rants about driving are ubiquitous among foreigners here.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372229763413</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 02:56:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372235522829-20</Id><Title>Hey Bacbacker</Title><Msg>Intel will be fine longterm. The reason the stock jumps all over the place short-term is because of morons like you that #$%$ their pants and sell their shares on the drop of the hat when some rumor surfaces of a glitch with Haswell....Remember when you did that, loser?</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372235522829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 04:32:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372240953965-21</Id><Topic><Title>Hurry up and put a projector in my phone, Intel</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372222328892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 00:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe Texas Instruments has patented [for ten plus years] DLP tech ["mirrors" on a microchip]. Digital Light Projection if I remember correctly. It can be projected at any size without loss of focus, definition, or color. I like where Intel is going with this, but where'd they get the idea?</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1372240953965</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 06:02:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372241615571-22</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Mini Rumors: Tablet with Intel Atom Microprocessor to Launch During Q4 of 2013, Says Analyst</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372188855274</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 15:34:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dual boot, wireless connectivity to tv and other tech, enterprise software, keyboard included, customer hardware upgradable (now I may be asking too much, but I'm asking!), all for under $600 (I'm still asking) and I buy!</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372241615571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 06:13:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372242494315-23</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo Miix Tablet, New S and U Series Units This Summer</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372123022958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 21:17:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now waiting for other companies to post about their tech.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372242494315</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 06:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372243722692-24</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is low-balling growth estimate</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366415409484</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 19:50:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Historically, Intel has been trading</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372243722692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 06:48:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372243922492-25</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is low-balling growth estimate</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366415409484</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 19:50:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Historically, Intel has been trading</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1372243922492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 06:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372248188022-26</Id><Title>ARM Holdings Raised to Buy From Hold by Benchmark Capital</Title><Msg>ARM Holdings Raised to Buy From Hold by Benchmark Capital Last update: 6/26/2013 6:12:09 AM (END) Dow Jones Newswires June 26, 2013 06:12 ET (10:12 GMT)</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1372248188022</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:03:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372250086037-27</Id><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Msg>It is funny to see you chumps spinning false information. I’m in Taiwan now and can tell you that NOBODY here takes DigiTimes seriously. Same thing goes for Seeking Alpha, DeepChip, SemiAccurate, and other rumor websites. For someone to say that Apple or any other fabless semiconductor company has signed a foundry deal for 10nm is just silly. 10nm negotiations have just started and will absolutely hinge on who delivers 14/16nm FinFETs as promised and at what price. If you guys read SemiWiki like Ashraf and 600k+ semiconductor professionals do you would know this already. A more detailed article on this subject will be posted on SemiWiki tonight. Now I'm off to Hong Kong to chat with the private equity folks. Yes, they read SemiWIki too.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372250233459-28</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is low-balling growth estimate</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366415409484</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 19:50:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>double digit growth (10%) of 20% is 2% of overall impact double digit growth (20%) of 20% is 4% of overall impact offset data center growth with expectations of PC client group growth PERCEPTION of a decline IDC says something about a 7% decline .... blah blah blah .... Intel is PC company so they are going to contract like PC's ..... blah blah blah There are lots of negative cases to be made following the market disruptions . Sandy Bridge was TOOOOOOOO good. Ivy Bridge was a TICK. Haswell will stand on the shoulders and take advantage of the 22nm process. From just the sentence context, I think Stacy said "integer math" rather than the transcribed "manager math".</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372250233459</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:37:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372250390369-29</Id><Title>Can China alone drive semiconductor growth?</Title><Msg>Good article by Bill Jewel. Unfortunately China is all about low cost phone and tablets so that rules out Intel. Google: Can China alone drive semiconductor growth?</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250390369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:39:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372250514202-30</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A guy, who runs his own website calling people Chumps on a message board. Funny stuff. DN is a complete and utter loser. NOBODY who is successful in life acts like this. Thanks for showing your cards....a large portion of what comes out of your mouth is clearly LIES and it WILL catch up to you - looks like it already has.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372250514202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372253392893-31</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give our regards to you buddy Morris. What a clown. Do you also post under Backbay_bstn Nenni?</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1372253392893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 09:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372254342962-32</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to sell set to box Internet TV this year</Title><Username>khitchdumb</Username><Timestamp>1372212808695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:13:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Other than the number of subs satellite operators are a poor analogy to what Intel is doing. . Because satellite operators own their own transport and control the quality and amount of bandwidth to the customer it is much easier for satellite operators to compete against cable for live TV than with the approach Intel planning to take. Intel owns neither the content, nor the transport. Therefore the viewing experience will depend on the Quality-Of-Service of the Internet connection the customer gets from the MSO. To be sure other OTTP operators like Netflix and Vudu have the same dependency but they're not trying to deliver live TV that will get interrupted when the Interconnection slows down. If a movie gets interrupted its frustrating but one just restarts it when the net connection returns. Who wants to watch recorded versions of CNN news? That's not live TV.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372254342962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 09:45:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372254361668-33</Id><Title>Intel Earns more than $1.0 just for buying up Bonds.</Title><Msg>It can clear more than $1B simply by buying back the bonds it issued just a year ago. What an easy way to make $1.0B</Msg><Username>mbislying</Username><Timestamp>1372254361668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 09:46:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372254907576-34</Id><Title>This price is not sustainable</Title><Msg>Look for the warning soon</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372254907576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 09:55:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372255074247-35</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Earns more than $1.0 just for buying up Bonds.</Title><Username>mbislying</Username><Timestamp>1372254361668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 09:46:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If INTC just bought the stock back that they were suppost to do, they would make even more. But they would rather pay the bond interest and the dividends. That's why the board needs to be replaced. They also recommended to not take the limited buy back, but fail to buy the shares they sold the bonds for.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1372255074247</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 09:57:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372255197503-36</Id><Title>Xeon Phi analysis</Title><Msg>Intel Xeon Phi is a recently released high-performance coprocessor which features 61 cores each supporting 4 hardware threads with 512-bit wide SIMD registers achieving a peak theoretical performance of 1Tflop/s in double precision. Many scientific applications involve operations on large sparse matrices such as linear solvers, eigensolver, and graph mining algorithms. The core of most of these applications involves the multiplication of a large, sparse matrix with a dense vector (SpMV). In this paper, we investigate the performance of the Xeon Phi coprocessor for SpMV. We first provide a comprehensive introduction to this new architecture and analyze its peak performance with a number of micro benchmarks. Although the design of a Xeon Phi core is not much different than those of the cores in modern processors, its large number of cores and hyperthreading capability allow many application to saturate the available memory bandwidth, which is not the case for many cutting-edge processors. Yet, our performance studies show that it is the memory latency not the bandwidth which creates a bottleneck for SpMV on this architecture. Finally, our experiments show that Xeon Phi's sparse kernel performance is very promising and even better than that of cutting-edge general purpose processors and GPUs. arxivDOTorg/abs/1302.1078 arxivDOTorg/pdf/1302.1078v1</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372255197503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 09:59:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372255399444-37</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to sell set to box Internet TV this year</Title><Username>khitchdumb</Username><Timestamp>1372212808695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:13:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You might as well get out of the way of IP TV. It's coming and there is absolutely nothing you can do about it. For the generation that is growing up using the internet for all video, they simply don't worry about the things you are talking about. I cancelled my DirecTV and I don't have access to cable. There is some downside to this but not enough to make me go back. Bottom line remains: Someone is going to do it and it might as well be Intel...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372255399444</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:03:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372255527707-38</Id><Title>Nenni Experiencing Economic Downturn</Title><Msg>He's back trying to promote his website here. Things must be really tough...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372255527707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:05:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372255548543-39</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1368630162296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"As far as my education or experience goes as an accountant, engineer, lawyer, manager or anything else, you know nothing about me. You make things up to suit your need" Don't you make up your BS education as needed? You are a parasite.</Msg><Username>chartstradamus</Username><Timestamp>1372255548543</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:05:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372255862746-40</Id><Topic><Title>30 Cents Off The Day's Low</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372097439467</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 14:10:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not only did the 350 DMA support at 23.40 hold but the stock regained the 50 DMA support at 24.06 today, so good recovery.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372255862746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:11:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372255941192-41</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni Experiencing Economic Downturn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372255527707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:05:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will Waldo take his long term gains on 24.00 before the market turns down again?</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372255941192</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:12:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372256045958-42</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to sell set to box Internet TV this year</Title><Username>khitchdumb</Username><Timestamp>1372212808695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:13:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course IP TV is happening. Comcast and other cable operators are already doing it. The difference is that when a cable company does it they use a separate IP channel to deliver it. Because of this cable operators don't count the data used to stream video against the customer's fixed monthly "Internet" allocation so with cable provided video streaming the customer still has all their "Internet" bandwidth for their PCs, tablets and smartphones. With OTTP streaming the customer has to worry about how much of the data allocation their TV watching has consumed.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372256045958</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:14:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372256177578-43</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to sell set to box Internet TV this year</Title><Username>khitchdumb</Username><Timestamp>1372212808695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:13:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now you are arguing with yourself. As it should be...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256177578</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:16:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372256196119-44</Id><Topic><Title>30 Cents Off The Day's Low</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372097439467</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 14:10:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so far, bounce from breakdown levels only managed to get to the FRIDAY gap up open highs. qld 64.80 area, and INTC stopped at what has been resistance in the 24 .20's. Upside may take to the spy to the 50 day, if 1600 can hold, but that's likely it.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372256196119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:16:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372256314173-45</Id><Topic><Title>30 Cents Off The Day's Low</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372097439467</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 14:10:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like I spoke too soon, 50 DMA still acting like resistance so will require more work to break down.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372256314173</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:18:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372256318806-46</Id><Title>Sooooo...</Title><Msg>Now that most everyone has realized the the market downturn based on the Bernanke remarks was silly, what do shorts have to construct an exit strategy? Nada, zip, zilch. And here comes earnings...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256318806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:18:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372256424328-47</Id><Title>INTC will be 25 by next week!</Title><Msg>INTC will be 25 by next week, then will get a bump towards 30 after earnings</Msg><Username>trader_the</Username><Timestamp>1372256424328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:20:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372256519333-48</Id><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Msg>Come on, shorts - just because you are back to getting your heads handed to you in a basket, doesn't mean that you can't jump around and make people laugh...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372256614146-49</Id><Title>ARM Starting to Look Aspirated</Title><Msg>Again. Might as well get things back to normal...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256614146</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:23:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372256963200-50</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How are the shorts having their heads handed to them. I simply don't understand how that is reflected in the trading.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1372256963200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372257152242-51</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People that are delusional act out such delusion to gain attention/feel like they are relative. The man's a 63 old boring old accountant that never got laid........he needs to feel important, and this is his venue. Agregiously sad, yes. Reality, yes.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372257152242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372257179721-52</Id><Title>ARM Chips Are Heading To Servers — But Intel Is Already There, Waiting</Title><Msg>What's all this ARM fuss about, Intel wonders, as it lays a trap for its latest rival. ARM systems-on-chips are breaking out of their beachhead in mobile and heading to server platforms, which will introduce more low-power processors into data center configurations. But Intel may have a surprise or two for its rival chip architecture. That's because a lot of the planned milestones for ARM-based processors we're expecting in 2014 are already in Intel's rear-view mirror. In December 2012, for instance, Intel released its own 64-bit system-on-a-chip (SoC) for servers, the Intel Atom S1200 (codenamed Centerton). The Centerton's power levels have been measured as low as 6W. And that's just a start. Intel has already announced plans to introduce a second generation of Atom SoCs for microserver in the second half of 2013 – way ahead of any other 64-bit SoC based on ARM architecture from Applied Micro and AMD. The new Intel Atom SoC, codenamed Avoton, will be based on 22-nm manufacturing technology and new Silvermont micro-architecture, which are expected to make it competitive against current and future SoCs based on ARM. Applied Micro's X-Gene SoC will be based on 40-nm technology, which in general offer less performance, higher power consumption, or both. From readwrite</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372257179721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:32:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372257220546-53</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Chips Are Heading To Servers — But Intel Is Already There, Waiting</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372257179721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:32:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But Wait, There's More ARM-based SoCs have other hurdles in front of them. For years, enterprise customers have coded their applications to run on Intel-based architectures. The introduction of ARM-based micro-servers will afford those customers a lot more options — but they'll have to weigh those options against the costs of hardware replacement and software migration to a whole new architecture. In a way, ARM's software compatibility problem is a lot like the situation faced by early-to-market hybrids in the automobile market. Sure, the early Toyota Prius and Honda Insight models saved their owners money on gas. Initially, though, those cumulative savings still didn't justify the higher cost of the hybrid engine system. That's changing now for hybrids as gas prices rise and hybrid technology gets cheaper. But that early dilemma is very similar to what new ARM chips will face: a market dominated by a single architecture and some very real overhead costs for customers who chose to migrate their software to the upstart technology. Only when the savings from using ARM exceed those software porting costs will ARM SoCs will become more attractive to enterprise customers. And you can bet Intel has set its sights on staying ahead of that intersection in order to maintain its leadership position in the server market. From readwrite</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372257220546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:33:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372257631036-54</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How are the shorts having their heads handed to them. I simply don't understand how that is reflected in the trading." [Shorts professed that Intel would get mauled back into the teens. Instead markets have rallied significantly and the stock has moved up by 60 cents. With earnings around the corner, shorts now have no exit strategy. They were hoping to get a lot more out of the only thing that would help them - a general economic downturn. Now we see that the economy is getting stronger just as the Fed indicated. And there wasn't even time for any of them to cover. The whole shorting strategy has been and continues to be faulty as the big Wall Street firms misjudged Intel, tablets and all of mobility...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372257631036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:40:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372257707229-55</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>could be the only one getting his head handed to him is waldo, still cheerleading for INTC, and currently up nada on a hold for over 3 years. missed every good opportunity to sell for real nice gains since March of last year.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372257707229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:41:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372258054898-56</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to sell set to box Internet TV this year</Title><Username>khitchdumb</Username><Timestamp>1372212808695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:13:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's obvious you don't understand the media business. And you don't help Intel by trying to justify a misguided business ambition. It only weakens your credibility elsewhere. This is the difference between drinking the Intel CoolAid and examining each business on its own merit.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372258054898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:47:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372258152770-57</Id><Title>Shills Reaction to Intel Moving Up by 75 Cents Since Yesterday</Title><Msg>Yadda, yadda, yadda something about the past...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372258152770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:49:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372258229417-58</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to sell set to box Internet TV this year</Title><Username>khitchdumb</Username><Timestamp>1372212808695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:13:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, now that I don't agree with your position the name calling begins. Just go away...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372258229417</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:50:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372258349332-59</Id><Title>Merlot_1 hiding as sanddollars the last few days</Title><Msg>Give a rest already you Intel TV hater. geeez.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372258349332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:52:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372258419431-60</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not interested in the Wallis history. I am just curious how he determines what appears to be the opposite in trading evidence. The personality issues just bore me. I don't care if someone wins or loses or has poor strategy. I know my caution outweighs his enthusiasm.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1372258419431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:53:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372258887072-61</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There have been (supposedly) reasons to be cautious since November. But the stock has moved up by almost 5 bucks. There is always risk. You just have to find a risk/reward level that you are comfortable with. I like Intel's risk/reward ratio based on its technology, road map, pipeline, fabrication, mobility strategy and manufacturing. I understand if you don't...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372258887072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372259130604-62</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not only a chump, but a rude one.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1372259130604</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:05:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372259211386-63</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you've been pumping non stop for over 3 years, oblivous to, or simply ignoring, each and every market turn.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372259211386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:06:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372259965990-64</Id><Topic><Title>Merlot_1 hiding as sanddollars the last few days</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372258349332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another Wally Alias. How many is that now, about 20?</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372259965990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:19:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372260158329-65</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni Experiencing Economic Downturn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372255527707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:05:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm touring Hong Kong. You are in Arcata Calfornia shilling on Yahoo groups non stop. Things must be really tough.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372260158329</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:22:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372260228689-66</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hinge on who delivers 14/16nm FinFETs It's really 20nm FinFets - at least that's what ASML calls the ARM foundry FinFet - I mean ASML - not some analyst. maybe you can argue with ASML on semiwiki SA had pretty good discussion about die size ... too bad TSMC won't be able to scale the backend until 10nm Intel has not only the lead in front end (transistor) - they also have a lead in backend. the analysts and market are slow as molasses but eventually they will figure it out... LRCX thanks for the P.O.s for double patterning - it's expensive isn't it but they won't have choice.. it's only getting worse... I promise you</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372260228689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372260261737-67</Id><Title>Short Interest. What do you make of the increase from June 1st?</Title><Msg>Settlement Date Short Interest Avg Daily Share Volume Days To Cover 6/14/2013 229,596,305 40,417,975 5.680549 5/31/2013 224,423,045 35,377,507 6.343665 5/15/2013 224,949,744 31,549,848 7.129979 4/30/2013 233,212,213 71,694,120 3.252878 4/15/2013 235,467,126 41,270,640 5.705439 3/28/2013 238,762,872 35,500,532 6.725614 3/15/2013 233,896,426 39,064,511 5.987440 2/28/2013 216,006,917 44,946,805 4.805835 2/15/2013 208,197,763 30,642,118 6.794496 1/31/2013 196,957,970 86,401,976 2.279554 1/15/2013 205,835,193 39,470,361 5.214931</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372260261737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:24:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372260935932-68</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni Experiencing Economic Downturn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372255527707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:05:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, Nenni if you have time in the midst of going around the message boards holding out your tin can, why don't you address the other 15 reasons that ARM's fabrication is toast. You ran out of blather after one...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372260935932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:35:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372260964804-69</Id><Topic><Title>Short Interest. What do you make of the increase from June 1st?</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372260261737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:24:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Um, because you can't fix stupid?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372260964804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372261161079-70</Id><Topic><Title>Nenni Experiencing Economic Downturn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372255527707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:05:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nenni there is a nice lighthouse in Arcata and I can make you shut up because I actually worked in fabs all around the globe</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372261161079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:39:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372261365066-71</Id><Title>INTC WILL MAKE LATE DAY RUN LIKE YESTERDAY</Title><Msg>EXPECT $24.5 CLOSE TODAY. $40 BY END OF YEAR</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372261365066</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:42:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372261515751-72</Id><Topic><Title>Short Interest. What do you make of the increase from June 1st?</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372260261737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:24:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do believe we will beat on Q2 earnings. Everything has been done to make the new CEO shine, including dumping as much as into Q1 as possible. It will be a fun post-earnings summer.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372261515751</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372261634136-73</Id><Title>It has always been about phone chips for the last 5 years.</Title><Msg>If Intel breaks into phones and takes massive market share, the stock goes up like a rocket. The TV thing is a surprise but it too has a huge upside for Intel. Oh yeah--I agree with the shorts when they trash Intel stock performance. They are of course factually correct in pointing out that Intel has not moved in 13 years. But the upside for Intel in phones, TV, and other new areas to come is all NEW! New revenue streams and massive net profit gains will come so 40 this year is still very possible. How air is what America is so so full of don't you know. Look at the blowhards on Fuxed up news. Their three pronged attack on Obummer has again gone into complete meltdown. Their attack is like a limp #$%$ without viagra from an 80 year old man. Obummer won. Get over it you pathetic crybaby loser clown KKK Repuke trash nuts. Just like the Inbred white trash in your party in the deep south, your time is fading away.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372261634136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372261793282-74</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>So far, the decline in the past month has played out like a correction within a long term uptrend. The major indexes were able to bounce off an oversold condition and their 100-day moving averages. Stocks adjusted themselves to the eventual tapering of the Fed bond buying program and might have overreacted in fear of higher interest rates. But the Fed isn't likely to start raising interest rates anytime soon. The stock market has a positive bias heading into the end of the quarter but the longer term direction will likely depend on the coming earnings season.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372261793282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:49:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372262087739-75</Id><Title>These Stock Alerts Are Da Bomb</Title><Msg>Got my daily picks and saw it soar up 350%. I couldn’t believe my eyes. Wow. Just Text the word Alerts without quotes to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT</Msg><Username>cmaynard628</Username><Timestamp>1372262087739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372262204453-76</Id><Topic><Title>Short Interest. What do you make of the increase from June 1st?</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372260261737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:24:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big boys holding price down by shorting more in a vain attempt to cover during the coming correction they keep talking about. They are praying for the correction and that INTC doesn't get any traction before they can cover. The big thing going right for them is INTC silience and their not buying the 6 billion in shares back. If either change, look for some panic covering that will lead to more covering. One little impetus will start the cascade and it will be great to watch.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1372262204453</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:56:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372262726856-77</Id><Topic><Title>Short Interest. What do you make of the increase from June 1st?</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372260261737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:24:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am surprised-Maybe those shorting Intel are buying into the 'death of the PC'? In a couple of years PCs will only be found in mueseums: Word processing, spreadsheets, video editing and viewing etc will all be done on your Smart Watch-I'm pretty sure.</Msg><Username>kip_castle</Username><Timestamp>1372262726856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 12:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372263147900-78</Id><Title>You still want your country back you A H Ol E s?</Title><Msg>Supreme Court strikes down DOMA; rules it interferes with states, ‘dignity’ of same-sex marriages HAAA HAAAA More Nice people to vote for Dems</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372263147900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 12:12:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372263185283-79</Id><Topic><Title>Short Interest. What do you make of the increase from June 1st?</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372260261737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:24:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The correction came and went... it was 5% and cut short by better than expected economic data.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372263185283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 12:13:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372263832731-80</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi analysis</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372255197503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 09:59:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you very much.</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372263832731</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 12:23:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372264023009-81</Id><Topic><Title>Short Interest. What do you make of the increase from June 1st?</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372260261737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:24:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wouldn't be so sure about that.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372264023009</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 12:27:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372264112540-82</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Shorts professed that Intel would get mauled back into the teens. Instead markets have rallied significantly and the stock has moved up by 60 cents." The stock fell considerably more than 60 cents. You didn't answer how the shorts are having their heads handed to them..</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1372264112540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 12:28:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372264473520-83</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>price falling again. Does that mean more shorts had their heads handed to them?</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1372264473520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 12:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372265027303-84</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the same logic, ARMH shorts are getting their heads handed to them, up 1.80 off the low, but let's not mention that</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372265027303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 12:43:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372265357338-85</Id><Topic><Title>It has always been about phone chips for the last 5 years.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372261634136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:47:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do Gays always spew the most venom? Must be a lot of RAGE inside. Shut up, moron.</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372265357338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 12:49:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372266028818-86</Id><Topic><Title>It has always been about phone chips for the last 5 years.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372261634136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:47:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I lost you at How... You truly are a dumb monkey.</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1372266028818</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372266174585-87</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi analysis</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372255197503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 09:59:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't have an Intel 10nm roadmap by any chance or when would you expect to see Intel publishing it. On EE times I picked up some intel stating that 10nm is about to be locked in without EUV. I believe the slow progress in regards to EUV will be another headache for the foundries.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372266174585</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:02:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372266481079-88</Id><Topic><Title>It has always been about phone chips for the last 5 years.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372261634136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 11:47:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New revenue streams are great and there are numerous reasons why Intel can leverage its world class fabs and chip making know how to capture meaningful market share in tablets, smartphones and forthcoming wearable computers. Intel also has a very good chance getting its processors inside cable settop boxes and continuing to sell servers to companies streaming pre-rcorded material. But there is an abundance of sound reasons why Intel will not be successful making a viable business competing directly against cable operators delvering live TV. You are correct on this point though. Intel's share price fate hinges on its success in mobile and has nothing to do with Intel Web TV, as long as the Web TV losses don't impact the company's overall financials.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372266481079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:08:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372266820041-89</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rude and a chump. You need to work on being nice.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1372266820041</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372267141169-90</Id><Title>Tetanus Shot - Humor</Title><Msg>Tetanus Shot (this applies to all ages) An old man in his mid-seventies struggles to get up from the couch then starts putting on his coat. His wife, seeing the unexpected behavior, asks, Where are you going?' He replies, 'I'm going to the doctor.' She says, 'Why, are you sick?' He says, 'Nope, I'm going to get me some of that Viagra stuff.' Immediately the wife starts working and positioning herself to get out of her rocker and begins to put on her coat. He says, 'Where the heck are you going'? She answers, 'I'm going to the doctor, too.' He says, 'Why, what do you need?' She says, 'If you're going to start using that rusty old thing, I'm getting a Tetanus shot.'</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372267141169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:19:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372267170199-91</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi analysis</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372255197503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 09:59:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Mayberry said that everything up to the 10-nm CMOS node – which is in development at Intel and will ramp production in 2015 - is effectively done. '</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372267170199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:19:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372267426017-92</Id><Topic><Title>Tetanus Shot - Humor</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1372267141169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:19:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One needs to attain a certain stage of live to really get that one. I must be there as I had a good laugh.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1372267426017</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372267596523-93</Id><Title>Aereo Is Leading The Charge Challenging Incumbent Media Giants</Title><Msg>This company is streaming live local TV and will be offering service in 22 cities by end of year. Service starts at $8/month and for $12/mo can add 20 hours of DVR storage. Broadcasters are irate but Aereo has support from multiple court rulings. Those that want to cut cable video and lower costs are far more likely to use this or get their HDTV Over-The-Air. Aereo has a novel approach and delivers service for an incredibly cheap price.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372267596523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:26:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372268295870-94</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi analysis</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372255197503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 09:59:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't post the article or any excepts but yeah Mayberry confirmed on eetimes that 10nm was done and coming in 2015 in an article dated 5/22/2013.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372268295870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:38:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372268437497-95</Id><Title>INTC would probably just be the stock to look at this quarter.</Title><Msg>I actually simply wanted to share this newsletter with absolutely everyone... It has an article with information of hot small cap stocks. Link:- gooDOTgl/7BwBS (Remove DOT &amp; Use . )</Msg><Username>reinaldo_willie</Username><Timestamp>1372268437497</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372268643303-96</Id><Topic><Title>INTC would probably just be the stock to look at this quarter.</Title><Username>reinaldo_willie</Username><Timestamp>1372268437497</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:40:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watching it go lower and lower</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372268643303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:44:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372268796171-97</Id><Title>Lagging</Title><Msg>but this is just old news for INTC. See you in the red at the end of the day</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372268796171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372269467376-98</Id><Title>Twenty Four Douleurs for Wallis!</Title><Msg>He's a paid shill. He's paid to pretend INTC is a buy over $24 to create demand when the insiders are dumping (which they've been doing with wild abandon lately).</Msg><Username>walrusweener</Username><Timestamp>1372269467376</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372270206840-99</Id><Topic><Title>Twenty Four Douleurs for Wallis!</Title><Username>walrusweener</Username><Timestamp>1372269467376</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No he is one of the INSIDERS that get FREE shares and just keeps selling them , For him INTC has always been a buy. He was a buy from 29,25 all the way down to 19.26 and will always be a buy , Would not you if you get free shares and keep sell them. As a shareholder you take all the risk and if you sell when INTC runs up you my make your $ 5-10, but the INSIDERS that get free shares can make $20-30 with no risk. I would always tell you to buy if I had that kind of deal</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372270206840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 14:10:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372271574866-100</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a chump, and so is anybody that says "I hate rich people", like Walliwsweaver did...that's incredibly rude, jealous and childish..... As is pumping stocks and leading people to the slaughther house like he does with no care in the world for any damage he does.. You take care of yourself, buddy.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372271574866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 14:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372272294576-101</Id><Title>Unless you're on the road all the time ...</Title><Msg>I don't see why you would dump your desktop for an all-mobile computer lifestyle. Don't you want the maximum of RAM? Don't you want the biggest possible screen? Don't you want the most powerful chip without worrying about battery life. I can understand the appeal of tablets and smartphones, but I don't understand why this leads to the abandonment of the desktop. I love that cockpit feeling which only a Desktop provides. My 24 inch screen seems too small, and the next one will go right to 30 inches.</Msg><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1372272294576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 14:44:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372272427240-102</Id><Title>To Intel BoD, please take this company private</Title><Msg>Offer long term shareholders a fair price, and rid yourself and us of this BS manipulation.</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1372272427240</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 14:47:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372273545506-103</Id><Topic><Title>Lagging</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372268796171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:46:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A random walk is a mathematical formalization of a path that consists of a succession of random steps. For example, the path traced by a molecule as it travels in a liquid or a gas, the search path of a foraging animal, the price of a fluctuating stock and the financial status of a gambler can all be modeled as random walks,</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372273545506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372274016196-104</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You're a chump, and so is anybody that says "I hate rich people", like Walliwsweaver did." [I never said I hate rich people. You are without a doubt a pathological liar.] [I've corrected you on this before but as I just stated you are a pathological liar. What I said was that rich people should pay their fair share of taxes. I stand by this. I don't hate anyone, not even the psychologically dysfunctional bullies who stalk me on this board because they believe I shouldn't be allowed to say anything that they disagree with.] [PS. Did I mention that you are a pathological liar?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372274016196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:13:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372274261032-105</Id><Title>Windows XP end of life</Title><Msg>WinXp is expiring for good in April 2014. This will surely lead to quite a deluge of new PCs. Hey won't all be replaced with iPads.</Msg><Username>mrpoorguy</Username><Timestamp>1372274261032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:17:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372274592015-106</Id><Topic><Title>Lagging</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372268796171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 13:46:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like you'd better feverishly work the board, price going up. Your precious $19 entry price slipping away. Better bring in your moronic alias: coinmaker.</Msg><Username>phil.latio777</Username><Timestamp>1372274592015</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:23:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372274667677-107</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There you go lying again, just like you lied when you said you worked 70 hours a week.....that's easily disproved by your posting history. everybody knows you are the psychopath here, not me. One minute you call shorts the skumm of the earth.......minutes later you are dancing around the fire, bragging about your short on ARM. YOU are a disgusting human being.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372274667677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:24:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372275007636-108</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi analysis</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372255197503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 09:59:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mike Mayberry, director of component research at Intel Corp. has looked down the highway of conventional silicon development and reckons things become foggy beyond about the 7-nm node. And the methods of pre-competitive collaborative research that have served the industry so far will have to change and be opened up, Mayberry said, as he gave a keynote speech to the IMEC Technology Forum being held here. Local research institute IMEC works in collaboration with all the major semiconductor companies and its two-day annual forum provides an opportunity for engineering managers and senior executives from around the world to congregate. Mayberry said that everything up to the 10-nm CMOS node – which is in development at Intel and will ramp production in 2015 - is effectively done.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372275007636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:30:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372275254027-109</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Easy enough to show, chump. Just copy my message that you say exists and post it up. I don't care if you do. But if you don't everyone will know that you are a pathological liar...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372275254027</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372275488555-110</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The top 10 percent pay 70 percent of the taxes, pal. You were a jerk to me the first time I posted here and now I see why........you're a jerk.</Msg><Username>mark.steffenhagen</Username><Timestamp>1372275488555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:38:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372275880846-111</Id><Title>Microsoft treats Build 2013 attendees to an Acer Iconia W3 Windows 8 tablet and a Surface Pro</Title><Msg>At its Build 2013 conference today, Microsoft announced that developers will be receiving an Acer Iconia W3 Windows 8 tablet and a Microsoft Surface Pro. Microsoft CEO Steve Ballmer announced the former at the start of the keynote and Julie Larson-Green, corporate vice president for Windows, revealed the latter at the very end. We assume that the Surface Pro won’t come with Windows 8.1, but it’s fair to say it will be a perfect computer on which Build developers can install the preview released today. Whether you attended Build today or not, the details you need to get Windows 8.1 are here. Intel co-sponsored the giveaway, but something tells us Microsoft was rather eager to comply. There’s a question of supply here: many believe the company wants to get rid of its first-generation Surface stock to make way for the next iteration. That being said, Microsoft traditionally gives away something at its conferences. In fact, two devices isn’t exactly something unique to this year’s event. At last year’s conference, Microsoft gave attendees a Surface RT and 100GB of SkyDrive storage. Nokia’s Richard Kerris also came on stage and announced everyone would be getting a Lumia 920 to boot. Yet the focus this year was clearly on Windows, so we’re not exactly surprised both giveaways are computers that sport Microsoft’s operating system. One is a tablet, and the other is a laptop that can be used as just a tablet, which pretty much sums up the state of the PC space right now. Today is the first day of Build 2013, which runs till Friday. As always, we’ll be keeping you posted on everything Microsoft reveals during its annual conference. From thenextweb</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372275880846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:44:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372275926549-112</Id><Title>Microsoft introduces global program to sell massively discounted Surface RT tablets to schools</Title><Msg>Now that's funny...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372275926549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:45:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372275962888-113</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It isn't that simple. The message was deleted by YaHoo. You did disparage wealthy people. You were high on the BS Buffett line of taxation that he intentionally twisted by not mentioning his capital gains were taxed lower than average folks because all capital gains were. You parroted that position with your class warfare Obama tune. Nothing personal, but it is true.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1372275962888</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372276046157-114</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The top 10 percent pay 70 percent of the taxes, pal. You were a jerk to me the first time I posted here and now I see why........you're a jerk." [But the top 10 percent have MORE than 70 percent of the income. So, that means the top ten percent are not paying their fair share. If you are rich you ought to be able to pay your share. You shouldn't expect your tax load to be born by the middle class...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372276046157</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372276124669-115</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He won't ever admit it. I knew I didn't need to search for any posts as many here know exactly "who" he is. It's also disgusting that he speaks of skummy people ruining the market...........then out the other side of his mouth he shorts stock and brags. He's a very, very, VERY sick man. My problem with him is that he uses this worldwide podium to incessanlty pump and bash whatever stock he's holding or shorting. he's a low-life.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372276124669</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:48:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372276171130-116</Id><Topic><Title>Windows XP end of life</Title><Username>mrpoorguy</Username><Timestamp>1372274261032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:17:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I own an XP machine, a Vista machine and a Windows 7 machine. Wallis asked a few days ago, Why people are still on XP? I can tell that there really isn't a penalty for being on XP versus Vista or 7. I use all three and sometimes XP will have trouble with a heavy javascript website but Firefox has plenty of extensions that handle that situation. XP is a tank. It works day after day after day. I remember way back when I had Windows 98 and once I heard about "System Restore" I had to upgrade to XP. That was a defining issue for me since I like to download lots of software and sometimes I get in trouble. "System Restore" is a beautiful way out of trouble. I'm amazed when I run into people who don't know about this feature and its ease-of-use. Once XP came out, the penalty for being on W98 became too extreme. I believe that when Windows 8.1 comes out and XP is EOL, the penalty for being on XP will become too great and we will have massive migration to Windows 8.1 and Windows 7. I say massive because the amount of XP users is still at 38% of all Windows users. That is phenomenally high for an O/S that is 12 years old. Goodbye XP. You served us so well. I will miss you, but time and progress march forward.</Msg><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1372276171130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:49:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372276232604-117</Id><Topic><Title>Xeon Phi analysis</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372255197503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 09:59:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congrats the Yahoo filter was kinder to you lol. Soooo how far away are the foundries from 10nm or even a real 14nm lol ? All these Intel 10nm devices will be tipping up in volume in 2016 and will wreak pecuniary havoc amongst their 14/16-20nm hybrid foundry competition. Windows 8.1 was previewed today and the Start button has returned as expected along with a boot to desktop option as well as a shutdown option. Not as fully desktop friendly as Win 7 but good enough not to hold back PC sales any more, the Vista moment has passed until the next time Microsoft decide to shoot themselves in the foot ! Xeon Phi is an all round seriously good piece of hardware that can really differentiate itself from its HPC competition, could create a new niche market once the next gen standalone Knights Landing tips up. So much real innovation coming from Intel and the dumb analysts still think Intel is a dinosaur, results in the coming years will rip that false notion from their minds and wallets ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372276232604</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:50:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372276309796-118</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to all the Monkey Jumping???</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372256519333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 10:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not true. I never said "I hate rich people". I did disparage those not willing to pay their fair share of taxes and make no apologies whatsoever for it. It's that simple. He said that I said "I hate rich people". It's a baldfaced lie. I don't hate anyone. Not even pathological liars or those who misrepresent the truth in support of pathological liars...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372276309796</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:51:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372276539521-119</Id><Title>Wallisweaver on a chaotic rant against Rich people again today......the irony?</Title><Msg>Is he doing his fair share for society by posting here 20 hours a day, 7 days a week and shorting stocks to boot? If he's awake, he's here pumping Intel and bashing ARM. Is he what you'd call a "productive citizen." Funny stuff.....</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372276539521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:55:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372276668784-120</Id><Title>The Dangers of Lying</Title><Msg>When the truth is a matter of record are obvious...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372276668784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:57:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372276725451-121</Id><Title>Microsoft Conference</Title><Msg>We should be getting more good news out of the Microsoft Conference. A nice lift in the news cycle...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372276725451</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:58:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372276812717-122</Id><Topic><Title>The Dangers of Lying</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372276668784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:57:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, just like a liar........you liars ALWAYS go on the offense and try to call other's liars. I especially like how you called shorts financial terrorists and then months later shorted ARM and bragged about it day after day after day. You poor little scmuck. Feeling sorry for you!</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372276812717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 16:00:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372276879798-123</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft introduces global program to sell massively discounted Surface RT tablets to schools</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372275926549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:45:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Here’s a thought: At $250, Microsoft is selling a full tablet computer and keyboard that contains Microsoft Office for less coin than it costs to buy Office by itself in certain SKUs. Far, far less, in fact." [The RT failure was clearly part of the reason for the huge drop in ARM's stock price. It began and ended the ARM incursion into PCs...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372276879798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 16:01:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372276949008-124</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft introduces global program to sell massively discounted Surface RT tablets to schools</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372275926549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:45:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They really overcooked inventory by millions of units which they now have to get rid of. Don't know what makes them think that an Snapdragon S800 follow-up still without legacy software support will fare any better but that's apparently what's next. Should be chewed up in a Bay Trail/Haswell sandwich but MSFT have trouble learning what's a bad idea until the market spells it out to them a few times ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372276949008</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 16:02:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372277589690-125</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street Punishes Me, I Punish Wall Street</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1352868002308</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 23:40:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More of your Tax the rich BS</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1372277589690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 16:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372277762634-126</Id><Topic><Title>The Dangers of Lying</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372276668784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:57:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lie number 1, if you bght intc at 24 in June 2010, you'll be fine in 6 months. it dropped to 17. lie number 2, it's good for 30, dropped to 19. on the way down from 29, at 26 he was saying the elevator back up will be quick, it dropped from 26 to 19, and on the meteoric rise back it promptly stopped at 26. non stop pumping, has many times called wall street a bunch of crooks, of course he wouldn't last a new york minute in any brokerage trading house. 3 long years pumping INTC at least since 24 in 2010, for squat</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372277762634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 16:16:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372278340129-127</Id><Title>Wallisweaver is a INSIDER at INTC thats why the none stop.</Title><Msg>No Wallis is one of the INSIDERS that get FREE shares and just keeps selling them , For him INTC has always been a buy. He was a buy from 29.25 all the way down to 19.26 and will always be a buy , Would not you if you get free shares and keep selling them. As a shareholder you take all the risk and if you sell when INTC runs up you my make your $ 5-10, but the INSIDERS that get free shares can make $20-30 with no risk. I would always tell you to buy if I had that kind of deal</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372278340129</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 16:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372278453929-128</Id><Topic><Title>Wallisweaver is a INSIDER at INTC thats why the none stop.</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372278340129</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 16:25:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just part of the good old boy system same as Jerry</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372278453929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 16:27:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372278546517-129</Id><Topic><Title>Wallisweaver is a INSIDER at INTC thats why the none stop.</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372278340129</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 16:25:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They both tell you there is some other reason why all the insiders are always SELLING</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372278546517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 16:29:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372278917359-130</Id><Topic><Title>Windows XP end of life</Title><Username>mrpoorguy</Username><Timestamp>1372274261032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:17:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Saw this comment on SA from KD2010 --- "The important thing to consider is that a home will now have more devices than a laptop and a desktop. Especially if they are around $300. Essentially a desktop sale translated to couple of laptops. Now a laptop sales are translating to multiple tablets.... Instead of one cpu, more cpus will be sold. People are still not going to do away their laptop. I am sure we all need that 14" or 15" slim ultrabook with SSD for $699. Our desire to own that nice slim ultrabook does not go away with rise of tablets. Obviously not too many people have desire to spend $1500 for a laptop. BTW: PC sales will rebound once Window 8 becomes normal part of your life. It is a transition. Usually it takes good 12 to 18 months for people to get used to newer windows." My Comment: Yes, I agree. We want multiple computers in different form factors that serve different needs. However, it would be nice if all of our devices tied together into one ecosystem with a common o/s and hardware compatibility.</Msg><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1372278917359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 16:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372280060290-131</Id><Topic><Title>Windows XP end of life</Title><Username>mrpoorguy</Username><Timestamp>1372274261032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:17:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many people will stay on XP, however, enterprises won't have a choice to switch. There are still many large companies on XP.</Msg><Username>mrpoorguy</Username><Timestamp>1372280060290</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 16:54:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372280126974-132</Id><Topic><Title>Wallisweaver is a INSIDER at INTC thats why the none stop.</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372278340129</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 16:25:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And what are you with all your bs?</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1372280126974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 16:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372280669485-133</Id><Topic><Title>What a bunch of psychopaths you guys are</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372182567715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CNBC conditions people to be greedy. All you had to do was buy at 19, sit tight forever and you'd make a mint with the Dividend and future share price gains. Oh well, somebody's gotta do it the smart way - might as well be me.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372280669485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 17:04:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372281575244-134</Id><Topic><Title>What a bunch of psychopaths you guys are</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372182567715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Matter of fact, CNBC wants transactions...it's good for their business. If everybody bought low, held and enjoyed the Dividends they'd be out of a job. Wallstreet wants transastions, lots of them as that's how the money piles up. My broker absolutely hates me as he made about 50 bucks off me on my buys in the 19's, 20's and 21;s and will make 10 bucks when I sell them all years from now.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1372281575244</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 17:19:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372283783662-135</Id><Title>Microsoft will keep pushing RT not because it provides value to the customer</Title><Msg>but to keep Intel honest. Ballmer has to go. Win 8.1 is the same old Win 8 with a start menu. No one likes the complexity of their junk.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372283783662</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 17:56:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372284470341-136</Id><Title>Mr Weaver huffed and he pumped, but the pig is still wallowing in the mud.</Title><Msg>Tomorrow he'll do better, you'll see.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372284470341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 18:07:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372286198023-137</Id><Title>Coinmaker77 How much did you lose on Alcoa today</Title><Msg>lmao</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1372286198023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 18:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372286279313-138</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft introduces global program to sell massively discounted Surface RT tablets to schools</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372275926549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:45:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple using this tactic for ages....</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1372286279313</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 18:37:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372286315804-139</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft introduces global program to sell massively discounted Surface RT tablets to schools</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372275926549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:45:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why give students useless RT ?</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1372286315804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 18:38:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372288461566-140</Id><Title>Take a look at CAMP chart, earnings tomorrow!</Title><Msg>going to be Huge</Msg><Username>tomsimpson293</Username><Timestamp>1372288461566</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 19:14:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372288490246-141</Id><Title>Lucy_Nuff gets on her knees and services Intel</Title><Msg>lucy_nuff • Aug 10, 2003 5:36 PM Flag Who cares??? Intel is sitting on $14 billion in cash and the penalty will have absoultely no bearing on future earnings potential. The $600 million would be taken as a one-time charge and would be viewed that way by wall street. This company has a virtual franchise on the future of technology in the world and will be the first to benefit from a a recovery and renewed IT spending. Furthermore, the $600 million may never be paid out. Use your head for something more than a hatrack, moron</Msg><Username>lucy_mutt</Username><Timestamp>1372288490246</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 19:14:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372288659183-142</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft introduces global program to sell massively discounted Surface RT tablets to schools</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372275926549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:45:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tax write off.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372288659183</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 19:17:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372288752790-143</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft introduces global program to sell massively discounted Surface RT tablets to schools</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372275926549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:45:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They're trying to get rid of the dang things. Saw a best buy commercial the other night. I shook my head as they made the RT tablets look so great when all they were doing is trying to get rid of them.</Msg><Username>lucy_mutt</Username><Timestamp>1372288752790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 19:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372291726080-144</Id><Topic><Title>Coinmaker77 How much did you lose on Alcoa today</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1372286198023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 18:36:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nuff will never answer to someone who has him dead to right. His forte is making absurd reckless idiotic statements, consistently the same every day. A type of guerilla warfare, where he posts a comment and then runs for the hills with tail between legs or quickly switches to another alias. Never around to account for humongous investment blunders and foolish prophecies. People dream of yahoo someday pulling his ticket.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1372291726080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 20:08:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372292674295-145</Id><Title>Intel's fortunes rising in Tablets, says Wells</Title><Msg>Yahoo news. Sukk on that, Bernstein.</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372292674295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 20:24:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372292770290-146</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's fortunes rising in Tablets, says Wells</Title><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372292674295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 20:24:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By Tiernan Ray Wells Fargo‘s chip analyst David Wong this afternoon offers up his thoughts on the landscape for application processors in tablet computers, chief among which is that Intel‘s (INTC) share of tablet processors could rise form perhaps 1% last year to 5% or more in 2013. Noting the recent announcement Intel will be featured in Samsung Electronics‘s (005930KS) “Galaxy Tab III” tablet computer, Wong sees further gains for Intel’s “Atom” line of processor based on its recently introduced “Silvermont” core, as it closes the gap with processors based on ARM Holdings (ARMH) designs, and possibly even some business with Apple (AAPL): Drivers of tablet processor growth for Intel include ramping Windows 8 tablet shipments and Intel’s entry into Android tablets with its Clover Trail Plus chips. In the longer term, we think that Intel is one of the few merchant chip companies that has an opportunity of gaining incremental revenue associated with Apple’s applications processor in iPad. We believe that Intel has a 2+ year manufacturing lead, which could result Apple seriously considering moving its foundry business to Intel or perhaps even using Intel processors in iPad [...] Samsung’s most recently launched Android tablet family, the Galaxy Tab 3, uses Intel’s Clover Trail Plus chip, Samsung’s Exynos processor, a Marvell processor for various SKUs. We think this implies that Samsung’s internal evaluation has found that there is good compatibility between Intel’s Atom and various ARM based processors for Android applications in general. Another inference is, we think, that at the moment ARM-based processors do not offer any advantage in terms of cost or power consumption compared to Intel x86 Atom processors. Over the next two years, as Intel’s accelerates its Atom technology roadmap to take advantage of Intel’s technology lead, we think that Atom may emerge with clear performance and/or power consumption advantages over alternative ARM based solutions that cannot</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372292770290</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 20:26:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372292899084-147</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's fortunes rising in Tablets, says Wells</Title><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372292674295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 20:24:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>canoot tap into Intel's manufacturing.</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372292899084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 20:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372295472864-148</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's fortunes rising in Tablets, says Wells</Title><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372292674295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 20:24:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wong doesn't realize that the "clear performance and/or power consumption" advantage comes with Silvermont.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1372295472864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 21:11:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372297070359-149</Id><Topic><Title>Lucy_Nuff gets on her knees and services Intel</Title><Username>lucy_mutt</Username><Timestamp>1372288490246</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 19:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! Lucy has been the worlds biggest Intel bagholder, except that time he BRILLIANTLY dumped Intel at 21 for Cisco at 21.......Cisco then plummeted to 13 and Intel rose to 29. ROFL! That actually happened and that's why he threw his aliases in the trash can. ROFL @ him.</Msg><Username>lucy_cisco</Username><Timestamp>1372297070359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 21:37:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372298684559-150</Id><Title>How smart do I look for bolting from ARMH?</Title><Msg>Anybody seen Getanid61? I wanted to thank him for pumping the living #$%$ out of ARMH and padding me bank acccount! Tah Tah, laddies !</Msg><Username>warreneast_61</Username><Timestamp>1372298684559</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 22:04:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>