<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357364600521-1</Id><Topic><Title>ARM A15 is a Power hog according to Anandtech. Wont fit in smartphones.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1357340502444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 18:01:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is the way I read it too. The Qualcom APQ8060A SoC (dual-core 28nm Krait) has the power plane for each of the cores isolated. They can turn down each core individually and are able to match the Atom. The standard ARM A15 part without the special QCOM power modifications has a worse power profile than Atom. There is a lot of information in this AnandTech article and nearly all of it will be a surprise to those who thought that ARM had a big power advantage. YIKES!!!</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1357364600521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 00:43:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357384296120-2</Id><Topic><Title>ARM A15 is a Power hog according to Anandtech. Wont fit in smartphones.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1357340502444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 18:01:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The A15 is a power hog by design and is intended to be used in conjunction with the A7 in a BIG.little configuration. The Exynos 5 is rumored to be the first chip that will use these.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1357384296120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 06:11:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357392281488-3</Id><Title>Intel's Next-Gen Atom "ValleyView" to Double CPU Performance, Triple Graphics Performance</Title><Msg>Intel's Next-Gen Atom "ValleyView" to Double CPU Performance, Triple Graphics Performance Full story: X-bit labs It has already been revealed both officially and unofficially that Intel Corp.'s next-generation Atom system-on-chip code-named Valleyview will be substantially faster and more capable than chips available today.</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1357392281488</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 08:24:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357392504048-4</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Next-Gen Atom "ValleyView" to Double CPU Performance, Triple Graphics Performance</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1357392281488</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 08:24:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While production of Intel Atom “Valleyview” chips for Bay Trail platform will begin in Q4 2013, it is now clear that they will be released only between February and April, 2014, according to the slides. Despite of all advantages, when it comes to the PC world, Intel Atom "ValleyView" will be a year late when compared to AMD's code-named Kabini system-on-chip due, according to reports, in Q1 2013.</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1357392504048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 08:28:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357392684412-5</Id><Title>14nm in 2013? Umm 22nm not even in until 2013 means 14nm in 2016?</Title><Msg>Did Wally Snooker you? Newly leaked Intel slides reveal that the company's 22nm smartphone chip are delayed to Q1 2014 at the earliest. The lowest-power ValleyView chip is likely to be the Bay Trail-T, which offers a sub-3W TDP. The Bay Trail-M has a sub-4W to 6.5W TDP, while Bay Trail-D offers a sub-12W TDP. These chips are aimed towards tablets and budget notebooks. Full details can be read at DailyTech. To be fair, it did seem overly ambitious to somehow be able to jam out ValleyView/Silvermont in 2013. Not only is the release a die shrink, which adds the FinFET "3D" transistor design first employed in 2012's Ivy Bridge personal computer chip release, but it also adds other features like a seventh generation graphics core (with DirectX 11 support). Also added is support for DDR3L (the low powered version of DDR3 for mobile devices), USB 3.0, and on-die security/authentication features. The chip also undergoes important structural changes; most notably, the current CedarView is comprised of 2 SoCs (processor+chipset), while the ValleyView brings the chipset onto the processor die, unifying the two chips into a single die. The chip will also be the first Atom to be offered in a quad-core variety.</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1357392684412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 08:31:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357392743284-6</Id><Topic><Title>14nm in 2013? Umm 22nm not even in until 2013 means 14nm in 2016?</Title><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1357392684412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 08:31:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction, 22nm not even until 2014 !</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1357392743284</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 08:32:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357392743285-7</Id><Topic><Title>14nm in 2013? Umm 22nm not even in until 2013 means 14nm in 2016?</Title><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1357392684412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 08:31:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction, 22nm not even until 2014 !</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1357392743285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 08:32:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357400568597-8</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Next-Gen Atom "ValleyView" to Double CPU Performance, Triple Graphics Performance</Title><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1357392281488</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 08:24:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Kabini" will be going up against low wattage Celeron and Pentium chips, NOT ValleyView.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1357400568597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 10:42:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357404346340-9</Id><Title>Don't let the Intel pumping confuse you.....</Title><Msg>Big.Little by Krysto on Friday, January 04, 2013 Cortex A15 coupled with Cortex A7 will use half the power on average. Also, I told you before that Mali T604 is more efficient than PowerVR in the latest iPads, and that's why Apple managed to use a more powerful GPU - because it's more inefficient. They sacrificed energy efficiency for performance, because they can use a very large battery in the iPad. I saw you're trying hard to "prove something" about Intel lately, and I'm not sure why. Is Intel is biggest "client" when they pay you for reviews here? Is that why you're trying so hard to make them look good? You're also always making unebelivable claims about what Intel chips will do in the future. Even if they get Haswell to 8W (is that for CPU only? The whole SoC? Is it peak TDP? Will it still need fans?), you do realize a Haswell chip costs as much as the whole BOM of an iPhone 5 right? Haswell chips will never arrive in smartphones, or in tablets that are competitive on price.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357404346340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:45:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357404653972-10</Id><Topic><Title>Don't let the Intel pumping confuse you.....</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357404346340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:45:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RE: Big.Little by mrdude on Friday, January 04, 2013 He's spot on about the pricing issue, though. Intel isn't going to start selling Haswell SoCs for $30, and if they do then they'll quickly go out of business. It's a completely different business model that they're trying to compete with. The Tegra 3 costs $15-$25 (and way closer to that $15 to date) while Intel charges $70+ for their CPU+GPU, and that's before you get to the chipset, WiFi and the rest. A low-TDP Haswell chip might offer great performance and fit in the same form factor (tablets), but if the tablet ends up costing $800+ and isn't Apple, well... nobody cares. It's not just a matter of performance but performance-per-dollar and design wins. Intel can't afford to drop prices to competitive levels on their Core products unless they can supplement it with very high volume. For very high volume you need to sell a lot of competitive SoCs that can do it all at a very reasonable price. The Tegra 3 was a big success not because it was an amazing performer, but because it offered decent performance for a very low price tag. Can Intel afford to do that with their cash cow business slipping? Remember that x86 seeing drops in sales and PCs aren't exactly doing very well right now. Intel already had to drop their margins and they've let fabs run idle and sent home engineers at their 14nm fab in Ireland all the while processor prices haven't decreased even a tiny bit. Those aren't signs of a company that's willing to compete on price</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357404653972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:50:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357404756105-11</Id><Topic><Title>Don't let the Intel pumping confuse you.....</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357404346340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:45:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RE: Big.Little by Krysto on Friday, January 04, 2013 "One reason the Pro version of the device will be more expensive is that it uses a PC-style chip from Intel Corp. INTC -0.87% (INTC), part of a family of chips that sells for between $177 and $225. The Nvidia Corp. NVDA +3.48% (NVDA) chip typically used in the Surface RT model costs about $28, according to an estimate by research firm UBM TechInsights." http://blogs.wsj.com/digits/2013/01/04/windows-8-f... iPhone 5's BOM is $188. iPad 3's BOM was $160. I wish Intel good luck if they think they are going to have competitive devices on the market where the chip alone costs as much as all the components in iPads and iPhones. Oh, but that's just for IVB chips. Did I mention Haswell will be 40% more expensive - so Haswell chips will be more like $250-$300. Yeah...good luck with that Intel.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357404756105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:52:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357404783795-12</Id><Topic><Title>Don't let the Intel pumping confuse you.....</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357404346340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:45:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RE: Big.Little by mrdude on Friday, January 04, 2013 While you may be willing to fork over that much cash, most people won't. If you don't believe me, check out the recent sales figures of Win8 devices. The Win8 tablets (excluding Surface RT) don't even make up 1% of all Win8 products sold. That's not poor, that's absolutely horrible. On the other side the cheap Android tablets and smartphones have been gaining significant market share and outselling even the iPhone and iPads. Price matters. A lot. Furthermore, device makers/OEMs are more likely to go with the cheaper SoC if the experience is roughly equal. Remember that a majority of tablet and smartphone buyers don't browse Anandtech for benchmarks but buy based on things like display quality or whether it's got a nice look (or brand name, in the case of Apple). If an OEM can take that $60 saved and put it towards a better display, a larger battery or more NAND then that means a lot more in differentiating yourself from the competition than being 10-15% faster in X benchmark. People forget that these are SoCs and not CPUs. They also forget that these aren't DIY computers but tablets. Think about how much people complain when they see a $900 Ultrabook with a #$%$ 1366x768 TN display but those same people don't utter a word about how Intel's ULVs cost the same as their 35W parts. If the Intel chip was cheaper you'd probably have a better display or a cheaper price tag. This same notion extends to tablets and smartphones. Qualcomm is in a place where they can offer something everybody wants; their LTE is second to none. What does Intel have to offer to warrant Intel prices? Currently Intel's chipsets cost as much as an entire Tegra 3 SoC. x86 PC/server and ARM SoCs are in a completely different universe when it comes to pricing, and unless you've got something special (see Qualcomm or Apple) or you're making and selling the device (Samsung), then you're going to have a very rough time of it.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357404783795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:53:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357404846204-13</Id><Topic><Title>Don't let the Intel pumping confuse you.....</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357404346340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:45:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RE: Big.Little by mrdude on Friday, January 04, 2013 Win8 and its devices aren't selling, so I'm not sure how Intel plans on suddenly making that OS and the products that run on it any better. Like I said, Win8 tablet sales have been really really poor. And as far as consumers go, it is directly competing with the iPad and Android. People are more inclined to buy a new shiny tablet than a laptop and they could care less for x86 compatibility. For your average user, the iOS app store has thousands of more applications than your x86 desktop if only for the fact that it makes it incredibly easy to search through, install and play with. x86 compatibility means very little to most folks, and you can argue that it's actually a detriment due to the x86 legacy's inherent safety issues (non-Metro) and higher prices. The "It's also a PC" shtick only works if people want PCs. Judging by the sales figures and the longer upgrade cycles, Win8's sales figures, it's clear they're obviously aren't that interested.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357404846204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:54:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357405197887-14</Id><Title>Should you listen to Wallisweaver, Marsavian, Semi-conductor guy or Alexander D.?</Title><Msg>RE: Big.Little by Ananke on Friday, January 04, 2013 They can't compete on pricing with x86 vs ARM. I'm in the business, I know. Intel has absolutely competitive process facilities. If they were strictly making chips, nobody can beat them. If they license the design and make chips - nobody can beat them either. However, coupling the own design R&amp;D expenses with own production, and their cost is higher. Products might be better, but cost is higher. On the marketing side, only price matters today. You may think performance is important, but in reality it defines 1% of the decision of 1% of the market.... Hence, the trend towards ARM designs. That trend was not accidental, it is structural, and I see no reason it will turn around. It is the reason why AMD is performing so poorly, just Intel is much larger and owns its fabs, it takes longer to become obvious they will have revenue problems.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357405197887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:59:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357405460086-15</Id><Topic><Title>Should you listen to Wallisweaver, Marsavian, Semi-conductor guy or Alexander D.?</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357405197887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, but... by jemima puddle-duck on Friday, January 04, 2013 Impressive though all this engineering is, in the real world what is the unique selling point for this? Normal people (not solipsistic geeks) don't care what's inside their phone, and the promise of their new phone being slighty faster than another phone is irrelevant. And for manufacturers, why ditch decades of ARM knowledge to lock yourself into one supplier. The only differentiator is cost, and I don't see Intel undercutting ARM any time soon. The only metric that matters is whether normal human beings get any value from it. This just seems like (indirect) marketing by Intel for a chip that has no raison d'etre. I'm hearing lots of "What" here, but no "Why". This is the analysis I'm interested in.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357405460086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:04:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357405545706-16</Id><Topic><Title>Let Us Not Forget</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357328528700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 14:42:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As a general rule stocks don't trade on their past, they trade on their future. Intel's future guidance and comments are more important than if they miss or meet or even beat.</Msg><Username>repklikint</Username><Timestamp>1357405545706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:05:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357405666928-17</Id><Topic><Title>Should you listen to Wallisweaver, Marsavian, Semi-conductor guy or Alexander D.?</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357405197887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It even gets sadder by Veteranv2 on Friday, January 04, 2013 Another Intel PR Article, it is getting really sad on this website. Now since you are still using Win8 which is garbage for ARM. Please us the correct software platform for ARM chips. I'd love to see those power measurements then. Anandtech did it again. Pick the most favorable software platform for Intel, give the least favorable to ARM. Way to go! Again.... Intel PR at its best...</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357405666928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:07:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357405956255-18</Id><Topic><Title>Should you listen to Wallisweaver, Marsavian, Semi-conductor guy or Alexander D.?</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357405197887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Consider by mugiebahar on Friday, January 04, 2013 While I always enjoy reading here, I have to admit this article is not 1 of them. I'm not slinging mud or anything but rather I think it's highly subjective to consider @ this point intel is in good standing to make in roads. I agree intel has the technology/money/resources/will power to make a killer chip that sips power better then anyone. But as so many have pointed out and cannot be changed, Intel doesn't have the ability to do it for a cheap competitive price. ARM has always will always be better in that. It's all about how a company is built. ARM doesn't need to finance a foundry much less several like intel. With over head and size comes problems changing business models, especially in manufacturing. The thing is while we don't know yet what the future holds as to the amount of things we will do on a phone, I can guarantee I won't be ripping a DVD, making CAD drawings on it. So fundamentally we will hit a wall that the cost is not worth the money. Am I wrong? While I know what the article is pointing to, which is a strong class leading, watt sipping intel. But they cannot win or be as noteworthy as the article points out. You can't ask a company to devalue their products, Why? Because you lose either because 1) you look desperate or 2) you acknowledge that you where ripping people off before. While they may have had legitimate reasons for pricing, or that technology brought prices down its perception that's the killer. Is Atom bad? No. But ask regular joe, he'll tell you it's #$%$ but why? Price and perception. Intel did something's right and sme wrong. They should have realized a while back desktops were good enough and push mobile chips to the better lower cost production. But now a company so heavy on top can switch just like that. Now ether they will have to restructure to be competitive in the mobile arena or just play second fiddle. But they can't right now (unless they change) be a mobile king as they are on the desk top only because of company structure nothing else.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357405956255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:12:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357406050117-19</Id><Topic><Title>Should you listen to Wallisweaver, Marsavian, Semi-conductor guy or Alexander D.?</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357405197887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ntel PR by UpSpin on Friday, January 04, 2013 Intel PR, nothing more. This article is misleading, confusing and compares totally different things. It's a shame to see such a bad written article on Anandtech, full with meaningless, misleading, graphs, which just sit there, without any further descriptive text. If a image isn't worth some text, it isn't worth to get shown at all! 1. There's no use in showing and even comparing Total Power Consumption numbers, because the systems are totally different. So don't show them! Everything else is misleading, most probably on purpose because the absolutely low-end Intel device looks good in this comparison, logically. But please, if you can't compare things, don't try to compare them. And if you can't compare them, also don't further use such numbers, like in Task Energy Total Platform. It's useless. You can't measure Qualcomm chips correctly, thus include Total Platform power draw? Poor excuse. If you can't measure it, don't post it, but don't post false and misleading numbers. 2. What is Average Power Draw? What's the use of it? You don't use those graphs in your Article at all! Do you know what this means? Exactly: Those graphs are useless and meaningless. Why do you post them? They are redundant because of the Energy graphs. So naturally, because of the much shorter run time of the A15 SoC, the Average graph looks disadvantageous for ARM, which is simply misleading. But well Intel is probably happy you posted hit and thanked you with cash, why else should a sane person post such misleading stuff. 3. GPU Power: What game? How did it run? Off-Screen? The same resolution on every tablet? The same API? The same FPS? It's not surprising that a low-end GPU struggling to keep maybe 10FPS consumes less power than a high-end GPU displaying 60FPS at a higher resolution. You haven't said anything about this issue, yet happily compare meaningless numbers. I'm sorry but this article is, right now, garbage. And the only reason for posting such a poor written article is that Intel must have paid you a lot of money for doing so. It's nice that you post such semi-scientifical articles, but the way you do in this case isn't great. This article is very very hard to read, because the reader has to do ALL the interpretation. You could remove 2/3 of all graphs, and the article would contain the same information. By just looking at the graphs Intel is the overall winner, which is, if you do some further comparisons based on your article wrong. At most Intel is, according to your graphs, on par with A15, CPU wise, which still is a nice outcome for Intel. The GPU is awful in the Intel SoC, the CPU competive. The A15 GPU is perfect, the CPU at least as efficient as the Intel one, but much faster. Yet, because the article is so confusing and I don't want to waste any further time doing the work a good writer should have done, I see ARM as the clear winner. Same or more efficient CPU, much faster CPU, much better GPU, overall winner! Similar argumentation for Tegra and Krait. Intel has a good CPU, but the SoC looks awful.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357406050117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:14:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357406090918-20</Id><Topic><Title>Should you listen to Wallisweaver, Marsavian, Semi-conductor guy or Alexander D.?</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357405197887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RE: Intel PR by powerarmour on Friday, January 04, 2013 "I see ARM as the clear winner. Same or more efficient CPU, much faster CPU, much better GPU, overall winner! Similar argumentation for Tegra and Krait. Intel has a good CPU, but the SoC looks awful." That was exactly my conclusion reading through it, I just couldn't be bothered to be eloquent enough to explain it like that as it seemed obvious to me. I look at the SoC as a whole, and apart from a 'slight' advantage on the CPU side in a few select (and likely x86 optimized) browser benchmarks, the Clover Trail SoC is really quite lacklustre.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357406090918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:14:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357408376997-21</Id><Title>INTC is going to have inventory and margin problems better sell before the big drop on earnings day. TIC TOC running out of time to sell</Title><Msg>INTC is going to have inventory and margin problems better sell before the big drop on earnings day. TIC TOC running out of time to sell. OH thats right just lower the forecast so they can beat it. LOL</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1357408376997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:52:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357410336491-22</Id><Topic><Title>ARM A15 is a Power hog according to Anandtech. Wont fit in smartphones.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1357340502444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 18:01:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how embarrassing.</Msg><Username>only_paper_money</Username><Timestamp>1357410336491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 13:25:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357410785937-23</Id><Title>AMD product was more power efficient - now they are powerhog</Title><Msg>ARM was much more power efficient, well not any more. Look like history will repeat.</Msg><Username>six_packers</Username><Timestamp>1357410785937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 13:33:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357410962559-24</Id><Title>Shorts are SCARED</Title><Msg>They have taken over the AnandTech comments section of the article and now they are copying-and-pasting those comments on this board. Most of the comments now revolve around how Intel can't compete in price. In the next few months that myth too will be busted. Shorts are running scared. The fact is, the AnandTech results are a MAJOR surprise to all the arm fannies and INTC shorts out there. All the power advantage they thought arm had has disappeared in thin air.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357410962559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 13:36:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357411957975-25</Id><Topic><Title>Don't let the Intel pumping confuse you.....</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357404346340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:45:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, you sure managed to repost a lot of sad but all inaccurate comments by some very upset ARM fanbois ;-). I can see this is a 'Conroe' moment for them, like it was for AMD fans when Conroe trounced Athlon64 and without the need of an on-die memory controller too, when they begin to realize the x86-ARM World dynamic is not how they visualized it to be and it has obviously devastated their egos ;-). I will answer all of them for you as you bothered to call me out in another post. ' I told you before that Mali T604 is more efficient than PowerVR in the latest iPads' Yeah sure at 4W it is very efficient lol. Power VR is the most efficient gpu architecture out there because it uses deferred tile based rendering which means only rendering the pixels that are visually seen so less work/power is needed by the gpu. 'Even if they get Haswell to 8W' They already have, notice the public demo last year. 'Haswell chips will never arrive in smartphones, or in tablets that are competitive on price.' Not true. There is a Sandy Bridge Celeron 867 in a $200 Chromebook. Obliviously these ARM fanbois have not observed the Celeronization of most of AMD's products, a process that has been under way for decades.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357411957975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 13:52:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357412514465-26</Id><Topic><Title>Don't let the Intel pumping confuse you.....</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357404346340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:45:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Intel isn't going to start selling Haswell SoCs for $30, and if they do then they'll quickly go out of business. ' Haswell ? No. Low power Haswell Celerons ? Easily and they would make money doing it. 'Intel can't afford to drop prices to competitive levels on their Core products unless they can supplement it with very high volume.' These clowns obviously think Intel only sells one cpu sku ;-). Intel can and will easily add low power Ivy Bridge/Haswell Celerons that are 50-100% faster than A15 but still fit in nicely with their present cpu price structures because the top line Core skus are 400-500% faster than A15 so there is plenty of room to fit these cheap Celerons in without affecting the price of the higher performance skus. Anybody would think ARM was a serious threat lol but I have always told you bashers it was no contest on the performance front and performance has and will always determine cpu price.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357412514465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:01:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357412722240-27</Id><Title>Shorts better cover Monday morning</Title><Msg>Read anandtech's new article. google with "anandtech power analysis" The trend is obvious... as arm tries to improve the performance on their chips, their power consumption increases. On the other hand, Intel is lowering the power consumption on their new chips while still improving performance. As it stands right now, the Cortex A15 (arm's latest and greatest) is consuming more power than a 5-year old Intel low-end Atom (Clover Trail) manufactured on a 3 year old process, and with only a small lead in performance. When Intel releases their Clover Trail+ in a few months, we will all of a sudden find that Clover Trail+ is beating the A15 in BOTH power consumption and performance. The new dual-core medfield will do the same in the smartphone market. What we will see is, smartphones with medfield inside will outperform arm's phones in both performance and battery life. Check the latest Antutu benchmark leaks for proof of this. Further off, in 2014, Intel is all set with Merrifield (for smartphones) and Bay Trail (for tablets) on 22nm FinFET process. In the cores, Broadwell will be ready on 14nm FinFET. Meanwhile, arm's fab are struggling to get to 20nm planar! There are serious questions on whether armv8 (A57) will make it's way into the market by 2015 let alone 2014.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357412722240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:05:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357412731132-28</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is going to have inventory and margin problems better sell before the big drop on earnings day. TIC TOC running out of time to sell</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1357408376997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:52:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just sold based on your comments. Called my broker at home and he bought my shares even though market closed. Your constant barrage of negative comments has left me scared chitless and terrified. Can't begin to count how many changes in underwear I've had to make. May also kill myself for good measure. You're always spot on and a credit to the human condition. Head over heels in love with Nuff. Nuff is god incarnate.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1357412731132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:05:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357413201405-29</Id><Topic><Title>Should you listen to Wallisweaver, Marsavian, Semi-conductor guy or Alexander D.?</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357405197887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unlike all the ARM foundries all the FABS that are producing Medfield/Clovertrail 32nm wafers would have been paid for by 32nm Sandy Bridge. All the 22nm FABS that will porduce BayTrail would have been paid for by Ivy Bridhge and Haswell. I can't think of a more cheaper way to get a leading edge wafer and as ARM is at least one generation behind prcoess wise what Intel is using on its mobile prioducts is leading edge for ARM vendotrs ;-). 'You may think performance is important' LOL, yeah customers are willing to give Intel billions of profits on their PC chips when there are much cheaper AMD/VIA alternatives because they are feeling charitable and not because they are willing to pay through the nose for the ultimate performance ;-). It would have been best if you hadn't had posted this clown's thoughts as he is probably the funniest of all of them ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357413201405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:13:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357413830815-30</Id><Topic><Title>Should you listen to Wallisweaver, Marsavian, Semi-conductor guy or Alexander D.?</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357405197887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM may not pay for the foundries but their vendors do by the price added on to the wafers to cover process development costs. Intel's mobile Atom chips are on fully depreciated n-1 process wafers already paid for by the PC chips. Like Otellini warned, Medfield will not be beaten on price and you better believe it because Intel's yields are among the best if not the best in the semi industry. East and his cocky ARMy has awakened a pleasantly sleeping 800lb Gorilla and he is not very happy about it and is charging his way full force now lol. Ask AMD how that story turns out in the end, a stock price that went from $42 to $2 in only a few years ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357413830815</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:23:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357414063433-31</Id><Topic><Title>Don't let the Intel pumping confuse you.....</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357404346340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:45:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hilarious to see all of the ARM fanbois coming out of the woodwork to moan, groan, whine, cry and complain about Intel having achieved power consumption parity so quickly. And given Intel's fabrication superiority they know that the future will snowball on them as Intel moves ahead in the power efficiency race, never to look back. Well except maybe to direct a Bronx cheer in the fanbois direction...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357414063433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:27:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357414241255-32</Id><Title>Here's why the margin and price myth will be busted</Title><Msg>by marsavian: Unlike all the ARM foundries all the FABS that are producing Medfield/Clovertrail 32nm wafers would have been paid for by 32nm Sandy Bridge. All the 22nm FABS that will porduce BayTrail would have been paid for by Ivy Bridhge and Haswell. I can't think of a more cheaper way to get a leading edge wafer and as ARM is at least one generation behind prcoess wise what Intel is using on its mobile prioducts is leading edge for ARM vendotrs ;-). [and the following: - Intel does not have to license from arm - Intel does not have to license the graphics as they have their own (starting with Merrifield and baytrail) - Intel does not have to license baseband from qualcomm as they have their own - Intel manufacture their own chips instead of fabless companies like qcom and nvida who have to pay fabs like tsmc - Intels products are better so they can price at premium]</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357414241255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:30:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357414384305-33</Id><Topic><Title>Should you listen to Wallisweaver, Marsavian, Semi-conductor guy or Alexander D.?</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357405197887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What;s this guy's problem, doesn't he have the intelligence to read a graph which BTW all revealed great granular information about all the cpu and gpus. 1. Total powe rconsumptions is very useful, it rwlls you wat your device is like when all the rubber hits the roasf. Only fanbois only interested ins coring points would not be interewsted like this clown. The only thing that ids garbage about this artcile is his stupid uninformned cpomments at the bottom of it. 'The A15 GPU is perfect, the CPU at least as efficient as the Intel one, but much faster.' LOL on all fronts. The PowerVR 544MP2 coming in Clovertrail+ (Z2580) will destroy the Mali T604 and at much lower power. A15 burns at least twice as much power as Atom and is sometimes beaten by it in benchmarks ! 'I see ARM as the clear winner' Yeah sure it is fanboi, keep the faith LOL !</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357414384305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:33:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357414429781-34</Id><Topic><Title>Don't let the Intel pumping confuse you.....</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357404346340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:45:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BAM, Louis!!! Wished I could have seen the look on the fanboi faces as they read this comment: "These clowns obviously think Intel only sells one cpu sku ;-). Intel can and will easily add low power Ivy Bridge/Haswell Celerons that are 50-100% faster than A15 but still fit in nicely with their present cpu price structures because the top line Core skus are 400-500% faster than A15 so there is plenty of room to fit these cheap Celerons in without affecting the price of the higher performance skus. Anybody would think ARM was a serious threat lol but I have always told you bashers it was no contest on the performance front and performance has and will always determine cpu price." [That's going to leave a mark...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357414429781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:33:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357414649616-35</Id><Topic><Title>Here's why the margin and price myth will be busted</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357414241255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:30:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh and cost will soar for arm's friends as fabs like tsmc and gf make transition to 28nm and below. Prices for mobile products will rise as a result giving Intel further advantage.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357414649616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:37:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357414815434-36</Id><Topic><Title>Don't let the Intel pumping confuse you.....</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357404346340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:45:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only a fool would constantly rate INTC a strong buy as Waldo the clown has forever, and only a tech geek would count on geekish developments as a predictor of stock price.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1357414815434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:40:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357414983927-37</Id><Topic><Title>Here's why the margin and price myth will be busted</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357414241255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:30:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's further commentary from marsavian: These clowns obviously think Intel only sells one cpu sku ;-). Intel can and will easily add low power Ivy Bridge/Haswell Celerons that are 50-100% faster than A15 but still fit in nicely with their present cpu price structures because the top line Core skus are 400-500% faster than A15 so there is plenty of room to fit these cheap Celerons in without affecting the price of the higher performance skus. Anybody would think ARM was a serious threat lol but I have always told you bashers it was no contest on the performance front and performance has and will always determine cpu price.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357414983927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:43:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357415335246-38</Id><Title>Merger</Title><Msg>Is it so crazy to think Apple and Intel would be a good merger?</Msg><Username>dusk000</Username><Timestamp>1357415335246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:48:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357415470045-39</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is going to have inventory and margin problems better sell before the big drop on earnings day. TIC TOC running out of time to sell</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1357408376997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:52:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't this comment similar to: "The problem is the forecast is for lower all year which is not good, No growth and lower margins". Have also noticed how lazy Nuff is, pasting the subject line into the body of the message. Here is a list of the recurring manure posted by Nuff, day in, day out, 24/7 ad nauseum: 1. Inventory problems 2. Low margins 3. Low growth 4. Problems with PC sales in general (microsoft &amp; tech in general prob. carrying over to Intel) 5. Apple not using Intel chips (ever) 6. Lower earnings forecast and actual low earnings causing huge price drop. 7. Oh, here's one of my favorites: a mysterious panic problem with trading during day generating for some odd reason only sellers and not a single buyer. 8. Fiscal cliff to hit and therefore Intel to get hammered. 9. Delays in new chip launches (possibly for several years). 10.. Here's one to expect in near future: debt ceiling to cause massive selloff.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1357415470045</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:51:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357415612092-40</Id><Title>What We Know Now: The Fanboi Rage Issue</Title><Msg>1.) ARM fanbois are ballistic about Intel getting big press on having evened up the power consumption race. The fear in the air is palpable. Expect this fear to spread to ARM shareholders and the ninnies on Wall Street who have bid ARM stock up to a ridiculous 74 P/E ratio. 2.) The economic rebound will lift Intel and negate the impact of Intel stock manipulation by Wall Street's largest firms: "A rebounding U.S. economy supports the case for equities in 2013, John Stoltzfus, Oppenheimer chief investment strategist, told CNBC this week. He ticked off a list of positives, including housing, auto sales, manufacturing, services and "decidedly supportive" monetary policy that make the current economic recovery "likely quite sustainable." 3.) Intel will get a major boost from both CES in January and the Mobile World Congress in February. Look for LTE in the US and lots of tablet news as Intel gets out of the gate quickly in 2013. CES starts on Tuesday with Intel working the press on Monday. Look forward to more news to make the ARM fanbois even more crazed. 4.) We know we are going to get news of a huge Intel deal or maybe more than one in the next 3 to 6 months. Will any of this break early, as in next week? Dunno, but you know it's coming...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357415612092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:53:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357415769647-41</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is going to have inventory and margin problems better sell before the big drop on earnings day. TIC TOC running out of time to sell</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1357408376997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:52:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly. The one man shill show trots out the same inventory, margin comments every single quarter. He ran out of new material years ago...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357415769647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:56:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357415960581-42</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now: The Fanboi Rage Issue</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357415612092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:53:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What I would give to see those fanbois' shell-shocked faces as they read the anandtech report.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357415960581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:59:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357416419786-43</Id><Title>Special Intel 'Ivy Bridge' chips to enable new laptops, tablets</Title><Msg>At CES, chip giant will discuss limited edition versions of its 3rd Generation Core processors that are Intel's most power efficient to date. Select ultrabooks and tablets from some vendors are expected.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357416419786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:06:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357416437239-44</Id><Topic><Title>ARM A15 is a Power hog according to Anandtech. Wont fit in smartphones.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1357340502444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 18:01:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'YIKES!!!' Like you I was actually shocked by this article. How power inefficient the A15 is and A9 too to a lesser extent as implemented by Nvidia. No wonder Qualcomm and Apple have been busy designing their own. Clovertrail is right up there with A6 and S4 for both performance and power efficiency clearly demonstrating there is nothing to prevent low power x86 processors. Intel say 1.7W TDP and it is clearly not a lie. Clovertrail+ (Z2580) is going to make a great phone chip this year with the same cpu but with a really competitive gpu and LTE and probably still around 2W unlike the Exynos5 4-8W power hog. I thought the moment of truth for the ARM pumpers/Intel bashers would happen with 22nm Silvermont but this 32nm Clovertrail(+) is good enough to make a serious statement in the market this year. I also thought that Haswell would be needed on the Core front but these low Power Ivy Bridges will be good enough, they will match A15 on power consumption but outperform it by 50-100% as well as being 64-bit and therefore have no 4 GB memory limit. The moment of truth has come for ARM much earlier than expected, they are about to see what real competition is like just like AMD, VIA, Tramsmeta, Cyrix etc have in the PC business and Intel has knocked down or out all of those opponents.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357416437239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:07:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357416473819-45</Id><Topic><Title>Should you listen to Wallisweaver, Marsavian, Semi-conductor guy or Alexander D.?</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357405197887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We will find out more on Monday at 1pm PT @ CES2013 Intel event. I think the event will be webcast. It was last year. That is one reason for flurry of bashing during the last couple days. The AnandTech article was eye-opening for many. "They can't compete on pricing with x86 vs ARM. I'm in the business, I know." If you are in the business then you know that your statement is not exactly accurate. Intel can compete on pricing. They chose to compete on value. There goal is to pile up the transistors on the chip and to create value for the customers. They will do that by putting more on the single chip, tightly control power, performance and then set pricing based on value. "If they were strictly making chips, ..." When the CPU, SoC or ... is in the final machine on the retailer's shelf, each CPU in that sysem has undergone ALL the same phases. People just confuse who the competitors are and fail to consider all the costs. They assign the cost of the ARM CPU out the foundry as the "cost of the CPU". There is additional engineering overhead that is part of that CPU beyond what the foundary charges. Intel customers will not have to staff those engineers (like QCOM, NVDA, ...) and can use the off the shelf parts. You have to be careful when assigning cost and price pressures. "However, coupling the own design R&amp;D expenses with own production, and their cost is higher. Products might be better, but cost is higher." The Intel cost may or may not be higher. You do not know the Intel cost, nor do I suspect that you know the actual other company costs. Even if you are "part of the business" you can only estimate these things. "You may think performance is important, but in reality it defines 1% of the decision of 1% of the market...." 1% of 1% is your guess. Right? My guess on decision elements .... not in any particular order except #1: 1. vendor (is it an Apple, Samsung, ....) of product that can basically do the job. 2. price ("cost" to them but not the "cost" to build the device) ... most won't buy if they can't afford (except maybe the guys) 3. is the product in front of me available. They won't buy a product that is not available 8-) and many won't wait for the back order to be filled 4. battery life ... makes a difference if say 50% different The reason that AMD is performing so poorly is that they misfired on several product designs. Big time.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1357416473819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:07:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357417234729-46</Id><Title>one against many</Title><Msg>Intel vs a whole bunch or people ARM/Broadcom/Qualcomm/Marvell/etc. It is the monolithic vs the diverse. It is a closed model vs an open model. An analogy would be Android vs Windows Phone. ARM IP model allows the customers greater share the revenue in the value chain and allows them greater opportunity of differentiation - much more important to un-Intel guys than squeezing last drops of performance out of a process. ARM is much smaller than Intel as a result of course. But look at the combined revenues of the names mentioned. A powerful coalition of the unIntel-igentsia</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357417234729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:20:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357418838989-47</Id><Topic><Title>one against many</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357417234729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:20:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is interesting that you used the analogy of Android vs. Windows Phone, when a better analogy would be android vs Apple and iOS. Like Apple's superior products, Intel will be equally successful in the mobile space by offering superior CPUs and SoCs.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357418838989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:47:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357418868675-48</Id><Topic><Title>Here's why the margin and price myth will be busted</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357414241255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:30:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's alexander#$%$ commentary: We will find out more on Monday at 1pm PT @ CES2013 Intel event. I think the event will be webcast. It was last year. That is one reason for flurry of bashing during the last couple days. The AnandTech article was eye-opening for many. "They can't compete on pricing with x86 vs ARM. I'm in the business, I know." If you are in the business then you know that your statement is not exactly accurate. Intel can compete on pricing. They chose to compete on value. There goal is to pile up the transistors on the chip and to create value for the customers. They will do that by putting more on the single chip, tightly control power, performance and then set pricing based on value. "If they were strictly making chips, ..." When the CPU, SoC or ... is in the final machine on the retailer's shelf, each CPU in that sysem has undergone ALL the same phases. People just confuse who the competitors are and fail to consider all the costs. They assign the cost of the ARM CPU out the foundry as the "cost of the CPU". There is additional engineering overhead that is part of that CPU beyond what the foundary charges. Intel customers will not have to staff those engineers (like QCOM, NVDA, ...) and can use the off the shelf parts. You have to be careful when assigning cost and price pressures. "However, coupling the own design R&amp;D expenses with own production, and their cost is higher. Products might be better, but cost is higher." The Intel cost may or may not be higher. You do not know the Intel cost, nor do I suspect that you know the actual other company costs. Even if you are "part of the business" you can only estimate these things. "You may think performance is important, but in reality it defines 1% of the decision of 1% of the market...." 1% of 1% is your guess. Right? My guess on decision elements .... not in any particular order except #1: 1. vendor (is it an Apple, Samsung, ....) of product that can basically do the job. 2. price ("cost" to them but not the "cost" to build the device) ... most won't buy if they can't afford (except maybe the guys) 3. is the product in front of me available. They won't buy a product that is not available 8-) and many won't wait for the back order to be filled 4. battery life ... makes a difference if say 50% different The reason that AMD is performing so poorly is that they misfired on several product designs. Big time.</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357418868675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:47:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357419654781-49</Id><Title>Look at Chump Wally Clever</Title><Msg>He has NO CLUE about the industry, the technicals, etc... He just copies and pastes any and all pro-Intel blogs he can. Good think he has Marsavian here to copy and paste. What a clueless, shameless Intel pumper</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357419654781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 16:00:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357419841548-50</Id><Topic><Title>ARM A15 is a Power hog according to Anandtech. Wont fit in smartphones.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1357340502444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 18:01:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The moment of truth has come for ARM much earlier than expected..." [Indeed. And one has to be impressed with Intel's efforts on pulling out all the stops to address the power consumption issues above everything else. We will now see those efforts bear fruit in terms of mobility market share...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357419841548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 16:04:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357420298716-51</Id><Topic><Title>one against many</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357417234729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:20:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One against Many. That's how the Server landscape looked 17 years ago when the lowly Pentium Pro was released onto the Server Market. Arrayed against it was the mighty Alpha, the powerful Power, the quick PA-Risc, the snappy Sparc, the mercurial Mips. All entrenched RISCs with rich powerful backers which along with the Mainframe chips had 100% of the Server market. So, as now with Mobile, Intel started with 0% marketshare and no rich backers. A funny thing has happened over those 17 years though, Intel out executed and out priced the entrenched competition. Now Intel x86 chips have both the majority of revenue and units in the Server market. The Riscs and Mainframes are still out there but they have been pushed back into niches. Don't be surprised if a similar outcome happens in the Mobile market over the next 17 years. There will be only so long customers will accept inferior performing products from established brands until they desert you then the snowballs soon turn into avalanches of fleeing customers. Notice has been served, x86 is coming for ARM from above and below, Core and Atom in a classic pincer movement. There will be casualties ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357420298716</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 16:11:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357420637524-52</Id><Topic><Title>Look at Chump Wally Clever</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357419654781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 16:00:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have "good enough" knowledge to get by :). Actually, I learned this trick today...from you...</Msg><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357420637524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 16:17:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357420655737-53</Id><Topic><Title>one against many</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357417234729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:20:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There will be casualties ;-)." [Fanbois, analysts, lucies, journalists and a ton of ARM (OMG the P/E is 74!!!) shareholders...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357420655737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 16:17:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357420933242-54</Id><Topic><Title>one against many</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357417234729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:20:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"one against many" [Unfortunately, the many don't work in ARM R&amp;D or ARM fabrication. And that's where they need them. No ARM finFET and no ARM 14nm production. And there won't be for many years, if ever...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357420933242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 16:22:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357421030551-55</Id><Topic><Title>Merger</Title><Username>dusk000</Username><Timestamp>1357415335246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:48:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone put a pencil to this and figure out what Intel shares would be worth? Personally thinking at least $100/share (if conservative). Many investors would be millionaires overnight. If Nuff bought, he could buy a woman and finally get laid.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1357421030551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 16:23:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357421490275-56</Id><Topic><Title>one against many</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357417234729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:20:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Through this distributed focus model, ARM is able to focus just on architecture of the core, the foundries on fabrication and the licensees on extending the core in the appropriate direction with their SOCs. Its not a one size fits all solution, which, while it can be better optimized, only operates at one point vs. many in the ARM. For example, in the next generation of chips coming from the ARM camp, you have Apple's A7 which is a completely unique design, Qualcomm's follow on to Krait and big.LTTTLE based Exynos 5 from Samsung. Three completely different chips tuned for different operating points all based on ARM from three solid chip designers. As you might have heard, the graphics core is becoming more improtant in the overall performance of the chip. This further favours ARM's model.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1357421490275</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 16:31:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357422675102-57</Id><Topic><Title>ARM A15 is a Power hog according to Anandtech. Wont fit in smartphones.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1357340502444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 18:01:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wbmw has done a nice analysis for all those graphically challenged ARM fanbois who need spoon feeding to understand graphical data ;-) investorshubDOTadvfnDOTcom/boards/read_msg.aspx?message_id=83095025</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1357422675102</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 16:51:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357431096757-58</Id><Topic><Title>one against many</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357417234729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:20:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One reason why Intel succeeded is they took their overhead and amortized it over a large number of devices. Much of the engineering is reused and processor parts are fused to make new products that match the market. Think about the words being used by Intel: CORE and UNCORE. I imagine that Intel has a couple cores and a couple of uncores that are then improved upon and optimized for particular products in narrow markets. Example: they probably have an UNCORE for their EX servers and an UNCORE for their EP workstations/servers and an UNCORE for their desktop clients and ..... The engineering is factored out of the industry into the Intel silicon. Example: In the 80286 and 80386 days, Compaq Computer would get an early CPU and their engineering staff would design a superior motherboard. Being first to market they could get a premium price for their systems. Intel began to put the glue logic onto a chipset and soon, the Compaq engineering staff could not beat the easily constructed Intel reference design by enough to warrant a premium. Compaq laid off or redeployed these engineers. Intel has accumulated sufficient IP to integrate the entire phone. Intel is able to amortise their engineering resources over a much larger number of chips and their overhead per device is low. The ARM market fragmentation is one of its strengths but it is also one of its weaknesses. Vanilla ARM is no match for Intel. ARM that is optimized by any company will have to amortise that extra cost over the number of devices manufactured. New Intel fabs have the same effect on early devices. Intel charges the fab cost to those devices until the fab is written off and then the "cost" drops.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1357431096757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 19:11:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357431703375-59</Id><Title>Give it up, haters</Title><Msg>I absolutely PROMISE you Intel would not have fab 42 coming online (most advanced Manufacturing facility in the world) if they hadn't already done the math on chips costs vs. their competitors. Just a stupid argument.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1357431703375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 19:21:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357432622335-60</Id><Topic><Title>Give it up, haters</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1357431703375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 19:21:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For me, one of the most telling decisions being made, is being made by the foundries. Their customers have pressured them to skip process nodes to narrow the lead that Intel has in the fab process. The foundries will eventually get to their target. They have low probability of doing it on their published schedules. The Intel words that strike terror and will not be repeated by any foundry: "the fastest ramp in our history" which are the words Intel repeats at each node.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1357432622335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 19:37:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357434682918-61</Id><Title>Intel's business practices...</Title><Msg>Dell * In 2006, Intel paid Dell almost $2 billion in “rebates,” and in two quarters of that year, rebate payments exceeded Dell’s reported net income * From 2001 to 2006, Intel granted Dell a privileged position vis-à-vis other computer makers in return for Dell’s agreement not to market any products from Advanced Micro Devices (“AMD”) (NYSE: AMD), Intel’s major competitor * Intel and Dell collaborated to market microprocessors and servers at prices below cost in order to deprive AMD of strategically important competitive successes</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357434682918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:11:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357434779768-62</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's business practices...</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357434682918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:11:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel threatened HP that it would derail development of a server technology on which HP’s future business depended if HP promoted products from AMD * Intel paid HP hundreds of millions of dollars in rebates in return for HP’s agreement to cap HP’s sales of AMD-based products at 5% of its business desktop PCs * In 2006, Intel and HP entered into an broader, company-wide agreement to pay HP $925 million to increase Intel’s shares of HP’s sales at AMD’s expense</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357434779768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:12:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357434831527-63</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's business practices...</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357434682918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:11:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel paid IBM $130 million not to launch an AMD-based server product * Intel threatened to pull funding for joint projects that benefited IBM if IBM marketed AMD-based server products * Intel pressured IBM to launch another AMD-based server only on an “unbranded” basis</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357434831527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:13:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357435281665-64</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's business practices...</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357434682918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:11:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One more reason AMD is going bankrupt. Intel makes better chips.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1357435281665</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:21:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357435530529-65</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's business practices...</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357434682918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:11:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Judge tosses claims in NY suit against Intel 12/9/2011 1:48 AM EST SAN FRANCISCO—A U.S. federal judge in Delaware Thursday (Dec. 8) dismissed several claims against Intel Corp. in an antitrust suit filed by New York's attorney general in 2009, according to an Associated Press report. The judge dismissed claims filed on behalf of individual computer buyers, ruling that the state lacked the statutory authority to bring the claims, according to the report. The judge also dismissed claims involving computer purchases made before November 2006, ruling that Delaware's three-year time restriction should apply, the report said. In 2009, Andrew Cuomo, then New York attorney general, filed a federal antitrust lawsuit against Intel, alleging that the world's No. 1 chip maker violated state and federal anti-monopoly laws.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1357435530529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:25:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357436060630-66</Id><Topic><Title>ARM A15 is a Power hog according to Anandtech. Wont fit in smartphones.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1357340502444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 18:01:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure works in the Chrome book nice, frankly awesome. Sorry you missin out.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357436060630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:34:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357436940811-67</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's business practices...</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357434682918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:11:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NY Attorney General Andrew Cuomo wanted to be Governor and a high profile lawsuit was the best way. NY agreed to drop the suit for Intel paying $6.5m for the lawyers that NY retained for the lawsuit. $6.5 million ????? The amount that the state of NY owed their If this had ANY MERIT, NY would have pushed forward.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1357436940811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:49:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357437113975-68</Id><Topic><Title>Give it up, haters</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1357431703375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 19:21:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The Intel words that strike terror and will not be repeated by any foundry: "the fastest ramp in our history" which are the words Intel repeats at each node." [Yes, it amazes me the information that Wall Street analysts apparently don't have access to. Intel ramped 22nm FinFET like a champ. ARM couldn't even get a decent ramp on 28nm planar. And statistics show that ARMs ramp is declining with each new process node. It's not difficult with Intel ramping up and ARM ramping down to see where this is going to end. It's going to end with ARM being the new AMD. ARM is the new AMD and PCs aren't dead, ARM is dead. We're just waiting for it to play out. This trend is going to have very rapid acceleration during 2013...] [Pretty sure that 2014 will be the year that all large Wall Street firms will offer a class to analysts entitled "What are Graphs and What do They Mean?" and another entitled "All about Fabrication - Not the Kind we do with the Media."]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357437113975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:51:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357437234304-69</Id><Title>Lenovo K5 with Intel Merrifield Dual-Core CPU and 5.5-Inch Full HD Display Leaks</Title><Msg>From SOFTPEDIA newsDOTsoftpediaDOTcom/news/Lenovo-K5-with-Intel-Merrifield-Dual-Core-CPU-and-5-5-Inch-Full-HD-Display-Leaks-318711.shtml It looks like Chinese handset maker Lenovo plans to launch a superphone next week at CES 2013, the K5. According to GizChina, Lenovo K5 will be powered by an Intel Merrifield dual-core processor clocked at 1.6 GHz – 2.0 GHz, which will be complemented by 2GB of RAM. The smartphone will be only 6.7mm thick and will ship with Android 4.2.1 Jelly Bean operating system out of the box. It will offer dual-SIM support and an impressive 13-megapixel rear photo snapper. Lenovo K5 will also sport a secondary 2-megapixel front-facing camera for video calls and a high-capacity 3500 mAh Li-Ion battery. Last but not least, the K5 will boast a 5.5-inch full HD capacitive touchscreen display (404ppi) and will be available for purchase for 3400 yuan, which is about $545 or €415.</Msg><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1357437234304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:53:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357437441648-70</Id><Topic><Title>Merger</Title><Username>dusk000</Username><Timestamp>1357415335246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:48:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMD will buy INTC at $3</Msg><Username>gh0613</Username><Timestamp>1357437441648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:57:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357437687219-71</Id><Topic><Title>Friday Apple Rumors: Alternate Choice (Intel and not TSMC!)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357354195078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 21:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will that bring INTC margin down significantly?</Msg><Username>gh0613</Username><Timestamp>1357437687219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 21:01:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357438934064-72</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K5 with Intel Merrifield Dual-Core CPU and 5.5-Inch Full HD Display Leaks</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1357437234304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:53:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holy cow. This is huge! Lenovo plus Merrifield. Amazing how fast Intel is moving! Seems like just yesterday Medfield came out and we are already moving on to bigger and better!</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1357438934064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 21:22:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357439107658-73</Id><Title>Woo Hoo more about Lenovo and Merrifield !!! LTE right from the start!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Lenovo aren’t known for their flagship devices, but this is all expected to change at CES where it is rumoured the Intel Merrifield equipped Lenovo K5 will be unveiled! When you think of manufacturers who really push the envelope and manage to keep crowds on the edges of their seats, Lenovo isn’t a someone who springs to mind, but according to sources close to the Chinese tech giant we should keep a close watch over them at CES! Thanks to a source on Weibo, we have learned that Lenovo will be launching a new flagship Android device at the show named the Lenovo K5. As you would expect the Lenovo K5 checks many of the same boxes as many of the 5-inch 1080 phones heading to market this year, but with the exception of dual-core Intel processor! image thumb5 Exclusive: Lenovo K5 Intel Merrifield, 5.5 inch, LTE Note 2 rival heading to CES It is expected the K5 will make use of the new dual-core Intel Merrifield CPU which was recently spotted in benchmarks running Android Jelly Bean 4.2.1, and managed a NenaMark score of 58.30 and an Antutu score of 31,612! Furthermore, it is expected that the dual-core Merrifield chip will support LTE right from the start! Unfortunately no images of the purported Lenovo K5 have been leaked, but further specification details reveal the phone will have a 5.5-inch 1080P display with 404ppi, 13 mega-pixel rear camera which can capture 15 photos per second and will measure in at less than 7mm! We’ll be watching this news closely!</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1357439107658</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 21:25:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357439495202-74</Id><Topic><Title>Friday Apple Rumors: Alternate Choice (Intel and not TSMC!)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357354195078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 21:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Intel margins are currently in the 60% range with 55% expected this quarter. TSMC margin is 45% as a silicon merchant. TSMC capacity, yield and historical performance are risks that would be different with Intel as the vendor. Those would have value to a company that needed their CPU on time and in appropriate quantity (Intel). Margins would probably move down from the 60% - 65% range down to the 55% to 60% range which is where they were when Intel was selling all the netbook Atom chips several years ago. It dropped to a low of 50% during the recessions but was at about 58% during the netbook peak. There is tremdous value to Apple by having access to Intel fabs. It would help them compete better with Samsung who is chewing into their iPhone market share. While Intel margins would move down if they became a foundry for Apple, the new revenue number would sky rocket. The lower margin % of the larger revenue number would more than offset. Intel will not fab for Apple without making a profit. Both the extra revenues and profit would be additive to Intel. That is the bogus argument that Covello makes. One of his unspoken assumptions is that Intel revenues remain constant. If so, his margin argument makes sense. For the last two years, his argument has been wrong.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1357439495202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 21:31:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357440158418-75</Id><Topic><Title>one against many</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357417234729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:20:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They all have to pay $$ for graphics licences, ARM licences, Fabbing... And none of these designs can be optimized for manufacturing. All these efforts will eventually fail, because they will all be INFERIOR chips which cost more.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1357440158418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 21:42:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357440468363-76</Id><Topic><Title>Friday Apple Rumors: Alternate Choice (Intel and not TSMC!)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357354195078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 21:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm starting to think it's going to be Intel and Apple, and I never thought that until now. I also think Intel is looking great even if they don't end up working with Apple. I have a feeling it IS going to be Apple with some sort of agreement that Intel won't put chips in Samsung phones.........or can they make such an agreement?</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1357440468363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 21:47:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357440847842-77</Id><Title>Intel Lexington headed to Kenya, India and very affordable</Title><Msg>Is Intel Lexington the INR 7,000 Intel-powered Android phone heading to India? We recently heard about Intel’s plans to launch Android phones for as low as INR 7,000 in the Indian market and now a report from Unwired View has come out with one such device that fits the bill perfectly. Codenamed Intel Lexington, it is supposed heading to Kenya, but that does not mean we cannot see it in India. From the looks of it, it seems like a reference design, so it is likely to launch with branding from some other company. There is no word on the specs, but looking at the image, we expect a 3.2 or 3.5-inch HVGA display and OS is likely to be Android 4.0 Ice Cream Sandwich.Intel Lexington1 Is Intel Lexington the INR 7,000 Intel powered Android phone heading to India? Apart from Motorola RAZR i, most of the Intel-powered Android smartphones have been based Intel’s reference designs like XOLO X900, so Intel Lexington makes perfect sense and Indian mobile manufacturers will be happy to re-brand it and sell it in the country for INR 7,000 or similar pricing.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1357440847842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 21:54:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357441158071-78</Id><Title>Making a Reference Design will make Intel Billions</Title><Msg>Intel Smartphone Reference Design Shortens Development Time January 11, 2012 The Android Phone Features a High-Resolution 4.03-Inch LCD Screen; Battery Life Is Expected to Be up to 8 Hours for 3G Voice Calls Intel’s Smartphone Reference design was getting a lot of attention at CES and may have finally put Intel firmly in the phone game. The Intel Smartphone Reference Design was developed to help reduce development time and costs for phone OEMs and carriers. The idea behind the reference design is to speed development time for phone manufacturers that, in turn, can focus on adding additional features and software. The phone features a high-resolution 4.03-inch LCD screen and is running Android Gingerbread OS on the company’s Medfield phone platform. A company representative said versions of the phone are also running Ice Cream Sandwich but none were being shown publicly at CES. Battery life on the reference phone, according to Intel, is expected to be up to 8 hours for a standard 3G voice call with standby power lasting up to 14 days. The phone also features a paparazzi-like “burst mode” that allows users to fire off 15 photos (from either one of two cameras on board) in about a second with 8-megapixel resolution. Mike Bell, general manager of Intel’s Mobile and Communications Group, joined Intel President and CEO Paul Otellini onstage at the CES keynote Tuesday afternoon to show the phone more broadly, but it was already getting the lion’s share of attention earlier in the day at Intel’s booth at the Las Vegas Convention Center. Otellini announced two new customers (Lenovo and Motorola) but it wasn’t clear whether either of these customers would be using the reference design as part of their go-to-market strategy. At a Credit Suisse conference last month, Otellini did say customers would be using the “guts” of the reference design in phones coming out later this year.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1357441158071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 21:59:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357441512442-79</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K5 with Intel Merrifield Dual-Core CPU and 5.5-Inch Full HD Display Leaks</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1357437234304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:53:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, everything my ARMH phone already does !! And mine costs way less !! Margarine squeazzing coming to Intel. Who is the carrier, tincan and string communications ? Way better stuff coming in April from Samwellhung. Stay stupid !! Stay backward!! stay Intel!!</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357441512442</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:05:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357441644885-80</Id><Topic><Title>Making a Reference Design will make Intel Billions</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1357441158071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 21:59:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mike Bell is truly a genius. The reference design approach to getting rapid adoption in the market is his origional idea.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1357441644885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:07:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357441753450-81</Id><Topic><Title>Friday Apple Rumors: Alternate Choice (Intel and not TSMC!)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357354195078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 21:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, when you can't beat em you better join them. Intel can't sell their own chips ...so they gotta build someone else's !!! Wow what a coup for ARMH technology !!!</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357441753450</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:09:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357441772042-82</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K5 with Intel Merrifield Dual-Core CPU and 5.5-Inch Full HD Display Leaks</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1357437234304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:53:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are MILLIONS and MILLIONS of people that hate both Apple and Samsung and Intel will start by getting those people and then eventually the phones will be so good and friends of friends of friends will hear about it/see it/play with it and it will snowball. Your hatred for Intel is hilarious because Intel is going nowhere and you can't stop it.</Msg><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1357441772042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:09:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357441877376-83</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K5 with Intel Merrifield Dual-Core CPU and 5.5-Inch Full HD Display Leaks</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1357437234304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:53:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder why they need a 3500 mAH battery. By comparison, the iPhone5 has a 1440 mAH battery. Not that is matters to the customer. After all they are getting an AnTuTu socre of 3 times what the iPhone gives so they don't care about a slightly heavier phone.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1357441877376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:11:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357442057352-84</Id><Topic><Title>Making a Reference Design will make Intel Billions</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1357441158071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 21:59:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder how much Intel will pay Lenovo and Moto to use their funky stuff ?? wink wink</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357442057352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:14:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357442106560-85</Id><Title>Fast and Furious</Title><Msg>News on Intel developments is coming in fast and furious. While the analysts imagined everyone at Intel sitting around wailing, "Oh,no the PC is dead!!!". obviously that wasn't the case. Intel was building a juggernaut line-up for 2013 and preparing to launch it on the world at CES next week. Yet more evidence that 2013 is going to be Intel's year...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357442106560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:15:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357442301441-86</Id><Topic><Title>arm's architecture is broken</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357345351920</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 19:22:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes yes yes so broken Intel may have to make arm chips. Wish I was that broken.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357442301441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:18:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357442417444-87</Id><Topic><Title>Fast and Furious</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357442106560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:15:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how much you down man ? sound like a lot...I mean for you.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357442417444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:20:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357442605735-88</Id><Topic><Title>Look at Chump Wally Clever</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357419654781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 16:00:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you usually pay for more than you need ?</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357442605735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:23:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357442750803-89</Id><Topic><Title>Fast and Furious</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357442106560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:15:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2013 is going to be the year of the Merrifield the chip that shattered people's perceptions of how much power could be stuffed into a smartphone. I don't think the 30K + AnTuTu benchmark number has sunk in yet. It's only when the get them in their hands will the feel the difference.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1357442750803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:25:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357442935003-90</Id><Topic><Title>ARM A15 is a Power hog according to Anandtech. Wont fit in smartphones.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1357340502444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 18:01:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ignorance level shown here is in a league of its own. ARMH is the glue for all the things Sammy, Apple, and the gang can do.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357442935003</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:28:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357443103637-91</Id><Topic><Title>Should you listen to Wallisweaver, Marsavian, Semi-conductor guy or Alexander D.?</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1357405197887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sell or short what they recommend.to buy...see they have some value.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357443103637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:31:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357443140604-92</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now: The Fanboi Rage Issue</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357415612092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:53:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fanboi rage continues to build as wave after wave of positive Intel news hits the wires. They know that ARM control over the mobility world is slipping away faster than they ever thought possible. Awwwwwwwwwwwwwwww, ain't that a shame...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357443140604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:32:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357443407934-93</Id><Topic><Title>Friday Apple Rumors: Alternate Choice (Intel and not TSMC!)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357354195078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 21:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An Apple/Intel deal would be for either foundry or parts. If it is for parts, Intel has a pricing and negotiating mechanism that they would probably follow. They have to be careful to stay on the legal side of the antitrust laws. If it is an Apple/Intel fabrication contract, it could be anything but it cannot constrain Samsung from anything like restricting who Intel could do business with. It would probably be structured to require a certain minimum number of wafers or parts and optional access to more without penalty. Intel is not foundry with standard pricing so any agreement is flexible.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1357443407934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:36:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357443919108-94</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now: The Fanboi Rage Issue</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357415612092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:53:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I read it and bought more ARMH immediately !!! How many more rumors and letdowns you got coming, this is some kind of rumor record, even for a shillitoe of your moral grade. How much you lost with this girl ?</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357443919108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:45:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357444222823-95</Id><Title>Paul Ottabeleaving, just could not deal with ARMH, he said ...let someone else try this !!</Title><Msg>The slush money was not working anymore !!</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357444222823</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 22:50:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357444813502-96</Id><Title>ALL the long pumpers have lost tons a dough...that is a fact.</Title><Msg>They gotta pump this outtadate co. What else they gonna do ?</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357444813502</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:00:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357444928862-97</Id><Title>The iWatch: An Early Indicator?</Title><Msg>It's difficult to regard the Apple-Intel iWatch rumor as anything other than positive for the Apple-Intel relationship. After all, why would Apple be interested in switching from ARM on a form factor of this size unless it's just a part of a larger consideration of using Intel going forward on a number of other products?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357444928862</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:02:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357445007871-98</Id><Title>sharing time for longs...how much are you down personally ???</Title><Msg>We all want to know about your long experience owning Intel. Did they pay you to buy it from the slush fund ? Please do tell.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357445007871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:03:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357445166758-99</Id><Topic><Title>The iWatch: An Early Indicator?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357444928862</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:02:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple does not need Intel. Can you understand this numbskills ?</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357445166758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:06:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357445195261-100</Id><Title>The iWatch Could Be The First Step In Apple's Plan To Kill The iPhone</Title><Msg>[What could be more positive than Apple working with Intel on the iPhone? That would be Apple working with Intel on the successor to the iPhone...] "Apple is reportedly exploring development of a watch-like product. Small-minded people will scoff at the idea of Apple building a watch. After all, who needs watches when you have a smartphone. Further, Apple is a company with $200 billion in annual revenue. A $100 watch which will sell in limited quantity is barely going to move the needle. While all of those are fair points, they're missing a much bigger picture. There is a line of thinking that the smartphone era will perish almost as quickly as it began. From businessinsider</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357445195261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:06:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357445329688-101</Id><Topic><Title>The iWatch Could Be The First Step In Apple's Plan To Kill The iPhone</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357445195261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:06:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There is a line of thinking that the smartphone era will perish almost as quickly as it began." [Oops, there goes ARM...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357445329688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:08:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357445531043-102</Id><Title>Sharing Time for Shorts</Title><Msg>How do you feel about being down 9 percent since Intel came off its recent low? Are you planning on hanging in as Intel moves back over 29? You shouldn't have to wait long...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357445531043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:12:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357445603292-103</Id><Topic><Title>sharing time for longs...how much are you down personally ???</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357445007871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:03:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some memories are painful, but this will help you learn. go intel go woohuu.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357445603292</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:13:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357446058513-104</Id><Topic><Title>Sharing Time for Shorts</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357445531043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:12:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally you da best little fabricator ...you are...HI Wallsters !! I missed you ...you told me you put me on ignore and that really hurt my feelings. I feel all better now we are budz again.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357446058513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:20:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357446112906-105</Id><Title>Intel Merrifield To Be Announced At 2013 Mobile World Congress</Title><Msg>Intel is not going to stay silent on the smartphone market. The technology giant is reportedly developing a special smartphone SoC processor known as Intel Merrifield. During the test using graphics benchmark application, NenaMark2, Intel Merrifield which used dual core technology capable of delivering 58 Fps. The new processor also showing a good performance while tested using the AnTuTu benchmark application, with 31612 points of result the outcome is 3 times better than the score achieved by the Galaxy S III and HTC One X which are powered by Tegra 3. Merrifield is rumored to be installed on Intel’s smartphone, Redhookbay, which allegedly will run on Android 4.2.1 Jelly Bean. Intel Merrifield is also rumored to run at the speed of 1.6 GHz to 2 GHz. For the graphics section, Intel Redhookbay is said to be powered by the PowerVR SGX 544MP. The smartphones was also allegedly to offer LTE (Long Term Evolution) connectivity. As quoted from Guru3D on Thursday (01/03/2013), SoC Intel is rumored to be announced at the 2013 Mobile World Congress in February.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357446112906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:21:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357446406294-106</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Merrifield To Be Announced At 2013 Mobile World Congress</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357446112906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:21:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you say margarine compression ? can ya ? better learn. Aint like sellin PCs with a monopoly and a slush fund ....ohno. VERY competitive and being fab a riific dont help much at all. Hi Wally .and his alter boy egos.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357446406294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:26:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357446497594-107</Id><Topic><Title>The iWatch Could Be The First Step In Apple's Plan To Kill The iPhone</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357445195261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:06:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kinda like da PC ?</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357446497594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:28:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357446628245-108</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Merrifield To Be Announced At 2013 Mobile World Congress</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357446112906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:21:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With 22nm, trigate and OOO all in place, I think its Intel's time to celebrate. 2103 is the year the power/performance/cost proposition of Intel's mobile chips crossed that invisible border.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1357446628245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:30:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357446890440-109</Id><Title>dear wally</Title><Msg>do u plan on buying the new watch ? uggh NO. how about the Intel TV ? uggh NO a intel phone ? well no, like the one I got a pc ? no , might get a tab though interesting.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357446890440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:34:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357447084935-110</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Merrifield To Be Announced At 2013 Mobile World Congress</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1357446112906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:21:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are u nuts? Intel is basically the mobile backbone with its servers targeting both cloud &amp; individual company data centers. Expect that business to grow from 20% of Intel's current profits to over 50% within 3 years. That alone makes INTC a $40 stock. Of course, none of the idiot analysts mention this when they trash Intel on a weekly basis.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357447084935</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:38:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357447228994-111</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts better cover Monday morning</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357412722240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:05:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM has no shot in the "PC" space - Haswell just made sure of that.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1357447228994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:40:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357447252714-112</Id><Title>what we now know : wally can cut and paste</Title><Msg>he is not much on thinking and stuff like that.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357447252714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:40:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357447397306-113</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts better cover Monday morning</Title><Username>bacbacker3</Username><Timestamp>1357412722240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 14:05:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow are you stoooopid and gullible. go intel gooooo</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357447397306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:43:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357447660360-114</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K5 with Intel Merrifield Dual-Core CPU and 5.5-Inch Full HD Display Leaks</Title><Username>cksrcn</Username><Timestamp>1357437234304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:53:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1357447660360</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:47:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357447926665-115</Id><Topic><Title>Give it up, haters</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1357431703375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 19:21:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ya think might a done sum figgurin and all that to see if it made a bit a sense ? wow thanks for the heads up. wooo hooo go intel</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357447926665</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:52:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357448186325-116</Id><Title>Wally, what other stocks you own ? I might wanna short them too !!!</Title><Msg>You have been so helpful in showing me what a barker Intel is....I mean you did not do it on purpose ..but from 27 to 21 has been pretty fun.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1357448186325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 23:56:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>