<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365826118056-1</Id><Topic><Title>Congress Guts STOCK Act</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1365824788342</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 23:46:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Submitted in the HOUSE by ERIC CANTOR (R) VA. Submitted in the SENATE by CHRIS #$%$ (D) of DE. QUICK, QUIET, BIPARTISAN, VOICE VOTE to overturn CONGRESSIONAL INSIDER TRADING LAW. 113th CONGRESS 1st Session S. 716 ------------------------------------------------------------------------------- AN ACT To modify the requirements under the STOCK Act regarding online access to certain financial disclosure statements and related forms. Be it enacted by the Senate and House of Representatives of the United States of America in Congress assembled, SECTION 1. Modifications of online access to certain financial disclosure statements and related forms. (a) Public, online disclosure of financial disclosure forms.— (1) IN GENERAL.—Except with respect to financial disclosure forms filed by officers and employees referred to in paragraph (2), section 8(a) and section 11(a) of the STOCK Act (5 U.S.C. App. 105 note) shall not be effective. (2) EXEMPTED OFFICERS AND EMPLOYEES.—The officer and employees referred to in paragraph (1) are the following: (A) The President. (B) The Vice President. (C) Any Member of Congress. (D) Any candidate for Congress. (E) Any officer occupying a position listed in section 5312 or section 5313 of title 5, United States Code, having been nominated by the President and confirmed by the Senate to that position.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1365826118056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:08:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365827201565-2</Id><Topic><Title>Congress Guts STOCK Act</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1365824788342</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 23:46:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am NOT US citizien but I called my GOP republican representative Jeff Denham around of December 2011 and urged him to pass the stock bill... Eric Cantor - a snake who's head needs to be cut off - and why you at it cut Reid's head off as well and feed it to the vulchers</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1365827201565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:26:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365828831865-3</Id><Title>You laugh at N Korea</Title><Msg>but the US is rotten to the bone - worse than Rome - you are a sick country Epic Failure by the Senate on Transparency Provisions in STOCK Act by Lisa Rosenberg April 12, 2013, 10:06 a.m. With little fanfare and even less disclosure, the Senate late yesterday passed a bill that will, if signed into law, gut the STOCK Act, a transparency measure enacted only a year ago. The STOCK Act’s history has been one of knee-jerk reactions rather than reasoned decision-making. Yesterday’s vote proved no different, with Senators overreacting and taking a hatchet to the law when a scalpel would do. The bill enacted last year would require already public financial disclosures of senior congressional and executive branch officials to be put online in order to prevent or root out insider trading. There were concerns that some provisions of the bill were overbroad and would put some government employees at risk. Rather than craft narrow exemptions, or even delay implementation until proper protections could be created, the Senate decided instead to exclude legislative and executive staffers from the online disclosure requirements. The sweeping exemption goes even farther than critics of the disclosure requirements requested. For those to whom online disclosure would still apply (the president, vice president, members of Congress, congressional candidates and individuals subject to Senate confirmation) the Senate bill made electronic filing of the information optional and struck the requirement that online information be searchable, sortable and downloadable, making even the disclosures that remain in the bill tepid and relatively unusable.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1365828831865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365828961707-4</Id><Title>ZTE Geek packs 2GHz dual-core Intel Clover Trail+</Title><Msg>I've seen about 50 tech articles on the ZTE Geek phone. And in general the press coverage of the IDF announcements has been huge. This is clearly one of the reasons why the IDC news didn't get much traction. IDF let everyone know where Intel is headed and its a very impressive road map. ARM doesn't even seem to have a road map for 2012. Their progress if it happens will all be 2013 and beyond. IDF trumped IDC. That's the story for this week. Hopefully the story for next week will be Intel guides higher in the midst of big new deal surprise announcements. Regardless, Haswell, Bay Trail, Airmont and 14nm FinFET volume production are on their way and the rest of the year is going to be on a ramp...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365828961707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:56:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365829144688-5</Id><Topic><Title>You laugh at N Korea</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1365828831865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:53:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm in complete agreement that the gutting of the Stock Act is totally despicable...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365829144688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:59:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365829314714-6</Id><Topic><Title>You laugh at N Korea</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1365828831865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:53:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>move to the DPRK, pack a lot of food before you go and learn to keep your thoughts to yourself. Enjoy.</Msg><Username>repklikint</Username><Timestamp>1365829314714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 01:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365842600599-7</Id><Topic><Title>(Ha, ha, ha...) ARM: 64-bit server chips shipping in volume late 2014 or early 2015.</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365803908903</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 17:58:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I were running a data center, I would let my competitors take the risk with ARM before I even venture into it. Especially when Intel seems to be in the forefront of delivering the best performance per watt with Avoton and its 14nm follow-ons. ARM 64-bit is DOA! ---- :) Even with 64bit ARM cores, the bulk of Intel's server sales will be safe. These 1/2U servers are for general workloads and Intel's CPU heavy model fits (virtualization etc). Microservers are a different matter as they are highly specialized and focused on specific workloads. Here 64bit isn't as important. Even Intel's 64bit core can only address 8GB of memory - assuming it's fully loaded.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1365842600599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 04:43:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365844060872-8</Id><Title>Dividend to $1.00</Title><Msg>That seems plausible on P.O.'s departure celebration.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1365844060872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 05:07:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365845893541-9</Id><Title>Biggest catalyst for PC upturn is late Summer-Fall</Title><Msg>no one buys PC' s in the spring. It's a back-to-school, end of fical-year, through Christmas, season for PC's.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1365845893541</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 05:38:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365854351527-10</Id><Title>Servers</Title><Msg>Any Server sales Intel MIGHT lose in the future to Microservers it will easily offset in the growth of other Server business. So stop this "ARM is about to change the world" ignorance. It's just wrong and stupid.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365854351527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 07:59:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365857022446-11</Id><Topic><Title>Servers</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365854351527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 07:59:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check infosys latest quarter guidance....it is slow in servers too.</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1365857022446</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 08:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365857259059-12</Id><Topic><Title>(Ha, ha, ha...) ARM: 64-bit server chips shipping in volume late 2014 or early 2015.</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365803908903</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 17:58:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like a big threat to Intel, Great news for enterprise consumer with more and more players coming in to the area.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1365857259059</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 08:47:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365857954250-13</Id><Topic><Title>Servers</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365854351527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 07:59:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not a 2-bit daytrader like you bro. Growth of servers, cell phones, etc. over the next 5 years is going to explode.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365857954250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 08:59:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365858368786-14</Id><Topic><Title>Servers</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365854351527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 07:59:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We bought a some used equipment from a server farm that went out of business. The stuff is a few years old and works fine and cost very little. The used market is pretty vibrant.</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1365858368786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:06:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365858448132-15</Id><Topic><Title>Servers</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365854351527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 07:59:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just shut up. Your goal here is to use a bunch of aliases and be a little knat bothering people. You are irrevlevant. Cloud computing market: $241 billion in 2020 Summary: The global cloud computing market will grow from a $40.7 billion in 2011 to $241 billion in 2020, according to Forrester Research. By Larry Dignan for Between the Lines | April 22, 2011 -- 02:08 GMT (19:08 PDT)</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365858448132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:07:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365858991994-16</Id><Topic><Title>Servers</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365854351527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 07:59:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We bought a some used equipment ...." ------------------------------------------------------- you get what you paid for and will have some near terms issues for sure , just the same who ever sold you would buy new one.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1365858991994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365859100465-17</Id><Topic><Title>Servers</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365854351527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 07:59:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the mix will change from Intel first to Intel last. That is the problem. The new entrants will be literally pouring in soon. The big thing is most won't be Intel chips !! Cheers old chap</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1365859100465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:18:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365859204022-18</Id><Title>Samsung mass producing high-performance NAND Flash memory using 10nm-class process technology</Title><Msg>Samsung mass producing high-performance NAND Flash memory using 10nm-class process technology 04/11/2013 9 Facebook 6 Twitter 1 LinkedIn 16 Share Samsung has begun mass producing a 128-gigabit (Gb), 3-bit multi-level-cell (MLC) NAND memory chip using 10 nanometer (nm)-class process technology this month. This chip will enable high-density memory solutions such as embedded NAND storage and solid state drives (SSDs). “By introducing next-generation memory storage products like the 128Gb NAND chip, Samsung is extremely well situated to meet growing global customer needs,” said Young-Hyun Jun, executive vice president, memory sales &amp; marketing, Device Solutions Division, Samsung Electronics. “The new chip is a critical product in the evolution of NAND flash, one whose timely production will enable us to increase our competitiveness in the high density memory storage market.” Samsung’s 128Gb NAND flash is based on a 3-bit multi-level-cell design and 10nm-class process technology, which means a process technology node somewhere between 10 and 20 nanometers. It boasts the industry’s highest density as well as the highest performance level of 400 megabits-per-second (mbps) data transfer rate based on the toggle DDR 2.0 interface. Utilizing 128Gb NAND flash memory, Samsung intends to expand its supply of 128-gigabyte (GB) memory cards, which can store as many as sixteen 8GB full HD video files. Samsung said they now will also increase their production volume of SSDs with densities over 500GBs for wider adoption of SSDs in computer systems, while leading the transition of main storage drives in the notebook market from hard disk drives (HDDs) to SSDs. Demand for high-performance 3-bit MLC NAND flash and 128Gb high storage capacities has been rapidly increasing, driving the adoption of SSDs with more than 250GB data storage, led by the Samsung SSD 840 Series. Samsung started production of 10nm-class 64Gb MLC NAND flash memory in November last year, and in less than five months, has added the new 128Gb NAND flash to its wide range of high-density memory storage offerings. The new 128Gb chip also extends Samsung’s 3-bit NAND memory line-up along with the 20nm-class 64Gb 3-bit NAND flash chip that Samsung introduced in 2010. Further, the new 128Gb 3-bit MLC NAND chip offers more than twice the productivity of a 20nm-class 64Gb MLC NAND chip.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1365859204022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:20:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365859429279-19</Id><Title>doesnt idc report already tell u that earnings will be bad???</Title><Msg>i dont understand why ppl r still long....essentially their earnings have been released by idc....</Msg><Username>warmninja</Username><Timestamp>1365859429279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:23:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365860465279-20</Id><Topic><Title>doesnt idc report already tell u that earnings will be bad???</Title><Username>warmninja</Username><Timestamp>1365859429279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>idiot</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1365860465279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365860577286-21</Id><Topic><Title>Servers</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365854351527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 07:59:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeh, another amd type of a pipe dream. lol</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1365860577286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:42:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365860775792-22</Id><Title>Intel should be at 24</Title><Msg>IDC report threw cold water on the momentum. Hoping for a 2 day pop.</Msg><Username>dr.detroit403</Username><Timestamp>1365860775792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:46:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365860910932-23</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest catalyst for PC upturn is late Summer-Fall</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1365845893541</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 05:38:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IDC and Gartner measures are from the same period one year prior. They don;t include detachable keyboards or Windows surface devices, many of which use Intel chips. This biases the report against Intel. However the drop was so dramatic that even if you add the above devices you come up with a really dramatic intel chip drop off, way more than predicted.</Msg><Username>luvinitallwu</Username><Timestamp>1365860910932</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:48:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365861124901-24</Id><Topic><Title>doesnt idc report already tell u that earnings will be bad???</Title><Username>warmninja</Username><Timestamp>1365859429279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes the truth is irritating, but ninja is right. Actually you are the real idiot.</Msg><Username>wrightwhoe</Username><Timestamp>1365861124901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:52:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365861451357-25</Id><Topic><Title>doesnt idc report already tell u that earnings will be bad???</Title><Username>warmninja</Username><Timestamp>1365859429279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>doesn't the fact that they didn't warn tell you that earnings will be ok? Indeed, it's warmninja and wrightwhoe who are the idiots.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1365861451357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365865198198-26</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung mass producing high-performance NAND Flash memory using 10nm-class process technology</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1365859204022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:20:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sammy is Korea's national pride and Intels number one threat. Not ARMH, Not Qcom, not Nvidia, Sammy.yes.</Msg><Username>repklikint</Username><Timestamp>1365865198198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 10:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365866513944-27</Id><Topic><Title>Will Wally tell how far underwater he is on INTC ?</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365813657227</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 20:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>going deeper soon</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1365866513944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:21:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365871623284-28</Id><Topic><Title>Will Wally tell how far underwater he is on INTC ?</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365813657227</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 20:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Free markets or mixed markets will beat the religious nuts and their utopia just like it beat Mao and Stalinism....I think anyway.</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1365871623284</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 12:47:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365872273097-29</Id><Topic><Title>Will Wally tell how far underwater he is on INTC ?</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365813657227</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 20:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>one minute you post Hold the next is Sell. Make up your mind nitwit</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1365872273097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 12:57:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365872575468-30</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest catalyst for PC upturn is late Summer-Fall</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1365845893541</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 05:38:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The question is..have we hit bottom? I am betting we have, and of course the rear view mirror tells us we were in freefall..we all knew that. When INTC is in major ascent Wallis won't be seagulling all over ARMH in every post.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1365872575468</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:02:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365873124717-31</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend to $1.00</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1365844060872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 05:07:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>harlan, (and I know we've communed in different aliases, different i.d.'s), I am a later remake of gemanicus, my namesake, who was great but never quite made emperor...you know that only fecalis floats to the top..."sub fecalis subjugo." Yet, I was emperor for a few months after Nero. I bagged Otho, and Galba (put his head on a statue of naked Julia), both of whom claimed the throne and crown of olives, but Vespasian bagged me and reigned another 8 anni...Soon I hope to come back as Nerva...even though he was a short-lived guy...I don't think Iupiter is ready to give me Trajano.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1365873124717</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:12:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365873273573-32</Id><Topic><Title>Here is What I Would Be Worried About if I Were an Intel Short</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365784716553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 12:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great post</Msg><Username>lorryclayes</Username><Timestamp>1365873273573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:14:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365873301401-33</Id><Topic><Title>(Ha, ha, ha...) ARM: 64-bit server chips shipping in volume late 2014 or early 2015.</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365803908903</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 17:58:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice find</Msg><Username>lorryclayes</Username><Timestamp>1365873301401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:15:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365873432182-34</Id><Topic><Title>Intel XOLO X500 (based on low-end Intel Lexington Z2420) scores similar to premium Samsung Galaxy, HTC One, and Sony Experia phones</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365769812557</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 08:30:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It amazes me how quickly Intel got into phones.</Msg><Username>lorryclayes</Username><Timestamp>1365873432182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:17:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365873578348-35</Id><Topic><Title>Asus Fonepad (based on Intel Lexington Z2420) Now Available in South East Asia</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365772392431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 09:13:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good info thanks</Msg><Username>lorryclayes</Username><Timestamp>1365873578348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:19:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365873685359-36</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE Geek spanks the top Arm SoCs, scores 29401 in the Antutu benchmark</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1365688995556</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good for intel</Msg><Username>lorryclayes</Username><Timestamp>1365873685359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365874513717-37</Id><Topic><Title>doesnt idc report already tell u that earnings will be bad???</Title><Username>warmninja</Username><Timestamp>1365859429279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The MSFT Surface Pro is not a "PC" because it has a detachable keyboard. The Dell XPS-12 is not a "PC" because it has a detachable keyboard. The pick-your-system is not a "PC" because it has a detachable keyboard. I can think of a couple million reasons why the IDC report may already be reflected in the Intel forecasts and in the share price. In March 2009, the Intel share price hit a low of $12.41 when the PER SHARE numbers were much lower than they are today. With larger revenues and profits AND 25% fewer shares than in 2009, many of the longs think that the current share price already reflects a more negative picture than is being painted. From wpcentral ... One thing to note about these IDC numbers is how they define a ‘PC’. Shipments of PCs fell 13.9%, but how does the IDC define a PC? Like this: "PCs include Desktops, Portables, Mini Notebooks, and Workstations and do not include handhelds, x86 Servers and Tablets (i.e. iPad and Android-based Tablets with detachable keyboards). Data for all vendors are reported for calendar periods." That means tablets and hybrids running Windows 8 were left out of the count for PCs. Devices like the Surface RT and Pro weren’t considered by the IDC to be PCs in their tally. While sales of these devices wouldn’t offset the decline of 13.9%, they would have helped improve the figure and give a better outlook. Personally I see any device running Windows 8 as a PC, so it’s odd to not consider the Surface Pro or ThinkPad Tablet 2 in those numbers.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1365874513717</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:35:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365874982288-38</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE Geek (Atom Z2580 Clovertrail+) smartphone is smoking fast, spanks the top ARM SoCs</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365680605869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 07:43:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. can wait to see bay trail</Msg><Username>lorryclayes</Username><Timestamp>1365874982288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:43:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365875088999-39</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE Geek spanks the top Arm SoCs, scores 29401 in the Antutu benchmark</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1365688995556</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No they wont. They are all going to do well. The whole sector. Every bodys doing special chips for the server market.arm is going to kick #$%$ watch.</Msg><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1365875088999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365875405491-40</Id><Topic><Title>(Ha, ha, ha...) ARM: 64-bit server chips shipping in volume late 2014 or early 2015.</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365803908903</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 17:58:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't the 8GB memory limit rather easy to expand in a release of a new part where Intel connects another address bit to a PIN? Would it be possible for one of the current Atom S12xx CPU to already have the address line implemented but no bonded connection from the die to an external pin ? I would not be surprised if the current Atom parts already support a larger memory space but the extra address lines are disable by a currently ground pin.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1365875405491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365875464190-41</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung mass producing high-performance NAND Flash memory using 10nm-class process technology</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1365859204022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:20:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel can't compete with Sammy just like Appley can't complete.</Msg><Username>bobbassiet</Username><Timestamp>1365875464190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:51:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365877359485-42</Id><Title>PC sales look like krap</Title><Msg>Everyone scooping up smartphones and tablets. PCs arent good for much anymore. Will become extinct in 10-15 years. By by Intel.</Msg><Username>stjdavis7</Username><Timestamp>1365877359485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:22:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365877463977-43</Id><Title>It hasnt done anything in 13 years</Title><Msg>Despite spending hundreds of billions on new fabs. Can you see where this is going?</Msg><Username>stjdavis7</Username><Timestamp>1365877463977</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:24:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365877514853-44</Id><Topic><Title>Here is What I Would Be Worried About if I Were an Intel Short</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365784716553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 12:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at a 20 year chart of Intel and you will see that shorts have nothing to worry about.</Msg><Username>stjdavis7</Username><Timestamp>1365877514853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365877958101-45</Id><Topic><Title>Here is What I Would Be Worried About if I Were an Intel Short</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365784716553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 12:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>come back Tuesday after hours</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1365877958101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:32:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365878027656-46</Id><Topic><Title>It hasnt done anything in 13 years</Title><Username>stjdavis7</Username><Timestamp>1365877463977</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:24:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"can you see where this is going"? Where is AMD now?</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1365878027656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365878083270-47</Id><Topic><Title>Here is What I Would Be Worried About if I Were an Intel Short</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365784716553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 12:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wally, get off the pipe man. Whew you got some real bad stuff, you get that on a street corner? and please disclose all your holdings just like you expect of your government officials.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365878083270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365879020714-48</Id><Title>Asus Intel smartphone coming this summer. New Nexus 7 tablet out in May with better specs?</Title><Msg>unwiredviewDOTcom/2013/03/18/asus-intel-smartphone-coming-this-summer-new-nexus-7-tablet-out-in-may-with-better-specs/ The FonePad apparently wasn’t a one-off partnership between Asus and Intel. The Taiwanese device maker seems to have grown pretty fond of the company sometimes nicknamed Chipzilla, and is planning on releasing at least one more device powered by an Intel processor. It will be a high-end smartphone. The Intel Atom Z2580 (Clover Trail+) will be inside. This has so far been Intel’s most high performing mobile chipset, by quite a margin. It’s expected to debut in the Lenovo K900 which should go on sale in China next month. And now we have another contender in the ‘Intel inside’ smartphone space. The Asus offering will sport a 5 to 5.5 inch touchscreen, according to the infamous “sources from the upstream supply chain” that DigiTimes loves to quote. The new Asus phone will be released in June at the earliest. If there won’t be a tablet attached to it in any way (say, a tablet dock a la the PadFone series), this could in fact be Asus’ first foray into the standalone smartphone business. And with a high-end offering priced well, it may make quite a splash in the market. But obviously we’ll have to wait and see. Also in rumorland, word is getting out that there will be a next generation Nexus 7 tablet coming from Asus. It will be more expensive than the current model ($249 compared to $199), but it will come with “enhanced specifications”, whatever that could mean. We’re hoping the $50 price bump, if real, will be easy to justify by the new device’s innards. This new Nexus 7 could be out in May, and if that’s correct, then we expect it to be unveiled during Google’s I/O developer conference that same month. [An intel phone with PadFone tablet dock...running Windows 8? Now that would be cool!. Also maybe new Nexus 7 will have Bay Trail inside, timing is right.]</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1365879020714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:50:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365879318456-49</Id><Topic><Title>Asus Intel smartphone coming this summer. New Nexus 7 tablet out in May with better specs?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1365879020714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:50:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would not be surprised to see next nexus 7 running dual boot (android and windows 8)</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1365879318456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:55:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365879387117-50</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC won't have 16nm in full production until 2016 - if everything goes according to plan</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1364955238060</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 22:13:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like this post!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1365879387117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:56:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365879541050-51</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE Geek spanks the top Arm SoCs, scores 29401 in the Antutu benchmark</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1365688995556</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK i will argue with you. 2 companies make almost all the money in smart phones...Apple and Sammy. See HTC, BB, Moto, yaddayadda...they are hanging by a thread. Apple and Sammy aint changing chipps any time soon. Hitting the speeds and price points will be a game of leap frog, Apple and Sammy like to tweak ...they don't like each other and they don't like Intel very much. What happens in the Chinese and non US is a variable I gotta give you that. I know Medatek is big in India (Armh), China I don't know what is going on.Business is more than having the tech.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365879541050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:59:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365880310226-52</Id><Topic><Title>It hasnt done anything in 13 years</Title><Username>stjdavis7</Username><Timestamp>1365877463977</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:24:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>13 years ago, Feb. 2000, ARMH, adjusted for splits, was trading at $48 per share. 13 years ago, Jan 2000, QCOM, adjusted for splits, was trading at $78 per share. 13 years ago, Jan 2000, AAPL, adjusted for splits, was trading for $27 per share. ED was trading at $17 and now $61. JNJ was trading at $34 and now $84. PG was $42 and now $80. IBM was $101 and now $212 "Can you see where this is going?" I think the true answer to his question is "Past performance is not indicative of future results".</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1365880310226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:11:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365880903660-53</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE Geek spanks the top Arm SoCs, scores 29401 in the Antutu benchmark</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1365688995556</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are one confused idiot...first you say "Hitting the speeds and price points will be a game of leap frog" and then you end with "Business is more than having the tech."? which one is it bonehead? High-tech is about making things better and better, making the impossible possible. Having the better performing product wins in this business. Open you eye shorty! Intel's chips are beating arm with 5 year-old architecture on depreciated process 32nm.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1365880903660</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:21:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365882214794-54</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE Geek spanks the top Arm SoCs, scores 29401 in the Antutu benchmark</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1365688995556</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok wally, you will see after earnings. You will learn the old fashion way now....losing money.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365882214794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:43:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365882484103-55</Id><Title>is Vindumbnuts Waldo's alter ego ?</Title><Msg>He is pretty confused how business works too and also likes to eat too many doughnuts. What else is he doing with the doughnut hole ?</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365882484103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:48:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365882592464-56</Id><Title>Intel set to collapse?</Title><Msg>Intel factories signal Windows 8, PC doldrums Low utilization rates at Intel factories are a sign of bad times for the PC industry. by Brooke Crothers April 12, 2013 2:51 PM PDT President Obama visits Intel&amp;#39;s Chandler Arizona facility last year when Fab 42 was being built. President Obama visits Intel's Chandler Arizona facility last year when Fab 42 was being built. (Credit: whitehouse.gov) Intel isn't churning out chips at the usual rate, reflecting the PC market's downturn and the slow uptake of Windows 8, according to an analyst. Intel's factory utilization is down around 60 percent, well below normal, said Jim McGregor, principal analyst for Phoenix based Tirias Research, in a phone interview. The news was first reported at ITWorld. "A lot of this started in September when holiday shipments of PCs didn't go the way they expected," McGregor said. "That [60 percent utilization rate] is increasing as they burn off inventory. But they're still going to have a challenge." The problem for Intel, the world's largest chip manufacturer, is that idle plants and idle production lines cost the company lots of money. Intel's newest factory in Arizona is not being utilized, according to McGregor.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365882592464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365882655237-57</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to collapse?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365882592464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:49:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"PC shipments are going to be lower this year and though they just signed up their first major foundry (contract manufacturing) customer, Altera, that doesn't start until at least next year. So they're going to have to struggle this year with excess capacity, " said McGregor. Related stories Goldman says 'sell' Microsoft, others downgrade stock "[Intel's] thinking was, at the end of 2012 we got the first true ultrabooks coming out, that's going to generate a lot of demand. And we've got Windows 8 coming out and that's also going to generate lots of demand. And we've got design wins in mobile." "Well, guess what, three strikes," McGregor said, referring to the fact that none of those scenarios turned out as forecast. Historically, McGregor believes Intel's factory utilization is at one of it's lowest points. "I haven't seen it this low probably since the beginning of 2000," he said. Intel is gearing up to make its next-generation Haswell processor for laptops and tablets and its Bay Trail and Merrifield chips for tablets and smartphones, respectively. Intel declined to comment.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365882655237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:50:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365882874660-58</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to collapse?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365882592464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:49:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rear view moron. Intel is shipping Haswell now.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1365882874660</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:54:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365883148389-59</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to collapse?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365882592464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:49:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haswell can't fill all those factories, coward. Man up and post under one alias instead of being a weasel and mocking others.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365883148389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:59:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365883536092-60</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to collapse?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365882592464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:49:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>doing a 'khitchdee' are we?</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1365883536092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365883637157-61</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Intel building so much capacity?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1364955944554</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 22:25:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will be interesting to hear from Intel again on capacity this Tuesday.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1365883637157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365883983373-62</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to collapse?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365882592464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:49:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But*h*e*a*d, have you seen the Intel's Haswell reference design? Youtube 'north cape'. Haswell will sell like crazy. Just like 7" Bay tail tablets.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1365883983373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:13:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365884495089-63</Id><Title>What We Know Now Just Before Earnings</Title><Msg>What we know now is that the big Wall Street firms and shorts have positioned themselves for a big Intel miss along with poor guidance for Q2. I don't expect for them to get either one for the following reasons: 1.) Intel likely set the bar pretty low for Q1. So, I don't see Intel having trouble getting over it. The shills expected an earnings warning last quarter and didn't get it. They expected one this quarter and didn't get it. It's them that doesn't get it. 2.) The economy has continued to gradually improve. This will likely affect Q2 guidance the most. 3.) Intel's gameplan has evolved and there is starting to be some recognition of this. Absolutely nothing positive has been included in the stock price. Mr. Market is still working on the "PC is dead" stupidity and is unable to see any of the many other positive factors in Intel's future. 4.) Intel's roadmap looks fabulous for the next two years and ARM has nothing to match it. Haswell, Bay Trail, Airmont, and the like will come in waves, each lifting Intel's mobility future. 5.) ARM's fabrication is going absolutely no where. They are stuck at 28nm while Intel gears up 14, 10 and 7 nm. 6.) Intel's foundry efforts are bearing fruit. The Altera deal changed many attitudes about Intel's future. 7.) Intel has many big deals that could break their way. I would be surprised not to hear about some of them in the next conference call. 8.) Intel's tablet future has improved dramatically. 9.) Intel's web TV venture has a chance to be a real break-through and has a chance to generate excitement and profits, while lifting everything in the Intel ecosystem. 10.) The ARM era is officially over. The word is starting to spread...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365884495089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365884819828-64</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to collapse?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365882592464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:49:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This guy nailed it. Poor fools thinking Haswell will majically make households run out and buy a computer. I'm typing from an HP Pavillion that works just fine! Allen_Wentz 18 hours ago All the techies here saying that the world is waiting for Haswell or whatever fail to get it. The market is not waiting for stronger chips, the market is already mostly satisfied by chips from 2 years ago, which is one reason why less PC and Mac desktop users are upgrading. Less upgrades = less sales; simple. Plus many folks are spending their discretionary tech monies on tablets/phones rather than on desktop upgrades. Note that the latest/greatest chips will not change those trends. And do not blame the desktop sales slump on Win8. Win8 desktop is irrelevant, and is DOA simply because it does not provide enough value add to justify the learning curve for mainstream users. Win7 makes sense because it is very solid and all previous Win versions have significant issues of one kind or another.</Msg><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1365884819828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:26:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365885528462-65</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Intel building so much capacity?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1364955944554</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 22:25:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel needs the capacity for Apple. Apple has huge volumes.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1365885528462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:38:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365885744340-66</Id><Topic><Title>Here is What I Would Be Worried About if I Were an Intel Short</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365784716553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 12:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"wally, get off the pipe man. Whew you got some real bad stuff, you get that on a street corner? and please disclose all your holdings just like you expect of your government officials." [Just to note to the board that this is the standard message for shill drill team. They avoid substantive posts instead preferring a barrage of character assassination and unsupported opinions. Post after post after post, this is the nature of their campaign. It's not by accident that their posts are voluminous and mindless as reflected by multiple IDs. It's by design. ]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365885744340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:42:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365885902814-67</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now Just Before Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365884495089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are officially wrong.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365885902814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:45:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365886052993-68</Id><Title>Intel sets up joint lab with China's Baidu for mobile apps</Title><Msg>The lab is part of an agreement the two companies signed on Thursday that will focus on developing software for China’s mobile Internet market. Developers in the country will have access to Intel-powered products, including PCs, tablets and mobile devices, to test and port software for Baidu and Intel platforms. “If you are a developer, you will now have more choices of platform, and more opportunities in business,” said Christos Georgiopoulos, Intel general manager for developer relations. Intel is investing in the lab as China has become the world’s largest market for PC and smartphones. But the company’s presence in tablets and handsets is still small. Instead, power-efficient chips from its rival ARM Holdings are powering many of today’s popular products, including Apple’s iPhone and iPad, and most Android devices. The chip maker is, however, steadily delivering new chips for use by Chinese vendors. PC maker Lenovo earlier this year unveiled its K900 smartphone, which is designed with Intel’s new “Clover Trail+” processor. Chinese handset maker ZTE is also using the same processor in its latest smartphone, called the ZTE Geek. From PC World</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365886052993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:47:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365886093259-69</Id><Title>Intel is projecting a record year in terms of revenue</Title><Msg>Last conference call, Intel projected 2013 revenue to grow in the "low single-digit percentage increase.". Just a 2% increase would be over the current record of $54 billion (2011). Their estimate for Q1 was $12.7 billion. If this turns out to be the case, then this means the rest of the year should average over $14 billion/quarter. To me, this is an indication that Intel will provide strong guidance for this quarter (Q2).</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1365886093259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365886151158-70</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now Just Before Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365884495089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"you are officially wrong." [A perfect example of an unsupported opinion. I rest my case...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365886151158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365886645649-71</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now Just Before Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365884495089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally you could not rest your case if the world depended on it..</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365886645649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365886718865-72</Id><Topic><Title>Intel sets up joint lab with China's Baidu for mobile apps</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365886052993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:47:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a joint lab...sounds like cheech and chong.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365886718865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:58:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365886830711-73</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now Just Before Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365884495089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Wally you could not rest your case if the world depended on it.." [Another perfect example of a content-free post from the shill drill team...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365886830711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:00:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365887064304-74</Id><Title>Both IDC and Gartner have an awful record on forecasting and counting sales of PCs</Title><Msg>Both IDC and Gartner have an awful record on forecasting and counting sales of PCs. The errors are usually on the low side because they have no good way to count all the emerging market "cottage" assemblers of PCs. I received the following message from Paul McWilliams who writes NextInning and is another old semiconductor guy who could teach me a thing or two: " Q) Does the severity of the fall off in PC sales surprise you? Does it change the time table for when Intel will be a growth story once again? A) The data doesn't surprise me at all. PC sales have been soft for quite a while now, and even as we were entering Q1 expectations were the quarter would be softer than usual. However, that doesn't stop financial writers from leveraging the data for sensational headlines. So IDC says PC shipments in the first quarter were down a record 13.9% sequentially to 76.3M units. Gartner disagrees and says PC unit volume was 79.2M, which represents an 11.2% decline. According to Gartner, this is the first time unit volume has been below 80M units since Q2 2009. Both IDC and Gartner say Hewlett-Packard was the big loser, and I believe that. Both also say Lenovo gained the most market share, and I believe that too. What I don't believe is the notion that IDC or Gartner can accurately gauge the number of PCs sold in a quarter. From Russ Fischer</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365887064304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:04:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365887171658-75</Id><Title>Both IDC and Gartner (cont'd)</Title><Msg>I can remember analysts on INTC conference calls not that long ago questioning Paul Otellini as to how his numbers could be as good as they were in light of the research reports published just ahead of INTC's quarterly releases. I forget exactly what Otellini said in response, but it was something along the lines, "I don't know, you'll have to ask them about their numbers. We're the ones selling the processors." Remember what it was like in the U.S. in the early 1990s when Michael Dell was building PCs in his dorm room? There were hundreds of small PC builders in virtually every major city in the U.S. - it was a highly fragmented industry. That's what it's like in emerging markets today. In China there are far more consumer electronics companies most U.S. citizens have never heard of than there are brand names you might recognize." According to these two market research companies, PCs were down somewhere between 4 and 12 million units. If we use an average of eight million units and an Intel ASP (Average Selling Price) of $100, the total impact is $800 million in revenue to Intel. $800 million is within the guidance given by Intel last quarter of "$12.7 billion plus or minus $500 million." I'm not going to get spun up about an Intel miss next Wednesday. Intel has always proved the forecasting companies wrong and I think it will prove them wrong again.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365887171658</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:06:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365887264188-76</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now Just Before Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365884495089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Repeating your same dumb stuff is content ? Most all of it is wrong in the degree that it affects the margins and growth of Intel. So your content junk. Have a bad week.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365887264188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:07:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365887345743-77</Id><Topic><Title>Both IDC and Gartner (cont'd)</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365887171658</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:06:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, let's knit some of this together. Since the Haswell CPU is such lower power, it will not heat up memory mounted physically close to it (heat on memory is a bad thing). Imagine an Intel "Compute Module" that would be about a 2.5'X2.5' square that mounts the CPU, with the stick-of-gum sized 128GB SSD along one side of the CPU and 4GB of DRAM mounted along the other side. The total value of this Compute Module would be: $100 - CPU + $128 - SSD + $30 - DRAM + $20 - power control chip embedded with the Haswell = $278 of Intel content per CONVERTIBLE PC. The extra $178 multiplied by 300 million PCs is another $53 billion in high margin revenue to Intel. That level of business, which seems a no-brainer for Intel, makes the mobile business look like just an attractive desert.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365887345743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:09:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365887490963-78</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now Just Before Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365884495089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Repeating your same dumb stuff is content ? Most all of it is wrong in the degree that it affects the margins and growth of Intel. So your content junk. Have a bad week." [That's three content-free posts from the shill drill team in three minutes. All volume, no content...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365887490963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:11:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365887748504-79</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now Just Before Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365884495089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Gartner says Intel getting Cisco as a foundry customer is a good move .. As for Intel, it has been extremely successful in the datacenter market over the past decade with its Xeon server chips becoming the market share leaders. Cisco's growing appetite for semiconductors could be just what Intel needs</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1365887748504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:15:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365887762265-80</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to collapse?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365882592464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:49:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Allen nailed it.</Msg><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1365887762265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:16:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365887879700-81</Id><Title>Intel Crystal Well offers huge performance leap from Intel Ivy Bridge 4000 series graphics</Title><Msg>Haswell will save your battery, Haswell has connected stand by, it promises higher performance per clock and for some it is important that. It also gets significantly better graphics. Since Intel makes huge dies, it won't be a problem to squeeze some L4 (fourth level cache) to boost memory bandwidth and lower the latency in some of its Haswell SKUs. The Haswell variant that is internally known as Crystal Well offers much larger L4 cache. The size of the cache is not clear, but we heard that there can be up to 64MB cache dedicated for graphics. This does sound a bit too much, From the mouth of engineers in the Far East, it could be that the L4 cache remains dedicated only for the GPU, but the other independent sources claim that L1, L2, L3 and L4 memory will be shared between CPU and GPU. We will have to look into which of these two theories is right. Crystal Well is reserved for GT3 based highest end processors from Intel, and we have heard that it remains an exclusive technology for Core i7 processors. You will have to pay up to enjoy it. L4 cache is nothing new to the GPU world and consoles have been using such cache to make the texture and antialiasing faster on them. Dedicated cache on GPUs has been considered by Nvidia and ATI (even before the 2006 AMD acquisition) for years. The main obstacle was always that the transistor count for GPU cache memory was very high and it would result in a huge chip, something that semiconductor manufacturers tend to avoid. It will be interesting to see Haswell Crystal Well in action when it launches later this year, but we are certain that we can see a huge performance leap from Intel Ivy Bridge 4000 series graphics. From Fudzilla</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365887879700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:17:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365888266955-82</Id><Topic><Title>Both IDC and Gartner have an awful record on forecasting and counting sales of PCs</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365887064304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and your predictions have been stellar!!!! hilarious</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365888266955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:24:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365888540246-83</Id><Title>remember last quarter ???</Title><Msg>meet expectations and then guided lower and sold off. rinse, repeat.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365888540246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365888540261-84</Id><Topic><Title>Both IDC and Gartner have an awful record on forecasting and counting sales of PCs</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365887064304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How was your prediction of Intel to 30 from 29? What about ARM to single digits from 22? You are a laughable circus clown. I mean just a complete boob.</Msg><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1365888540261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365888780737-85</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Crystal Well offers huge performance leap from Intel Ivy Bridge 4000 series graphics</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365887879700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>joint research and crystal methods....what kind of company is this !! up in smoke.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365888780737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:33:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365888888875-86</Id><Topic><Title>Both IDC and Gartner have an awful record on forecasting and counting sales of PCs</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365887064304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How was your prediction of Intel to 30 from 29? What about ARM to single digits from 22? You are a laughable circus clown. I mean just a complete boob." [Just to note to the board that this is the standard message for shill drill team. They avoid substantive posts instead preferring a barrage of character assassination and unsupported opinions. Post after post after post, this is the nature of their campaign. It's not by accident that their posts are voluminous and mindless as reflected by multiple IDs. It's by design. ]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365888888875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:34:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365888943727-87</Id><Topic><Title>remember last quarter ???</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365888540246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:29:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"meet expectations and then guided lower and sold off. rinse, repeat." [Another perfect example of a content-free post from the shill drill team...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365888943727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:35:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365889074943-88</Id><Topic><Title>Both IDC and Gartner have an awful record on forecasting and counting sales of PCs</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365887064304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, you can dish out calling people on bad predictions but can't take it. Hypocrite.Shell of a man hypocrite. Look at you. A grown adult playing message board wars. LOL! What a B-O-O-B ! Defend your horrendous stock predictions............you can't. RACK.</Msg><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1365889074943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:37:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365889230268-89</Id><Title>Heads up on Wallisweaver</Title><Msg>He's a putz that pumps Intel at any price and bashes ARM at any price. ARM's up 100 percent since he called them out last year, Intel down 30 percent since he pumped them last year. LOL! Man's a nutcase. Floods the board with a million aliases to pump Intel and is eaten alive with the need to control a stupid message board. Make sure to point and laugh at him as you walk by.</Msg><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1365889230268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:40:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365889321160-90</Id><Topic><Title>remember last quarter ???</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365888540246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:29:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stop stalking me you weirdo it is freaking me out, I will call my mommy. Wally if she drops like she is hot and gets too cold to hold you gonna call the SEC FBI CIA again ???</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365889321160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:42:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365889324572-91</Id><Title>Should Intel Shorts Be Worried About Tuesday? Heck, Yeah...</Title><Msg>Of course in the medium to long term shorts should be extremely worried about Haswell, Bay Trail, Airmont and Intel's 14nm FinFET production coming on line. But there are some short term possibilities that they should be worried about headed into earnings. Their biggest worry should be the big Intel announcement designed to coincide with earnings and Otellini's departure. It seems fairly likely that Intel would like Otellini's last conference call to be a pleasant and uplifting experience. As such it would also seem likely that Intel would have planned one or more things to ensure that this will happen. Therefore I think the biggest worry for Intel shorts is that Intel has some big announcements that they have held back, just for earnings and just for Otellini. Otellini is a pretty feisty guy and I think he would like an opportunity to put a stick in the eye of some of the dogpuke analysts that have done their level best to make each and every Intel conference call a miserable experience. So, what are the possibilities? The most obvious would be the Cisco deal. Everyone thinks it's happening but we haven't had any formal announcement. I'd be mildly surprised if we don't get confirmation of the Cisco deal on Tuesday. The second most obvious possibility would be the foundry deal involving the major mobility player that was mentioned by one of the Intel managers recently. This could be a pretty big deal depending on who it is. Next up would be some sort of deal with Apple, either foundry or iWatch. Any sort of deal with Apple would be huge and would crush shorts into a 14nm size packet. And a fairly solid possibility would be a formally announced start date for the web TV project. Or a combination thereof. The danger for shorts I think is to assume that this is just another conference call and that Otellini's departure will have no effect on it. Big, huge honking downside for shorts if they are wrong on this assumption.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365889324572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365889439223-92</Id><Topic><Title>remember last quarter ???</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365888540246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:29:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"stop stalking me you weirdo it is freaking me out, I will call my mommy. Wally if she drops like she is hot and gets too cold to hold you gonna call the SEC FBI CIA again ???" [Just to note to the board that this is the standard message for shill drill team. They avoid substantive posts instead preferring a barrage of character assassination and unsupported opinions. Post after post after post, this is the nature of their campaign. It's not by accident that their posts are voluminous and mindless as reflected by multiple IDs. It's by design.]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365889439223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:43:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365889495252-93</Id><Topic><Title>Heads up on Wallisweaver</Title><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1365889230268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"He's a putz that pumps Intel at any price and bashes ARM at any price. ARM's up 100 percent since he called them out last year, Intel down 30 percent since he pumped them last year. LOL! Man's a nutcase. Floods the board with a million aliases to pump Intel and is eaten alive with the need to control a stupid message board. Make sure to point and laugh at him as you walk by." [Just to note to the board that this is the standard message for shill drill team. They avoid substantive posts instead preferring a barrage of character assassination and unsupported opinions. Post after post after post, this is the nature of their campaign. It's not by accident that their posts are voluminous and mindless as reflected by multiple IDs. It's by design.]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365889495252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:44:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365889619346-94</Id><Topic><Title>Heads up on Wallisweaver</Title><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1365889230268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where did his gang go ? Only hear from vinnie loves donuts and junky. All the normal ones left.</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1365889619346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:46:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365889638997-95</Id><Topic><Title>Heads up on Wallisweaver</Title><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1365889230268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I actually find it very informative when a poster is signaled out who's stock predictions have been so pathetic. Intel a strong buy at 29? REALLY?</Msg><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1365889638997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:47:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365890061424-96</Id><Topic><Title>remember last quarter ???</Title><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365888540246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:29:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>remember how mad you were Walleye ? it was so funny.rinse repeat.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365890061424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:54:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365892610757-97</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE Geek packs 2GHz dual-core Intel Clover Trail+</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365828961707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 00:56:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice post wallis</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365892610757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:36:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365892641386-98</Id><Topic><Title>Intel XOLO X500 (based on low-end Intel Lexington Z2420) scores similar to premium Samsung Galaxy, HTC One, and Sony Experia phones</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365769812557</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 08:30:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good post ideal_invst</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365892641386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:37:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365892699464-99</Id><Topic><Title>Asus Fonepad (based on Intel Lexington Z2420) Now Available in South East Asia</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365772392431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 09:13:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice post again ideal_invst</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365892699464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365892725234-100</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE Geek (Atom Z2580 Clovertrail+) smartphone is smoking fast, spanks the top ARM SoCs</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365680605869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 07:43:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, good post</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365892725234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:38:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365892740897-101</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE Geek (Atom Z2580 Clovertrail+) smartphone is smoking fast, spanks the top ARM SoCs</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365680605869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 07:43:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree too</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365892740897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365892788587-102</Id><Topic><Title>(Ha, ha, ha...) ARM: 64-bit server chips shipping in volume late 2014 or early 2015.</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1365803908903</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 17:58:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good point</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365892788587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365892847329-103</Id><Topic><Title>Asus Intel smartphone coming this summer. New Nexus 7 tablet out in May with better specs?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1365879020714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 14:50:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sounds exciting</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365892847329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365892904462-104</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC won't have 16nm in full production until 2016 - if everything goes according to plan</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1364955238060</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 22:13:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>again you can't argue with facts</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365892904462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365892933965-105</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC won't have 16nm in full production until 2016 - if everything goes according to plan</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1364955238060</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 22:13:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep can't argue with this</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365892933965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:42:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365893029633-106</Id><Topic><Title>ZTE Geek spanks the top Arm SoCs, scores 29401 in the Antutu benchmark</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1365688995556</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ok shorty, we will see what you say after numbers are released</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365893029633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:43:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365893115316-107</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Intel building so much capacity?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1364955944554</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 22:25:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will apple/ intel be announced at earnings conference call????</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365893115316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365893163462-108</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Intel building so much capacity?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1364955944554</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 22:25:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will deal be announced on Tuesday?</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365893163462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:46:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365893255527-109</Id><Topic><Title>Here is What I Would Be Worried About if I Were an Intel Short</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365784716553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 12:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice post wallis. seems like some shorty have a personal issue with you. not sure why.</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365893255527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:47:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365893306673-110</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is projecting a record year in terms of revenue</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1365886093259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 16:48:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>record revenue! watch out shorts!</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365893306673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:48:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365893428926-111</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo K900 Benchmarks fly past quad core Snapdragon</Title><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358221736919</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 22:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice post lucy</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365893428926</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:50:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365893523483-112</Id><Title>$24 Post Earnings</Title><Msg>All bad news has already been priced in. We are down from $29. Although earnings on Tuesday won't be a blow-out, what will be said about the second half of 2013 will definitely be much better. I say we pop to $24 on Wednesday, and began the trek slowly back to $29.</Msg><Username>garyg474</Username><Timestamp>1365893523483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365893575253-113</Id><Topic><Title>$24 Post Earnings</Title><Username>garyg474</Username><Timestamp>1365893523483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:52:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agree with you</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365893575253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:52:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365893653199-114</Id><Topic><Title>Heads up on Wallisweaver</Title><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1365889230268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at him post furiously.</Msg><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1365893653199</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:54:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365893678065-115</Id><Topic><Title>Intel set to collapse?</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1365882592464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 15:49:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yikes.</Msg><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1365893678065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:54:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365895112862-116</Id><Topic><Title>Should Intel Shorts Be Worried About Tuesday? Heck, Yeah...</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365889324572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:42:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe new design wins. Intel inside the next Nexus 7 or Amazon Kindle are two possibilities.</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365895112862</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 19:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365895520349-117</Id><Topic><Title>REMEMBER APPLE/INTEL DEAL IN MAY AFTER MICRON PURCHASE OF ELPIDA IS COMPLETED</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1365725511465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:11:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>deal coming in may</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365895520349</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 19:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365895654459-118</Id><Topic><Title>Should Intel Shorts Be Worried About Tuesday? Heck, Yeah...</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365889324572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:42:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I heard of a chromebook hybrid that runs both Android and Chrome OS with intel inside.</Msg><Username>aladeisright</Username><Timestamp>1365895654459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 19:27:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365895671342-119</Id><Topic><Title>Heads up on Wallisweaver</Title><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1365889230268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the lower it goes the more he loves it ....must be a deep sea diver. S&amp;M ?</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1365895671342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 19:27:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365896987230-120</Id><Topic><Title>Heads up on Wallisweaver</Title><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1365889230268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for a view of the biggest INTC shill Waldo, I suggest you look in the mirror.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1365896987230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 19:49:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365897824445-121</Id><Topic><Title>Should Intel Shorts Be Worried About Tuesday? Heck, Yeah...</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365889324572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:42:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am wondering just how far it is gonna drop I am worried it may only be 2 or 3 bucks. [Just to note to the board that this is the standard message for shill drill team. They avoid substantive posts instead preferring a barrage of character assassination and unsupported opinions. Post after post after post, this is the nature of their campaign. It's not by accident that their posts are voluminous and mindless as reflected by multiple IDs. It's by design. thought I would save you some time Wally.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1365897824445</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 20:03:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365898578420-122</Id><Topic><Title>$24 Post Earnings</Title><Username>garyg474</Username><Timestamp>1365893523483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:52:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All bad news has already been priced in. We are down from $29. Although earnings on Tuesday won't be a blow-out, what will be said about the second half of 2013 will definitely be much better. I say we pop to $24 on Wednesday, and began the trek slowly back to $29. [Just to note to the board that this is the standard message for shill drill team. They avoid substantive posts instead preferring a barrage of character assassination and unsupported opinions. Post after post after post, this is the nature of their campaign. It's not by accident that their posts are voluminous and mindless as reflected by multiple IDs. It's by design.]</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1365898578420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 20:16:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365898895946-123</Id><Topic><Title>Should Intel Shorts Be Worried About Tuesday? Heck, Yeah...</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365889324572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:42:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks but you could save me much more time by not posting your content-free messages at all...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365898895946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 20:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365898929140-124</Id><Title>hugh market cap</Title><Msg>Intel has a market cap and the most you can expect is a trade of about 10%</Msg><Username>tradertrader2012</Username><Timestamp>1365898929140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 20:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365899042603-125</Id><Topic><Title>Heads up on Wallisweaver</Title><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1365889230268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"for a view of the biggest INTC shill Waldo, I suggest you look in the mirror." [You are amazing!!! Your response to being chastised for posting content-free messaging is to post more content-free messaging and unsupported opinions. You are the shill's shill, butkus... ]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365899042603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 20:24:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365899183046-126</Id><Title>Note to Shills</Title><Msg>We hereby stipulate to you having posted 10,000 content-free messages. Now take the next three months off...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365899183046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 20:26:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365899749036-127</Id><Topic><Title>Note to Shills</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365899183046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 20:26:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep posting nonsense waldo, your geek speak skills have gotten you no where for years and have absolutely nothing to do with the price action for INTC, zilch, zero, nada.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1365899749036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 20:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365902326502-128</Id><Topic><Title>$24 Post Earnings</Title><Username>garyg474</Username><Timestamp>1365893523483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:52:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NOTHINGS EVER PRICED IN TO A STOCK GOOBER!</Msg><Username>nk499</Username><Timestamp>1365902326502</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 21:18:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365902376096-129</Id><Topic><Title>$24 Post Earnings</Title><Username>garyg474</Username><Timestamp>1365893523483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:52:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb #$%$'s!</Msg><Username>nk499</Username><Timestamp>1365902376096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 21:19:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365902433185-130</Id><Topic><Title>Note to Shills</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365899183046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 20:26:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how selling INTC for 19.77 working for you shill ?</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1365902433185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 21:20:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365906555896-131</Id><Title>There is still no ARM A15 based chips around. Samsungs chips won't</Title><Msg>be around until next month.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1365906555896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 22:29:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365911269060-132</Id><Topic><Title>$24 Post Earnings</Title><Username>garyg474</Username><Timestamp>1365893523483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 18:52:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two more content-free posts from the shill drill team...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365911269060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 23:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365911343232-133</Id><Topic><Title>Short Earnings Worry Poll Recap</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365785002548</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 12:43:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The largest danger to shorts on earnings is the announcement of: 1.) The Cisco deal. 2.) The foundry deal involving a major mobility player. 3.) Some sort of deal with Apple, either foundry or iWatch. 4.) A formally announced start date for the web TV project. 5.) A combination of these. 6.) Something else:____________ Less</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365911343232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 23:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>