<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359263514594-1</Id><Topic><Title>66 million shares traded at 20.96</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1359156676058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 18:31:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How did you like the 60 million share trade TIC TOC up INTC goes</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1359263514594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 00:11:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359263633248-2</Id><Topic><Title>66 million shares traded at 20.96</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1359156676058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 18:31:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was 60 million on the up TIC , TIC TOC are you ready to say OH NO up INTC goes</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1359263633248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 00:13:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359269924666-3</Id><Title>Difference Between Intel and ARM</Title><Msg>"In the epic space battle at the Mutara Nebula between Captain James T. Kirk and Kahn Noonien Singh in “The Wrath of Khan,” Spock observes of Khan at the critical turning point of the battle, “He is intelligent, but not experienced. His pattern indicates two-dimensional thinking.” Luckily, we are intelligent, experienced, and thinking three-dimensionally!" [With the development of FinFET, Intel left ARM's two-dimensional thinking behind. Since then the gap has grown wider...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359269924666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 01:58:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359270502824-4</Id><Title>Intel Making Apple's ARM Chips Will Leave Samsung Behind</Title><Msg>Intel fabs are running at much less than capacity and are over a generation ahead of all the other possible foundries for Apple. Intel is already running at 22nm and moving to 14nm, while TSMC, the largest alternative, is now at 28nm and moving to 20nm. Apple could therefore skip a generation from the 32nm used in the iPhone 5 and iPad 4, going straight to 14nm, and use the process shrink for better performance and better battery life and be a generation ahead of competitors. Even if Apple takes a more conservative approach, it can move all its ARM chip production to Intel's already proven 22nm process while rivals deal with any teething troubles in the ramp up of equivalents. Apple also wants to move all the business it can from Samsung (SSNLF.PK), its greatest rival in the high end smartphone market. It would certainly prefer that Samsung didn't see Apple's optimized ARM chip designs before they are part of a shipping iPhone or iPad. In addition Samsung has no great incentive to even move as fast as TSMC, as while it produces Apple's ARM chips, Samsung and Apple are both on the same fab process. This can create the impression that Apple is falling behind other rivals and therefore the iPhone and iPad are not as premium as they used to be. Apple's main advantage now in ARM chips is the integrated graphics licensed from Imagination. In benchmarks, Apple's A6X is competitive in CPU tests but surges ahead in areas like games, which can use the better graphics. However Samsung too can integrate better graphics, and given the size of the Galaxy screen, has every incentive to do so. So it makes sense for Apple to move to Intel and once again increase the performance gap between iPhone/ iPad and the Android phones and tablets. If the usual 2 years for a chip generation holds, iPhones made now with chips from Intel's 14nm line will still be competitive in 2015 when Samsung moves to that process. So then Apple will be able to market its cheaper 2 year old iPhones to the mid range as being as up-to-date as the best Samsung phones. In summary, if it produces Apple's ARM chips, Intel: gains new production of 300+ million chips / year $5.5-6bn (+11-12%) more revenue at $18 to $20 per chip 50% gross and 40% operating profit should be possible (TSMC makes mid to upper 40s gross with an operating profit of low to mid 30s) possible exclusivity premium from Apple and / or payments for equipment for foundry upgrades strong further use of the current 22nm lines where depreciation has largely been paid for with x86 production good yields, as many problems will have been sorted out with x86 better fab utilisation diversifies revenue stream away from x86 and Wintel will reinforce Intel's position as the no. 1 chip producer Apple gains: exclusivity from a trusted partner, possibly in exchange for a premium, who won't produce chips for Samsung. strong partner it has no need to subsidize, able to produce all the ARM chips Apple needs worldwide chip production from up to 8 fabs reducing possibilities of disruption in the supply chain US produced chips - important given the commitment to US manufacturing faster access to future chip processes which give longer battery life and/ or better performance helps with marketing iPhone as always ahead of other phones removes the Samsung drag on improvements and increases the time it takes for Samsung to catch up Samsung loses: revenue down by $3.5-4bn (current ARM chip production for Apple) chip costs for its own phones and tablets go up no more foundry subsidies from Apple paying for plant and new equipment lower throughput to take care of depreciation. weakens position as no.2 chip producer by revenue reduces likelihood of holding on to a large part of Apple's NAND memory chip needs (Apple is the world's largest buyer) Samsung clearly hopes that it can replace the profits from chip production by selling more phones and tablets. It may well do, if being a generation behind Apple doesn't make Samsung's top end ranges look like also-runs.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359270502824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 02:08:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359270503953-5</Id><Topic><Title>Difference Between Intel and ARM</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359269924666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 01:58:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel didn't invent FinFETs, they productized them first because they were supplying gazillions of chips to the PC market. Now it's the turn of the foundries to do the same with the mobile chip market. FinFETs are new technology but not rocket science and all the foundries have the best scientists working on them. They have time and they have money.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359270503953</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 02:08:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359271269684-6</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Making Apple's ARM Chips Will Leave Samsung Behind</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359270502824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 02:08:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel making Apple's ARM chips will kill low power IA, Intel's favorite project. They would never do that. Secondly, Intel is not in a position to fab anything other than chips they have fabbed before which are their own chips. They are not designed to operate like a foundry.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1359271269684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 02:21:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359271273170-7</Id><Topic><Title>Difference Between Intel and ARM</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359269924666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 01:58:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel didn't invent FinFETs, they productized them first because they were supplying gazillions of chips to the PC market." [Supplying "gazillions of chips to the PC market" had nothing to do with it. They produced them first because they put ten years of development into it.] "Now it's the turn of the foundries to do the same with the mobile chip market. FinFETs are new technology but not rocket science and all the foundries have the best scientists working on them. They have time and they have money." [Amazing how many factual errors you can put in two sentences. FinFETs are rocket science. That's why it took ten years of development. The foundries don't have the best scientists working for them. Otherwise they woudn't be a constant two to three years behind Intel in R&amp;D. They don't have time. You yourself just said it takes 4 years on average for each new node. Well, it only takes Intel half of that and FinFET is not going to be the average node development for ARM. Don't expect to see any ARM FinFET for years and years from now. Too little, too late as Intel will own mobility by then. The money is another issue as only TSMC and Samsung can keep up and we're not too sure about TSMC any more. No matter how many times you say it, the fabless model is broken. Simply because it is fabless and doesn't provide money for fabs. It leaves it up to the foundries to find the money and more and more of them are dropping by the wayside unable to come up with the billions for construction. And even if they did, they don't have the technology. Game over...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359271273170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 02:21:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359271616157-8</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Making Apple's ARM Chips Will Leave Samsung Behind</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359270502824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 02:08:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel making Apple's ARM chips will kill low power IA, Intel's favorite project. They would never do that." [Intel won't make ARM chips. They'll force Apple to convert. Apple will do it because of the superiority of the technology. End of story...] "Secondly, Intel is not in a position to fab anything other than chips they have fabbed before which are their own chips. They are not designed to operate like a foundry." [Sure, Intel managed FinFET but can't figure out how to make chips for Apple. If that allows you to sleep at night, just keep mumbling it to yourself as you drift off to fantasy land...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359271616157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 02:26:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359297955532-9</Id><Topic><Title>Difference Between Intel and ARM</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359269924666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 01:58:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not that the foundries are broken, it's that they aren't structurally or economically equipped to produce leading edge technology. ARM promoters that continue to argue this point and claim the foundries will match Intel's ability in manufacturing sound completely clueless and it further undermines their credibility. The ARM camp, along with its foundries needs to reconcile the fact that their role is to produce trailing-edge technology and be happy with it. It's not a bad business because there are a lot of products that don't need leading-edge, it's just not the products and markets Intel is targeting.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1359297955532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 09:45:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359300055250-10</Id><Title>NO SMALL WONDER</Title><Msg>More than DOUBLE average daily Trading Volume......Barracudas moving in to Capture that 4 1/4% Dividend coming up in a few days. Why Not? Who can blame them, I did the same.....beats the hek out of 0.04% Chase pays me on my Savings.</Msg><Username>foreverdonquijote</Username><Timestamp>1359300055250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:20:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359300208955-11</Id><Title>Intel Foundry &amp; Huge Capital Expenditure to decimate TSMC, GloFlo, &amp; Samsung</Title><Msg>With power/performance getting close to par between x86 and ARM, the only way ARM-based mobile SoC vendors can keep up with Intel is on process and manufacturing. Intel's ace has always been process and manufacturing. Fabless chip vendors (Qualcomm, nVidia, TI, Xilinx, Altera, etc.) have gotten around this by going to TSMC and other foundries who have managed to keep costs low due to their location and by spreading R&amp;D costs over a large number of customers. Further, the foundries were not forced to compete with Intel on process nodes till now since Intel used its advanced factories for its own captive manufacturing. And the ARM-based Intel competitors have vastly benefited by it. This strategy will not work any more. Intel, with its new foundry services and huge capital expenditure, is going to force the issue with foundries. Having decided to offer foundry services, I think Intel will go after the premium fabless companies that don't compete with Intel (Xilinx, Altera, and perhaps even TI and several others) - and they, in order to retain their leading marketing positions, would want Intel to manufacture their chips for them. This will have the effect of cutting off the air supply to TSMC and other foundries. If their premium customers who are capable of paying for capital investment, delivery priority, etc. move over to Intel, the foundries will have to fork up the capital investment themselves...and/or rely on the second-tier fabless companies to do so. Neither is a great proposition for the foundries. With Intel Foundry taking away the premium fabless vendors, the foundries will be unable to keep up with the investment needed to help ARM-based mobile SoCs compete with Intel. And once they fall behind, it will be difficult for them to catch up with Intel - so Intel will have a long-term advantage! So Intel wins in all 3 areas: Intel Foundry/Arm ===== ========== Power/Performance Check Check Leading Process Nodes Check No Manufacturing volumes Check No Absolutely see this as the end-game. There is no other reason for Intel to expand its manufacturing capacity and capital outlay so significantly.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359300208955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:23:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359310650451-12</Id><Topic><Title>NO SMALL WONDER</Title><Username>foreverdonquijote</Username><Timestamp>1359300055250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:20:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4ever - do You Invest in INTC and keep it - or do You mostly just trade INTC ?....I Invest and keep.</Msg><Username>atexeight</Username><Timestamp>1359310650451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 13:17:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359310835026-13</Id><Topic><Title>66 million shares traded at 20.96</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1359156676058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 18:31:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you look at the NASDAQ afterhours trading log for INTC on the nasdaqDOTcom site, there was a flurry of activity at that price about 16:37. There were several several 2m share trades and there were several marked as CANCELLED. There were none on the after hours log for 66m shares so that is likely a market maker settling trade to clear their books for the day. I have never seen a cancelled trade likt that but the volume did pop from 30m to 100m at the end of the day. Intel can buy 25% of the volume and there is a 1 block trade exception on the buyback. My first thought is the Intel buyer taking a 66m block.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359310835026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 13:20:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359318693776-14</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Foundry &amp; Huge Capital Expenditure to decimate TSMC, GloFlo, &amp; Samsung</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359300208955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:23:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone who suggests that it is an "end game" for either (ARM or Intel) is exaggerating. The market does not want a single architecture nor does it want a single supplier. Every customer wants to have the lowest price for its component parts to maximize profits and will therefore cultivate competitors for its vendors. These competitors will then be primarily be used as a lever or club to get better pricing and if needed used as an alternate supplier. If Intel did not exist, a competitor would be created. Think about Facebook creating the OpenCompute group to get better pricing on equipment they want. The semiconductor industry is a capital intensive industry. There is a high capital barrier to entry (takes billions and billions for entery) and continuation. Cash and investment is the oxygen that allows it to breathe. There are 3 large, heathy sources of semiconductors today: Intel, TSMC and Samsung. The TSMC BOD and management is faced with funding decisions. They have a number of risks. How to fund. Who funds. How to handle the prospect of just the possibility of a large customer or two vaporizing. Intel/Samsung could capture them through a customer deal or foundry deal. Or not.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359318693776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 15:31:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359319601441-15</Id><Title>If you want some real bargains, look at gold stocks...</Title><Msg>like ABX, NEM and IAG. They are so oversold it is absurd....</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1359319601441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 15:46:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359322705494-16</Id><Topic><Title>If you want some real bargains, look at gold stocks...</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1359319601441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 15:46:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NEM pe 199 with ta spiral down. lol</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1359322705494</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 16:38:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359323556348-17</Id><Title>What a disgusting human being/regime/8 years of US History</Title><Msg>Here are the main highlights revealed by the USAF. Keep in mind that all the data below relate to United States Air Force aircraft used by one woman over a sixteen month period. Several of these flights included Ms. Pelosi's guests, such as grown children, grandchildren, various in-laws, friends and hangers-on. Over 95% of the trips were between the west coast and Washington DC, for what you might call a commute between home and the office. READ it and WEEP!! Total trips: 85 over a 68 week period, or 1.25 average trips per week. Total mileage: 206,264 miles, or 2,427 average miles per trip. Totalflying time: 428.6 hours, or an average of 5 hours per trip. Cost to the taxpayers: $2,100,744, or $27,715 per trip, or $1,285,162 per year! Cost of in flight food and alcohol: $101,429; $1,193 per trip; $62,051 per year. On one junket to Baghdad, according to the Air Force report, she had the aircraft bar stocked with Johnny Walker Red Scotch, Grey Goose Vodka, E&amp;J Brandy, Bailey's Irish Cream, Maker's Mark Whiskey, Courvoisier Cognac, Bacardi Rum, Jim Beam Whiskey, Beefeater Gin, Dewar's Scotch, Bombay Sapphire Gin, Jack Daniels Whiskey, Corona Beer and several varieties of wine. This was obviously a very important "gubment bidness" trip. Evidence generally speaks for itself, and in Ms. Pelosi's case it speaks the language of abuse and (evidently) a serious familial drinking problem, for in a single year she and her spawn drank an amount in excess of the net income of the average employed American! When she said, "... If the stimulus doesn't pass, five hundred million people might lose their jobs...", I thought she was unintentionally revealing her ignorance. I'm now more inclined to think she was pickled. Even though she can no longer abuse the USAF, she can either fly on her broom, or fly Southwest Airlines, where bags fly free.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359323556348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 16:52:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359325712088-18</Id><Topic><Title>What a disgusting human being/regime/8 years of US History</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359323556348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 16:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is not the btch board....this is the Intel board...got it????</Msg><Username>jravera</Username><Timestamp>1359325712088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 17:28:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359326504737-19</Id><Topic><Title>What a disgusting human being/regime/8 years of US History</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359323556348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 16:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The selective outrage is stunning. I noticed you were silent on the VA state representatives holding a quick session during the inaugural address to restructure their Electoral process. Wait till an opponent is out of town to hold the vote. Did you see it? Which blog did you copy/paste this from? It seems to be on many of them, word for word. Did you write it or simply forget to give credit to the author? I searched for the double quoted first line after READ it and WEEP. It found 14,100 matches for that character by character, exact match. "Total trips: 85 over a 68 week period, or 1.25 average trips per week." 14,100 websites where people have copied and pasted this unchanged. 95% of these were for commute related according to it. For the remaining 5%, how do they compare with the others in the House/Senate? Did you bother to look? Why not compare with Darrell Issa? He is from CA too and not used to saving a dime so his numbers would provide a ceiling number to compare with. I will do some digging. "Even though she can no longer abuse the USAF, she can either fly on her broom, or fly Southwest Airlines, where bags fly free." The broom comment? Insulting and beneath you. Fly Southwest? Southwest flights between CA to DC all have 1 stop with double the travel time. The departure/arrival times limited and unlikely to match the appointment calendars. It can be done, but I would not want to do it weekly.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359326504737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 17:41:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359326891646-20</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Foundry &amp; Huge Capital Expenditure to decimate TSMC, GloFlo, &amp; Samsung</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359300208955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:23:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alex: The definition of "end game": the final part of a game, battle, or political process when the result is decided I did not indicate that the result would be a complete elimination of ARM and the foundries. Nor the victory of a single architecture. However, with its integrated design and manufacturing prowess, Intel should and will work towards expanding x86 in the mobile and embedded computing spaces which will have the effect of reducing the ARM/foundries competition to a minor role with presence in some segments. IMO, Intel will do this with a combination of: a) better SoCs b) more advanced process nodes than the foundries c) higher manufacturing capacity (b) and (c) both have huge costs - Intel will spread the costs with an expanding Intel Foundry footprint targeted towards premium fabless customers. This will, of course, result in negative revenue impact on the foundries impacting their ability to invest in expensive future process nodes as well as new factory capacity. This is how I see the next couple of years playing out.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359326891646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 17:48:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359326934671-21</Id><Topic><Title>What a disgusting human being/regime/8 years of US History</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359323556348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 16:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm just pasting something someone sent to me. Hey man, tell your buddy Flumoxed to stop posting his virtriol (not surprised at all if Flumoxed is you) and I'll stop posting politicol stuff that's sent to me.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359326934671</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 17:48:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359326987632-22</Id><Topic><Title>What a disgusting human being/regime/8 years of US History</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359323556348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 16:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sad to see you take up for Nancy Pelosi, buddy. Just SAD.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359326987632</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 17:49:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359327150416-23</Id><Topic><Title>What a disgusting human being/regime/8 years of US History</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359323556348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 16:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's the author. I didn't right it. This an opinion board. I think Nancy Pelosi is disgusting, but hey. USAF Took Nancy Pelosi's Jet Away Submitted by emalvini on Wed, 01/02/2013 - 22:29</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359327150416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 17:52:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359327405303-24</Id><Topic><Title>What a disgusting human being/regime/8 years of US History</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359323556348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 16:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whoops, here's the author. I didn't write it, but I sure think she's disgusting. USAF Took Nancy Pelosi's Jet Away Submitted by emalvini on Wed, 01/02/2013 - 22:29</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359327405303</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 17:56:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359327595225-25</Id><Topic><Title>What a disgusting human being/regime/8 years of US History</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359323556348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 16:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fly Southwest? Southwest flights between CA to DC all have 1 stop with double the travel time. The departure/arrival times limited and unlikely to match the appointment calendars. It can be done, but I would not want to do it weekly. ______________________-- Well now that you put it that way, I totally see why a person in her position should take the Air Force Jet home 1.25 times per week fly family around, booze it up, etc.... LOL! SMH.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359327595225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 17:59:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359331280889-26</Id><Title>Didn't Intel just buy part of Motorola?</Title><Msg>What are the details? I gotta tell ya, I have a new Razr M by Motorola and that is an AMAZING phone. What are the odds that Intel chips will be in ALL Motorola phones in the future? That's what I want. I want Intel inside all Motorola manufactured phones. Is it possible?</Msg><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1359331280889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:01:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359333680267-27</Id><Title>What does all the Motorola/Intel news mean? Baseband?</Title><Msg>CCI approves Intel-Motorola Mobility deal PTI Jan 25, 2013, 06.07PM IST NEW DELHI: CCI has given its approval to global chip maker Intel's proposed acquisition of Motorola Mobility's certain assets including patents, saying the combination would not have any direct impact on competition in India. As per the deal Intel would acquire certain assets of Motorola Mobility such as non-Indian intellectual property rights, including patents and patent applications. The chip maker would also buy tangible assets of the company located in the US besides getting the rights to hire some American employees of Motorola Mobility, among others. "... the market for cellular baseband processors is competitive on account of presence of major players including Qualcomm, MediaTek, Texas Instruments and Broadcom," CCI said in its order dated January 22. Motorola Mobility subsidiaries in India are Motorola Mobility India and Motorola Mobility Chennai. The regulator said the assets of Motorola Mobility which are being acquired by Intel do not presently generate any revenue in India. As per the order, Intel is a recent entrant into the production of components for wireless hand held devices including cellular baseband processors. The company has various subsidiaries in India including Intel Technology India, Intel Mobile Communications India and McAfee Software. Intel and Motorola Mobility had reached 'Asset Purchase Agreement' in December, 2012, following which they approached CCI for approval.</Msg><Username>joseywales_outlaw</Username><Timestamp>1359333680267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:41:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359335688435-28</Id><Title>How did you like the last 15 of trading on Friday and the big 60 million plus after hours.</Title><Msg>Not must time left to cover now. TIC TOC get ready for the move up in INTC</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1359335688435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:14:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359335807083-29</Id><Title>Can you tell the deference in trading yet? The shorts are really trying to cover now</Title><Msg>Can you tell the deference in trading yet? The shorts are really trying to cover now</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1359335807083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:16:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359337451811-30</Id><Topic><Title>I told all my clients to sell Friday before the the correction that coming</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1359215417324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 10:50:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raystock's clients don't hire him for stock advice. They hire him when he picks them up on the street corner!!! Raystock is a loser and liar who always buys high and then lies.</Msg><Username>mister_quarter</Username><Timestamp>1359337451811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:44:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359339030103-31</Id><Topic><Title>Can you tell the deference in trading yet? The shorts are really trying to cover now</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1359335807083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:16:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have not been able to tell. I can't see shorts trying to cover or any of the other things you see. I saw the volume pop up and the cancelled trades for after hours. I don't have any to tell when shorts are covering nor the big boys/money enter/leaving. You have better eyes than i do.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359339030103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 21:10:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359341064128-32</Id><Topic><Title>What a disgusting human being/regime/8 years of US History</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359323556348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 16:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"right" it? probably needed someone to "reed" it to you, dittohead.</Msg><Username>misanthropope</Username><Timestamp>1359341064128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 21:44:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359342128575-33</Id><Title>When is Intel's beta going to go up??</Title><Msg>Stock making no movements on low volume.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1359342128575</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 22:02:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359342323149-34</Id><Topic><Title>What a disgusting human being/regime/8 years of US History</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359323556348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 16:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On Wikipedia and unchallenged. Unchallenged by anyone. The Bush initiated security policy required an airplane that could travel from home district to DC without refueling. Southwest Air does not qualify since they have no non-stop flights. If you fly SouthWest that far, you will be lucky to not have to change planes. Pelosi Use of government aircraft In March 2009, the New York Post wrote that the conservative watchdog group Judicial Watch obtained emails sent by Pelosi's staff that requested that the United States Air Force (USAF) provide specific aircraft—a Boeing 757—for Pelosi to use for taxpayer-funded travel. Pelosi responded that the policy was initiated by President Bush due to post-9/11 security concerns (Pelosi was third in line for presidential succession) and was initially provided for the previous Speaker, Dennis Hastert. The Sergeant at Arms requested, for security reasons, that the plane provided be capable of non-stop flight, requiring a larger aircraft. The Pentagon said "no one has rendered judgment" that Pelosi's use of aircraft "is excessive."</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359342323149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 22:05:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359342737179-35</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Foundry &amp; Huge Capital Expenditure to decimate TSMC, GloFlo, &amp; Samsung</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359300208955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:23:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Anyone who suggests that it is an "end game" for either (ARM or Intel) is exaggerating. The market does not want a single architecture nor does it want a single supplier. Every customer wants to have the lowest price for its component parts to maximize profits and will therefore cultivate competitors for its vendors. These competitors will then be primarily be used as a lever or club to get better pricing and if needed used as an alternate supplier. If Intel did not exist, a competitor would be created. " [I think it would be erroneous to conclude that we are currently in the "end game". However, I think it's quite possible that it really is "game over" and we are just waiting for it to play out although it will take years for it to be fully realized - perhaps 5 years to be substantially reflected in the marketplace. Bottom line is that FinFET is a disruptive technology (i.e. a new technology that has a serious impact on the status quo and changes the way people have been dealing with something, perhaps for decades). Of course, ARM would have us believe that this is not the case. But at this point we have no reason to believe ARM can do FinFET. Ortellini said ARM wouldn't have FinFET EVER. Now he's a guy who knows quite a bit about FinFET. I can't see him making that comment without thinking that FinFET is a mighty hurdle to get over. But here's the rub - It's not whether ARM can do FinFET but how long it will take. If it takes ARM four years to reach volume production on FinFET, then that's just the same as never. Because Intel will own mobility if ARM gets stuck at 20nm planar for four years. Intel will be doing 7nm by that time and have a huge advantage in both performance and power efficiency. But wait, this will never happen because Intel doesn't have the capacity to take over all of ARM's foundry business. Oh, wait. My bad. Yes, they do have the capacity. Not only do they have the capacity but they built that capacity with no serious strain on their cash flow. Intel is ready to flood the market with state-of-the-art FinFET production. And plan on building more. And this doesn't even include other disruptive factors substantially in Intel's favor. Like 450mm. Intel will be first to 450mm production on 10nm. ARM will still be stuck on 20nm planar when this happens. ARM has nothing to compete with either. And Intel will probably be first to EUV as well. Intel is therefore on the verge of opening up technological, economic and manufacturing advantages that are easily classified as disruptive. And just because the market wants competition doesn't mean the market is going to get it. If ARM can't do FinFET, then no one else is going to come along with a decade of time and $25 billion to develop it. We know that ARM will be at least 2 years behind on FinFET and 4 years is very possible. So, the question isn't whether it will be disruptive. It already is disruptive. Anyone with half a brain knows how remarkable an achievement FinFET is. The question is how disruptive. Looking pretty disruptive. All the evidence points to ARM being the next Lotus 1-2-3... ]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359342737179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 22:12:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359343714132-36</Id><Topic><Title>What a disgusting human being/regime/8 years of US History</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359323556348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 16:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and me have nothing and I mean NOTHING in common if you think Nancy Pelosi is a good person. You disgust me just as much, liberal filth.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1359343714132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 22:28:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359344610100-37</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Foundry &amp; Huge Capital Expenditure to decimate TSMC, GloFlo, &amp; Samsung</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359300208955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:23:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lackeygarret apparently doesn't agree with Wally......and he looks more credible to me! by lackeygarrett . Jan 25, 2013 9:15 AM . Permalink Yes, ARM's ecosystem is the key differentiator that gives them an insurmountable moat that no other company can compete with. Approximately 30% of the semi space has adopted the ARM architecture and the stated goal by ARM's management is to engage the whole semi space for their TAM. With processors costs decreasing and functionality increasing, more and more processors are being used for 2-way communications. This requires a 32-bit+ processor. Electrical devices can only run as fast as the network they run on, so as the mobile internet proliferates and the telcom networks keep increasing speed with LTE, more and more devices will be used. The amount of processors being deployed yearly is growing larger year by year. This expanding market share pie will continue for the foreseeable future. When LTE-A becomes mainstream the platform used will be all IP (using SoC's) and based on Software Defined Radio, which will be the catalyst for the Internet of Things. This leads to a Smart Planet, which will use a Smat Grid, which is enabled by a smart meter, where the metering industry for 2-way communicating meters is consolidating onto the ARM architecture. The smart grid and the internet will be based on heterogeneous computing/networking which merges the wired and unwired world together allowing interoperability between all electrical devices, regardless of the device's platform, protocol or operating system. That is the requirement for future-proofness. That is why ARM is a long term investment.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1359344610100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 22:43:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359346944511-38</Id><Topic><Title>Can you tell the deference in trading yet? The shorts are really trying to cover now</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1359335807083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:16:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coinmaker (Nuff) doesn't have indicators or anything to go by. He makes outlandish statements to support a long or short position. Most of this posts are "hit and run" types where he isn't around to answer another post in reply to his original. One of his strangest behaviors is where one of his aliases is long, supporting Intel and another one bashes it. He truly does have several split personalities. Wally Weaver is Nuff's arch nemesis probably in his crazy world something akin to Sherlock Holmes vs. Prof. Moriarity.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1359346944511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 23:22:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359347115066-39</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Foundry &amp; Huge Capital Expenditure to decimate TSMC, GloFlo, &amp; Samsung</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1359300208955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:23:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The one word that ARM fanbois try to avoid at all costs is FinFET. Any article supporting ARM that doesn't include a discussion of fabrication and FinFET is as worthless as a white crayon...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1359347115066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 23:25:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359348781155-40</Id><Topic><Title>Can you tell the deference in trading yet? The shorts are really trying to cover now</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1359335807083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:16:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you describe is a "perfect prediction" scam.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1359348781155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 23:53:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>