<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-07"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370578027620-1</Id><Title>I could use some help with this "cannibalization" logic.</Title><Msg>If analysts are saying that INTC will cannibalize their revenues with tablet sales, how does the logic break down? It seems to me, that the analysts were slamming INTC because they didn't participate in the tablet's explosive growth. By definition, that would mean that INTC was not providing CPUs to the tablet market. People were already not buying PCs. Got it. Agreed. However, people cannot "extra not" buy PCs. When a tablet was purchased, INTC completely missed that revenue. Now that INTC will earn money on the tablet, the tablet the person was going to buy anyway to complement their PC, how is this making less money? For all intents and purposes, INTC is entering a new, explosive market. Tablet are not PCs. Not much real work is done on a tiny monitor, unless your work solely consists of writing emails. The closest so far to a tablet cannibalizing a PC is the ASUS Trio (which looks wicked). The projected price is north of $2000 with an ATOM and a Haswell CPU... not really cannibalization, the opposite, in fact. Can some one who understands the "target $18" analysts shed some light on this for me?</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370578027620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 00:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370578731564-2</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is no ANd</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1370566425786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:53:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am really questioning if the ARM foundries will be able to afford to see the day that FinFET gets launched. To be able to afford such a very high cost there has to be a reasonable amount of business at a reasonable amount of profit. As mentioned before not nearly enough money makes it back to the foundries. The costs are staggering, and they barely managed to pull off 28nm. Do I think ARM could eventually come up with 16nm FinFET? Yes, eventually. If Intel never entered their market. Given enough time all those bold predictions from ARM could have come true, ARM could have eaten Intel's lunch. Instead they are seeing the wrath of Intel with surgical precision come into their market and cherry pick it. The question is no longer "if" the day will happen but how deep Intel will go into the market:" I also think that ARMH is a fabulous $7 stock with a $35 fairy tale premium. Many years ago I was trying to decide to buy Microsoft or Intel. I went Intel because I felt we were entering a hardware era. What we've seen is that people time and time again will place down good money on good, new exciting hardware. Little devices that inform you that send you text messages to your phone to let you know the power is out at your house may be the type of thing people will buy if it's cheap enough. Keep in mind the more of these $2 processors there are floating around the more servers they will need. Intel is going to fill it's factories up with profitable business first. I do believe Warren East was right, there may come a day where you are surrounded by tons and tons of low level ARM processors in your life. It's where ARM could go to grow in realistic terms without having cutting edge hardware. It was a sober direction for ARMH to head after looking into his crystal ball. But first we will have year of people coming on this board saying "You guys just don't understand, ARMH has this secret design that will leapfrog Intel next year."</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1370578731564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 00:18:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370579392002-3</Id><Topic><Title>Ashraf - tried</Title><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370574991211</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>eir951, Shoot me a PM over at Seeking Alpha :)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1370579392002</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 00:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370579516539-4</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is no ANd</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1370566425786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:53:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am really questioning if the ARM foundries will be able to afford to see the day that FinFET gets launched. They will - they have no choice - sink or swim - but they will have yo pay for it. ARM's happy day's are over... Fab equipment spending: 23% growth for 2014 06/04/2013 Fab equipment spending will grow two percent year-over-year (US$ 32.5 billion) for 2013 and about 23 to 27 percent in 2014 ($41 billion) according to the May edition of the SEMI World Fab Forecast. Fab construction spending, which can be a strong indicator for future equipment spending, is expected to grow 6.5 percent ($6.6 billion) in 2013, followed by a decline of 18 percent ($5.4 billion) in 2014. The new World Fab Forecast report covers fab information on over 1,140 facilities, including such details as capacities, technology nodes, product types, and spending for construction and equipment for any cleanroom wafer facility by quarter. Fab equipment spending for the second half of 2013 is expected to be much stronger with a 32 percent growth rate or $18.5 billion compared to the first half of 2013. The equipment spending increase in the second half is attributed to growing semiconductor demand and improving average selling price for chips. 2014 is expected to have about 23 to 27 percent growth year-over-year (YoY) to reach about $41 billion, which would be an all-time record. Looking at product types, the largest amounts of spending on fab equipment in 2013 will come from the foundry sector, which increases by about 21 percent. This is driven mainly by capex increases by TSMC. The memory sector is expected to have an increase of only one percent — after a 35 percent decline in the previous year. The MPU sector is expected to grow by about five percent. A double-digit increase in the Analog sector in 2013 will still translate into low absolute dollar amounts, compared to the other sectors.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1370579516539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 00:31:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370580399086-5</Id><Title>A good jobs report tomorrow and the stock should cross $25.</Title><Msg>That is if no Analyst bad mouths the pig.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370580399086</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 00:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370580867129-6</Id><Topic><Title>I could use some help with this "cannibalization" logic.</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370578027620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 00:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to do some research about stocks. The book, "Securities Analysis" by Graham and Dodd is a start. If that doesn't help you understand stocks, try the book "Where are all the customers yatchs". Good luck.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370580867129</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 00:54:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370581198168-7</Id><Topic><Title>I could use some help with this "cannibalization" logic.</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370578027620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 00:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>haha. i have finance degree. my post was to illustrate that the bear analysts are looking the wrong way. i was hoping some one who understands them better could help me understand their logic... because it doesn't seem to match "usable" logic. time will tell.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370581198168</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 00:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370582486530-8</Id><Title>Tablets did not cannibalize PCs for gamers</Title><Msg>The ability to have more than one graphics card (SLI and Crossfire) held off the PC refresh. Most games are graphic intensive, not CPU intensive. Stronger CPUs and multi-threading doesn't help most games, yet. SLI and Crossfire extended the refresh from 3 years to 5 years. Most gamers buy a good, solid motherboard and a really good graphics card. Two to three years later, another card. Only towards the end, when the best CPU for the motherboard is about $200-250, will they upgrade the CPU. Tablets are something you control your TV and music with. Something on which you play Angry Birds and Candy Crush, or keep your kids busy. Now it will change with Windows tablets. When the gamers refresh, it will be everyone who bought Sandy Bridge and before, not Ivy Bridge. Everyone running XP, not Win 7. If you want to know when the next big refresh will be for gamers, count 5 years forward from start of SLI and Crossfire.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370582486530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 01:21:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370582813816-9</Id><Topic><Title>Ashraf - tried</Title><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370574991211</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What ever, you are full of s. Yahoo either deletes the whole message of let you post whatever you have. It doesn't cut you off in mid sentence (unless reach character limit). You are a short and can't back up your argument.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370582813816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 01:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370584799259-10</Id><Topic><Title>Ashraf - tried</Title><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370574991211</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey vinnie, blo m e</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370584799259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 01:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370587849985-11</Id><Topic><Title>I could use some help with this "cannibalization" logic.</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370578027620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 00:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, I agree with you. You can't stand around and bash intel because the PC market is stagnant and supposedly being consumed by the growth in Tablet/phones, (without intel inside( then when intel gains traction in tablets/phones, say that intel will cannibalise their PC sales. My thoughts are that intel is doing two things; 1. Maintaining their share of PC/Server sales. 2. Regaining their share of netbook (PC) type chips, displaced by ARM in media consumption devices. All this whilst enjoying the 300% rise in popularity of tablet type devices.</Msg><Username>gooddigger</Username><Timestamp>1370587849985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 02:50:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370596202312-12</Id><Topic><Title>I could use some help with this "cannibalization" logic.</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370578027620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 00:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry. I wasn't trying to be rude. I appreciate the advice. It's nice to see civility on this board. I hope the "haha" didn't come off the wrong way.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370596202312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 05:10:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370599875139-13</Id><Topic><Title>I could use some help with this "cannibalization" logic.</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370578027620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 00:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has been cannibalizing its own products for decades. Cannibalization was part of Andy Grove's "only the paranoid survive mantra" and its why consumers have enjoyed buying PC's with double the speed for the same money for nearly 30 years. The history shows Intel knows how to do this and make industry-leading profit. In the late 90's the price for a reasonably configured IBM Thinkpad laptop was about $3500. Intel did well. By 2003 an even more powerful Thinkpad could be had for $1800. Intel still did well. ASP's for laptops dropped to maybe $500 and Intel continues to make great profit. Why is this? Because while the ASP's are changing Intel also increases its efficiency in chip production that allows them to expand the market while making great margins. At the same time by absorbing additional functionality into their chipsets they increase their BOM, and they provide more after-market software and services including security. Intel has been pushing down the price of PC's while expanding the market for decades. They know how to do this very well. But you have to get a laugh from the crowd that said "Intel would never" make a CPU that competes with ARM then turn around and say, "Sure, but Intel can't make money selling these low priced tablets". What you need to know is that the industry leader always makes money.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1370599875139</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 06:11:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370600349630-14</Id><Topic><Title>Derivatives Shifting</Title><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1370237011973</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 01:23:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do not stay in the market into the weekend!</Msg><Username>geraldomcginty</Username><Timestamp>1370600349630</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 06:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370600615649-15</Id><Title>why did pre-market start at 5:45 with INTC down 0.35? Anything besides "Derivatives Shifting"</Title><Msg>6:04 @ down 0.27 I can't find any real news. What's the word?</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370600615649</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 06:23:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370601550664-16</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Stock: Getting Its Mojo Back</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370575873186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>can of bulls ...or cannibals ? Mopho or mojoe ? 24.4 on worries.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1370601550664</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 06:39:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370602044973-17</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Stock: Getting Its Mojo Back</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370575873186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samsung top end smart phone lower growth issues Google it.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1370602044973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 06:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370604557855-18</Id><Topic><Title>why did pre-market start at 5:45 with INTC down 0.35? Anything besides "Derivatives Shifting"</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370600615649</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 06:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is very sad. Seems to me the bear analysts are working overtime to create doubt and disillusion. I have grown tired of the especially sickening theatrics of these analysts but I won't allow my defiance to cost me as dearly as I have in the past. I wonder where are the other 20 or so analysts who have rated INTC as a hold? The timing of this analyst assault is perfect to work against the stock while a market correction is looming. INTC gave up all it's gains since the grand Haswell/computex exposure. How sick is that? INTEL needs to do some type of damage control. .</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1370604557855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 07:29:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370604627809-19</Id><Title>amd downgraded to sell</Title><Msg>amd downgraded to sell again</Msg><Username>two_dollar_stock</Username><Timestamp>1370604627809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 07:30:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370605198519-20</Id><Title>Sterne Agee‘s Vijay Rakesh today reiterates a Neutral rating on the shares, and a $20 price target</Title><Msg>Sterne Agee‘s Vijay Rakesh today reiterates a Neutral rating on the shares, and a $20 price target, writing that this week’s announcements at the Computex trade show in Taipei, Taiwan, offer fodder for both bull and bear: We believe there is something in INTC for everybody. For the bulls, it is new product ramps at advanced nodes that close the power gap with ARM and significantly improve the chances of end-market success. For Bears it is that the core PC market which is still ~60%+ of revenues continues to be sluggish, Capex requirements for ROI continue to be high, and the success of Silvermont might hasten the decline of PCs and NBs.</Msg><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370605198519</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 07:39:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370605653475-21</Id><Title>Stock futures dip ahead of key May jobs report</Title><Msg>Stock futures dip ahead of key May jobs report</Msg><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370605653475</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 07:47:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370606199524-22</Id><Title>INTC DOWNGRADED TO SELL SELL SELL</Title><Msg>BAWAHAAAAAAAAAAA</Msg><Username>jerusalen339</Username><Timestamp>1370606199524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 07:56:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370607040958-23</Id><Title>downgraded by investment analysts at Piper Jaffray from a “neutral” rating to an “underweight”</Title><Msg>Is there no end to this #$%$?</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1370607040958</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:10:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370607138292-24</Id><Title>insiders know the job numbers ahead of time</Title><Msg>buy now. INTC will open at 25. Close at 26.</Msg><Username>dimebag_eddie</Username><Timestamp>1370607138292</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370607241039-25</Id><Topic><Title>downgraded by investment analysts at Piper Jaffray from a “neutral” rating to an “underweight”</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1370607040958</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:10:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is unbelievable. INTEL Mgmt., are you reading these analysts' comments? I am sure you have your ways (legal) to make these guys accountable. Last two days (downgrades) after quick run-up is a clear conspiracy...</Msg><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1370607241039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:14:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370607310195-26</Id><Title>Inventec demo 7-inch Windows 8 tablet powered by Intel Bay Trail</Title><Msg>Inventec Lyon reference design specs: •7-inch IPS panel at 1280 x 800 screen resolution with 10-point capacitive multi-touch •1.66GHz Intel Bay Trail processor •2GB of RAM •64/128GB of storage •Front and rear cameras, parts can be specified by buyers •Ports: microSD card slot, micro USB, micro HDMI port and a headset jack •Wi-Fi only, 3G and LTE versions are not planned •Dimensions are approx 200 x 120 x 11mm, weighing 470g •Aluminium construction and four colour options •Windows 8, but it is intended to ship with Windows 8.1 I noticed during the video that the system had a recorded Windows Experience Index of 2.0 which is pretty low, but as most will know this ‘benchmark’ score is determined by the performance of the weakest part of the system. This system is going to come with Windows 8.1 when it ships in “autumn this year” when this Windows update is launched. MobileGeeks note that the battery life is currently about half of what it should be when the drivers are optimised; it should last 10 hours in that case. It may also be the case of the Windows Experience Index score is currently being hobbled by an unoptimised graphics driver, for instance.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1370607310195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370607441135-27</Id><Topic><Title>downgraded by investment analysts at Piper Jaffray from a “neutral” rating to an “underweight”</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1370607040958</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:10:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No end till the big houses cover a large % of the huge short positions they are stuck in.</Msg><Username>r.idonius</Username><Timestamp>1370607441135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370607539529-28</Id><Topic><Title>Tablets did not cannibalize PCs for gamers</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370582486530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 01:21:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are numerous tasks for which smaller screen tablets will not cannibalize desktops or even some notebooks. Ask any software developer, video editor, financial analysts, web designer or content creator and they will tell you that multiple monitors and large displays deliver much better productivity than even a standard-sized 22" desktop display. The thought of someone using a tiny 10" tablet or an 8" or 7" tablet as a substitute for these tasks is laughable. Plus there is the raw performance advantage of the desktop CPU, the high-end graphics accelerator and potentially terabytes of high-speed local storage. Once a person has the above they will likely ALSO have an Ultrabook or high-end notebook and they may probably also want a dual-boot Windows/Android tablet to handle minor business tasks and personal content consumption. What is important is that the various devices offer 100% compatibility with their network and critical software. The best way to achieve this is to have x86 across all the devices. A Haswell tablet, depending on the configuration may give offer some overlap to a notebook's capabilities but Haswell tablets will deliver roughly the same revenue to Intel as a notebook. A Bay Trail class tablet is an extension to the core tools, it isn't a substitute.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1370607539529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:18:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370607627519-29</Id><Title>Piper is Sell-side Analis try to scare you:his Firm wants to buy INTC if you sell</Title><Msg>Win-Win strategy: Buy INTC SHort ARM, I can see ARMH will be in the 20's in ayear</Msg><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1370607627519</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:20:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370607716800-30</Id><Topic><Title>INTC DOWNGRADED TO SELL SELL SELL</Title><Username>jerusalen339</Username><Timestamp>1370606199524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 07:56:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like a bleating sheep. BTW Sheep aren't very bright.</Msg><Username>r.idonius</Username><Timestamp>1370607716800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:21:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370608783834-31</Id><Topic><Title>Tablets did not cannibalize PCs for gamers</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370582486530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 01:21:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also, FWIW nearly all the Clovertrail+/Bay Trail tablets demoed at Computex have been configured with 32 bit not 64 bit Windows. More than likely this is a business choice not a technical limitation but if tablets come the 32 bit Windows version it will limit the amount of RAM and overall performance of these systems. This may also be one of the differentiators between a Haswell tablet and Bay Trail going forward.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1370608783834</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:39:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370608868444-32</Id><Title>Intel drops on downgrade Piper Jaffray cuts chip giant to underweight</Title><Msg>Intel drops on downgrade Piper Jaffray cuts chip giant to underweight</Msg><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370608868444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:41:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370609059109-33</Id><Title>Feds as now limited effects on unemployment at 7.6% vs 7.5%: Stop QE now!!!</Title><Msg>Stop wasting $85B for banksters &amp; put $85B in structural change...like education.....building road...school....University....Solar....Energy....Lithium....R&amp;D....Health Sciences....Technology.....!!! and also protect kids in Oklahoma's schools....!!!</Msg><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370609059109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370609243141-34</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is no ANd</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1370566425786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:53:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "battle" between the ARM ISA and Intel (x86) has yet to start and will last the bulk of the rest of the decade. Personally, I still think it can be a win-win for both. Currently there is only a small crossover (Intel low end V ARM high end) in the CPU space and this will expand over the next few years as is it becomes more about the SoC and total solution rather than just the CPU alone. It's firms like QCOM and not ARM (the company) that Intel has to "worry" about. As it stands today - in terms of shipping product (and thus market share) - neither side has really done anything yet (in terms of taking market share). Despite all the positive noise about Intel's app processor SoC's for smart phones, she's still has less than 1% of the market. It's the same for the ARM ISA server push, well less than 1%.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1370609243141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:47:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370609690428-35</Id><Title>We are entering Intel warning season..</Title><Msg>This is the time (next week) for them to warn if they are not meeting estimates. A week or 2 before their "quiet period". Analysts have put a lot of fear into shareholders.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1370609690428</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:54:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370610050176-36</Id><Title>MISM is the next big gainer</Title><Msg>Have you checked out the chart on MISM. It looks prime to make a huge run to atleast double its current price.</Msg><Username>gfry679</Username><Timestamp>1370610050176</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:00:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370610273509-37</Id><Topic><Title>Feds as now limited effects on unemployment at 7.6% vs 7.5%: Stop QE now!!!</Title><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370609059109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:44:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah just what we need more centralized power and decisions made by political horse trading. The market place makes better R&amp;D, energy, education, etc. decisions then any bureau. See the former USSR and current DPRK for details.</Msg><Username>everywhere41</Username><Timestamp>1370610273509</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:04:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370610320329-38</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like I have found another winner. Check out MISM</Title><Username>rworkman979</Username><Timestamp>1370449813504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:30:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing out this</Msg><Username>angelzamora528</Username><Timestamp>1370610320329</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:05:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370610503536-39</Id><Topic><Title>Intel drops on downgrade Piper Jaffray cuts chip giant to underweight</Title><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370608868444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:41:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a JOKE</Msg><Username>bridgecrew</Username><Timestamp>1370610503536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:08:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370610540212-40</Id><Title>100% Dividend Increase</Title><Msg>Unbelievable news just came out after the close yesterday! Concurrent (CCUR) is raising their quarterly cash dividend from $0.06 to $0.12 , an increase of 100%, with their next quarterly cash dividend being paid to shareholders this month! This equals an annual dividend of $0.48 and CCUR closed yesterday at an extremely undervalued $7.08! CCUR's dividend yield is now an insanely high 6.8%! CCUR's Mediahawk VX on demand video server technology just surpassed Cisco (CSCO)'s CDE 250 to become the #1 highest rated VOD product used by pay-TV companies, according to Current Analysis (industry leading unbiased review source)! Over the past 4 quarters, CCUR's operating profit has skyrocketed from $187,000 to $413,000 to $876,000 to $1,233,000 for HUGE growth of 559%! CCUR's profits could continue to rapidly increase in the upcoming quarters with the recent signing of a HUGE contract with Virgin Media! CCUR's MediaHawk VX unified CDN solution will be used to support Virgin TV Anywhere, a new cloud-based entertainment service that gives customers the flexibility to enjoy their favorite TV content on computers, laptops, tablets and smartphones! Last quarter, excluding share-based compensation and non-cash amortization, CCUR earned non-GAAP EPS of $0.16! This puts CCUR on track to earn non-GAAP EPS of $0.64 this calendar year! A P/E of just 20 to 30 based on potential full year non-GAAP EPS of $0.64 would make CCUR a $12.80 to $19.20 per share stock! CCUR looks ready to explode in the upcoming days!</Msg><Username>asj48493</Username><Timestamp>1370610540212</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:09:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370610765569-41</Id><Title>Piper downgrade today destroying any INTC momentum</Title><Msg>My model now says expect a test of $24 very soon.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1370610765569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370610947082-42</Id><Topic><Title>Piper downgrade today destroying any INTC momentum</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1370610765569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what a BS?</Msg><Username>imbluesclues</Username><Timestamp>1370610947082</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:15:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370611014248-43</Id><Title>Pre-Opening Shenanigans</Title><Msg>Pre-opening did have Intel down by 25 cents and ARM up by 60 cents. Now Intel down by 10 cents and ARM is down by 76 cents. Now who would engage in such pre-market manipulation? Well, other than the big Wall Street firm skkumbaggs. LOL</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370611014248</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:16:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370611279644-44</Id><Topic><Title>Feds as now limited effects on unemployment at 7.6% vs 7.5%: Stop QE now!!!</Title><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370609059109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:44:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no....just put the money at the right place.....not GOV dictated...lol</Msg><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370611279644</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370611279824-45</Id><Title>CNBC PETE the con man and Wall Street suckered you all INTC what 2 to 3 days before all the downgrades</Title><Msg>And what you don't think WALL STREET didn't know all the downgrades were coming. What a FN joke SEC should put someone in jail for the CON job they pulled</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611279824</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370611289908-46</Id><Title>Intel exec says Silvermont trumps ARM in power, performance</Title><Msg>Intel executive Dadi Perlmutter responds to ARM's claims of processor superiority over Silvermont A top Intel executive said the power and performance battle with ARM is over, because Intel's upcoming chips based on its Silvermont architecture are ahead on key metrics required to deliver strong performance and battery life on smartphones and tablets. Intel's upcoming mobile chips based on the Silvermont are better at power and performance than ARM's fastest Cortex-A15 chips, said Dadi Perlmutter, executive vice president and general manager of the Intel Architecture Group, in an interview at the Computex trade show this week. "Cortex-A15 is not even close to Silvermont. They are higher power and much behind us on performance which means they are on the wrong scale," Perlmutter said. The response comes after ARM at Computex claimed processor superiority over Intel, saying its processors are a generation ahead on performance and power draw. ARM made comments about processor superiority when it introduced the new Cortex-A12 processors targeted at smartphones and tablets from US$200 to $350. "Based on what I've seen on [Cortex] A15 so far, which is the top of the line on performance, it's not anywhere near [Silvermont], not on performance, not on power," Perlmutter said. From computerworld</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370611289908</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:21:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370611320647-47</Id><Topic><Title>Pre-Opening Shenanigans</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370611014248</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:16:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallace, seriously ?</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1370611320647</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:22:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370611382402-48</Id><Topic><Title>Piper downgrade today destroying any INTC momentum</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1370610765569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First of all, you don't have a "model" unless it is one you put together with airplane glue. Secondly you don't have the half million shares that your frequent posts ..."just bought 10K more shares" would assume.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1370611382402</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:23:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370611472660-49</Id><Topic><Title>Intel exec says Silvermont trumps ARM in power, performance</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370611289908</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:21:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perlmutter said that improved performance per watt on Silvermont chips comes through improved circuitry and power management. Silvermont chips will be made using a 22-nanometer process that introduces a more efficient 3D transistor structure to pack in more circuitry while reducing the size of a chip. Intel has a manufacturing advantage over its rivals, and its performance per watt will get better with its mobile chips code-named Airmont next year, Perlmutter said At the same time, Perlmutter said his eye will not move away from ARM. "I never ignore competition. If they don't do a good job now, they will do a better job next time. But we are not going to stand still," Perlmutter said.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370611472660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370611514823-50</Id><Topic><Title>Feds as now limited effects on unemployment at 7.6% vs 7.5%: Stop QE now!!!</Title><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370609059109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:44:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is giving the money ? the government. So it becomes a political process instead of a market process of where the right place is.</Msg><Username>everywhere41</Username><Timestamp>1370611514823</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370611527957-51</Id><Topic><Title>Intel exec says Silvermont trumps ARM in power, performance</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370611289908</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:21:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Going forward, more performance will be needed on chips with less power consumption, Perlmutter said. He rejected the idea of "good-enough" computing, saying tablets and smartphones could use more performance to make the user experience richer. "This all requires computing. It's all going to be done in smaller form factors while not standing still on performance. It's just going to get better," Perlmutter said. He said human interfaces, like voice interaction, gaming, 3D modeling and gesture recognition, will reach mobile computing devices someday. Intel will make mobile devices richer than just mundane e-mail and web browsing clients. "Computers still struggle with basic voice recognition. Good enough computing? No way. It's good enough computing for what's being done today, but completely not good enough for where people will need to go," Perlmutter said.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370611527957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370611532657-52</Id><Topic><Title>Piper downgrade today destroying any INTC momentum</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1370610765569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy under $22 for long term.....QE is about to looose momentum....even with QE unemployment raising to 7.6% so??? Sell on the news today???</Msg><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370611532657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:25:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370611608584-53</Id><Title>I DO HOPE YOU KIDDIES ARE</Title><Msg>BUYING the dips. Be long and strong kiddies,buy those dips,and drink all your milk.</Msg><Username>bigcraigc</Username><Timestamp>1370611608584</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:26:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370611629242-54</Id><Topic><Title>Feds as now limited effects on unemployment at 7.6% vs 7.5%: Stop QE now!!!</Title><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370609059109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:44:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's our money....the Gov money no???....we just need to tell Obama who is the boss...meaning tax payers!!!</Msg><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370611629242</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370611648826-55</Id><Title>SEC someone should go to JAIL for the CON job CNBC and WALL STREET pulled on all the suckers that were coned into buying INTC</Title><Msg>right before all the downgrades, WHAT a CON JOB they pulled off. PUT someone in JAIL</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611648826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370611765666-56</Id><Title>Next Up</Title><Msg>Intel Mac upgrades on Monday! Then on to the very important Samsung event on the 20th!!!</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370611765666</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:29:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370611793385-57</Id><Topic><Title>SEC someone should go to JAIL for the CON job CNBC and WALL STREET pulled on all the suckers that were coned into buying INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611648826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SEC someone needs to go to JAIL for IN YOUR FACE CON JOB ,THEY pulled off</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611793385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:29:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370611872731-58</Id><Topic><Title>SEC someone should go to JAIL for the CON job CNBC and WALL STREET pulled on all the suckers that were coned into buying INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611648826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THIS is as bad as the PENNY stock crooks with fake companies</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611872731</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:31:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370611922850-59</Id><Title>INTC: Buy under $22</Title><Msg>all goodies are priced in....!!!</Msg><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370611922850</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:32:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370611937685-60</Id><Title>Intel CEO Krzanich - defend your shareholders</Title><Msg>A total disgrace of what the bear analysts did to shareholders this week during a big Intel product announcement. Borderline illegal. Show some leadership Mr. CEO!</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1370611937685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:32:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370612040920-61</Id><Topic><Title>Feds as now limited effects on unemployment at 7.6% vs 7.5%: Stop QE now!!!</Title><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370609059109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:44:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree it is our money, but the process of where it goes to precisely is determined by politics not economics. It would be better left in our hands. SEE chariman Mao for more info. Since the recipients of these grants did not earn it they would not value it to the same degree and they are now beholden to the government, Demo or Repub.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1370612040920</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:34:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370612081950-62</Id><Topic><Title>SEC someone should go to JAIL for the CON job CNBC and WALL STREET pulled on all the suckers that were coned into buying INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611648826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone needs to go to JAIL for this CON job Wall Street pulled on investors</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370612081950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370612266615-63</Id><Topic><Title>SEC someone should go to JAIL for the CON job CNBC and WALL STREET pulled on all the suckers that were coned into buying INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611648826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe the con job is this outfit downgrading intc. I don't see where he gave a valid reason, he just said it without any supporting facts. Another con job</Msg><Username>aball1941</Username><Timestamp>1370612266615</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370612310721-64</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Stock: Getting Its Mojo Back</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370575873186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wally wrong again.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1370612310721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:38:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370612332733-65</Id><Title>Intel Downgrade...</Title><Msg>Just wait a few months, when Intel chips gain market share in Tablets and Phones...SP above $30</Msg><Username>donalhump</Username><Timestamp>1370612332733</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:38:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370612354237-66</Id><Title>Pipper Jaffray, is short INTC, well before their downgrade.</Title><Msg>Goldman Sachs also does the the same thing. Holding and loading up short positions on INTC before they harshly downgrade a stock. They may cover quickly since other firms have no reason to downgrade. This is easy quick profits for Piper Jaffrey and their customer accounts.</Msg><Username>bobpaulovich</Username><Timestamp>1370612354237</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:39:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370612363894-67</Id><Topic><Title>INTC: Buy under $22</Title><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370611922850</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:32:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? Once a POS always a POS!</Msg><Username>bridgecrew</Username><Timestamp>1370612363894</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:39:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370612512994-68</Id><Topic><Title>Piper downgrade today destroying any INTC momentum</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1370610765569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All true, but there is some entertainment value (mostly laughs) worth keeping him off of the ignore list. Like your comment about the airplane model, but based on his comments not sure he could build even a model airplane,....</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1370612512994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:41:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370612650039-69</Id><Topic><Title>SEC someone should go to JAIL for the CON job CNBC and WALL STREET pulled on all the suckers that were coned into buying INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611648826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone needs to go to JAIL this is even worse than the PENNY stock fake companies most people NO not to invest in them.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370612650039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:44:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370612666537-70</Id><Title>Piper Unknown - Data Lacks Integrity .. INTC will be 30 Soon</Title><Msg>Everyone knows INTC has some great products in the works and guess what companies are still upgrading their PCs! yes the tool they have to work on ... Cant work on a tablet no power and not eay to use. Sorry IPADs are toys for the uneducated. to surf and use FB. BTWL do you own DD REV and Income are solid only can improve with new products and new Haswell chip! No brainer IMHO</Msg><Username>beer.snob</Username><Timestamp>1370612666537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:44:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370612719090-71</Id><Title>ARM in Freefall - Again</Title><Msg>ARM down 97 cents now, headed to breaking $40 again. The Intel/ARM differential is positive again today after a mere one day in the other direction out of weeks. The differential is the best indicator that the tipping point has been reached. The big Wall Street firms are obviously frantic to develop an exit strategy for their short positions. Yesterday they got their heads handed to them in a basket. Let's see how they do the rest of today...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370612719090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370612724711-72</Id><Topic><Title>SEC someone should go to JAIL for the CON job CNBC and WALL STREET pulled on all the suckers that were coned into buying INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611648826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Things like this is why people are not investing anymore, The SEC and our GOV need to fix this</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370612724711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:45:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370612762754-73</Id><Topic><Title>so much for Wallys tipping point, he is palpably stunned</Title><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1370529611913</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:40:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wally are you always this wrong about so many things ?</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1370612762754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370612803430-74</Id><Topic><Title>SEC someone should go to JAIL for the CON job CNBC and WALL STREET pulled on all the suckers that were coned into buying INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611648826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>investors smart index give piper Jefferies a 2.8 percent accuracy rating on ratings of intc. Take this info if you like, but a 2.8 percent accuracy don't mean much to me.</Msg><Username>aball1941</Username><Timestamp>1370612803430</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:46:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370612878285-75</Id><Title>INCREDIBLE, INSTITUTION INVESTORS STEALING SHARES FROM SLEEPING RETAIL INVESTORS</Title><Msg>GOOD TIME TO BUY FOR THE PUSH TO $28</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370612878285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:47:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370612937835-76</Id><Title>WHY DO I HAVE THE FEELING IT WILL END GREEN TODAY?</Title><Msg>Because instititutions and buying hand over fist right now</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370612937835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370612983832-77</Id><Title>HASWELL CAN GO FANLESS INTO TABLETS!</Title><Msg>INSTITUTIONS ARE BUYING LIKE MAD RIGHT NOW</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370612983832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:49:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370612984102-78</Id><Title>Looks Like the Fudd Fade Started Early</Title><Msg>Hmmmm, are the big Wall Street boys fading already?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370612984102</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370613037331-79</Id><Topic><Title>WHY DO I HAVE THE FEELING IT WILL END GREEN TODAY?</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370612937835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:48:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I actually agree. but head wally is still an irritant tho.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1370613037331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370613043714-80</Id><Title>Bearish analysista are trying to scare you (SA)</Title><Msg>http://seekingalpha.com/article/1487062-intel-bearish-analysts-are-trying-to-scare-you?source=email_investing_ideas&amp;ifp=0</Msg><Username>atlefx</Username><Timestamp>1370613043714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370613077994-81</Id><Topic><Title>SEC someone should go to JAIL for the CON job CNBC and WALL STREET pulled on all the suckers that were coned into buying INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611648826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"investors smart index give piper Jefferies a 2.8 percent accuracy rating on ratings of intc. Take this info if you like, but a 2.8 percent accuracy don't mean much to me." [I'm surprised it's that high...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613077994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:51:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370613152352-82</Id><Topic><Title>INCREDIBLE, INSTITUTION INVESTORS STEALING SHARES FROM SLEEPING RETAIL INVESTORS</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370612878285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:47:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some never learn.When the big money is flooding the press with negative stories its time to buy.</Msg><Username>r.idonius</Username><Timestamp>1370613152352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:52:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370613175273-83</Id><Topic><Title>INTC: Buy under $22</Title><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370611922850</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:32:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already did at $13 and then again at $21. What do I do next?</Msg><Username>dc7177</Username><Timestamp>1370613175273</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:52:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370613206207-84</Id><Topic><Title>Piper downgrade today destroying any INTC momentum</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1370610765569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is a fun clown to watch. ;^)</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1370613206207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370613276732-85</Id><Topic><Title>INTC: Buy under $22</Title><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370611922850</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:32:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Already did at $13 and then again at $21. What do I do next?" [Laugh out loud at Wall Street and the shills...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613276732</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:54:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370613337109-86</Id><Title>INSTITUTIONS HAVE BEEN BUYING SINCE $19</Title><Msg>THESE ANALysts BAD MOUTH AND PUSHED IT DOWN UNBELIEVABLY TO $19 AND THEY ARE STILL TRYING TO ADD SHARES NOW. When it's clear Intel will be dominate in mobile, the stock price will be over $30. Look how quickly it went from $20 to $24. Look for the same kind of move to $28 and similar moves to $40 by end of the year.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370613337109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:55:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370613408364-87</Id><Title>Good News</Title><Msg>There's just too much good news out there now for Wall Street to perpetuate the myth that Intel isn't doing well. Intel shorts now in freefall...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613408364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:56:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370613467373-88</Id><Title>Intel Shorts Roar Out of the Blocks</Title><Msg>Then fall down, go boom...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613467373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370613497471-89</Id><Topic><Title>HASWELL CAN GO FANLESS INTO TABLETS!</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370612983832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:49:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This chip is really amazing for all kinds of uses. INTC are receiving a lot of inquiries about this new technically advanced chip .. and this is just PH1</Msg><Username>beer.snob</Username><Timestamp>1370613497471</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:58:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370613621120-90</Id><Title>Check out AnandTech's story on Bay Trail</Title><Msg>anandtechDOTcom/show/7038/intel-demonstrates-bay-trailt-running-windows-8-and-android-422 Last month Intel took the covers off its next-generation Atom microarchitecture, codename Silvermont. The first consumer implementation of Silvermont will be Bay Trail, a quad-core SoC for tablets. At Computex, Intel demonstrated its own Bay Trail-T reference platform: a 10-inch 2560 x 1440 tablet, weighing 611 grams and about the thickness of a 3rd/4th generation iPad (Intel wouldn't provide specific measurements, but it felt close). This reference design is a huge step for low end Windows 8 tablets as well as Intel. If Intel's reference design uses a 2560 x 1440 panel, it's safe to say that at least some of its customers will do the same. The fact that Intel is also showing the reference platform running the latest version of Android means that we'll finally see Intel go after the Android tablet market as well. It's too early to talk about performance or battery life, but Intel promises that both will be very good.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370613621120</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:00:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370613642413-91</Id><Topic><Title>INTC: Buy under $22</Title><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370611922850</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:32:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big boys selling high....to retails.....and will short from Hamptons soon or later???</Msg><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370613642413</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:00:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370613715280-92</Id><Topic><Title>Looks Like the Fudd Fade Started Early</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370612984102</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, one of the more impressive fades in Fudd history now taking place!</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613715280</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:01:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370613723216-93</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Shorts Roar Out of the Blocks</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613467373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great to see that you are belting out that 70 hour work week again this week and paying your fair share. Boom!</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613723216</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:02:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370613787832-94</Id><Topic><Title>Looks Like the Fudd Fade Started Early</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370612984102</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The market is up nicely and Intel is in the red. You are one serious piece of work.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613787832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:03:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370613819324-95</Id><Title>Back in Black</Title><Msg>I'm now back in the black on my ARM puts and I didn't even have to wait until January. Thought I'd better post it up because I know a lot of the shills were really worried about me. LOL</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613819324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:03:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370613820332-96</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Shorts Roar Out of the Blocks</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613467373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally....quit stealing my lines.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1370613820332</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:03:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370614005803-97</Id><Topic><Title>Piper downgrade today destroying any INTC momentum</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1370610765569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you tell me what was Piper's opinion on the stock prior to today? How accurate was he in his upgrade/downgrade?</Msg><Username>logietan</Username><Timestamp>1370614005803</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:06:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370614033568-98</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Shorts Roar Out of the Blocks</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613467373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You could have said "boom, boom, boom"...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370614033568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:07:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370614039686-99</Id><Title>Piper Is A #$%$</Title><Msg>Their clients must have loaded up.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1370614039686</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370614104014-100</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Shorts Roar Out of the Blocks</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613467373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, everyone who bgh the Baron's bounce above 25 is escatic, terrible price action in INTC as the nasdaq rallies well off the lows of yesterday. Congratulations, 3 years and you're up .50</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1370614104014</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:08:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370614185134-101</Id><Title>Good Insidermonkey article!</Title><Msg>.insidermonkeyDOTcom/blog/intel-corporation-intc-news-triumph-over-arm-holdings-plc-armh-4th-generation-processor-16-million-investment-more-163102/</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1370614185134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:09:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370614194481-102</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Shorts Roar Out of the Blocks</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613467373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Congratulations, 3 years and you're up .50" [Congratulations, 6 months and you are down $5.30]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370614194481</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:09:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370614293036-103</Id><Title>Shorts Miss Yet Another Opportunity to Cover</Title><Msg>Fudd fade just happened too fast for them. Boom, boom, boom, boom...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370614293036</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370614306452-104</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Shorts Roar Out of the Blocks</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613467373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When I said it before you were disparaging, now you have stolen it. FOUL is called !!!</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1370614306452</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370614363989-105</Id><Title>I don't think Krzanich has sent over the required #$%$ and blow, yet.</Title><Msg>The bears are out of ammo and we're going to finish green today. There should be some sort of investigation. Even if it's not illegal, the public won't like the timing. Although, we don't trust them anyway, what's left to lose?</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370614363989</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:12:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370614414499-106</Id><Topic><Title>I don't think Krzanich has sent over the required #$%$ and blow, yet.</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370614363989</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:12:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and by #$%$, I mean h00ker5.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1370614414499</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370614471076-107</Id><Title>Running Out of Baskets</Title><Msg>Intel longs keep handing shorts their heads in a basket...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370614471076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:14:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370614545851-108</Id><Title>TIME TO BUY, THIS THING IS GOING TO EXPLODE NEXT 2 WEEKS ON ANY DESIGN WINS WITH APPLE OR SAMSUNG</Title><Msg>Next week is wwdc. I have a feeling there will be a surprise instore. Following is samsung june 20 event, intc will explode if intel inside galaxy s4 phone</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370614545851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:15:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370614649860-109</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Shorts Roar Out of the Blocks</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613467373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, the ref has left the building. Piper Jaffray wanted to talk to him in the parking lot...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370614649860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:17:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370614807996-110</Id><Title>GO WATCH THE INTEL KEYNOTE WITH TOM KILROY</Title><Msg>ITS AT THE INTC SITE. 14:15 Merrifield sample phone 16:40 Bay Trail sample (surface pro look-alike) 30:05 fanless Haswell THESE ARE KILLER PRODUCTS WE'LL BE SEEING STARTING IN A COUPLE MONTHS FROM NOW. INTEL WILL DOMINATE</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370614807996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:20:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370614841132-111</Id><Title>I must say if a stock goes up on a downgrade it is going to keep going up</Title><Msg>as it is said so it will be.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1370614841132</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:20:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370615017006-112</Id><Title>Downgrades followed by</Title><Msg>warning. Soon.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1370615017006</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:23:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370615183769-113</Id><Topic><Title>Downgrades followed by</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1370615017006</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:23:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only warning intc will give is to their competition.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1370615183769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:26:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370615203908-114</Id><Topic><Title>Running Out of Baskets</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370614471076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:14:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$24 was the raging debate in 2011 and here we are 2 years later. Yes INTC is sure a screamer.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1370615203908</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370615351881-115</Id><Topic><Title>Good News</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370613408364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:56:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>myth? where's the $3 eps you spoke of years ago? Until they deliver it is not a myth. ceo even quit early</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1370615351881</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:29:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370615387770-116</Id><Topic><Title>INSTITUTIONS HAVE BEEN BUYING SINCE $19</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370613337109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look how fast it went from $30 is in the bag to $20.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1370615387770</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:29:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370615472468-117</Id><Topic><Title>SEC someone should go to JAIL for the CON job CNBC and WALL STREET pulled on all the suckers that were coned into buying INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611648826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pumpers like ww but they have a huge audience, ww only has a few fools in here</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1370615472468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:31:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370615522795-118</Id><Title>POOR tiglet2l, HE LISTENED TO COVELLO AND WAITED FOR INTC TO GO TO $16 AND MISSED MOVE FROM $19 TO $25</Title><Msg>WHAT A LOOSER</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370615522795</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:32:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370615566737-119</Id><Topic><Title>SEC someone should go to JAIL for the CON job CNBC and WALL STREET pulled on all the suckers that were coned into buying INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611648826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a bank CD</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1370615566737</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:32:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370615597267-120</Id><Title>Haswell-based tablets have the potential to devastate the market</Title><Msg>Intel's (NASDAQ: INTC) new fourth generation Core processors (Haswell) included low power Systems on Chip (SOCs) that are being used in thin tablets without fans, a first for the Core series. These Haswell-based tablets have the potential to devastate the market for ARM Holdings' (NASDAQ: ARMH) tablet processors. Without a swift response from ARM's Common Platform partners, International Business Machines (NYSE: IBM), Samsung, and GlobalFoundries, the ARM processor ecosystem could lie in ruins by this time next year. Compelling improvements Intel made a number of significant improvements that enabled it to fit a Core processor into the thin tablet form factor, but the main ones were improved power management and the development of single chip SOCs, eliminating the Platform Controller Hub, an accessory chip needed by the previous Core generation. These Core SOCs still consume roughly five times the power (5-10 Watts) compared to a typical ARM processor, but they are usually more than five times faster. Getting into the 5-10 Watt range allows these SOCs to be used in a tablet, and it can be thin since no fan is required.</Msg><Username>beer.snob</Username><Timestamp>1370615597267</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:33:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370615610844-121</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell-based tablets have the potential to devastate the market</Title><Username>beer.snob</Username><Timestamp>1370615597267</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:33:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow !</Msg><Username>beer.snob</Username><Timestamp>1370615610844</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:33:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370615739124-122</Id><Title>Intel's Haswell Tablet Breakthrough</Title><Msg>Intel's (NASDAQ: INTC) new fourth generation Core processors (Haswell) included low power Systems on Chip (SOCs) that are being used in thin tablets without fans, a first for the Core series. These Haswell-based tablets have the potential to devastate the market for ARM Holdings' (NASDAQ: ARMH) tablet processors. Without a swift response from ARM's Common Platform partners, International Business Machines (NYSE: IBM), Samsung, and GlobalFoundries, the ARM processor ecosystem could lie in ruins by this time next year. This is the first paragraph.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1370615739124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:35:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370615961028-123</Id><Title>that indian guy is</Title><Msg>eating some toxic curry</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1370615961028</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:39:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370616035278-124</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Haswell Tablet Breakthrough</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1370615739124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:35:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The potential is huge and any analyst with integrity will know that... buying more off all the suckers selling.!</Msg><Username>beer.snob</Username><Timestamp>1370616035278</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:40:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370616142438-125</Id><Title>Intel Apps Processor Outperforms NVIDIA, Qualcomm, Samsung</Title><Msg>See press release by ABI research that just came out with the title above. ======================= Intel’s latest application processor, Z2580, sets the bar for performance and current drain in smartphones. It outperformed the competition in ABI Research’s benchmark testing of the Lenovo K900 smartphone, powered by Intel’s XMM6360 modem chipset and Z2580 application processor. Jim Mielke, VP of engineering at ABI research, notes: “The benchmarks were impressive but the real surprise was the current consumption recorded during the benchmarks; the new processor not only outperformed the competition in performance but it did so with up to half the current drain.” Mielke went on to add: “Intel did significant work to bring the current drain down on their well-recognized high-performance processors but the competitors did not help themselves. The ARM architecture used by nearly all of Intel’s competitors is well known for its low power performance but in bringing the processing power up closer to PC levels, the current drain has taken a significant hit.” Since high-end smartphones require this level of performance, Intel is well positioned for strong growth over the next few years. Mielke continues, “Combining the high-end modems (the XMM6360 is used in both the Lenovo K900 and the Samsung Galaxy S4 i9500) with their application processors for high- to mid-tier solutions, and single-chip EDGE chips for low-cost phones makes Intel a rare full portfolio provider.”</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1370616142438</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370616285181-126</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is no ANd</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1370566425786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:53:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. But it's going to stand that Intel will be successful growing in smartphone and tablets. ARMH has great designs that their FABs won't be able to execute on. The FABs are ARM's weak link and the most excellent opportunity Intel has to neutralize their threat. My point is that it won't matter for ARM because they have so many different avenues of growth. An 800MhZ ARM processor at 60nm is super old technology, but just think about how cheaply that they can be made. Throw it into a $10 SoC and it can go into appliances, car radios, and other gadgets. Even though it's old technology think about how much that little thing can do, especially if it's designed to only do a few tasks. This is magnitudes larger in scope than all the server business ARMH could ever realistically hope to get. Though I agree with Wallis most of the time I don't think that Intel wants every last ARM processor sale at the super low end. I don't believe Intel's intent is to take out ARMH from the market. Instead they are simply trying to neutralize ARMH's threat.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1370616285181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370616485822-127</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Apps Processor Outperforms NVIDIA, Qualcomm, Samsung</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1370616142438</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:42:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel's chip are a definite differentiator in the market.. huge market share improvement with new chip offering</Msg><Username>beer.snob</Username><Timestamp>1370616485822</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370616622590-128</Id><Title>Pit Boss in Hoboken</Title><Msg>Just back from Vegas, and noticed that the casino Pit Bosses remained in the shadows, running the show and calling all the shots. It reminds me of the High Frequency/Flash Traders who are working inside computer equipped basements across the River in Hoboken, N.J. High speed cable link-ups are directly connected to the stock exchanges to cut down the execution time. Every little bit of an advantage helps to increase the volume. It all starts by creating a false momentum and then quickly moving from both sides of each BID and ASK penny position until the magic number is reached. These massive computer systems make it easy and they joke about "shooting fish in a barrel". Then the hammer is slammed down in the blink of eye with a flick of the switch. Before the last trade is even executed, the next victim is being selected and the process begins all over again. This goes on thousands of times every market day and currently 65% of the market's volume is conducted by these High Frequency Traders. It has NOTHING to do with value or worth. There is NO analysis on the merits, sales, profits,dividends, outlook or CEO. A good stock is no different from a bad stock. All that matters in this casino is the spread and how quickly it takes to hit the magic number. As we speak, these trades being made by the millions and those 10 cents positions held for milliseconds add up. These Pit Bosses working the numbers in Hoboken, are dressed in $2,500 Italian suits and driven home in limos; they don't live in Jersey.</Msg><Username>sanorleans</Username><Timestamp>1370616622590</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370616737037-129</Id><Title>Looks like MISM is about to run. Forget (board)!</Title><Msg>Keep an eye on MISM, A little birdie told me that this thing is about to get a huge awarness campaign.</Msg><Username>jackson.hall659</Username><Timestamp>1370616737037</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:52:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370616919472-130</Id><Topic><Title>SEC someone should go to JAIL for the CON job CNBC and WALL STREET pulled on all the suckers that were coned into buying INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611648826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SEC put someone in JAIL for this CON job CNBC and Wall STREET pulled</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370616919472</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370617013996-131</Id><Title>Yet Another Big Wall Street Firm Short Exit Strategy Blows Up on the Launching Pad</Title><Msg>This one courtesy of Piper Jaffray. Amazing that the SEC can't see these guys colluding on price manipulation. How is it that these guys stay out of jail. Well, it was good for a laugh...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370617013996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370617313519-132</Id><Topic><Title>Yet Another Big Wall Street Firm Short Exit Strategy Blows Up on the Launching Pad</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370617013996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:56:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah Waldo, don't cha just love how much INTC is up on the week. nada, despite the Baron's pump. Meanwhile, off the lows yesterday, the QLD popped 3.00</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1370617313519</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370617556364-133</Id><Title>Lenovo launches K900 Intel phone in India.</Title><Msg>After announcing the K900 flagship device in January this year, Lenovo finally launched the phone in India. The phone, which comes with pretty solid specifications, is priced decently in the Indian market and will be available for sale July onwards. Lenovo K900 runs on the latest Android version Jelly Bean 4.2.2 out of the box. The phone or rather a phablet comes with a 5.5-inches IPS LCD capacitive touch-screen. The resolution is 1080 x 1920 pixels and the phone comes with Gorilla Glass 2. Under the hood of the Lenovo K900 runs a dual-core 2 GHz Intel Atom processor. Lenovo K900 comes with just one internal memory variant, 16 GB. However, there is a memory card slot and the memory can be expanded to an additional 32 GB via MicroSD card slot. Lenovo K900 comes with 2 GB RAM. The back panel sports a whopping 13 MP rear end snapper with dual-LED flash. The video-calling camera is 2 MP. The phone comes with features like geo-tagging, touch focus, face detection, auto-focus, etc. The phone does not have multiple colour options and comes with a non-removable 2500 mAh battery. Priced at Rs 32,900, the phone is a decent deal. While the phone skips the quad-core processor, Lenovo made up by pricing the phone in the sub-35k mark. Also, the 13 MP rear end camera will definitely be a strong selling point. While Lenovo K900 cannot be directly compared to other Android flagships like HTC One and Samsung Galaxy S4, the phone is definitely a strong phone in the tablet category. It mixes simplicity with interesting features and a strong camera. While Lenovo still needs to make a mark in the Indian market, with adequate marketing and decent pricing, the phone-maker can gain a slice of the burgeoning smartphone market. [ folks, this country has a population that competes with China. over 1.2 Billion! Simply 1% amounts to over 12 million units]</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1370617556364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:05:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370617793878-134</Id><Topic><Title>Yet Another Big Wall Street Firm Short Exit Strategy Blows Up on the Launching Pad</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370617013996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:56:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They got quite a bit more than a laugh out of it. Glad you enjoy it. When you were a kid you must have loved others knocking down your blocks.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1370617793878</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:09:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370617813121-135</Id><Title>If you haven’t seen MISM you need to drop everything else</Title><Msg>Hearing a rumor that MISM is about to get pumped</Msg><Username>alexander.beck495</Username><Timestamp>1370617813121</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:10:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370617891586-136</Id><Title>THEY'VE PINNED IT JUST UNDER $24.50</Title><Msg>FOR WEEKLY OPTIONS TO EXPIRE. The downgrade will was to get it under $24.50 this morning.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370617891586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:11:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370618031100-137</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo launches K900 Intel phone in India.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1370617556364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Many of the world’s fastest-growing smartphone markets are in Asia,” said JD Howard, vice president, Mobile Internet Digital Home business operations and business development. “Lenovo has built a strong smartphone base in China, and last year we began offering our smartphones in additional markets. The Lenovo K900 is a world-class smartphone, which will compete well around the world. Intel has been an ideal partner for developing the K900 and ensuring an outstanding user experience for our customers.” The new Intel® Atom™ processor platform ("Clover Trail+") brings Intel’s classic product strengths, including high performance that lets users enjoy smooth Web browsing, vibrant, glitch-free, full HD movies, and an Android* applications experience that launches fast and runs great. The product’s 2GHz dual core Intel Atom processing also features Intel® Hyper-Threading Technology, supporting four simultaneous application threads and further enhancing the overall efficiency of the Intel Atom cores and platform. “The K900 embodies the value propositions of high-performance Intel®architecture and great battery life with Lenovo’s product and design innovation,” said Hermann Eul, Intel vice president and general manager of the Mobile and Communications Group. “We look forward to our continued partnership with Lenovo across a range of mobile market segments, and to working closely with them to bring the K900 smartphone experience with Intel Inside® to more consumers around the world.”</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1370618031100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370618128300-138</Id><Topic><Title>SEC someone should go to JAIL for the CON job CNBC and WALL STREET pulled on all the suckers that were coned into buying INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611648826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CNBC and Wall Street con on INTC is even worse than the PENNY stock fraud with fake companies, Investors no know to invest in the PENNY stock fraud, But INTC is a DOW 30 company , Someone from CNBC and Wall Street needs to go to jail for this CON on INTC this time it is so IN YOUR FACE</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370618128300</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:15:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370618185280-139</Id><Topic><Title>THEY'VE PINNED IT JUST UNDER $24.50</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370617891586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:11:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And a mighty fine job they did.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1370618185280</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:16:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370618188356-140</Id><Topic><Title>THEY'VE PINNED IT JUST UNDER $24.50</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370617891586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:11:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely correct. Ain't it a magnificent thing to watch them manipulate the price with no accountability from the SEC. Call options almost always expire worthless, that's why you should always sell and hardly ever buy them.</Msg><Username>angstromatic</Username><Timestamp>1370618188356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:16:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370618241969-141</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo launches K900 Intel phone in India.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1370617556364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice .. More good news and the MMs are still trying to hold it down!</Msg><Username>beer.snob</Username><Timestamp>1370618241969</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370618363830-142</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell-based tablets have the potential to devastate the market</Title><Username>beer.snob</Username><Timestamp>1370615597267</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:33:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time to push this baby higher..</Msg><Username>beer.snob</Username><Timestamp>1370618363830</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:19:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370618402735-143</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Apps Processor Outperforms NVIDIA, Qualcomm, Samsung</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1370616142438</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:42:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This underscores an underlying weakness with ARMH, and that is that as long as the performance expectations for devices was minimal ARM looked good, but ARM cores weren't designed to scale and weren't designed for performance. Now that smartphones and tablets demand near PC-like power to deliver a rich experience the ARM camp is struggling to move upscale as they are finally realizing that power efficiency suffers greatly while increasing performance. It's really not surprising they would be blind-sided by this, they had no experience making high-performance chips. Every indication is that from here on out Intel will have the leading product.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1370618402735</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370618415342-144</Id><Title>Haswell to dominate tablets</Title><Msg>not Sony Z Haswell 1920 display Windows $1150 Asus Transformer Tegra4 2560 display Android $599 smaller than Sony Z lighter than Sony Z 2x batter life of Sony Z No Fan unlike Sony Z With Win8.1 coming to ARM, there is no reason to buy an Intel based tablet</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370618415342</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:20:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370618503426-145</Id><Topic><Title>SEC someone should go to JAIL for the CON job CNBC and WALL STREET pulled on all the suckers that were coned into buying INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611648826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The money lost this time by investors is billions, This is twice CNBC Pete the CON man and Wall Street CONed investors in INTC. Someone needs to go to JAIL or maybe this time someone that lost a lot of money just might take the law into there owe hands and fix it.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370618503426</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:21:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370618648912-146</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Haswell Tablet Breakthrough</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1370615739124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:35:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Breakthroughs are great.. would be nice to have a multitasking tablet instead of what we have with the PAD</Msg><Username>beer.snob</Username><Timestamp>1370618648912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:24:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370618705105-147</Id><Title>Dagger Marsavian Dagger !!!</Title><Msg>eir951 • 4 minutes 15 seconds ago Flag 0 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 0 Reply Haswell to dominate tablets not Sony Z Haswell 1920 display Windows $1150 Asus Transformer Tegra4 2560 display Android $599 smaller than Sony Z lighter than Sony Z 2x batter life of Sony Z No Fan unlike Sony Z With Win8.1 coming to ARM, there is no reason to buy an Intel based tablet</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1370618705105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:25:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370619012477-148</Id><Topic><Title>THEY'VE PINNED IT JUST UNDER $24.50</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370617891586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:11:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The open interest in $24.50 calls is 10k contracts and 2k in puts. Yesterday the call open interest was 1,800 contracts so someone opened (through selling or buying to open) 8k contracts yesterday. I doubt that 10k call contracts is enough for "them" do worry about. If the market stays up, Intel should finish up regardless of the options. Anyone who wanted out the calls exited when Intel dropped to $24.20's. Option IV jumped from the 22 area to 30 and the extra option premium is attracting arbitragers.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1370619012477</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370619029093-149</Id><Topic><Title>SEC someone should go to JAIL for the CON job CNBC and WALL STREET pulled on all the suckers that were coned into buying INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611648826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Put the MFers in jail</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370619029093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:30:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370619097106-150</Id><Topic><Title>Piper downgrade today destroying any INTC momentum</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1370610765569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These people have had a 21 price target on the stock. Before that they had a $19 dollar price target. They have not been as bearish as GS but they have been down on INTC for a long time. Just another disgruntled bear that can stand to see INTC charge higher.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1370619097106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:31:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370619331096-151</Id><Title>Is it me......but this look like Sell higher on the news from Hedge Funds???</Title><Msg>But next week the reality will catch in.....QE is going downward??? meaning????</Msg><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370619331096</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:35:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370619402426-152</Id><Title>Start your DD on MISM ASAP</Title><Msg>MISM looks like it is ready to pop. Have been doing some research on it for the past few weeks. Start your DD on MISM</Msg><Username>jacobavery557</Username><Timestamp>1370619402426</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:36:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370619665023-153</Id><Title>Intel Apps Processor Outperforms NVIDIA, Qualcomm, Samsung, According to ABI Research</Title><Msg>Intel Apps Processor Outperforms NVIDIA, Qualcomm, Samsung, According to ABI Research AUSTIN, Texas--(BUSINESS WIRE)--ABI Research reports that Intel’s latest application processor, Z2580, sets the bar for performance and current drain in smartphones. It outperformed the competition in ABI Research’s benchmark testing of the Lenovo K900 smartphone, powered by Intel’s XMM6360 modem chipset and Z2580 application processor. Jim Mielke, VP of engineering at ABI research, notes: “The benchmarks were impressive but the real surprise was the current consumption recorded during the benchmarks; the new processor not only outperformed the competition in performance but it did so with up to half the current drain.” “The benchmarks were impressive but the real surprise was the current consumption recorded during the benchmarks; the new processor not only outperformed the competition in performance but it did so with up to half the current drain.” . Table 1, below, shows a sampling of handsets/tablets that have been introduced lately with new chipsets from NVIDIA, Qualcomm, Samsung, and Intel. Some notable findings include: • For the CPU test, three phones scored in the 5000 range for performance, but of the three, Intel stood out with only 0.85A of average current vs. 1.38A for the Samsung Exynos Octa, and 1.79A for the Qualcomm APQ8064T. • Similar trends are seen for each test. If one of the chips did have lower current, the performance was significantly lower or if the performance was better, the current was higher. • The only test where a competitor matched the performance of the Intel Z2580 was for 1080p video record. ◦ The Samsung Galaxy S4 i377 had lower current drain but this was not due to the Qualcomm APQ8064T. Instead it was because of a separate image processor from Fujitsu. ◦ The Samsung Exynos Octa performed well without a separate image processor in both the 1080p and 3D graphics tests; outscoring all but with proportionally higher current compared to t</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1370619665023</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370619745747-154</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is no ANd</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1370566425786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:53:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as is it becomes more about the SoC and total solution rather than just the CPU alone. It's firms like QCOM and not ARM (the company) that Intel has to "worry" about. FYI Intels voltage regulator integrated as many as discrete 7 chips, Intel "integrated" DRAM via 2.5D, they are working on integrating RF - it's a myth that Intel is behind in SoCs just like x86 is too power hungry - how many years did the ARM camp beat this drum?. Why did Samsung select Intel SoC - because 22nm is around the corner and they probably got sneak preview of 14nm - ARM's FinFet is a hoax - it's 20nm design rules. In order to obtain FinFet to match Intel they need to spend megatons on capex while getting very little die shrink going from 20nm planar to 14/16nm FinFet. Nobody will be able to match Intels cost structure and I can only laugh at the analyst clowns from Piper et al - who is running A15 in volume production NOBODY</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1370619745747</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:42:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370619798024-155</Id><Title>Analyst: Intel Atom chip outperforms Nvidia, Qualcomm and Samsung</Title><Msg>tgdailyDOTcom/mobility-features/72046-analyst-intel-atom-chip-outperforms-nvidia-qualcomm-and-samsung Analysts at ABI Research report that Intel’s latest Atom processor - the Z2580 clocked at 2.0 GHz - sets the bar for performance and current drain in smartphones. "It outperformed the competition in ABI Research’s benchmark testing of the Lenovo K900 smartphone, powered by Intel’s XMM6360 modem chipset and Z2580 application processor," confirmed Jim Mielke, VP of engineering at ABI research. "The benchmarks were impressive but the real surprise was the current consumption recorded during the benchmarks; the new processor not only outperformed the competition in performance but it did so with up to half the current drain." According to Mielke, for the CPU part of the benchmark test, three phones scored in the 5000 range for performance, but of the three, Intel stood out with only 0.85A of average current vs. 1.38A for the Samsung Exynos Octa, and 1.79A for the Qualcomm APQ8064T. "Similar trends are seen for each test. If one of the chips did have lower current, the performance was significantly lower or if the performance was better, the current was higher," Mielke continued. "The only test where a competitor matched the performance of the Intel Z2580 was for 1080p video record." Meanwhile, the Samsung Galaxy S4 i377 had lower current drain which ABI attributed to a separate image processor from Fujitsu, rather than the Qualcomm APQ8064T. The Samsung Exynos Octa performed well without a separate image processor in both the 1080p and 3D graphics tests; outscoring all but with proportionally higher current compared to the Z2580 from Intel. "Intel did significant work to bring the current drain down on their well-recognized high-performance processors but the competitors did not help themselves. ...</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370619798024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:43:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370619820195-156</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst: Intel Atom chip outperforms Nvidia, Qualcomm and Samsung</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370619798024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:43:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ARM architecture used by nearly all of Intel’s competitors is well known for its low power performance but in bringing the processing power up closer to PC levels, the current drain has taken a significant hit," Mielke added. "Since high-end smartphones require this level of performance, Intel is well positioned for strong growth over the next few years Combining the high-end modems (the XMM6360 is used in both the Lenovo K900 and the Samsung Galaxy S4 i9500) with their application processors for high-to mid-tier solutions, and single-chip EDGE chips for low-cost phones makes Intel a rare full portfolio provider."</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370619820195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:43:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370620197980-157</Id><Topic><Title>Dagger Marsavian Dagger !!!</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1370618705105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:25:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiot. First of all that review is wrong about the batery life ...Sony claims should get 15 hours battery life (pocket-lintDOTcom/news/121504-sony-vaio-duo-13-slider-ultrabook-hybrid-sports-intel-haswell-and-4g-lte), which is more than that battery hog tegra4 which is using a larger 8180-mAh battery just to get to 10 hours battery life. Second, Haswell is at least 5 times faster than the tegra 4, so it make sense for sony to charge a premium. third, the Sony runs Windows so MS is charging a premium to run windows. And finally dumb a**s**s**, you should be comparing the tegra4 with Bay Trail which will be coming out within months. Bay Trail will outperform your tegra4 in both speed and battery life hands down.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370620197980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:49:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370620274902-158</Id><Topic><Title>Dagger Marsavian Dagger !!!</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1370618705105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:25:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bay trail will beat that tegra 4 of yours in price too!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370620274902</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370620571258-159</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst: Intel Atom chip outperforms Nvidia, Qualcomm and Samsung</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370619798024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:43:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The analysts who are currently downgrading INTC should be publicly humiliated. Ashraf's little SA piece was way too weak IMO.</Msg><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1370620571258</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:56:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370620789128-160</Id><Title>Dow look like it need a breather!!!!</Title><Msg>10-15% by july!!!????</Msg><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370620789128</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:59:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370620846441-161</Id><Title>Intel pinned today at 24.5</Title><Msg>That is what it looks like. Dont let these small tides jitter you. Be a long term value holder. you will get dividend as well as the stock will reach at least 30 by end of this year</Msg><Username>trader_the</Username><Timestamp>1370620846441</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:00:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370620908421-162</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst: Intel Atom chip outperforms Nvidia, Qualcomm and Samsung</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370619798024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:43:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I did tell blueredmonk that Clovertrail+ would be a more power efficient phone chip than Krait and the A15/A7 hybrid and so it looks in practice and Merrifield has not even arrived yet ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370620908421</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:01:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370621025891-163</Id><Title>Piper Perma Intel Bear simply does not believe that companies will switch to Intel from Arm chips.</Title><Msg>He is entitled to his opinion and he has a sell on Intel based upon his opinion. How is it he is so so sure? I mean he knows the Intel chip is going to be used by Samsung and then he after the announcement, downgrades to sell. Could it be he hates Intel guts? Is he a former AMD fanboy who lost huge money when AMD crashed from 49 down to 1.60? No matter really because he must believe what he says and when the numbers come in making him look stupid, he will be forced to take his target price up. It is comical the price target keeps going up while he holds a sell on the stock. Intel turning green today, if it does, will make him look very very stupid indeed.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1370621025891</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:03:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370621350636-164</Id><Title>I think MISM is about to go to $1+</Title><Msg>MISM is looking good here. They show some huge assets in their financials so the book value is atleast .50 cents per share. I am loading up</Msg><Username>sampsonj895</Username><Timestamp>1370621350636</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:09:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370621751037-165</Id><Topic><Title>Dagger Marsavian Dagger !!!</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1370618705105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:25:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this" comparison" shows really how stupid you are</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1370621751037</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:15:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370622154524-166</Id><Topic><Title>Piper Perma Intel Bear simply does not believe that companies will switch to Intel from Arm chips.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1370621025891</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:03:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The sell side analysts will become their own victims - I was heard the term "drinking each others bathwater" - that's what the sell side dudes are doing they repeated the ARM hype (low power / intel won't have a chance) so many times that they started to believe it - they are not able to analyze the Intel versus ARM scenario rationally</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1370622154524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:22:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370622160281-167</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Haswell Tablet Breakthrough</Title><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1370615739124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:35:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sub headline is NO FAN! Huge breakthrough! What an ENORMOUS technological breakthrough! Sony Z Haswell 1920 display Windows $1150 Asus Transformer Tegra4 2560 display Android $599 smaller than Sony Z lighter than Sony Z 2x batter life of Sony Z No Fan unlike Sony Z With Win8.1 coming to ARM, there is no reason to buy an Intel based tablet</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370622160281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370622391173-168</Id><Title>Please realise a sell rating on options day is nothing more</Title><Msg>than the crooks trying to play the public for there benefit.Intel is very well positioned to advance significantly higher through the end of the yearr</Msg><Username>thebegining6</Username><Timestamp>1370622391173</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:26:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370622780370-169</Id><Topic><Title>Piper downgrade today destroying any INTC momentum</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1370610765569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very powerful day for Intel as it is easily benchpressing 4 negative analysts</Msg><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1370622780370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:33:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370622823640-170</Id><Title>ARM is getting slaughtered</Title><Msg>wow !</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1370622823640</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:33:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370622959528-171</Id><Title>The Mother of All Fudd Fades</Title><Msg>I pity the fools who shorted Intel 40 cents down. LOL The big Wall Street analysts are like the Keystone Cops of price manipulation...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370622959528</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:35:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370623237689-172</Id><Title>ARM Powers Down Past $40</Title><Msg>Heed the differential as it provides proof positive that the tipping point has been reached. ARM down $1.36, Intel up 4 cents. Another huge daily differential of $1.40.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370623237689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370623378247-173</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is getting slaughtered</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1370622823640</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:33:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM now down 21 percent from its recent high. How is Wall Street going to explain this??? The news from the last week is overwhelming...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370623378247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:42:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370623381915-174</Id><Title>Putting in the double top in the market make sure you take profits in all your stocks today</Title><Msg>Putting in the double top in the market make sure you take profits in all your stocks today</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370623381915</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:43:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370623480906-175</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is getting slaughtered</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1370622823640</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:33:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do any of these daily, obsessive/excessive ARM posts have to do with Intel?</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1370623480906</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:44:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370623576672-176</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Powers Down Past $40</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370623237689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:40:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wallisweaver, You're looking pretty smart these days :)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1370623576672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:46:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370623577505-177</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is getting slaughtered</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1370622823640</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:33:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It shows how Intel is killing the ARM ecosystem.</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1370623577505</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:46:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370623649196-178</Id><Topic><Title>Please realise a sell rating on options day is nothing more</Title><Username>thebegining6</Username><Timestamp>1370622391173</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is Friday. Not options day. Weekly options are expiring but those expire every Friday that Monthly options don't expire. There was only 1,800 $24.50 call contracts open on Wednesday and that was the BIG strike. Nothing exciting or even interesting in INTC options today.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1370623649196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:47:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370624028226-179</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst: Intel Atom chip outperforms Nvidia, Qualcomm and Samsung</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370619798024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:43:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>:) Change the benchmark, and things look different. 1.38A for Quad A15's eh?</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1370624028226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370624384804-180</Id><Title>Intel: Money Flow Index going down now 67</Title><Msg>DMA 7 $24.73 broken down..... DMA50:$23.21 next?? DMA200:$21.72???</Msg><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370624384804</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:59:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370624460963-181</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Money Flow Index going down now 67</Title><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370624384804</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:59:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RSI=61 at 71=OVERBOUGHT at under 30=OVERSOLD...Intel is well priced in now...better lower entry point!!</Msg><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370624460963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:01:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370624467261-182</Id><Title>Analysts who shorted Intel while trying to manipulate it are EXPOSED for what they really are</Title><Msg>their effect on the market or Intel pps for that matter is short lived as they constantly losing credibility.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1370624467261</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:01:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370624719963-183</Id><Title>ARM Holdings plc (ARMH): Should You Doubt This Company’s Prospects?</Title><Msg>British chip designer ARM Holdings plc (NASDAQ:ARMH) is a company that has inspired immense confidence within the tech industry for quite some time now, and the optimism has trickled down to the Street as well, as the company has delivered stellar results over the past few quarters. The main reason behind that has been the fact that ARM Holdings plc (NASDAQ:ARMH)-designed chips that are, in turn, manufactured by companies such as QUALCOMM, Inc. (NASDAQ:QCOM), NVIDIA Corporation (NASDAQ:NVDA), and Samsung, can be found in around 90% of the world’s smartphones and a considerable percentage of tablets as well. However, a recent announcement by Samsung Electronics with regard to its Galaxy tablet range seems to have dented that confidence to some extent, with ARM shares taking a plunge. This is because Samsung has said that it would be using the Clover Trail+ processor manufactured by ARM Holdings plc (NASDAQ:ARMH)’s bigger rival, Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC), in a particular version of its yet-to-be-released Galaxy Tab 3. In fact, some analysts have already started to express the viewpoint that ARM’s glory days are nearing their end. But then, when I hear about this news, the first thing that comes to my mind is whether Intel is really aiming at going one up over ARM Holdings plc (NASDAQ:ARMH) at present, or whether it’s more of a question of ensuring the company’s own survival in a post-PC world. If you ask me, it’s more of the latter, and attaining supremacy over rivals such as ARM and its licensee QUALCOMM, Inc. (NASDAQ:QCOM) may not exactly be a priority for Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) right now. At least, that’s the way it should be for Intel, especially after its core PC business is fast moving into oblivion. From that aspect, the Samsung design win definitely spells celebration time at Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC). After all, Samsung is the second largest maker of tablets after Apple and controls around 18% of the worldwide tablet market, according to</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1370624719963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:05:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370624830391-184</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is getting slaughtered</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1370622823640</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:33:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Won't be long before the stock price starts with a 3 then a 2.</Msg><Username>armsuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1370624830391</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:07:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370624998428-185</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Powers Down Past $40</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370623237689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:40:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's never nice when people lose money on a stock but ARMH was pumped so high on so many false premises it was just a matter of time before a reality check would affect the stock severely and we did our level best to warn them. It's still overpriced by a factor of 3 or 4 so the price correction still has much more time to run its course over the coming months and years.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370624998428</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:09:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370625001854-186</Id><Topic><Title>Please realise a sell rating on options day is nothing more</Title><Username>thebegining6</Username><Timestamp>1370622391173</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>true to your name.</Msg><Username>thebegining6</Username><Timestamp>1370625001854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:10:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370625828127-187</Id><Topic><Title>Please realise a sell rating on options day is nothing more</Title><Username>thebegining6</Username><Timestamp>1370622391173</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That remark was uncalled for. Alex offers insight into options trading and how he sees it affecting the stock price. I , as well, find it unlikely that an analyst would waste an actual downgrade on a weekly option trade. I agree they are crooks, but it seems more likely to me that the purpose would be for short covering etc.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1370625828127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370626610168-188</Id><Title>Why are James Covello/Romit Shah quiet ??</Title><Msg>They still have $16 price target. Unbelievable ....</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1370626610168</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:36:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370626702572-189</Id><Title>Sony Takes Fight To Apple On Battery Front With Intel's Haswell</Title><Msg>Computex in Taipei, Taiwan, is one of the largest tech trade shows in the world with 1,700 exhibitors at this year’s get together where Intel INTC +0.12% (INTC) introduced many new innovations. One of them is a new line of Haswell processors to be used by Sony (SNE) to power its Vaio Pro for up to 25 hours without a charge. The new Vaio Pro will be available by the end of June in Europe. Haswell’s improvement in battery life is even better than the targets Intel[/entity] had set when it had initially announced it was working on Haswell. Clearly, Intel did not have its head buried in the sand and saw the shift in consumer buying from laptops to tablets such as iPads from Apple (AAPL). iPads are great for content consumption but lack in capability for content creation, sophisticated graphics and heavy duty analysis that requires significant computing power.</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1370626702572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:38:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370627269596-190</Id><Title>Intel says Bay Trail-powered tablets will start under $199</Title><Msg>Agam Shah, IDG News Service @agamsh Jun 5, 2013 6:10 AMprint Intel expects tablets containing its upcoming Atom processor, code-named Bay Trail, will cost under $200, a company executive said Wednesday. “We believe we can push it well below the $199 price point,” said Hermann Eul, vice president and general manager of Intel’s Mobile and Communications Group, during a news conference at Computex in Taipei. This is a new low price for tablets with Intel processors. Intel has revised its projected tablet price several times, with the most recent being for tablets between $200 and $399. Now the pressure is on device makers to offer Intel-based tablets under $199.</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1370627269596</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370627371966-191</Id><Title>The real jobs number we won't know until it is revised and if they told you today the market would have sold off BIG TIME</Title><Msg>The real jobs number we won't know until it is revised and if they told you today the market would have sold</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370627371966</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:49:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370627422901-192</Id><Title>Deep pocketed Interest behind shorting heavily</Title><Msg>Will not allow Intel to surge even with an amazing product line till they have a chance to cover and pull money out of related ARM products which could be effected negatively</Msg><Username>sat5843</Username><Timestamp>1370627422901</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370627474122-193</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst: Intel Atom chip outperforms Nvidia, Qualcomm and Samsung</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370619798024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:43:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll just make up some new results that refute these ones.</Msg><Username>thebluereddork</Username><Timestamp>1370627474122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370627549406-194</Id><Topic><Title>The real jobs number we won't know until it is revised and if they told you today the market would have sold off BIG TIME</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370627371966</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:49:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone know the jobs number should have been a lot lower, It will just be revised down 40,000-50.000 next month like always</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370627549406</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:52:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370627654130-195</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Powers Down Past $40</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370623237689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:40:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>realistically, he should have sold his put the first time ARMH was down here, only to hold on during the ride to 50.00. Far better to have re-entered at the far higher price levels, as I believe you did up near 48.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1370627654130</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:54:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370627716640-196</Id><Topic><Title>The real jobs number we won't know until it is revised and if they told you today the market would have sold off BIG TIME</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370627371966</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:49:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like the CNBC and Wall Street crooks con you into INTC before the drop</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370627716640</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 13:55:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370628442686-197</Id><Title>INTC is such an object lesson...</Title><Msg>all about the lying cheating thieving "analysts" on Wall Street who manipulate and try to drive the pps their way. With INTC you know you're holding gold, and you can watch these miscreants do their malicious mischief. The day is coming when they are all in the slammer...same cell...the Bernie Madoff award..</Msg><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1370628442686</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:07:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370628584841-198</Id><Title>Always remeber to take some profits in all your stocks, Stocks that should have held there gains are going red</Title><Msg>Always remeber to take some profits in all your stocks, Stocks that should have held there gains are going red</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370628584841</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:09:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370628746642-199</Id><Topic><Title>Always remeber to take some profits in all your stocks, Stocks that should have held there gains are going red</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370628584841</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:09:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The horses are dead and going red</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370628746642</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:12:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370628757891-200</Id><Topic><Title>INSTITUTIONS HAVE BEEN BUYING SINCE $19</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370613337109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It did post $27 this year. Goes to show that unless revenues are up, having the best won't be enough.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1370628757891</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370629067284-201</Id><Title>Look on Yahoo insider transaction, Institutional have sold over 83 million shares or almost 3% of holdings</Title><Msg>Look on Yahoo insider transaction, Institutional have sold over 83 million shares or almost 3% of holdings</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370629067284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370629093937-202</Id><Topic><Title>INSTITUTIONS HAVE BEEN BUYING SINCE $19</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370613337109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has said revenue will be over $54 billion this year, the highest in its history</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1370629093937</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:18:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370629144317-203</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO BUY, THIS THING IS GOING TO EXPLODE NEXT 2 WEEKS ON ANY DESIGN WINS WITH APPLE OR SAMSUNG</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370614545851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:15:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope you are right. Intel inside the Tub 3 hasn't caught investors' fancy, so it's not auto matic. Them Intel pals must sell their ware big time for Intel to get a kick up. IMHO, company good news as in getting this/that other contract for parts, don't have the impact you would hope for.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1370629144317</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:19:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370629349103-204</Id><Topic><Title>Look on Yahoo insider transaction, Institutional have sold over 83 million shares or almost 3% of holdings</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370629067284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:17:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one is adding shares not insiders or Institutional, just look on yahoo insider transactions</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370629349103</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:22:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370629352771-205</Id><Topic><Title>HASWELL CAN GO FANLESS INTO TABLETS!</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370612983832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:49:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel insiders have been doing the opposite. What is going on??????????</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1370629352771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:22:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370629391975-206</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO BUY, THIS THING IS GOING TO EXPLODE NEXT 2 WEEKS ON ANY DESIGN WINS WITH APPLE OR SAMSUNG</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370614545851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:15:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>keep drinking the koolaide, Haswell launch this week was a disappointment by many accounts</Msg><Username>eir951</Username><Timestamp>1370629391975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:23:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370629550717-207</Id><Topic><Title>Dagger Marsavian Dagger !!!</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1370618705105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:25:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM A15 strikes again and not in a good way ... gizmodoDOTcoDOTuk/2013/06/hands-on-with-toshibas-new-android-tablets-stunning-specs-but-shocking-design/ 'As you’d imagine from Nvidia’s cutting-edge chip, performance was pretty blazing (although, this being a pre-production sample, the games we were playing with crashed a fair bit–that’s to be expected). Battery life is promised at 9.5 hours on all the tablets, though obviously we didn’t have time to verify that. What we can say, though, is that the Tegra 4-packing tablets get uncomfortably hot when you start pushing them, far more so than any other tablet we’ve played with before. To be brutally honest, none of the tablets are really worth the money.'</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370629550717</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:25:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370629564591-208</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Powers Down Past $40</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370623237689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:40:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Indeed. I got back in at $47.90 and then $49.90, so I averaged in the $48's. Covered at $45, but then reshorted to $41.22. Reshorted at $40.85, so that seems to be working.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1370629564591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:26:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370630067075-209</Id><Topic><Title>INCREDIBLE, INSTITUTION INVESTORS STEALING SHARES FROM SLEEPING RETAIL INVESTORS</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370612878285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:47:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Silly me, you can check intitutional and insider activity right here at yahoo finance! Seems there's been a net selling on both sides.....</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1370630067075</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:34:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370630169647-210</Id><Topic><Title>Look on Yahoo insider transaction, Institutional have sold over 83 million shares or almost 3% of holdings</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370629067284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:17:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look up the facts</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370630169647</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:36:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370630364941-211</Id><Topic><Title>coinmaker77 = itakebackmyapology = walrusweener</Title><Username>iknow.whoyouare</Username><Timestamp>1370540286164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:38:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>beware of this sick individual</Msg><Username>iknow.whoyouare</Username><Timestamp>1370630364941</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:39:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370630524098-212</Id><Topic><Title>Look on Yahoo insider transaction, Institutional have sold over 83 million shares or almost 3% of holdings</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370629067284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:17:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stop lying. I have reported you to yahoo</Msg><Username>iknow.whoyouare</Username><Timestamp>1370630524098</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370630712383-213</Id><Topic><Title>INCREDIBLE, INSTITUTION INVESTORS STEALING SHARES FROM SLEEPING RETAIL INVESTORS</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370612878285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:47:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree. This is the time to buy if you are a believer in both products and management. They've obviously got the products, but management has been an issue for a very long time now. May management be wide awake now, for I fear this is get it done or get out, no more chances.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1370630712383</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370630781459-214</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst: Intel Atom chip outperforms Nvidia, Qualcomm and Samsung</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370619798024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:43:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That guy "Ashtray" has no life..All he does is obsess over this stock every waking moment of his empty life..Maybe Ashtray should by a pet goldfish and chill out..We shall remain long and buy all appreciable dips..Downgrades are valuable and we don't need Ashtray babbling on every boring day,</Msg><Username>pentomic</Username><Timestamp>1370630781459</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370630912844-215</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is such an object lesson...</Title><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1370628442686</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:07:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>holding gold, that's a joke, gold's in a bear market, and nothing wrong with downgrading a stock near an overbght top as this was early in the week.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1370630912844</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:48:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370630969080-216</Id><Topic><Title>Piper downgrade today destroying any INTC momentum</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1370610765569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sales always trump downgrades. Heck, sales change people's minds!</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1370630969080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:49:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370630975130-217</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst: Intel Atom chip outperforms Nvidia, Qualcomm and Samsung</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370619798024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:43:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's "Ashraf". Not sure who this "Ashtray" guy is ;)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1370630975130</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370631130055-218</Id><Topic><Title>INCREDIBLE, INSTITUTION INVESTORS STEALING SHARES FROM SLEEPING RETAIL INVESTORS</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370612878285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:47:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They've obviously got the products, but management has been an issue for a very long time now. I am always amazed by such idiotic logic - who is accountable for products? Moron</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1370631130055</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370631228223-219</Id><Topic><Title>INCREDIBLE, INSTITUTION INVESTORS STEALING SHARES FROM SLEEPING RETAIL INVESTORS</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370612878285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:47:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>semi_equip_junkie, lol!</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1370631228223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370631347032-220</Id><Topic><Title>Intel pinned today at 24.5</Title><Username>trader_the</Username><Timestamp>1370620846441</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:00:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope you are right. Hope all companies have a banner rest of the year, for there are folks depending on them divs and, when the time comes to harvest, some nice cap appreciation.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1370631347032</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:55:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370631653205-221</Id><Topic><Title>Intel pinned today at 24.5</Title><Username>trader_the</Username><Timestamp>1370620846441</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:00:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Been holding for a long time, and plan to hold for an even longer time. Preaching to the choir, my friend :)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1370631653205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:00:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370631720704-222</Id><Topic><Title>Downgrades followed by</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1370615017006</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:23:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not interested in the chatter. What matters is sales.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1370631720704</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370631846392-223</Id><Topic><Title>Piper downgrade today destroying any INTC momentum</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1370610765569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is on the way to $28!Bogus downgrade will not stand!Go Intel!</Msg><Username>jamesleeredman</Username><Timestamp>1370631846392</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:04:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370631871756-224</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC PETE the con man and Wall Street suckered you all INTC what 2 to 3 days before all the downgrades</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370611279824</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Focus on sales and you will always be right.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1370631871756</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:04:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370632016442-225</Id><Title>Can I Get A Picture?</Title><Msg>Of Coinmaker holding his head in the basket it got delivered in today at the end of the Fudd Fade?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370632016442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:06:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370632229707-226</Id><Topic><Title>HASWELL CAN GO FANLESS INTO TABLETS!</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370612983832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:49:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Checked with Yahoo finance, seems net sales from both sides. Intel partners have to sell big.</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1370632229707</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:10:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370632306960-227</Id><Title>Samsung Galaxy Tab 3 in 8 and 10.1 inches, Packs Intel SoC</Title><Msg>Samsung brings us the final two models for their Samsung Galaxy Tab 3 line-up. Intel chipsets all around.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370632306960</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370632782542-228</Id><Title>Hey CNBC I will tell you why people are not coming back just look what you did to INTC you FN crooks</Title><Msg>Hey CNBC I will tell you why people are not coming back just look what you did to INTC you FN crooks</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370632782542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:19:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370632893692-229</Id><Topic><Title>Hey CNBC I will tell you why people are not coming back just look what you did to INTC you FN crooks</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370632782542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CNBC and Wall Street can only F people so many times.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370632893692</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:21:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370633179435-230</Id><Topic><Title>Hey CNBC I will tell you why people are not coming back just look what you did to INTC you FN crooks</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370632782542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone I know is going to cash and not coming back anytime soon.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370633179435</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:26:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370633715397-231</Id><Topic><Title>Hey CNBC I will tell you why people are not coming back just look what you did to INTC you FN crooks</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1370632782542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Everyone I know is going to cash and not coming back anytime soon." As Yogi Berra said: "Nobody goes there anymore. It's too crowded."</Msg><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1370633715397</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:35:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370633903586-232</Id><Title>What the heck happened, some Analyst bad mouth the pig again today</Title><Msg>These dudes are at it everyday now it seems.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370633903586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:38:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370633955310-233</Id><Title>Poor Mr Weaver keeps pumping while the Analysts keep dumping.</Title><Msg>Its really funny whats going on.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370633955310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:39:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370633984188-234</Id><Title>insiders are taking profit???</Title><Msg>Insider Transactions Reported - Last Two Years Date Insider Shares Type Transaction Value* Jun 3, 2013 HOLT WILLIAM M Officer 65,494 Direct Option Exercise at $19.04 per share. 1,247,005 Jun 3, 2013 KILROY THOMAS M Officer 41,250 Direct Option Exercise at $19.51 per share. 804,787 Jun 3, 2013 HOLT WILLIAM M Officer 65,494 Direct Automatic Sale at $25.70 per share. 1,683,195 Jun 3, 2013 KILROY THOMAS M Officer 41,250 Direct Automatic Sale at $25.55 per share. 1,053,937 Jun 2, 2013 KILROY THOMAS M Officer 7,970 Direct Option Exercise at $19.04 per share. 151,748 Jun 2, 2013 JAMES RENEE JO Officer 41,250 Direct Automatic Sale at $25 per share. 1,031,250 Jun 2, 2013 PERLMUTTER DAVID Officer 535,000 Direct Option Exercise at $21.52 - $22.11 per share. 11,671,0002 Jun 2, 2013 HOLT WILLIAM M Officer 7,919 Direct Option Exercise at $21.09 per share. 167,011 Jun 2, 2013 KILROY THOMAS M Officer 7,970 Direct Automatic Sale at $24.99 per share. 199,170 Jun 2, 2013 HOLT WILLIAM M Officer 7,919 Direct Automatic Sale at $25.30 per share. 200,350 Jun 2, 2013 PERLMUTTER DAVID Officer535,000 Direct Automatic Sale at $25.10 per share. 13,428,500</Msg><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370633984188</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:39:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370634158567-235</Id><Topic><Title>Piper Perma Intel Bear simply does not believe that companies will switch to Intel from Arm chips.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1370621025891</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:03:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MS enterprise software means Intel is in the game. May the force always be with Intel. Live long (forever, really) and prosper, Intel! Beam me up, Krzanich! Makes we wanna sing, "The sun will come out tomorrow, Bet that dollah that tomorrow, there'll be Intel!"</Msg><Username>yw23t</Username><Timestamp>1370634158567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:42:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370634364637-236</Id><Title>Chinese Xeon/Xeon Phi supercomputer destroys speed record and will get much faster</Title><Msg>arstechnicaDOTcom/information-technology/2013/06/chinese-supercomputer-destroys-speed-record-and-will-get-much-faster/ A Chinese supercomputer known as Tianhe-2 has been measured at speeds of 30.65 petaflops, or 74 percent faster than the current holder of the world's-fastest-supercomputer title. The speed is remarkable partly because the Intel-based Tianhe-2 (also known as Milkyway-2) wasn't even running at full capacity during testing. A five-hour Linpack test using 14,336 out of 16,000 compute nodes, or 90 percent of the machine, clocked in at the aforementioned 30.65 petaflops. (A petaflop is one quadrillion floating point operations per second, or a million billion.) Linpack benchmarks are used to rank the Top 500 supercomputers in the world. The Top 500 list's current champion is Titan, a US system that hit 17.59 petaflops. Tianhe-2 achieved 1.935 gigaflops per watt, which is slightly less efficient than Titan's 2.143 gigaflops per watt. Tianhe-2's numbers were revealed this week in a paper by University of Tennessee professor Jack Dongarra, who created the Linpack benchmarks and helps compile the bi-annual Top 500 list. Dongarra's paper doesn't say whether Tianhe-2's Linpack measurement was officially submitted for inclusion in the Top 500 list. Ars has asked him if the measurement will put Tianhe-2 on top when the next list is released, but we haven't heard back yet. In any case, the new Top 500 rankings will be unveiled on June 17. Scheduled to arrive in the National Supercomputer Center in Guangzhou before the end of this year, Tianhe-2 is being assembled and tested at China's National University for Defense Technology (NUDT). Once operational, Tianhe-2 "will provide an open platform for research and education and provide high performance computing service for southern China," Dongarra wrote. Tianhe-2 is built with Intel Ivy Bridge and Xeon Phi processors. "There are 32,000 Intel Ivy Bridge Xeon sockets and 48,000 Xeon Phi boards for a total of 3</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370634364637</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370634435608-237</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese Xeon/Xeon Phi supercomputer destroys speed record and will get much faster</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370634364637</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:46:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tianhe-2 is built with Intel Ivy Bridge and Xeon Phi processors. "There are 32,000 Intel Ivy Bridge Xeon sockets and 48,000 Xeon Phi boards for a total of 3,120,000 cores," Dongarra wrote. It has storage of 12.4PB and memory totaling 1.4PB. NUDT built its own proprietary interconnect which Dongarra describes as "an optoelectronics hybrid transport technology" that "uses a fat tree topology with 13 switches each of 576 ports at the top level." Tianhe-2 runs Kylin Linux. Tianhe-2 has a theoretical peak performance of 54.9 petaflops. Measurements for the Top 500 list always fall somewhat short of theoretical peaks, but Tianhe-2 could certainly improve on its score of 30.65 petaflops if it ran Linpack across the entire system. Tianhe-2 is the follow-up to Tianhe-1, which was #1 in the world in November 2010 and ranked eighth in the most recent list, with a speed of 2.57 petaflops.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370634435608</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:47:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370635189422-238</Id><Topic><Title>insiders are taking profit???</Title><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370633984188</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:39:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like 4 people. Holt, Kilroy, Perlmutter and James. James .... planned sale set up in January. Perlmutter .... lost in last Intel reorg. Holt ... looks like real sales although a couple were triggered by expirations. Kilroy ... looks like real sales too. Perlmutter..... Intel CEO shakes up units, creates 'new devices' group The chipmaker's main product groups - including the PC client group, mobile communications and data center unit that previously reported to Intel Architecture group chief Dadi Perlmutter - now report directly to Krzanich. After Perlmutter transfers his business groups, he and Krzanich will "define his next significant contribution at Intel," according to the email described by the source. Renee James ... from SEC Form 4 ... was planed in January. Transactions reported on this Form 4 were made pursuant to trading instructions adopted by the undersigned on January 30, 2013 that are intended to comply with Rule 10b5-1(c).</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1370635189422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:59:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370635398410-239</Id><Topic><Title>insiders are taking profit???</Title><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370633984188</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:39:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buttmuncher has a tiger by the tail there ;^)</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1370635398410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 16:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370635832780-240</Id><Title>Trapped buying again at 25</Title><Msg>Hoping for 29. Bad combination</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1370635832780</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 16:10:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370635888390-241</Id><Title>Bye bye 25</Title><Msg>Warning coming soon</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1370635888390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 16:11:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370636656919-242</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese Xeon/Xeon Phi supercomputer destroys speed record and will get much faster</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1370634364637</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:46:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no record of the world's most powerful and fastest supercomputers in this country as they are top secret. The Chinese can gloat all they want on the surface, but they should mind the store as all that U.S. tech that's in "their" new toy may be watching them. ;-P</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1370636656919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 16:24:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370636695870-243</Id><Title>Piper Jaffray</Title><Msg>I started a 'kick' portfolio for Piper Jaffray. They just downgraded Intel to 'underweight' and set a price target of $20/share. This portfolio accompanies the one I started for Alex Choy-Incidentaly his porfolio is ahead 1.04%-His 'faux' portfolio is composed of three stocks he dissed. I plan to create more portfolios composed of pundit's picks or pundit's kicks. I'll revisit them periodically and see how they fare. The public's memory is short and too often when pundits are wrong they suffer no consequences and of course they don't brag about their mistakes.</Msg><Username>kip_castle</Username><Timestamp>1370636695870</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 16:24:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370636756694-244</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Mr Weaver keeps pumping while the Analysts keep dumping.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370633955310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch and learn my man, watch and learn.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1370636756694</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 16:25:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370637084034-245</Id><Title>Piper Jaffray recent record on Intel stock.</Title><Msg>They reiterated a neutral rating on March 19, 2013 with a target of $21 a share. The stock at the time closed at $21.14 a share. Whoever listened to this clown, miss out on a gain of between 16% if sold today or 23% if sold at its recent high within a 10 week period. And now the clown wants us to sell the stock after Intel makes a huge break in tablet market with Samsung Galaxy win.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1370637084034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 16:31:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370637198414-246</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Mr Weaver keeps pumping while the Analysts keep dumping.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370633955310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't see any credible analysts dumping [on] Intel or its stock. So Mr. Intel board member what is going on that is so funny?</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1370637198414</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 16:33:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370637444778-247</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Mr Weaver keeps pumping while the Analysts keep dumping.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370633955310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has Waldo ever not pumped INTC? Pump in 2010 at 24 on the way to 17.00, pumped about the elevator going back up on the drop from 29 when it was at 26 on the way back to 19. and here it sits 3 years later on the 24 from 2010, up .60. The reversal in the QLD from spy500 1600, 65.44 to over 69 as the QQQ outperformed and even AAPL went up.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1370637444778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 16:37:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370637655209-248</Id><Title>Piper Jaffray downgraded Intel stock back in January 3, 2011 to Neutral.</Title><Msg>The stock was just below $21 a share at the time. Within 4 months, the stock rose as much as 10%, saw some profit taking in August. Only to start a huge run all the way to $29 within 16 months of the downgrade. That's a gain of 38%. And Piper Jaffray considers this a neutral?</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1370637655209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 16:40:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370639796598-249</Id><Title>Intel Apps Processor Outperforms NVIDIA, Qualcomm, Samsung</Title><Msg>ABI Research reports that Intel’s latest application processor, Z2580, sets the bar for performance and current drain in smartphones. It outperformed the competition in ABI Research’s benchmark testing of the Lenovo K900 smartphone, powered by Intel’s XMM6360 modem chipset andZ2580 application processor. Jim Mielke, VP of engineering at ABI research, notes: “The benchmarks were impressive but the real surprise was the current consumption recorded during the benchmarks; the new processor not only outperformed the competition in performance but it did so with up to half the current drain.”</Msg><Username>2mbm</Username><Timestamp>1370639796598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:16:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370640219788-250</Id><Title>Thunderbolt Interconnect Announcement at AAPL WWDC ???</Title><Msg>On February 23, 2011 simultaneously, INTC and AAPL announced and released "Light Peak" - rebranded as "Thunderbolt." INTC has been coy about when Thunderbolt Interconnect will be released / ready but... If, as INTC did in the past, INTC gives AAPL a period of Thunderbolt exclusivity, would it not make sense for both companies to announce it on Monday? Just a hunch... I've been wrong before...</Msg><Username>jeffreyklotzlongmeadow</Username><Timestamp>1370640219788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370640312737-251</Id><Topic><Title>INSTITUTIONS HAVE BEEN BUYING SINCE $19</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1370613337109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 09:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh ?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1370640312737</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370640608343-252</Id><Topic><Title>Piper Jaffray recent record on Intel stock.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1370637084034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 16:31:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiots! Intel on the way to $28 after upgrades.Time to buy is now!</Msg><Username>jamesleeredman</Username><Timestamp>1370640608343</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:30:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370641234064-253</Id><Title>dow up 207</Title><Msg>intc is down 7 cents. something fishy here. my 26 puts are working very well for me.</Msg><Username>philip_914</Username><Timestamp>1370641234064</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:40:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370641277217-254</Id><Title>Piper - "Pipe Her" is no GOOD: downgrade worth 0.06$? he should be fire..........d</Title><Msg>He wants to buy but can't buy @lower price ================ eom =======================================</Msg><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1370641277217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:41:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370641662045-255</Id><Title>this pig had a breakout then a day later a breakdown. go figure</Title><Msg>it's a very bearish sign.</Msg><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1370641662045</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370642322143-256</Id><Topic><Title>Thunderbolt Interconnect Announcement at AAPL WWDC ???</Title><Username>jeffreyklotzlongmeadow</Username><Timestamp>1370640219788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:23:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>search on mac world uk for "New Mac Pro at WWDC" authored by Karen Haslam...</Msg><Username>jeffreyklotzlongmeadow</Username><Timestamp>1370642322143</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:58:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370643365974-257</Id><Topic><Title>this pig had a breakout then a day later a breakdown. go figure</Title><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1370641662045</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:47:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So sell it and go away.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1370643365974</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 18:16:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370643445087-258</Id><Topic><Title>dow up 207</Title><Username>philip_914</Username><Timestamp>1370641234064</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:40:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are all so proud for you. Bye bye</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1370643445087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 18:17:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370644941690-259</Id><Title>Not to be outdone, some Analyst will bad mouth the pig on Monday.</Title><Msg>They are jumping all over each other to bad mouth this stock. Gets them popularity in the internet media. Meanwhile poor Mr Weaver is busy pumping INTC all day everyday.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370644941690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 18:42:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370645974204-260</Id><Topic><Title>dow up 207</Title><Username>philip_914</Username><Timestamp>1370641234064</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:40:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Monday WWDC, big news for Intel sucker...you are going to loose your shorts on that 26put! HAHAHAHAHAHAH</Msg><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1370645974204</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 18:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370646040668-261</Id><Topic><Title>this pig had a breakout then a day later a breakdown. go figure</Title><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1370641662045</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:47:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorties you are going to pay big time Monday ...Apple's WWDC will be big news for Intel.</Msg><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1370646040668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 19:00:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370646069059-262</Id><Topic><Title>dow up 207</Title><Username>philip_914</Username><Timestamp>1370641234064</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:40:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>loose?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1370646069059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 19:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370646131870-263</Id><Title>Little birdie told me INTC shortie gonna pay big time monday</Title><Msg>BIG BIG news at Apple WWDC event on Monday</Msg><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1370646131870</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 19:02:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370646143827-264</Id><Topic><Title>this pig had a breakout then a day later a breakdown. go figure</Title><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1370641662045</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:47:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as was no div increase announcement, as was ceo hanging it up early. keep listening to ww who said it would hit $24 in 2011 and at $29 he said $30 was in the bag. LOL.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1370646143827</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 19:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370646166427-265</Id><Topic><Title>Piper Jaffray recent record on Intel stock.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1370637084034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 16:31:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>then why did I buy at</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1370646166427</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 19:02:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370646169629-266</Id><Topic><Title>Little birdie told me INTC shortie gonna pay big time monday</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1370646131870</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 19:02:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorts will s their pants Monday HAHAHAHAHHAAH</Msg><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1370646169629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 19:02:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370649458305-267</Id><Title>Tablet Cannabilisation Intels Perspective</Title><Msg>To put into perspective. In 2010 intel shipped approx. 40million atom cpu's for netbook type devices. Size of Tablet/netbook market approx 50million units. In 2012 intels market share of Tablet/Netbook type devices were near 2%. In 2013 intel will ship possibly a conservative 30% of all CPU's for Tablets, in a market that will mushroom to +200 million units. So intel Atom sales should increase 50% since 2010. That is in a market where intel has essentially no presence in last year. Figures for PC sales decline generally reflect the consumers adoption of tablets away from netbooks this last couple of years. Fair enough, though analyst are almost saying that intel is being hammered because it will regain and grow the consumption CPU sales it lost to ARM. Little is mentioned about the 100% growth forecast of consumption CPU's (ATOM/ARM for Tablets), and little is said about intels growth expectations in mobile phones, where intel last year had near zero market share.</Msg><Username>gooddigger</Username><Timestamp>1370649458305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 19:57:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370650972721-268</Id><Title>Bay Trail Surface Pro Clone</Title><Msg>youtubeDOTcom/watch?v=h8d6J-Mg9zI</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1370650972721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 20:22:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370651248738-269</Id><Title>The piper analyst name is Gus. Gus is who i listen to</Title><Msg>to tell me who will win the horse race or a heavy weight boxing match.I don't listen to gus who works on crooked wall street to tell me what investments to make.</Msg><Username>a33stacybb</Username><Timestamp>1370651248738</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 20:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370651695328-270</Id><Title>Samsung Galaxy Tab 3 10.1" w/ Intel inside Hands-on</Title><Msg>youtubeDOTcom/watch?v=1Fzh_6g_oaQ</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1370651695328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 20:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370653253295-271</Id><Topic><Title>this pig had a breakout then a day later a breakdown. go figure</Title><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1370641662045</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:47:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"as was no div increase announcement, as was ceo hanging it up early. keep listening to ww who said it would hit $24 in 2011 and at $29 he said $30 was in the bag. LOL." [The stock hit $24 multiple times in 2011, dufus. Are you getting senile in your old age? And we are good for $30. We had another good differential day today. I suppose you find no meaning in ARM's 20 percent plummet. This is why you will be surprised when Intel hits 30. You just can't teach an old grumpy, crotchety dog new tricks... ]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370653253295</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 21:00:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370653407405-272</Id><Title>Analyst: Intel's smartphone chip offers significant power savings vs. ARM</Title><Msg>So far, Intel's Clover Trail+ Atom processor has only found a design win or two within Asian smartphones. But if ABI Research's report is accurate, smartphone makers and consumers alike should start clamoring for it. In tests comparing almost all of the latest smartphone application processors, Intel's Atom Z2580 chip based on the Clover Trail+ architecture delivered comparable performance to the Samsung Exynos Octa and the Qualcomm APQ8064T. But Intel's chip also consumed 60 percent of the current of the Exynos Octa, and less than half (47 percent) of the current of the Qualcomm chip. (The Octa chip is found within European versions of the Samsung Galaxy S4, while the Qualcomm chip is used in the U.S. version.) ABI Research's report measured the current draw, where current times voltage equals power. But the assumption is that the operating voltages are comparable. In short, Intel's Atom offers the same performance but with a much lower power draw than competing chips, ensuring longer battery life and significantly undercutting the ARM proposition its chips offer much longer battery life than traditional X86 chips. If the ABI report is true, then Intel stands a good chance of cutting into the traditional smartphone market. In fact, James Mielke, vice president of engineering at ABI, told PCWorld that his firms' tests show that as the ARM providers increased the performance of their chips, the current drain scaled up as well, reducing battery life. This would imply as ARM's licensees scale up the clock speeds of their chips to meet the increasing demands of apps and other phone software, the battery life of those phones could dip as well. From PCWorld</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370653407405</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 21:03:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370653481448-273</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst: Intel's smartphone chip offers significant power savings vs. ARM</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370653407405</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 21:03:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel did significant work to bring the current drain down on their well-recognized high-performance processors but the competitors did not help themselves, " Mielke said in a statement. "The ARM architecture used by nearly all of Intel’s competitors is well known for its low power performance but in bringing the processing power up closer to PC levels, the current drain has taken a significant hit.”</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1370653481448</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 21:04:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370654337209-274</Id><Topic><Title>this pig had a breakout then a day later a breakdown. go figure</Title><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1370641662045</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:47:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, but it was actually way back in 2010 when you said those who bght INTC at 24 would be fine in 6 months, and it then promptly proceeded to drop to 17 instead with you holding all the while ever since then. and still down well off the peak reached way back in 2004 when AMAT was 26 and the smh 45.00, and INTC a mind numbing 34.00.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1370654337209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 21:18:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370657322613-275</Id><Title>gsmarena shows both Galaxy Tab 3 8" and 10.1" having Intel inside</Title><Msg>The 7" shows dual core CPU running at 1.2Ghz so not sure if it has Intel inside or not. Also interesting is gsmarena shows two Galaxy S4 variants - mini and Active. However, the Zoom is not there. I still think the Zoom will have Intel inside, maybe it comes later than June that is why it is not shown yet. I hope we hear about it on June 28.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1370657322613</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 22:08:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370657470951-276</Id><Topic><Title>gsmarena shows both Galaxy Tab 3 8" and 10.1" having Intel inside</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1370657322613</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 22:08:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>correction: June 20</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1370657470951</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 22:11:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370657498138-277</Id><Title>Will Apple announce a switch to Intel at WWDC?</Title><Msg>Could happen.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370657498138</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 22:11:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370657674925-278</Id><Topic><Title>gsmarena shows both Galaxy Tab 3 8" and 10.1" having Intel inside</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1370657322613</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 22:08:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some very cool pictures of the Zoom: thevergeDOTcom/2013/6/7/4407386/purported-samsung-galaxy-s4-zoom-pictured-in-leaked-image techtasticDOTorg/2013/06/exclusive-first-real-pictures-of-the-galaxy-siv-zoom-sm-c101/</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1370657674925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 22:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370657798673-279</Id><Topic><Title>gsmarena shows both Galaxy Tab 3 8" and 10.1" having Intel inside</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1370657322613</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 22:08:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think only an Intel chip can be powerful enough for baby</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1370657798673</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 22:16:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370657873593-280</Id><Topic><Title>Will Apple announce a switch to Intel at WWDC?</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370657498138</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 22:11:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will happen ;)</Msg><Username>devildoggy008</Username><Timestamp>1370657873593</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 22:17:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370659761577-281</Id><Topic><Title>Will Apple announce a switch to Intel at WWDC?</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1370657498138</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 22:11:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>look who is always pumping an Intel/Apple deal - will the Apple deal pumper. The more you pump the less likely how is TSMC 20nm ramp coming?I bet you Apple already regretting - I red Apple bought 80%b of Elpida LPDRAM output. very strong demand fpr LPDRAM - maybe Samsung is beginning to realize they can make more money in particular with LPDRAM - they know they won't be able to compete with Intel's 22 and 14nm SoC</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1370659761577</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 22:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370663085971-282</Id><Topic><Title>this pig had a breakout then a day later a breakdown. go figure</Title><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1370641662045</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 17:47:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>getting to $24 many times 2 years ago is not growth, it is crapola and for the #1 cheerleader to act like he hasn't been wrong is so typical. old age? funny from a guy mid 60s that won't be as much if he ever gets married. ARMH dropping is fine with me but armh holders have had a huge run because as you know intc and armh were both at 24 at the same time. mobile mobile mobile</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1370663085971</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 23:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>