<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360731600263-1</Id><Topic><Title>GloFo's roadmap</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360712161031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 18:36:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At low power, Intel is releasing the first production on their 22nm finfet process end of this year. Subsequently, they are on an accelerated rollout for 14nm which will happen just one year later at the end of next year. GloFo (and TSMC and Samsung) are correspondingly accelerating their low power rollouts to match. I think this is risky for all of them.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360731600263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 00:00:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360734334747-2</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confirms Web TV Service</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360693769264</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:29:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>--- You're prolly just really upset that the ARM Bubble is descending into the land of sharp objects and that all the Intel news is really good.--- OK now this comment plainly shows you are a dimwit. Where did I ever say ARMH was great? I tried to raise what I see as valid concerns about this latest INTC strategy, and this is your intelligent response? I see absolutely no good reason why this announcement could not wait for a new CEO. What is the urgency? Go ahead justify it if you can... not that anything you say will affect my ultimate decision to invest in INTC (or not).</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360734334747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 00:45:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360734501677-3</Id><Topic><Title>GloFo's roadmap</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360712161031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 18:36:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Risk is and always has been the nature of the semiconductor chip manufacturing business. Nothing new there.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360734501677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 00:48:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360735416056-4</Id><Topic><Title>GloFo's roadmap</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360712161031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 18:36:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"At low power, Intel is releasing the first production on their 22nm finfet process end of this year. Subsequently, they are on an accelerated rollout for 14nm which will happen just one year later at the end of next year. GloFo (and TSMC and Samsung) are correspondingly accelerating their low power rollouts to match. I think this is risky for all of them." [Intel already has 22nm FinFET production. Intel already has 14nm FinFET production and will have full volume by year end. No ARM foundry has ever done FinFET or is close to doing it. All the risk is on the ARM foundry side who is at least two years from a half-step to 14nm. ARM foundries have shrunk from 19 in number at 90nm to three now. Get real...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360735416056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 01:03:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360735576106-5</Id><Topic><Title>GloFo's roadmap</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360712161031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 18:36:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I tried to raise what I see as valid concerns about this latest INTC strategy, and this is your intelligent response?" [You say you have nothing against Intel and then you engage in non-stop bashing. Quit peeing on our heads and telling us it's raining...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360735576106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 01:06:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360736236599-6</Id><Topic><Title>iWatch Rumors</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360648552388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 00:55:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aren't the iPhone, iPad and iPod using iOS This site seems to claim that the iwatch would use iOS wwwDOTcbcDOTca/news/yourcommunity/2013/02/apple-iwatch-rumours-put#$%$-tracy-fans-on-alert.html Last time I checked, iPod, iPhone and iPad do not have Intel inside.</Msg><Username>m00nsh1ner</Username><Timestamp>1360736236599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 01:17:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360737394078-7</Id><Topic><Title>GloFo's roadmap</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360712161031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 18:36:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well that settles it then. You don't really want to engage in any proper discussion of INTC business strategy do you (or perhaps you are simply blind)? Well go ahead... get your pompoms out and be a cheerleader if you prefer. I'll stick to proper and careful analysis of my existing and potential investments. Good luck to you anyway.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1360737394078</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 01:36:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360738501085-8</Id><Topic><Title>GloFo's roadmap</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360712161031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 18:36:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's Intel's process roadmap at low power? The foundries are all building low-power processes to meet the demand for mobile targeted semi-conductors.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360738501085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 01:55:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360757078292-9</Id><Topic><Title>Tigh level of performance is displayed</Title><Username>alliecastagnaeymxqunm1099</Username><Timestamp>1304341235000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-05-02 09:00:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>edwardantony835</Username><Timestamp>1360757078292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 07:04:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360758670910-10</Id><Topic><Title>Intel TV went over like a fart in church</Title><Username>livindalifeaquatic</Username><Timestamp>1360714910817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:21:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>actually, you should google "the farting preacher" and watch it. It is very entertaining. In fact, I think you're him.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360758670910</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 07:31:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360760957400-11</Id><Topic><Title>Intel TV went over like a fart in church</Title><Username>livindalifeaquatic</Username><Timestamp>1360714910817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:21:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Best part was, I smell Heaven's bakery cooking up something good for you sister... only mildly funny otherwise...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1360760957400</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:09:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360761952255-12</Id><Topic><Title>TV's are coming with cameras these days.. They are watching you..</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360709895021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:58:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Link with said TV with camera? laptops have cameras too that can in principle be activated remotely with hackers...Who prevents you from placing a sticker on the lens???</Msg><Username>maximum_probability</Username><Timestamp>1360761952255</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:25:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360762674241-13</Id><Topic><Title>So much for Intel making any progress with Lava</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1360708985186</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:43:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somebody explain to me how this is not a SEVERE blow to Intel. How they gonna make it with someobody like Apple when they can't even advance with Lava? DAGGER.</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1360762674241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:37:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360763841918-14</Id><Topic><Title>Intel TV went over like a fart in church</Title><Username>livindalifeaquatic</Username><Timestamp>1360714910817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:21:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The original farting preacher, the guy who looks more like a used car salesman, is funniest.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360763841918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:57:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360764132858-15</Id><Title>Microsoft CFO Tami Reller that “New devices that run on Windows RT . . . won't be released this spring.” This quote and the paucity of available Windows RT devices led Woody Leonhard of InfoWorld to describe Windows RT as “circling the drain”</Title><Msg>Looks like Clover Trail killed Windows RT stone dead just like we said it would. betaDOTfoolDOTcom/markhibben/2013/02/12/does-arm-still-have-momentum/24269/</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360764132858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:02:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360764677190-16</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft CFO Tami Reller that “New devices that run on Windows RT . . . won't be released this spring.” This quote and the paucity of available Windows RT devices led Woody Leonhard of InfoWorld to describe Windows RT as “circling the drain”</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360764132858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM on Windows tablets is not interesting because there's already several really good ARM based tablets out there. Its very difficult for Surface RT to compete with the iPad and the handful of Android tablets out there, all of which have been refined over a few generations of product. Where ARM is really going to make an impact is in laptop. Microsoft doesn't realize this now, but they've laid the groundwork with WindowsRT for full blown Window laptops based on ARM. The big advantage as I see it is the form factor. They can be fanless and thinner than the MacBook Air. I know you Intel fans don't agree this would sell and the performance gap is too much, but look at the way the MacBook Air was pitched. The selling point was its dimensions and weight not its processor. Most people even now, after decades of Intel indoctrination about the need for MIPS, don't really care how fast their laptop gets the job done as long as they don't have to wait for anything. ARM chips now and in the future can easily provide that. ARM in laptops is what Intel really needs to fear and for good reason.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360764677190</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:11:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360765099550-17</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confirms Web TV Service</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360693769264</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:29:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A project like this has minimal impact on Intel's resources. I believe Intel is using its own Off-The-Shelf silicon for the box and the entire rest of the service and content deals can be negotiated by a relatively small staff. The box itself is quite simple. For those concerned about the cost impact to Intel's bottom line I'd say not to worry, this project is too small to matter. Same for the distraction factor. It just won't use that many resources. It's easy to see how it would be beneficial for Intel and why they'd do it. The most important part of this box is being able to eliminate the cable settop box cable companies require to deliver live programming to each HDTV. A household with two cable settop boxes pays about $120/year in equipment rental fees. Supposedly, with the Intel box live independent video can be delivered to any number of devices that have a modern Intel CPU. By modern I believe that will mean Intel CPU's that have integral hardware security to perform the secure link between the Intel box and device used for watching the video content. This could be an Intel tablet, an Ultrabook, an Intel based smartphone. The cable settop rental fees goes away so the cost savings helps pay for the Intel box. The power of this solution for Intel is the homeowner has the Intel box they want every device they bring into the home to have Intel inside so that it could be a display device. It offers a great reason not to buy an iPad, iPhone or any ARM device because ARM wouldn't have the embedded CPU security and won't serve as video clients to Intel's box. HUGE WIN for Intel! Now as far as the value proposition to the consumer goes I really would have liked to have seen a value play and a la carte options, but it's clear the near monopoly control cable companies have over content and distribution makes this near impossible for anyone to do. So we shall see if Intel's intelligent bundles are more palatable than those offered directly by cable companies. Consumers can already record TV and "catch up" on missed programs so I doubt those features will be a game changer. So it seems that the two best contributions Intel can make are; 1). Lower price for content to the consumer (but they're limited in this area). and 2). Ability to eliminate the cable settop box and deliver live HDTV to as many fixed or portable devices as the consumer has without extra cost. This one Intel can fix and simultaneously promote Intel inside. I have read that Intel permits the camera spying feature to be disabled. For now, I'll assume that is true and disabling the feature doesn't make the consumer pay more for the service.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360765099550</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:18:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360765517958-18</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft CFO Tami Reller that “New devices that run on Windows RT . . . won't be released this spring.” This quote and the paucity of available Windows RT devices led Woody Leonhard of InfoWorld to describe Windows RT as “circling the drain”</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360764132858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ha, ha, ha... Listen to yourself...will you go in for a ARM laptop versus a Bay Trail laptop that can provide better performance at similar battery life? Sure, you will...but most people are rational buyers! Also Big Assumption - Microsoft will make full Windows run on ARM...!! When Intel delivers better SoCs than ARM at comparable price points, why would Microsoft try to push ARM? And, if Microsoft tries to do that to get better margins, other OEMs will go with Intel SoCs to deliver better products - so Microsoft will be shooting itself in its foot...</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1360765517958</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:25:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360765868123-19</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft CFO Tami Reller that “New devices that run on Windows RT . . . won't be released this spring.” This quote and the paucity of available Windows RT devices led Woody Leonhard of InfoWorld to describe Windows RT as “circling the drain”</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360764132858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch how Surface Pro gets decimated over time by a huge range of Windows 8 Tablets and better Ultrabook Convertibles/Detachables from OEMs. Apple gets to sell its products at premium prices because no other OEM can deliver products with MacOS. Not so with Microsoft. Too many hardware OEMs license Windows, they are used to competing at cut-throat prices. Can Microsoft really compete with them...unless they yank their licensing model? If they do, they are in bigger trouble.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1360765868123</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:31:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360765999715-20</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft CFO Tami Reller that “New devices that run on Windows RT . . . won't be released this spring.” This quote and the paucity of available Windows RT devices led Woody Leonhard of InfoWorld to describe Windows RT as “circling the drain”</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360764132858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Where ARM is really going to make an impact is in laptop. Microsoft doesn't realize this now, but they've laid the groundwork with WindowsRT for full blown Window laptops based on ARM.' Yeah MSFT is going to #$%$ victory from the jaws of defeat lol. No-one wanted a WARM tablet but the are all going to fall over themselves to buy a WARM laptop when the alternative is the tougher Haswell not CloverTrail. Man, you are DELUSIONAL !! LOL</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360765999715</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:33:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360766110242-21</Id><Title>Rubio had to drink water REAL BAD!</Title><Msg>Obummer, despite the spewing by the media so called experts, has the GOP House by the BALLS! Those idiots made a deal that cuts the sheeet out of the military if nothing is done. Now Obummer can smile and look like he cares about that but clearly a LIB wants to cut the military and so he will smile and let the sequester cuts happen. What is even funnier is that he is the commander and chief and thus has the power to pick and choose where the cuts take place. He will simply look into GOP districts of house members and cut the military spending there to screw them with their clan. Golly Gee--How shocking that a Chicago gang with Obummer would know how to play dirty politics. Yeah sure those good old boys of the south are shocked. HAA HAAA Those Yankees from Chicago are the ones who burnt the south to the ground to end the civil war in 1865. Now you think they are not gonna cut the southern military bases? HAAA HAAA The guys in Chicago are laughing. Stupid southern trash rightwing #$%$ should know better to ppppluck with us by now--say they as they laugh. Go suck on some grits and cornbread Mitch because you are screwed. You are going to be primaries for making that deal with Obummer and some teaparty nut will run and likely lose the senate seat to a conservative Dem. Did you see how Obummer was laughing at the Rightwing trash? It was funny.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1360766110242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:35:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360766248718-22</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft CFO Tami Reller that “New devices that run on Windows RT . . . won't be released this spring.” This quote and the paucity of available Windows RT devices led Woody Leonhard of InfoWorld to describe Windows RT as “circling the drain”</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360764132858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As expected, you are assuming people are driven in their purchase decisions solely by MIPS and not by lightness and thinness and all-day battery life. Look at the ARM ChromeBook. Why is it selling so well?</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360766248718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:37:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360766415326-23</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confirms Web TV Service</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360693769264</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:29:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Comcast Streampix service is $4.99 a month. It requires digital TV service but then says that movies can be watched on the TV or on a laptop.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1360766415326</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:40:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360767339193-24</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Confirms Web TV Service</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360693769264</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:29:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Comcast Streampix webpage says that Streampix requires one of their digital TV services. But then the Streampix service is only an additional $4.99 . Then the Comcast internet service webpage says that Streampix is included with their 30MB per second service.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1360767339193</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:55:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360767954393-25</Id><Title>Guys, Intel already indicated that users can shut off camera on its Internet TV Box</Title><Msg>So I think that Intel is well aware of user discomfort with the idea and privacy issues. Definitely having a live camera aimed at you in your living room is extremely intrusive. IMO, if Intel has any insidious thoughts of using this camera in future to get advertising data, it will have to rethink its plans. But keep in mind that the camera can be used for video chats (Skype, etc.) and video conferencing. That will be a neat feature to have on your set-top box.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1360767954393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:05:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360768430283-26</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft CFO Tami Reller that “New devices that run on Windows RT . . . won't be released this spring.” This quote and the paucity of available Windows RT devices led Woody Leonhard of InfoWorld to describe Windows RT as “circling the drain”</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360764132858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because it is cheap but there are cheaper Intel chromebooks. Transmeta already tried this longer battery life laptop approach, nobody bought their slow devices and the company went bankrupt.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360768430283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:13:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360768474973-27</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft CFO Tami Reller that “New devices that run on Windows RT . . . won't be released this spring.” This quote and the paucity of available Windows RT devices led Woody Leonhard of InfoWorld to describe Windows RT as “circling the drain”</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360764132858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember 22nm is on the way with 14nm closely behind. All Intel-based devices will be thin and light - with comparable battery life - and comparable (or better) performance than ARM. There goes all your arguments... BTW, there is a $199 Asus Chromebook based on Celeron which is doing well. There are rumors of a Google-branded Chromebook based on Core i5. If Chromebooks take off, there will be a wide-range of Intel powered Chromebooks - from Atom to Pentium to Celeron to Core i3/i5/i7.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1360768474973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:14:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360768550133-28</Id><Topic><Title>Rubio had to drink water REAL BAD!</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1360766110242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:35:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How on earth the republican party ever let those trashballs on the far right into their party is pathetic. Just think how screwed the Democratic party would be now if those KKK boys on the far right were still in the Democratic party. Thanks GOP for taking the southern strategy and turning into an American version of the #$%$ party. Women hate you Republicans and that is why it is you cannot get anything nowadays boys. If you are a religious nut---a birther--a teaparty clown---a born again--highschool dropout--you for sure NEVER ever vote DEM and so the Dems do not have to even talk to you. Obummer can look at you and laugh and do whatever. Yeah---you hate Illinois and California and New York---BUT--they hate you back you clowns on the right and they have the power. Can you imagine a high tech company trying to recruit college grads with PHDs in engineering to work in Alabama? HAAA HAAA When it comes to brain drain--you good old boys have a problem. The smart guys in the deep south move north and work and stop eating grits. But cheer up because in 8 years or so--the Hispanic vote in Texas will take Texas back to the Lib Dems and leave the republican party as NEVER EVER winning a Presidential election again unless it dumps the far right. LBJ--A great Lib from Texas Clinton--a great Lib from Arkansas. YES---the Libs are coming and they are all of your kids under 30 KKK boys. They do not even see color when they see their friends. They marry across race and simply are disgusted with your old views. That rebel flag? They wipe their rumps with it. YEAH---Regon was from Illinois boys. He passed immigration reform you clowns. Deal with it.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1360768550133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:15:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360768688318-29</Id><Topic><Title>Guys, Intel already indicated that users can shut off camera on its Internet TV Box</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1360767954393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:05:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being able to disable the spying feature is good, provided doing so doesn't make the consumer pay more for the service. I would question the effectiveness of using the camera for Skype or any videoconferencing as most people have their settop box benath the TV or behind the glass door of a wall unit. And most new HDTV's are too thin to support an equipment box. In the most likely settop box location the Intel camera would be about crotch level for people watching TV on their sofa. And don't think for a moment that dangling the carrot of living room videoconferencing will make spying on families acceptable.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1360768688318</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:18:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360768849288-30</Id><Topic><Title>TV's are coming with cameras these days.. They are watching you..</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360709895021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:58:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>orwells 84 comes to mind. this is getting out of control.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1360768849288</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:20:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360768995173-31</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft CFO Tami Reller that “New devices that run on Windows RT . . . won't be released this spring.” This quote and the paucity of available Windows RT devices led Woody Leonhard of InfoWorld to describe Windows RT as “circling the drain”</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360764132858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"As expected, you are assuming people are driven in their purchase decisions solely by MIPS and not by lightness and thinness and all-day battery life. Look at the ARM ChromeBook. Why is it selling so well?" [Gee, how did the lightness, thinness, battery life do on the RT? It's circling the drain. People care about performance. Surface Pro's good reviews are a solid indication. And the advantages you speak of will all disappear this year. Then what will you use to prop up your silly ARM apologist arguments?]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360768995173</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:23:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360769148705-32</Id><Title>You care about privacy but young people do not.</Title><Msg>Yeah--I am careful but young people who buy everything want the camera on. Times change. Do you know what? A black man is President. Intel phones are coming and this TV thing might end up being a massive hit for Intel--I mean a good thing as in hit song. Intel should be 40 soon. Buy in before June and ride it up to 40 before Christmas. the new guy is already running Intel--paul O is now just a figure head. You know him? I do.</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1360769148705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:25:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360769887453-33</Id><Topic><Title>So much for Intel making any progress with Lava</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1360708985186</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:43:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not even the ultimate Intel fanboys can spin this DASTARDLY turn of events. LAVA choosees ARM after giving Intel a chance. WOW!</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1360769887453</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:38:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360770274473-34</Id><Title>16 Reasons Why Intel Should Have a Higher P/E Than ARM</Title><Msg>P/E ratios are all about the future and future earnings. And future earnings are to a very large extent all about fabrication. Intel's fabrication has reliable economics, is based on FinFET and the roadmap extends all the way down to 5nm. ARMs future on the other hand is substantially unknown because its fabrication roapmap essentially ends at 20nm. ARM doesn't have FinFET and not even 20nm production yet. In fact, 28nm still isn't close to being fully ramped and everyone believes ARM will be at 28nm for a substantial part of its production for years and years. ARM is attempting to implement a half-step to 14nm FinFET because it is clearly losing the fabrication race and also because its 20nm planar only offers limited performance improvements at a significantly increased cost. No one knows if it will be successful or when. The bottom line is that Intel will have volume production on 14nm for at least two years while the bulk of ARM is still at 28nm. This represents a two process node lead that will have huge implications in the marketplace. It means that Intel has a bright fabrication, financial and economic future while ARM fades to black. Here are 16 solid, factual, confirmable reasons why Intel's bright fabrication future should result in the company having a higher P/E ratio than ARM: 1.) Fewer ARM fabless start-ups, Even fewer rising stars, Large fabs acquiring small ones, Dropping number of foundries, deals and investments. 2.) The number of designs that the ARM foundries can support at each node is dropping. At 65nm it was 65 to 80, at 40nm, it was 40 to 50, at 28nm, it was 20 to 30, at 20nm, it will be 12-16 and at 14nm it will be 5 to 8. 3.) The time to ramp on each new ARM node is getting longer. 4.) The complexity of each node is increasing dramatically. 5.) The costs of each new node are getting higher while the benefits are getting smaller. 6.) Foundries are forced into a bad economics move to 20nm planar which is costly at minimal benefit. 7.) Foundries are forced into attempting a half-step to 14/16nm even though they haven't yet successfully assimilated 20nm upon which the move is based. 8.) Because of extremely high cost in process technology and SoC development, the relationship between fabless companies and foundries has become sensitive. 9.) Foundries will select their customers very carefully, and the criteria for acceptance will involve financial returns as well as technical capabilities. So, the rich will get foundry services and the rest of the ARM shops will be left hanging. So much for the ARM hoardes helping to compete with Intel. 10.) There is also the complementary factor that, with the increasing cost of implementing SoC designs at most advanced technology node, only a small number of fabless companies can participate. 11.) Whenever the partnership between a fabless company and foundry established, it would not be easy to change, as the change means high cost that should be paid by both parties. In other words, when an ARM shop makes a deal with one of the few remaining ARM foundries, then they are STUCK, and can only get unstuck by the application of large sums of money. And then who will they go to? One of their other one or two choices, if they even have that many? 12.) At 20nm and 14nm, the foundry business model will probably be slightly changed. An IDM-like collaboration between fabless companies and foundries will be expected. So the ARM foundries are going to have to become virtual IDMs (like Intel) in order to compete as these levels. Expect higher costs and lots of problems on implementation. 13.) Fabless companies have to accept a slow ramp-up of wafer volumes because of the IP qualification and parametric yield challenges. 14.) ARM Design teams will need to be manufacturing-aware and have in depth understanding of the process variables that have to be included as part of design disciplines. There will be the need for collaboration between fabless company and foundry on understanding the process variations. 15.) Fabless companies cannot assume that their designs will give high yields based on their legacy interfaces that are in place with foundries. There is the need to anticipate potential yield problems and address them at the design implementation phase, and DFM factors have to be carefully analyzed. 16.) Fabless companies will need to build stronger process and product engineering and DFM expertise. It means a extra cost of 50-100M USD per year.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360770274473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:44:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360770783781-35</Id><Topic><Title>So much for Intel making any progress with Lava</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1360708985186</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:43:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, if you are genuinely interested in the answer.... Almost every OEM/carrier use different suppliers. Samsung/Asus/Acer/HP/Dell all have devices based on both Intel and ARM. All carriers provide devices from different OEMs/chipsets/OS. Even when Intel delivers the best SoCs with 22nm, 14nm and 10nm, some ARM SoCs will be competitive for some devices. So it will be a bipolar world - we have to wait and see which pole the market tilts towards more than the other. With its process advantage and capex, I suspect it will be towards Intel.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1360770783781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:53:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360772679795-36</Id><Title>Benchmarked: Lava Xolo X500 running on Intel Atom Z2420 Lexington</Title><Msg>"From our above analysis one thing is clear - some real powerful things come in small packages and the Xolo X500 is definitely one of them. It has really outperformed other smartphones in the same price range as well as in the graphical comparison with the Desire SV. The display is vibrant and has good viewing angles..." From thinkdigit</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360772679795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:24:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360772895453-37</Id><Topic><Title>Benchmarked: Lava Xolo X500 running on Intel Atom Z2420 Lexington</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360772679795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:24:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's cute how you say I'm on ignore but you read EVERY WORD I type. Why don't you address how the newest XOLO has ARM inside? ARM is dying yet going into new phones??!!! Stay in your fantasy world. You might be dangerous to society if you leave it.</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1360772895453</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:28:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360773270771-38</Id><Title>INTC - One of the worst companies to work for</Title><Msg>I know some people that work for INTC. They are thinking of leaving. It sounds like it might not be the best place to work for. Coworkers are leaving. Some paycuts are occurring, and some good people are being let go, which means more work for people that are staying.</Msg><Username>pens_2011</Username><Timestamp>1360773270771</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:34:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360773627630-39</Id><Title>WHats wrong with Rackspace hosting today (RAX)</Title><Msg>anyone know ??</Msg><Username>hecla40coming</Username><Timestamp>1360773627630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:40:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360773836941-40</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Rumors?</Title><Username>jshantazia41</Username><Timestamp>1360770590886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:49:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>really do not be troubled my dude, simply just make absolutely sure to read through the upcoming post asap.</Msg><Username>wwhichard80</Username><Timestamp>1360773836941</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:43:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360774108664-41</Id><Title>Are you going to retire in the next 5 years, Could you take a 2008 type hit and still retire? anyone?</Title><Msg>You know WALL STREET will #$%$ over soon</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360774108664</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:48:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360774136875-42</Id><Topic><Title>Benchmarked: Lava Xolo X500 running on Intel Atom Z2420 Lexington</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360772679795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:24:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LAST year Intel..........THIS year ARM... but you keep on trying to decieve people here. ____________ Last year, we exclusively managed to get our hand-on the first Intel smartphone, the Lava Xolo X900. Ever since, the Xolo X900, Lava has managed to get a lot of attention. Earlier in the year it even launched the first smartphone based on Intel’s Lexington chip, the Xolo X500 and today the folks at Fone Arena have published a hands-on of the Xolo A1000, which becomes the company’s first 5-inch Android smartphone. Apparently they managed to get their hands on a prototype in the capital. According to the post, the A1000 flaunts a slim form-factor of 8.8mm and is superior to most 5-inch phablets in terms of industrial design. Unlike the X900 it is based on a dual-core ARM chipset. It also has a 2,100-mAh battery and it will run Android 4.1 Jelly Bean.</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1360774136875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:48:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360775022277-43</Id><Topic><Title>Benchmarked: Lava Xolo X500 running on Intel Atom Z2420 Lexington</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360772679795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:24:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know why the ARMH fanbois post here on the INTC board if ARMH is so great,you sound a bit on the insecure side to me. ARMH is a flyspeck that INTC is going to swat IMO.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1360775022277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:03:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360775679915-44</Id><Topic><Title>AMD and ARMH up over 2% and INTC .3%</Title><Username>jin_18do8</Username><Timestamp>1360687743738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:49:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very true, the market does not see Intel as being in growth mode but instead in decline mode. However, it's still hard to see how a company with such great leading edge technology assets can totally implode. I've seen it happen to other technology companies but in general their demise has come due to a basic paradigm shift in the technology which they were not ready for. In Intel's case, I agree that they missed the initial mobile wave of design wins, but it does appear that they're well on their way to attacking this market segment with what appears to be superior products. I guess only time will tell if they missed the "mobile boat" or not, and if this is enough to destroy the company.</Msg><Username>gator_billf</Username><Timestamp>1360775679915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:14:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360775807247-45</Id><Topic><Title>Are you going to retire in the next 5 years, Could you take a 2008 type hit and still retire? anyone?</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360774108664</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:48:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>already retired. Only holding Intel and some bond CEFs. Not stupid enough to be overweighted in stocks right now.</Msg><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1360775807247</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:16:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360776273620-46</Id><Topic><Title>AMD and ARMH up over 2% and INTC .3%</Title><Username>jin_18do8</Username><Timestamp>1360687743738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:49:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am getting worried about the selection of the next CEO. Someone from outside could really destroy this company. A shift toward bs gadgets vs highest tech would be very bad. Can you spell HP?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360776273620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:24:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360776598109-47</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft CFO Tami Reller that “New devices that run on Windows RT . . . won't be released this spring.” This quote and the paucity of available Windows RT devices led Woody Leonhard of InfoWorld to describe Windows RT as “circling the drain”</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360764132858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ChromeBook by Intel has half the battery life. The Chrome Book approach is not the longer battery life approach but the browser is the only application you need approach. There's a difference.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360776598109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:29:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360776762347-48</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft CFO Tami Reller that “New devices that run on Windows RT . . . won't be released this spring.” This quote and the paucity of available Windows RT devices led Woody Leonhard of InfoWorld to describe Windows RT as “circling the drain”</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360764132858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surface Pro got lousy reviews and its going to flop big time. Where do you get your well-researched data from? Intel is behind on power/performance and will continue to stay at its relative position ad infinitum. Likely it will fall further behind as the foundries accelerate.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360776762347</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:32:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360777517265-49</Id><Topic><Title>Are you going to retire in the next 5 years, Could you take a 2008 type hit and still retire? anyone?</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360774108664</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:48:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Market fills like a house of cards ready to fall any day. Just don't known whats going to pull the wrong card out.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360777517265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:45:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360778234731-50</Id><Topic><Title>Are you going to retire in the next 5 years, Could you take a 2008 type hit and still retire? anyone?</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360774108664</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:48:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never Retire Women do not like men who are out of the game. Work until you drop. Own your own business. BUT---Intel pays a Div so if you are retired, it is not bad.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey5</Username><Timestamp>1360778234731</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:57:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360778380521-51</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft CFO Tami Reller that “New devices that run on Windows RT . . . won't be released this spring.” This quote and the paucity of available Windows RT devices led Woody Leonhard of InfoWorld to describe Windows RT as “circling the drain”</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360764132858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surface Pro got great reviews and ARM is now behind on power/performance and will continue to stay at this relative position ad infinitum.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360778380521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:59:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360778570155-52</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft CFO Tami Reller that “New devices that run on Windows RT . . . won't be released this spring.” This quote and the paucity of available Windows RT devices led Woody Leonhard of InfoWorld to describe Windows RT as “circling the drain”</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1360764132858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>khitchdee, That's not going to be an issue when Bay Trail hits this year.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1360778570155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:02:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360778782866-53</Id><Title>Is it time to buy INTC?</Title><Msg>Is it time to buy INTC?</Msg><Username>michaelsbill51</Username><Timestamp>1360778782866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:06:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360778810632-54</Id><Title>Short Interest in Chip Makers on the Rise (AMAT, ARM, NVDA)</Title><Msg>Short Interest in Chip Makers on the Rise (AMAT, ARM, NVDA) 7:27a ET February 13, 2013 (Benzinga) The short interest in semiconductor makers was mixed during the latter two weeks of January. The number of shares sold short in Applied Materials (NASDAQ: AMAT), ARM Holdings (NASDAQ: ARMH), Micron Technology (NASDAQ: MU) and Texas Instruments (NASDAQ: TXN) increased between the January 15 and January 31 settlement dates. But short interest in Advanced Micro Devices (NYSE: AMD), Broadcom (NASDAQ: BRCM), Intel (NASDAQ: INTC), Marvell Technology (NASDAQ: MRVL), Nvidia (NASDAQ: NVDA) and Qualcomm (NASDAQ: QCOM) declined during that time. The largest percentage changes in short interest in the stocks of chip makers between the January 15 and January 31 settlement dates happened to Applied Materials, ARM Holdings and Nvidia. Applied Materials This equipment and services provider to the semiconductor industry saw short interest jump about 40 percent in late January to 16.73 million shares. That was the highest number of shares sold short since November and the largest daily average volume in almost a year. Short interest was less than two percent of the float. At the end of January, Applied Materials lost its chief financial officer to Qualcomm. Applied Materials has a market capitalization of more than $16 billion and a dividend yield near 2.6 percent. The long-term earnings per share (EPS) growth forecast of this S&amp;P 500 component is about nine percent. The price-to-earnings ratio (P/E) ratio is greater than the industry average. Of the 19 analysts who follow the stock that were surveyed by Thomson/First Call, just seven recommend buying shares. The mean price target, or where the analysts expect the share price to go, is less than the current share price. That means the consensus view is that there is no potential upside at this time. The share price is more than 15 percent higher year to date and hit a new 52-week high on Monday. The stock has outperformed the Nasdaq and competitor KLA-Tencor (NASDAQ: KLAC) over the past six months. ARM Holdings The number of shares sold short in this multinational semiconductor and software design company rose more than 18 percent to about 5.37 million. That followed a 12 percent jump in short interest in the previous period. But the short interest is still just a little more than one percent of the float. This microprocessor designer has a market cap of about $20 billion and a dividend yield near 0.3 percent. The company saw its stock downgraded few times in January due in part to valuation. Its return on equity is about 14 percent, and the long-term EPS growth forecast is more than 22 percent. Six out of the 10 analysts polled recommend buying shares, while none recommend selling. The current share price has overrun the analysts' mean price target. But the high individual price target suggests more than 12 percent upside potential. The share price hit a new multi-year high last week, and shares are now up more than nine percent year to date. Over the past six months, the stock has outperformed Applied Materials, Nvidia and the Nasdaq. Nvidia Short interest in this maker of graphics chips for mobile devices decreased more than 24 percent to 16.66 million shares. That is the smallest number of shares sold short since November and represents less than three percent of the float. In late January, the world was still reacting to the release of Nvidia's Project Shield mobile gaming device. Nvidia also said it would build smartphones and mobile devices with its Tegra chips and sell them in emerging markets. The company has a market cap of more than $7 billion and a dividend yield near 0.8 percent. The long-term EPS growth forecast of this S&amp;P 500 component is more than 10 percent and the P/E ratio is less than the industry average. The consensus recommendation is to hold shares, and it has been for at least three months. But analysts believe the shares have some room to grow, as their mean price target is almost 20 percent higher than the current share price. Note that the target is well less than the 52-week high from almost a year ago. Shares have traded mostly between $12 and $13 since October. Over the past six months, the stock has underperformed Qualcomm and the Nasdaq but outperformed AMD.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1360778810632</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:06:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360778887388-55</Id><Topic><Title>Benchmarked: Lava Xolo X500 running on Intel Atom Z2420 Lexington</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360772679795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:24:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanis Wally errrrr WilliamDavis. Wink! Posting old Xolo 500 news when there's been a Xolo 900 since then and now the newest Xolo on ARM. So desperate and pathetic you are.</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1360778887388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:08:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360779630722-56</Id><Topic><Title>Are you going to retire in the next 5 years, Could you take a 2008 type hit and still retire? anyone?</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360774108664</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:48:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How long did it take for most of us to get back to even, 3-5 years would be my guess and there are still investors that are not back to even I bet. How long did it take for you to get back to even? anyone?</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360779630722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:20:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360780366734-57</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation UPDATED NEWS!</Title><Username>konfliktgebietjudith</Username><Timestamp>1360605742311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:02:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one. I will subscribe now.</Msg><Username>mayredeanmable</Username><Timestamp>1360780366734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:32:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360782457220-58</Id><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro is not just for work</Title><Msg>forbesDOTcom/sites/jasonevangelho/2013/02/12/surface-pro-can-run-diablo-iii-portal-2-other-aaa-games-why-isnt-microsoft-evangelizing-this/ Surface Pro Can Run Diablo III, Portal 2, Other AAA Games - Why Isn't Microsoft Evangelizing This? Since Microsoft‘s Surface Pro launched, I’ve engaged in fascinating discussions with my Twitter followers about its capabilities. In doing so, I’ve identified what could be an important area of opportunity for Microsoft’s marketing department: They need to play up the fact that this tablet/ultrabook hybrid is quite adept at running a wide range of AAA video games. The Surface Pro handles Diablo III at 1920 x 1080 resolution with most specs except shadows maxed out. Popular MOBA League of Legends kicked out a smooth 30FPS (frames per second) at the same resolution with quality settings defaulted to High. How about the endlessly-playable, touch-enhanced version of Civilization V? Beautiful, stable, and a joy to experience on the Pro’s excellent display. Ditto for Portal 2, XCOM: Enemy Unknown, and StarCraft II. Surprised? So was the majority of my Twitter audience. As I spent the day testing various high-profile — and most importantly, evergreen — game releases, a fascinating trend emerged. People previously on the fence about purchasing a Surface Pro reversed course and started hunting down the hardware. Their prior perceptions held that the Surface Pro was strictly a business machine. Nevermind that Microsoft is targeting anything but the business professional with their new breakdancing-laden commercial. The culture Microsoft has fostered for decades assumes that the Surface Pro is for work. It’s time for Redmond to change the messaging. Tech-savvy consumers want to carry around a single multipurpose device. One that fits the bill at work, is easy to travel with, and powerful enough to aid in productivity. Shouldn’t that same device be useful during leisure time? Several of my Twitter followers want to play World of Warcraft during their downtime, and had no idea that the Surface Pro’s Intel Core i5, 4GB of RAM, and integrated Intel HD 4000 graphics could facilitate that These aren’t “hardcore” gamers, but they represent an important — and arguably sizable — potential demographic for Microsoft. As the company knows from its wildly successful Xbox platform, people play games beyond Angry Birds and Cut The Rope. Sure, using my isolated Twitter feed is anecdotal evidence at best, but I’m confident that Microsoft is failing to educate consumers about the Surface Pro’s power and flexibility. Until the 128GB iPad 4 can run games like Diablo III and Portal 2, let's stop the comparisons I shouldn’t be evangelizing the Surface Pro’s gaming chops, Microsoft should. In fact, one of my followers suggested starting a site that logs which games run well on the device. Even a token gesture like this would serve to educate — and surprise — potential Surface Pro buyers. Microsoft could partner with Blizzard and highlight Diablo III or World of Warcraft humming away on the machine for a future advertisement. I can’t help wonder what would happen if the official Microsoft Twitter accounts embarked on a simple campaign explaining that the Surface Pro can handle these and many more titles. I’d wager that thousands of replies would be laced with shock. What about a Surface Pro exclusive Halo, Fable, or Forza title? If Microsoft wants to maximize sales and mindshare of the Surface Pro, they need to combat the endless comparisons to the iPad 4. They can be effective in that battle if they do things like tout the device’s gaming capabilities, and bundle the Surface Pro with the excellent Type Cover. What about you? Did you realize the Surface Pro could handle popular games like LoL, WoW, and Diablo III? Does knowing this change your stance?</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1360782457220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:07:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360783238816-59</Id><Title>I Just Bought 5k Shares</Title><Msg>Will sell between 23-24 in next 90 days. glta</Msg><Username>hayseed_blitch</Username><Timestamp>1360783238816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:20:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360785084905-60</Id><Title>A15 chip is complete garbage</Title><Msg>Forget about any new design wins for this chip. With ARM insiders selling out, its the beginning of the end for ARMH.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1360785084905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:51:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360786734678-61</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation UPDATED NEWS!</Title><Username>konfliktgebietjudith</Username><Timestamp>1360605742311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:02:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one. I will subscribe now.</Msg><Username>overwovestephanie</Username><Timestamp>1360786734678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:18:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360787463792-62</Id><Topic><Title>WHats wrong with Rackspace hosting today (RAX)</Title><Username>hecla40coming</Username><Timestamp>1360773627630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:40:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>check router maker netgear today if you don't believe me...</Msg><Username>hecla40coming</Username><Timestamp>1360787463792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:31:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360787602282-63</Id><Topic><Title>Are you going to retire in the next 5 years, Could you take a 2008 type hit and still retire? anyone?</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360774108664</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:48:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw the fall coming in '07 (Pearlstein, Washington Post, saved my rear end, but I was suspect anyway - market was at high PE, and at record prices), and I was largely out of stocks in the spring of '08. Back in the market late '08, into early 09, then sold some quick gains, and back in select issues over the next 2 yrs, now selling and buying selectively, special situations. The core of my holdings are sm, med, lg cap ETFs, value and growth and emerging markets and int'l sm caps, and health and banking. All are on dividend reinvestment. I'm all in, and have been for time time - I hold a smalal % of cash for prudence/quick access.. Companies like Intel paying 4%, I'd be a fool not to be all in. PEs are low, energy costs coming down in the US, free trade growing. The US is one budget deal away from a huge resurgence. I see a continued bull for another 4 years, then re-look. On the other hand, I can take a hit like 2007/8 with no impact on my lifestyle.</Msg><Username>clcellve</Username><Timestamp>1360787602282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:33:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360788098112-64</Id><Topic><Title>Are you going to retire in the next 5 years, Could you take a 2008 type hit and still retire? anyone?</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360774108664</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:48:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd like to see Nuff lose everything in the market. Hoping he becomes so poor that he has to eat/drink his own waste to survive.</Msg><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1360788098112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:41:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360789029330-65</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Rumors?</Title><Username>jshantazia41</Username><Timestamp>1360770590886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:49:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Checking it out right now.</Msg><Username>claudias.ayala72</Username><Timestamp>1360789029330</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:57:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360789197495-66</Id><Title>Good chance to close over support today</Title><Msg>That would be a good sign.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1360789197495</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:59:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360789264799-67</Id><Topic><Title>Good chance to close over support today</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1360789197495</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did it... A small victory</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1360789264799</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:01:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360790259303-68</Id><Topic><Title>Good chance to close over support today</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1360789197495</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what was your support level?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360790259303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:17:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360790430788-69</Id><Title>Intel....leaving it's area of expertise and going HOLLYWOOD!</Title><Msg>If that isn't a recipe for disaster I don't know what is?</Msg><Username>fattymcbutterpants2001</Username><Timestamp>1360790430788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:20:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360791800053-70</Id><Title>Thanks Chambers for the market selloff tomorrow, Just don't talk</Title><Msg>Thanks Chambers for the market selloff tomorrow, Just don't talk</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360791800053</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:43:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360792131292-71</Id><Title>Baytrail: Intel's Basket case chip</Title><Msg>Intel is producing Baytrial because it likes to finish projects that it has started, but the indication from the Surface Pro launch is clear -- they would rather sell high priced Core series Haswells into tablets than cheap Baytrails. There's no other way they're maintaining ASPs with the continuing growth in the tablet market. Secondly, when compared with core series laptops, a Baytrail based tablet would suck at running legacy apps. Intel doesn't ever want to put out an under-performing solution with their chips. At this point Intel's claims that heavily tweaked idle power will result in a major average power draw reduction will have to be tested in the market. Too bad they couldn't accelerate their deployment of 14nm for Haswell.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360792131292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:48:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360792756844-72</Id><Topic><Title>Thanks Chambers for the market selloff tomorrow, Just don't talk</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1360791800053</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:43:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nuff, you're taking it up the rump since you're holding CSCO. Spread your cheeks and take it like the whimp you are!</Msg><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1360792756844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:59:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360793037159-73</Id><Topic><Title>Baytrail: Intel's Basket case chip</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360792131292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:48:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Baytrail will keep ARM at bay. It does things better than any ARM chip.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1360793037159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:03:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360794041882-74</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Rumors?</Title><Username>jshantazia41</Username><Timestamp>1360770590886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:49:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAMMER !!</Msg><Username>daxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360794041882</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:20:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360794053323-75</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Rumors?</Title><Username>jshantazia41</Username><Timestamp>1360770590886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:49:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAMMER !!</Msg><Username>daxwang</Username><Timestamp>1360794053323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:20:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360795337945-76</Id><Topic><Title>Good chance to close over support today</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1360789197495</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>21:23 was the support level this morning.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1360795337945</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:42:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360795947758-77</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Corporation UPDATED NEWS!</Title><Username>konfliktgebietjudith</Username><Timestamp>1360605742311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:02:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like your free article.</Msg><Username>lenieceangela</Username><Timestamp>1360795947758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:52:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360796337599-78</Id><Title>61% Downside Ahead For ARM Holdings As Lofty Expectations Meet Harsh Reality -at Seeking Alpha-</Title><Msg>Interesting article would appear the ARMH bubble is about to burst.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1360796337599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:58:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360798651631-79</Id><Topic><Title>Intel....leaving it's area of expertise and going HOLLYWOOD!</Title><Username>fattymcbutterpants2001</Username><Timestamp>1360790430788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:20:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With intel they hired some of the best and brightest people in that feild to run things.Intell will be just fine.My personal belief are people will love it to be able to interact with each other over the tv.This could be a big hit .Intell will make money in advertising and selling the devices.Looks like a win win plus they will make a mothly income selling the service. This will be a big money maker.</Msg><Username>kravcleve</Username><Timestamp>1360798651631</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:37:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360800656035-80</Id><Topic><Title>Baytrail: Intel's Basket case chip</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360792131292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:48:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the Surface Pro launch is clear -- they would rather sell high priced Core series Haswells into tablets than cheap Baytrails." Intel would "rather" but they will sell what the customer wants. ASUS is building a Lexington based "Fonepad". Intel will not maintain ASP at their current levels but that will not slow them from selling a lower cost part into a socket at a lower price. Hitting a specific product "ASP" is not the Intel goal. They will have to sell more chips at a lower ASP to make up for any cannibalization. "Secondly, when compared with core series laptops, a Baytrail based tablet would suck at running legacy apps. Intel doesn't ever want to put out an under-performing solution with their chips." When compared to core series, you are right, Baytrail would underperform in comparison. ASUS is smart enough to know how their system will perform and will target it for the market they want. Their name is on the front too. IMO, I am not sure what legacy app would not perform quite fine on a system configured with a Baytrail. "At this point Intel's claims that heavily tweaked idle power will result in a major average power draw reduction will have to be tested in the market." The recent detailed power measurements on Atom vs ARM had me scratching my head. ARM had a lower IDLE draw but the ATOM seemed to have a lower EXECUTION draw. I think it is due to the onchip ATOM cache memory. The ATOM has to maintain coherrency of the cache even when idling but has a lower miss rate (accesses memory less) than ARM. When you access external memory, it takes larger buffer transistors to drive the address and data lines lines. When running an application, ARM has to access external memory more and burns more power than the ATOM because ATOM memory references are satisfied by cache hits. When idling, ATOM has to power the cache. Intel CPU designs in the future (maybe except server chips) will have an onchip voltage regulator that will allow them to lower the voltage (reduces power consumption) or completely power down chip sections. "Too bad they couldn't accelerate their deployment of 14nm for Haswell." A 22nm Haswell with its redesigned power distribution system will be fine. Intel release 14nm midyear with Haswell but it is more likely they will stay on schedule and move 14nm into productions this year but not with Haswell as a lead product.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360800656035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:10:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360800982374-81</Id><Topic><Title>Intel....leaving it's area of expertise and going HOLLYWOOD!</Title><Username>fattymcbutterpants2001</Username><Timestamp>1360790430788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:20:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are unaware of the secret details of this. I think we'll all be stunned, INTC the next Disney with semiconductors, and INTC stock at $100 in a year. Stay tuned...to INTC TV.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360800982374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:16:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360801309553-82</Id><Title>INTC TV will be HUGE!!!!</Title><Msg>Wait til you hear the details and see the pricing. And, "customer will buy directly from us"....well, whom might INTC buy to expand its "us" persona? Netflix? Disney? This is going to be huge.....</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360801309553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:21:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360801348137-83</Id><Title>INTC $50 in one year, $100 in two...</Title><Msg>HUGE things are about to happen.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360801348137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:22:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360802763944-84</Id><Title>Surface Pro gets worst repairability score for any tablet "ever" !?? ROFL!</Title><Msg>Surface Pro flops in repairability test, says iFixit Worst score ever for a tablet after a tear-down, says DIYer site, matches lousy score of Apple's MacBook Pro with Retina By Gregg Keizer February 13, 2013 04:21 PM ET . Computerworld - Popular do-it-yourself website iFixit today gave Microsoft's Surface Pro tablet the lowest-possible repair score, just 1 out of a possible 10, after spending hours getting the device open. "The Surface Pro received a 1 out of 10 score on our repairability scale -- the worst any tablet has ever received," said Miroslav Djuric, iFixit's chief information architect, in an email Wednesday. "The display assembly is anchored down with the most adhesive we've ever seen on a small device. In fact, it took us well over an hour to figure out how to get inside -- an iFixit first." Microsoft introduced the Surface Pro in mid-2012, but started selling it only last Saturday, Feb. 9. Within hours, the $999 128GB configuration sold out. The $899 model with 64GB of storage space, however, remains in stock on Microsoft's online store. The Surface Pro iFixit tore apart was the latter; presumably the 128GB model differs only in the SSD's (solid-drive storage) number of gigabytes. More on Surface The tear-down experts encountered copious amounts of adhesive that fixed the display and battery to the case. "We tried every method we could think of to free the screen, including cutting the adhesive, to no avail," iFixit said in the step-by-step notes documenting the disassembly. "This Pro requires a pro method. Thankfully, we have one: We call it the 'Heat-It-Up-and-Poke-It-Till-It-Does-What-We-Want' method." Djuric knocked the battery adhesive, too. "We don't understand the point of heavily-glued batteries. This kind of planned obsolesce is completely unnecessary," he wrote. On the plus side, Micron's 1.8-in. RealSSD C400 solid-state drive could be easily removed and replaced with one sporting more storage, assuming the do-it-yourself managed to get inside the Surface Pro without damaging a component or sheering off a cable. Other iFixit finds included confirmation of the Intel CPU, an Intel Core i5-3317U; a Wacom chip that drove the tablet's pen-based digitizer; and a pair of ultra-tiny fans to keep everything cool. iFixit also applauded the battery inside the Surface Pro, pegging the LG-made 42 Wh (watt-hour) component the "Cadillac of batteries." But although the battery was rated for 7.4 volts of current -- twice as much as the 43 Wh battery inside Apple's fourth-generation iPad -- earlier testing by reviewers revealed battery lifespans as low as four hours. Microsoft has hinted it will sell an external battery expansion pack, or a battery-powered keyboard, to alleviate the Pro's power limitations. But the fixation with glue and what iFixit said was a "tad crazy" number of screws, pushed the repairability score of the Surface Pro to the minimum of just 1 out of 10. Of course, some tablets have scored nearly as low: Apple's fourth-generation iPad garnered just 2 out of 10 last fall. But Microsoft has pitched the Surface Pro as a dual threat, able to replace both an ultrabook-style PC and a tablet, positioning that makes the device's score all the more notable for matching the rating earned by Apple's Retina-equipped MacBook Pro, which iFixit last year called the "least-repairable laptop we've taken apart."</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1360802763944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:46:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360802784170-85</Id><Topic><Title>Baytrail: Intel's Basket case chip</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360792131292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:48:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If there was no Haswell in the picture then I agree Intel would provide what the customer wanted. But with Haswell in the running for tablet and with a $200+ ASP, selling any Baytrail based systems would cannibalize Haswell sales. Why would they want any of that? They would put all their marketing muscle behind Haswell and not Baytrail for tablets. If what you say about idle power is true, then Haswell should start approaching the power dissipation point suitable for acceptable tablet battery life. I'm somewhat skeptical about Intel's idle power theory.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360802784170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:46:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360802913307-86</Id><Topic><Title>INTC $50 in one year, $100 in two...</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360801348137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:22:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope you're right buddy. Could sure use some more greenbacks. A suitcase full of c-notes would help.</Msg><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1360802913307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:48:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360803075160-87</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro gets worst repairability score for any tablet "ever" !?? ROFL!</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1360802763944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:46:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh Dear !!!!!!</Msg><Username>pumpers_worst_nightmare</Username><Timestamp>1360803075160</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:51:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360804572453-88</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro gets worst repairability score for any tablet "ever" !?? ROFL!</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1360802763944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:46:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sounds like a bunch of chimpanzees who smelled a banana. C'mon, you idiot... you don't fix them...you throw these things away.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360804572453</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:16:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360805116926-89</Id><Topic><Title>INTC $50 in one year, $100 in two...</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360801348137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:22:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This same loser used to post as "flumoxed" and claimed to "know things he couldn't tell us" that would take Intel to the moon......That was last year. He has no morals. Read his posts. On days he's on his period, he changes his mind on Intel as many as three times.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1360805116926</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:25:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360805727223-90</Id><Topic><Title>INTC $50 in one year, $100 in two...</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360801348137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:22:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are right. There's a very big deal going down with this one. Details will become clear in Q2.</Msg><Username>previs_beameister</Username><Timestamp>1360805727223</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:35:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360805738610-91</Id><Topic><Title>INTC $50 in one year, $100 in two...</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1360801348137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:22:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hard to believe a grown man would spend his entire life assuming ridiculous aliases &amp; posting garbage on a chat board,nuff you"re a complete waste of air &amp; space.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1360805738610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:35:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360806639530-92</Id><Topic><Title>Baytrail: Intel's Basket case chip</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360792131292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:48:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If an Intel customer wants to buy a Haswell for their product, Intel will sell it to them. If an Intel customer wants to buy a Baytrail for their product, Intel will sell it to them. Sometimes a Baytrail based product will "cannibalize" a Haswell product and sometimes someone will buy a Haswell when all is needed is a Baytrail. Intel and their customer would prefer to sell the higher priced product and they will market it more heavily. Neither will pass up a sale for a lower priced product and the market will determine the mix. A lower revenue sale is still more than a NO SALE. If you remember the power disspation curves of the 22nm Intel Trigate, the power consumption continued to drop as you lowered the voltage. With the VTR onchip, Intel can control the voltage with more granularly. "then Haswell should start approaching the power dissipation point suitable for acceptable tablet battery life" I agree with your statement. I doubt that an Intel customer would buy a Haswell to fit into the tablet form factor though when a less powerful CPU would do the job at their desired price point. The market will determine what is built.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360806639530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:50:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360806866305-93</Id><Topic><Title>Intel....leaving it's area of expertise and going HOLLYWOOD!</Title><Username>fattymcbutterpants2001</Username><Timestamp>1360790430788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:20:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But there're not,INTC has had all the right people &amp; know how for years FATSO.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1360806866305</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:54:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360807720033-94</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro gets worst repairability score for any tablet "ever" !?? ROFL!</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1360802763944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:46:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Of course, some tablets have scored nearly as low: Apple's fourth-generation iPad garnered just 2 out of 10 last fall." That is why Apple's 4th version just got a 2.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1360807720033</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:08:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360808663194-95</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Pro is not just for work</Title><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1360782457220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:07:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel Haswell GT3 Graphics To Ship With Low Power Ultrabooks Hardware Posted 2 months ago by Hassan Mujtaba Intel Haswell GT3 to Power 3rd Generation Ultrabooks Now as we reported a day ago, Intel plans to launch Ivy Bridge-Y series low TDP chips in Q1 2013. Haswell series chips would arrive in Q2 2013 with the most basic Dual Core models featuring GT1 and GT2 level graphic chipsets. Chinese publication of VR-Zone now confirms that there would also be Haswell-U based chips featuring the GT3 level graphic chipsets which would be fused on certain CPUs with TDP ranging between 15-25 Watts (14″ and 15″ models). The following is an Haswell-U Core i7 series ES with a rated TDP of 15W: If you didn’t know already, Haswell GT3 graphics chipset is said to be 3 times faster than Ivy Bridge HD 4000 series and would most probably be know as the Intel HD 5000 series graphics chip. The specific codename of the chip is ‘Intel Haswell HD Graphics – GT3ULT’ from a leaked specification shot by VR-Zone. Furthermore, the Haswell GT3 chips would come with 40 Execution units compared to 16 EUs on IvyBridge. This however doesn’t rules out the possibility of Haswell GT3 graphics on desktop variants but we have to wait to see those. Haswell is expected in April-June 2013. wccftechDOTcom/intel-haswell-gt3-graphics-ship-power-ultrabooks/#ixzz2Kn6YSzJZ</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1360808663194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:24:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360809161308-96</Id><Title>Intel Web TV Getting Some Positive Spin</Title><Msg>Judging from the titles of the articles, it seems that the press think that Intel might be on to something with its web TV offering. Here's a few: Has Intel cracked the TV problem that Apple couldn't? Could Intel Be the Next Big Threat to Netflix and Redbox? Intel's web TV service will be smart But the real proof is in how much effort the board shills are putting into trying to create negative spin. Looks like Intel has a winner...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360809161308</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:32:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360809937132-97</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Web TV Getting Some Positive Spin</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360809161308</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:32:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The live television and on-demand content that Intel has announced isn’t something Netflix or Redbox offer, and it could be a key point for winning over customers. If Intel can match content quality and amounts to Netflix and RedBox while also exclusively offering live content, it may be able to steal customers from both sides of the fence… A multilevel service like this can draw in customers who currently only use online services to watch video but want more, only use traditional cable or satellite but want online video, or pay for both traditional and online services but want it all in one package." From wallstcheatsheet</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360809937132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:45:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360810607102-98</Id><Title>61% Downside Ahead For ARM Holdings</Title><Msg>[Don't miss Ashraf's informative article as he identifies quite a few of the sharp pointy objects that the ARM Bubble is descending towards. I think his evaluation of the stock value at $16.80 is a bit high but it's in the ballpark...] Conclusion ARM's stock is in a bubble that is set to burst as soon as the signs that the major growth spurt that it experienced as smartphones ramped fade very quickly over the next year or two. The earnings/revenue growth will slow substantially, and with the advent of competitive pressures from Intel, it is unlikely to maintain a monopolistic position in the smartphone/tablet space for much longer. Further, the server opportunity, should it prove to be more than a mirage, will add next to nothing to the top and bottom lines, as the unit volumes are simply nowhere near what they are in the spaces that ARM is traditionally used to competing in. Finally, as insiders continue to sell out of their positions, it will eventually dawn on the buyers that they have been sold an overpriced, overinflated, and over-hyped stock. At Qualcomm's or TSMC's valuation of roughly 20x earnings, ARM -- based on FY2013E projected earnings, is worth roughly $16.8/share, implying 61% downside. Given that the highest analyst price target is $50/share, and further, given that the stock has tried and repeatedly failed to hold above $44, 15% optimistic, hype-driven upside for over 60% of very real, numbers-based downside seems like a near no-brainer short sale at these levels.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360810607102</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:56:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360810635639-99</Id><Topic><Title>Baytrail: Intel's Basket case chip</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360792131292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:48:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My statement is Baytrial will be completely ignored by Intel for all practical purposes. They don't want it to succeed.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360810635639</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:57:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360810837693-100</Id><Topic><Title>Baytrail: Intel's Basket case chip</Title><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1360792131292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:48:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"My statement is Baytrial will be completely ignored by Intel for all practical purposes. They don't want it to succeed." [Remind me again - who dresses and feeds you? And it's Bay Trail...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360810837693</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:00:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360810975782-101</Id><Title>61% Downside Ahead For ARM Holdings As Lofty Expectations Meet Harsh Reality</Title><Msg>[Don't miss Ashraf's informative article as he identifies quite a few of the sharp pointy objects that the ARM Bubble is descending towards. I think his evaluation of the stock value at $16.80 is a bit high but it's in the ballpark...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360810975782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:02:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360811180464-102</Id><Topic><Title>61% Downside Ahead For ARM Holdings As Lofty Expectations Meet Harsh Reality</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360810975782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:02:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At Qualcomm's or TSMC's valuation of roughly 20x earnings, ARM -- based on FY2013E projected earnings, is worth roughly $16.8/share, implying 61% downside. Given that the highest analyst price target is $50/share, and further, given that the stock has tried and repeatedly failed to hold above $44, 15% optimistic, hype-driven upside for over 60% of very real, numbers-based downside seems like a near no-brainer short sale at these levels.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360811180464</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:06:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360811491002-103</Id><Title>Fudzilla: 1-chip Haswell aims at 50 percent lower average power</Title><Msg>Intel's Haswell comes in at least four major processor lines. The first to launch are quad- and dual-cores with 37, 47 and 57W TDPs, followed by H line with quad-core processors only. After Q3 13 we can expect the new low power U-series. The last to launch in Q4 13 is the 1-chip Y processor line. The Haswell 1-chip platform has integrated I/O and it is optimized for Ultrabooks. It is the new magic chip that can drive Ultrabook TDPs down dramatically. Intel is targeting 80 percent of 2-chip dual-core Haswell performance with these chips, but with an average power saving of close to 50 percent. Idle power consumption should be up to 3.5 times lower. The Y processor line has a TDP of 11.5W, while its SDP should be as low as 7.5W. Scenario Design Power or SDP represents the average workload expected from a tablet or detachable Haswell notebook. Average power comparison estimates are based on Windows 7 MM07 Office productivity suite, while the idle power claim is based on Win 8 Idle display on. Despite the fact that the Haswell Y line is still a long way off and it won't be introduced before Q4 2013, the processors look really interesting and having Core i7 or Core i5 class performance at around 7W definitely sounds nice.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360811491002</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:11:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360811669351-104</Id><Topic><Title>Fudzilla: 1-chip Haswell aims at 50 percent lower average power</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360811491002</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:11:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should the ARM Bubble make it into the second half of 2013 (unlikely given the proliferation of pointy objects just in the last week), Haswell is guaranteed to let all of the air out...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360811669351</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:14:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360811738873-105</Id><Topic><Title>61% Downside Ahead For ARM Holdings As Lofty Expectations Meet Harsh Reality</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360810975782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:02:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMG, didn't know you could sink so low. Now you are pumping Ashraf's Seeking Alpha articles. Anybody else watching Wally's complete and utter implosion over the last 2 years?????</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1360811738873</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:15:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360812455378-106</Id><Title>Intel Beats Apple's iTV To The Punch</Title><Msg>Yesterday, Apple CEO Tim Cook, in a fireside chat, tried to convince the world that Apple is still the center of innovation in the technology world. Cook said that about one quarter of Apple employees were working on new products. There were no specifics but presumably new products include iTV. While Cook was being vague, Intel was beating iTV to the punch, at least in terms of announcing a new TV service with a fair amount of details. What is a semiconductor company doing announcing a TV service? Besides making semiconductors, Intel also employs more than 10,000 programmers and has taken stakes in about 400 start ups. Many of these start ups are related to media. Intel brought in Erik Huggers, who had previously launched a high profile internet based service and app called iPlayer at BBC. Huggers hired a dream team from companies such as Apple, Microsoft and Rovi. Intel’s history in TV boxes is one of failures. Some readers may recall failed efforts like Logitech’s Revue based on Google technology that used TV optimized chips from Intel. In 2011, Intel closed its retail TV business. In spite of Intel’s past failures, there is precedence of success in Xbox. Microsoft, a software company, ended up producing a hugely successful device in Xbox. Special Offer: Daily stock picks from Forbes Dividend Investor are up 11.7% vs. 7.4% for identically timed buys of the S&amp;P 500 index from July 11, 2012 through February 6. Average yield on buys is 5.8%. Click here for a membership offer from Steve Forbes. Intel is not only producing a TV set top box, it plans to provide streaming content over the internet. Intel will be competing not only with cable providers such as Comcast, but also with the likes of Netflix and Hulu Plus. There is no way to know if this time will be a charm for Intel in the TV business. However, Intel does bring some advantages and the effort is worthwhile. The Intel name is not only well known to consumers, it is a well-respected name. Content providers are wary of Apple; they saw what Apple did to the music business and they do not want to make the same mistake again. Content providers are likely to welcome a major technology firm such as Intel with open arms just to make sure Apple does not become dominant in providing video content. For this reason, I have recommended to my subscribers a small starter position in Intel. Will Intel ultimately become a threat to Apple iTV? One thing is for sure, Intel has beaten Apple to the punch by announcing the service.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1360812455378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:27:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360813870291-107</Id><Title>Succession Planning</Title><Msg>EVERY company has a succession plan...........so now Intel is going outside to find a new CEO ? Doesn't speak highly of Intel as a forward looking company.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1360813870291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:51:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360815445707-108</Id><Topic><Title>Succession Planning</Title><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1360813870291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:51:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are taking their time and looking inside and out. It's called being responsible. I thought you sold your 1800 shares and moved on to another Dividend payer?</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1360815445707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 23:17:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>