<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362114054188-1</Id><Topic><Title>big.Little is a joke</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1362103214543</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 21:00:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasted of Silicon</Msg><Username>only_paper_money</Username><Timestamp>1362114054188</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 00:00:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362115310820-2</Id><Topic><Title>Question for everyone</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1362105531821</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 21:38:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A15 is too much of a power hog to go into a phone and the big.Little concept cannot be implemented" Tegra 4, using big.LITTLE, but with all A15s, will be in a ZTE phone...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362115310820</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 00:21:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362115832040-3</Id><Topic><Title>Question for everyone</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1362105531821</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 21:38:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>big.LITTLE should be the poster child for ARM's failing, fading fabrication. It clearly illustrates the chewing gum, bailing wire, and duct tape solutions that ARM is having to implement simply because they don't have Intel's state-of-the-art fabrication and manufacturing...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362115832040</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 00:30:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362116789323-4</Id><Title>The Problem with ARM</Title><Msg>ARM Holdings designs a simple processor...other companies licenses this design and modify it in any way they want. As they modify and build upon their previous modifications, they in essence create their own "architecture". You can see it more clearly now with the addition of the A15 and it's power consumption issues. Each ARM licensee are scrambling to develop an "architecture" that will blend the A7s and A15s into the same SoC but somehow mimimize the use of the A15s to reduce power consumption. Samsung is trying to implement their Exynos using the big.Little concept while nVidia is doing their own implementation (Tegra 4). The problem is that the logic of when to use the A15s and when to use the A7s reside on the software. The software developers need to add this logic in each of their programs. This means EVERY software (including OSes such as Android) will have to have special code written specifically for the Exynos "architecture" and Tegra "architecture". Therein lies the problem. Software developers do not want to do this. The amount of maintainance needed to maintain code for each and every "architecture" and their iterations would be too cumbersome. Samsung gave up on their Exynos for their next Galaxy products. nVidia is proclaiming to the world how great their Tegra 4 is, even when it is not even close to finish. No doubt they are trying to convince phone makers to sign up and thereby convince to software developers to support their "architecture". In the end, there can only be 1 or 2 architectures that software developers can support. Intel will be one.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1362116789323</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 00:46:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362117361549-5</Id><Topic><Title>The Problem with ARM</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1362116789323</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 00:46:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tegra 4 uses an A15 as its 5th core... Too bad... it was a nice speech...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362117361549</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 00:56:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362120537070-6</Id><Topic><Title>Question for everyone</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1362105531821</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 21:38:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>big.LITTLE is a simple idea that makes sense. It's not difficult to realize in a real system and will require minimal changes at the OS and app level while providing significant battery life benefits. I didn't read all this from an ARM blurb. I made it up based on my understanding. The initial reports about Samsung abandoning their Exynos Octa appear to be heresay. Their published power/performance numbers have been analyzed and found to lie in the ballpark for smartphones. Intel has a 6 month advantage very 2 years in the best case for low power chips (e.g. between Q4, 2103 when they release their first 22nm low power chip till Q2, 2014 when TSMC cathes up with its 20nm). During this small window they may be slightly better than the best ARM offering, the remaining 18 months they wont. With their miniscular presence in the mobile market at present, what does that tell you about their future prospects?</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1362120537070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 01:48:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362124792660-7</Id><Topic><Title>More A15 benchmarks (Ubuntu Linux)</Title><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1362061374239</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 09:22:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do a google for "ARM big little white paper" and it will answer all your questions. Big/little has different usage models, and one of them can have all 8 cores visible to the OS.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1362124792660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 02:59:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362125036975-8</Id><Topic><Title>The Problem with ARM</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1362116789323</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 00:46:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>? Big/little has several usage models, but none of them require end user software changes (ie, Software developer support). The simplest usage model doesn't even need any kernel/OS changes, while the more complex model does need kernel/OS changes they are small and are easy to add/maintain.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1362125036975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 03:03:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362125333584-9</Id><Topic><Title>Question for everyone</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1362105531821</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 21:38:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Er, the A15 can go into phone, the latency switch is 20-30 micro seconds and needs no changes for software developers...</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1362125333584</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 03:08:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362126201306-10</Id><Title>How are Lenovo Yoga sales doing?</Title><Msg>No word yet from Lenovo, but this is what we know from their website. They have two models, one is 11 inch with Nvdia processor and the other is a 13 inch with Intel Core processors. The Nvdia version which operates on a windows RT OS was introduced at $949 during the holidays. The Intel version which runs on a full Windows 8 OS was introduced at $1329 during the holidays. From the two, the 11 inch non Intel version has only 3 reviews by customers, with about 4 stars. The 13 inch Intel Core version has 73 reviews with about 4.5 stars. This alone could be telling us that more have bought the Intel version. With a review ratio of 73 to 3, I would say quite a bit more. Also, Lenovo currently has a sale with a $30 coupon on the 13 inch Intel version. Whereas they have a whopping $350 coupon on the 11 inch version. They are cutting the price of the ARM version by about 12 times over the Intel version. That's gotta tell us something too. At least at Lenovo, things don't seem good at all for ARM based products.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1362126201306</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 03:23:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362126614591-11</Id><Title>More comparisons at Lenovo between ARM and Intel.</Title><Msg>Looking at their tablets, they sell their thinkpad tablets only with Intel processors. With their ideapad models, they have 3 version. The Lynx k3011 is an Intel Atom version. It's a new model and is priced with no coupons. The A series is the cheapest with Nvdia processors and is priced with a $70 coupon. Nearly 40% off of the cheapest choice. The S2110 versions have Qcom processors, are the second cheapest versions, and are priced with a $160 coupon. That's nearly 30% off. So this tells us that even though Intel versions are the most expensive, they must be much more in demand since no coupons are necessary to sell them at this point. ARM versions much be doing pretty bad to require such large discounts with coupons by Lenovo.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1362126614591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 03:30:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362126779790-12</Id><Topic><Title>More comparisons at Lenovo between ARM and Intel.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1362126614591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 03:30:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the way, the thinkpads versions, both of which are only powered by Intel Atom processors have no coupons available. Meaning that they must be selling pretty well. At least well enough for Lenovo to not bother offerring any discounts.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1362126779790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 03:32:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362143592919-13</Id><Topic><Title>More comparisons at Lenovo between ARM and Intel.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1362126614591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 03:30:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well they don't need to discount them. The 5 year old Atom core outperforms all the ARM chips listed so you know which one folks want to buy. Another intangible is that the Intel Inside brand sells. They know that Intel builds a high quality product even if they don't know how it performs.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1362143592919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 08:13:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362143851761-14</Id><Title>Any more questions about Intel battery life? Intel on Android????</Title><Msg>Intel Breaks Into ARM Territory With 7-Inch Asus Tablet Posted: February 28, 2013 11:15AM Author: EuroFight Intel has finally broken into the low-cost Android tablet market with the debut of a 7-inch tablet running an Intel Atom Z2420 processor. The tablet is designed by Asus and is priced at a modest $249. It features 3G data and voice connectivity, as well as boasting a 1280x800 screen and nine hours of battery life. The tablet's closest ARM competitor is the HP Slate 7, a 7-inch tablet with a dual-core processor and six hours battery life, but no 3G connectivity which is available for $169. The Asus tablet is one of the first mobile devices to feature a Lexington chip from Intel's low-cost Clover Trail series of processors. Intel hopes this series will help it gain some of the mobile market share currently dominated by the likes of ARM-based devices. Source: CNET</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362143851761</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 08:17:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362144122149-15</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Could Be Buffett Target &amp; 3 Chip and Big Data Stocks on the Move at Wall St. Cheat Sheet04:45pm EST</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1362088766920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 16:59:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It seems logical to me those short shares are Buffets.Thats certainly one of the best strategies to bring the price down to a range where he could accumulate. Why would a fund want to pay 4.4% dividend on a stock which has little downside ?</Msg><Username>r.idonius</Username><Timestamp>1362144122149</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 08:22:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362144364575-16</Id><Topic><Title>The TRUTH about Intel Corporation...</Title><Username>wayne.garza</Username><Timestamp>1361975360186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks a lot!</Msg><Username>bdanny124</Username><Timestamp>1362144364575</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 08:26:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362144773589-17</Id><Title>ARM is well known by consumers now............for all the wrong reasons</Title><Msg>Did Microsoft actually have a plan to destroy ARM when it released the pitiful RT platform?</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362144773589</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 08:32:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362145275504-18</Id><Topic><Title>INTC could possibly end up being the stock to monitor this week.</Title><Username>rodney_leboeuf</Username><Timestamp>1362138405346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 06:46:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>huge potential here</Msg><Username>dennisortiz82</Username><Timestamp>1362145275504</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 08:41:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362146518153-19</Id><Topic><Title>The TRUTH about Intel Corporation...</Title><Username>wayne.garza</Username><Timestamp>1361975360186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report</Msg><Username>todd.meyn</Username><Timestamp>1362146518153</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:01:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362146751071-20</Id><Topic><Title>INTC could possibly end up being the stock to monitor this week.</Title><Username>rodney_leboeuf</Username><Timestamp>1362138405346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 06:46:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>best ever</Msg><Username>andres.wansley</Username><Timestamp>1362146751071</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:05:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362147047671-21</Id><Topic><Title>INTC could possibly end up being the stock to monitor this week.</Title><Username>rodney_leboeuf</Username><Timestamp>1362138405346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 06:46:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great well writeen</Msg><Username>bwillie45</Username><Timestamp>1362147047671</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:10:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362147262565-22</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Rumored to be bought out!</Title><Username>ericking531</Username><Timestamp>1361967974894</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 07:26:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>informative</Msg><Username>bob.evans70</Username><Timestamp>1362147262565</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:14:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362147812924-23</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is well known by consumers now............for all the wrong reasons</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362144773589</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 08:32:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice theory.</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1362147812924</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:23:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362148707148-24</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is well known by consumers now............for all the wrong reasons</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362144773589</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 08:32:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's rare to read something plausible and clever on this board...yes, that's interesting.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362148707148</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:38:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362148750458-25</Id><Topic><Title>The TRUTH about Intel Corporation...</Title><Username>wayne.garza</Username><Timestamp>1361975360186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>ashley_littell</Username><Timestamp>1362148750458</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:39:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362148812667-26</Id><Topic><Title>Fantasy land articles about Buffet buying INTEL showed up the past several days</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1362146727137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:05:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when you're in the market don't you feel like your back in 7th grade and the news is all about which girl got felt up by which guy at the movies last saturday afternoon, who's hot, and who's a nerd?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362148812667</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:40:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362149010703-27</Id><Topic><Title>With Intel grabbing Altera orders, can we now begin speculating about future Apple hookup?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361998258469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:50:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Altera going to INTC is a big deal but more of a reflection of Xilinx moving to TSMC than anything else. In the FPGA business whoever is first to a process node wins big market share. Xilinx was at UMC and lagged Altera/TSMC @ 40nm by close to a year and Altera gained huge market share. Xilinx moved to TSMC and beat Altera to 28nm by a month or so. Xilinx will probably beat Altera to TSMC 20nm as well. Since Altera prefers a high performance process they can probably use the same Intel process as the microprocessors, not the SoC ultra low power version which is a big challenge for INTC. If so Altera can beat Xilinx to 14nm by a significant margin and win back market share. Apple is at TSMC 20nm. For 14nm they will probably use Samsung again which will ramp about the same time as Intel 14nm SoC or maybe earlier. Xilinx will probably use Samsung 14nm as well. IMHO</Msg><Username>semiconductorguy</Username><Timestamp>1362149010703</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:43:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362149044510-28</Id><Title>Just reinvested my IRA dividend, picked up over 100 more shares</Title><Msg>Keep on truckin.</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1362149044510</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:44:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362149159669-29</Id><Title>Who bought Apple at 700?</Title><Msg>I bought Intel at 20.</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1362149159669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:45:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362149212727-30</Id><Topic><Title>The TRUTH about Intel Corporation...</Title><Username>wayne.garza</Username><Timestamp>1361975360186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice work! thanks a lot!</Msg><Username>troylee677</Username><Timestamp>1362149212727</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:46:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362149434756-31</Id><Title>ACORDING TO WALLIS--</Title><Msg>"Intel is a $40 stock" that is "good for $30" That Wallis is a real card! TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1362149434756</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:50:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362149459954-32</Id><Title>YTRV- Statement of Ownership Filed-13G read at Investershub</Title><Msg>look for some bigger news coming!!!!</Msg><Username>gorhill</Username><Timestamp>1362149459954</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:50:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362149803176-33</Id><Topic><Title>INTC could possibly end up being the stock to monitor this week.</Title><Username>rodney_leboeuf</Username><Timestamp>1362138405346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 06:46:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cant wait for pick</Msg><Username>ninorichard776</Username><Timestamp>1362149803176</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:56:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362150018781-34</Id><Title>If Buffet buys Intel....</Title><Msg>I'll never have to work again... oh, wait, don't work now. At least shorts like Nuff will be screwed royally. Nuff will be flipping burgers or working as a bathroom attendant to make ends meet.</Msg><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1362150018781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:00:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362150312023-35</Id><Topic><Title>If Buffet buys Intel....</Title><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1362150018781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:00:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least that's a job,better than posting trash from a chat board.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1362150312023</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:05:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362150546836-36</Id><Topic><Title>If Buffet buys Intel....</Title><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1362150018781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:00:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buffet loves IBM. I bet he buys it and sells it to IBM.</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1362150546836</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:09:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362150638354-37</Id><Title>Is Intel positioning itself for a buyout?</Title><Msg>35/share.</Msg><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1362150638354</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:10:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362150780804-38</Id><Topic><Title>= = Analyst Predicts Decline to 17.07 =SEE REPORT=</Title><Username>blackscott588</Username><Timestamp>1361404069367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good update.</Msg><Username>nickring916</Username><Timestamp>1362150780804</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:13:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362150815713-39</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>blacknick671</Username><Timestamp>1361906263256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:17:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good update.</Msg><Username>nickring916</Username><Timestamp>1362150815713</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:13:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362151007161-40</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel positioning itself for a buyout?</Title><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1362150638354</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:10:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that the buy out value?</Msg><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1362151007161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:16:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362151462806-41</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (INTC)</Title><Username>frankbryant786</Username><Timestamp>1361483522525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:52:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report.</Msg><Username>mikereed359</Username><Timestamp>1362151462806</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:24:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362152115225-42</Id><Topic><Title>If Buffet buys Intel....</Title><Username>harrydick836</Username><Timestamp>1362150018781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:00:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seriously, how can Buffett buy Intel? With what money. The company is already worth over $100 Billion and this is at the current ridiculously cheaps stock price. He may decide to buy about 10% of the company which will place alot of buying pressure raising the stock price. But the whole company? I think Intel is not concerned about $35 a share. With the kind of investments they are making for the future, they are shooting for much higher stock price. Something where their valuation alone reaches around 12 to 15 range. And EPS of at least $3 in the next 2 to 3 years suggesting a stock price of $36 to $45.</Msg><Username>floridajk99</Username><Timestamp>1362152115225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:35:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362152912841-43</Id><Title>What the neck is Intel doing with a 9 P/E.Shows</Title><Msg>you algorithmic geeks programing machines don't know squat about companies.</Msg><Username>a33stacybb</Username><Timestamp>1362152912841</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:48:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362153249196-44</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is well known by consumers now............for all the wrong reasons</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362144773589</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 08:32:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft doesn't have enough collective intelligence to do anything that clever, but you're right on the outcome. Consumers haven't really been aware what processor was in their smartphone because the vendors promote their own flavor of ARM's design. So Windows RT is the public's first recognition of ARM because they had to learn about it when they discovered ARM doesn't run their legacy Windows software. So ARM has become the processor associated with "No you can't". Whereas the Intel brand is associated with "Yes, you can".</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1362153249196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:54:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362153672011-45</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>linkosarah</Username><Timestamp>1362149300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:48:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ntel (NASDAQ: INTC) has had many years of excellent growth and is currently the firm to beat in the microprocessor space. With a current dividend yield of 4.37% and a P/E of 9.66 I don’t see any reason to pass up this juggernaut of the semiconductor space. Over the next few years Intel is expected to gain around 5% a year in terms of EPS; the stock also has a one-year target price of around $23.50, depending on the analyst that you have. At today’s levels, $23.50 would represent a very reasonable gain, especially when you throw in the 4.37% yield.</Msg><Username>messerlysee</Username><Timestamp>1362153672011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:01:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362153855533-46</Id><Topic><Title>With Intel grabbing Altera orders, can we now begin speculating about future Apple hookup?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361998258469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:50:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Apple is at TSMC 20nm. For 14nm they will probably use Samsung again which will ramp about the same time as Intel 14nm SoC or maybe earlier. Xilinx will probably use Samsung 14nm as well." Intel's 14nm SoC is coming in 2014.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1362153855533</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:04:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362154295660-47</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>linkosarah</Username><Timestamp>1362149300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:48:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this article.</Msg><Username>lindslymargie</Username><Timestamp>1362154295660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:11:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362154628406-48</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is well known by consumers now............for all the wrong reasons</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362144773589</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 08:32:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are right---the notion of Ballmer tying his shoes in the morning and cleaning himself up is unthinkable...but don't you love serendipity?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362154628406</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:17:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362154781210-49</Id><Topic><Title>The TRUTH about Intel Corporation...</Title><Username>wayne.garza</Username><Timestamp>1361975360186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude this is awesome !!!!</Msg><Username>kirk.gallardo</Username><Timestamp>1362154781210</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:19:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362155248776-50</Id><Topic><Title>ARM is well known by consumers now............for all the wrong reasons</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362144773589</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 08:32:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think Microsoft cares that much about ARM one way or the other but it is clear that Microsoft's big push in that effort is going to hurt ARM. Window RT is not working out very well for them and has left consumers a bit confused. Intel will fix all this for them by releasing an x86 chip that will work with a regular WIndows OS and be power thrifty. This year is kind of the tipping point for ARM in my estimation. Intel is getting to the point where they have competitive chips for mobile devices and on the other hand the needs of smart phones are sort of outgrowing ARM which really never evisioned this much performance being needed by a phone. I am heavily long both MSFT and INTC. I really think folks are badly underestimating both companies and their push toward mobile. Obviously they underestimated the growth in smart handsets but make no mistake they are able competitors. MSFT virtually destroyed AAPL on the desktop and INTC virtually destroyed AMD in the CPU market. One thing I know about both companies is that they may not get it exactly right out of the box but they are relentless. Get ready for the rise of Wintel in the mobile space.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1362155248776</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:27:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362155525198-51</Id><Topic><Title>What the neck is Intel doing with a 9 P/E.Shows</Title><Username>a33stacybb</Username><Timestamp>1362152912841</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:48:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Frankly, I think INTC is the only fairly valued stock out there. All others are grossly overpriced.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362155525198</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:32:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362156035545-52</Id><Topic><Title>INTC could possibly end up being the stock to monitor this week.</Title><Username>rodney_leboeuf</Username><Timestamp>1362138405346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 06:46:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i want this report send it already</Msg><Username>johngardella72</Username><Timestamp>1362156035545</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:40:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362156826154-53</Id><Title>voulme picking up!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>25 million now .........</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1362156826154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:53:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362157392422-54</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>linkosarah</Username><Timestamp>1362149300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:48:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have entered my email address.</Msg><Username>messerlysee</Username><Timestamp>1362157392422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362157405535-55</Id><Topic><Title>What the neck is Intel doing with a 9 P/E.Shows</Title><Username>a33stacybb</Username><Timestamp>1362152912841</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 10:48:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MSFT is even more poorly valued. It is projected to out grow most S&amp;P 500 companies but is priced at less then 9x next years earning. Even if INTC's revenues don't grow the EPS will increase about 10% because of buybacks. It doesn't make sense but it is an opportunity for patient investors.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1362157405535</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362157405769-56</Id><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Msg>Microsoft’s Surface Pro is an odd duck. On the one hand, it offers the performance and x86 compatibility that Surface RT lacks. It’s also far faster than Clover Trail-based tablets, which use Intel’s low-power Atom processor. This performance, however, comes at a cost. The Surface Pro’s battery life is substantially worse than Surface RT or Atom-based tablets, it’s significantly heavier (2 pounds, compared to 1.5 for RT) and it’s noticeably thicker than low-power designs. extremetechDOTcom/computing/149481-on-the-hunt-for-the-surface-pros-battery-life</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362157436102-57</Id><Topic><Title>voulme picking up!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1362156826154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:53:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The short were back shorting 1m shares per day during the first half of Feb. Intel is buying back shares against them. It is an interesting battle to watch.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1362157436102</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362159344154-58</Id><Topic><Title>INTC could possibly end up being the stock to monitor this week.</Title><Username>rodney_leboeuf</Username><Timestamp>1362138405346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 06:46:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Checking it out right now.</Msg><Username>vitowilliam326</Username><Timestamp>1362159344154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:35:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362159967254-59</Id><Topic><Title>Who bought Apple at 700?</Title><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1362149159669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:45:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well when I was out saying sell Apple and buy Intel back in December folks laughed. They say that Intel hasn't done anything for 5 years. But look how high Apple has gone. You don't make any money in stocks looking in the rear view mirror. My Intel is higher then what I paid and is nicely outperforming Apple plus I get a fat divy check today. :-)</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1362159967254</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:46:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362161713078-60</Id><Title>Omnivision article bullish on Ultrabooks</Title><Msg>"Further, OmniVision remains optimistic about the impact of Intel’s (INTC) Ultrabooks and other similar products. It is in an advantageous position as the decline in the PC and notebook business is being offset by the rising popularity of tablets and smartphone devices." Can anyone enlighten us as to what the Omnivision visibility on Ultrabooks might be? Maybe they're seeing a lot of video/parts orders?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362161713078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:15:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362162245188-61</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny to watch your sour grapes over RT aborting at birth. PS, check Amazon and Best Buy CUSTOMER reviews and over and over you'll read that people are actually cool with the batter life of 5.5 hours. Ya think Intel is going to sit around and not put better chips with longer battery life in the Pro quickly? Again, your sour grapes over RT failing miserabily are hilarious. What was it Samsung said about RT Tablets? Oh yeah, they said "NO THANKS." LMAO! Don't bother to reply with ARM's stock price since you can't prove that you own any and actually said about a year and a half ago that you DIDN't own any ARM.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362162245188</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:24:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362162578565-62</Id><Topic><Title>INTC could possibly end up being the stock to monitor this week.</Title><Username>rodney_leboeuf</Username><Timestamp>1362138405346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 06:46:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i want this report send it already</Msg><Username>kylesjames857</Username><Timestamp>1362162578565</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:29:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362162833339-63</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chump, "Funny to watch your sour grapes over RT" Really... what did you claim I said.. " Don't bother to reply with ARM's stock price since you can't prove that you own any" DId you notice that ARMH is at a 52-week high...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362162833339</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:33:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362162934203-64</Id><Topic><Title>INTC could possibly end up being the stock to monitor this week.</Title><Username>rodney_leboeuf</Username><Timestamp>1362138405346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 06:46:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good potential</Msg><Username>russellbernard622</Username><Timestamp>1362162934203</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:35:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362162941748-65</Id><Topic><Title>voulme picking up!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1362156826154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:53:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alex - where are you getting this info? TIA</Msg><Username>stockjock44</Username><Timestamp>1362162941748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:35:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362163020614-66</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>L M F A O at the Original Poster.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362163020614</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:37:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362163025173-67</Id><Topic><Title>voulme picking up!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1362156826154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:53:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it going to take an act of god to get us based at $21 ? Where are the value investors ? Absurd being stuck in this range as the company is starting to do everything right .</Msg><Username>pentomic</Username><Timestamp>1362163025173</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:37:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362163087512-68</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO! Run along now, kid. getanid61•Aug 25, 2012 1:05 PM Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362163087512</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:38:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362163884678-69</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All of that is true so it would make sense that anyone interested in today's Surface Pro is willing to accept the weight, the battery life and the thickness for the unparalleled performance it delivers. Once Haswell arrives the weight, battery life and thickness will be so close to today's underperforming tablets the difference won't be important but the Haswell tablet will still be more powerful than the rest.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1362163884678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:51:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362163951071-70</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, y ahoo will let you post the link for it... Let me know when you find it... btw, did you notice ARMH is at a 52-week high...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362163951071</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:52:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362164234668-71</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HaHa! Are you now saying you never said that? Yes you are, and that shows how much of a little baby you are. You just showed your true colors, a jealous little old divorced baby. LOL! PWNED. Have a great weekend, putz. Bye now!</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362164234668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:57:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362164363977-72</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You saying you never said RT was better than Pro back in August of last year? DESPERATE!</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1362164363977</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:59:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362164446645-73</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chump, Got it... you got NOTHING !!!!! Look what you've been reduced to... PATHETIC !!!! btw, did you notice ARMH is at a 52-week high...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362164446645</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:00:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362164841575-74</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"btw, did you notice ARMH is at a 52-week high..." [ARM hasn't been at a 52-week high for over three weeks now, dimwit. They have been putting in the triple top to indicate that they are at the beginning of the long road down...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362164841575</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:07:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362165437573-75</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He knows the link to his remarks are not available anymore, so he uses that technicality to say " I got nothing". I'm smiling big over here knowing how big of a coward he is (by his own very actions) and how desperate HE really is. LOL at RT boy.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362165437573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:17:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362165496656-76</Id><Title>What price is Apple a good buy at?</Title><Msg>It hasn't even hit TRUE capitulation yet, has it?</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362165496656</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:18:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362165658142-77</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chump, "He knows the link to his remarks are not available anymore" Then how did you get your date of Aug 25... CHUMP !!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362165658142</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:20:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362165823429-78</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I clicked on MY posting history, and it shows me responding to link YOU started on August 25th. Anybody can click on my posting history and see YOUR thread. Who's the CHUMP now? You just got PWNED!</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362165823429</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:23:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362165833246-79</Id><Title>Buying</Title><Msg>The buying has totally vanished for the last hour and a half. Amazing!</Msg><Username>medisys</Username><Timestamp>1362165833246</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:23:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362165878863-80</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chump, repeat: post a link... Chump !!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362165878863</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:24:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362166037934-81</Id><Topic><Title>voulme picking up!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1362156826154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:53:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Short information on nasdaqDOTTcom for Intel shows that the short interest from 1/31 to 2/15 increated from 196m to 208m. There are about 22 trading days per month and 11 trading days per 1/2 month. short interest increased by 208.2 - 196.9 = 11.3m shares. 11.3m short shares increase over 11 trading days is 1m shares per day. date shortInterest averageVolume 2/15/2013 208,197,763 30,642,118 1/31/2013 196,957,970 86,401,976 IMO, the share buy back program has two goals. One is to buy back the shares. The second and probably more important goal is to SHAPE THE CHART for the positive. The buy back wants to give the impression of LARGE SHARE ACCUMULATION. They could buy shares quickly but it is more important to shape the chart to grab the interest of the chartists. It appears like the share price takes a hit early in the day and then again in the last 10min of the day when the buy back is turned off. During the day, the steady buying is pushing up the bottom.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1362166037934</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:27:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362166046531-82</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chump, repeat: post a link... Chump !! _________ My word, I knew you were a loser, but you're just down right childish. Acting like you never said RT was better than PRO when YOU know you did. What a little worm. Chump doesn't even do a guy like you justice. I'm laughing so hard now knowing how week and feeble your 52 year old butt is. LMAO! Thanks for a HUGE laugh at your expense. Again, THANKS!</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362166046531</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:27:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362166118726-83</Id><Topic><Title>voulme picking up!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1362156826154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:53:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorts obviously winning the battle. Man some people really hate Intel.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362166118726</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:28:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362166533130-84</Id><Topic><Title>Who bought Apple at 700?</Title><Username>jimbohomegamedyall</Username><Timestamp>1362149159669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:45:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bought aapl at $478, will get out at $500... sometime... just not today... LOL... in INTC at $21.15 average... would have liked to have bought at $20, but I got in too soon...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1362166533130</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:35:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362166555649-85</Id><Topic><Title>CAN'T HOLD 21!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1361372693275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:04:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>uppppppppppppppppppp</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1362166555649</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:35:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362166624315-86</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chump, "Chump doesn't even do a guy like you justice. " AGREE !!!!! But if you insist on digging your hole... I'm happy to provide the shovel...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362166624315</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:37:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362166792755-87</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just clicked on Chumpanid61's post history and do indeed see what he says is there. Poor Getanid61, desperate and pathetic. What a putz.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1362166792755</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:39:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362167522162-88</Id><Topic><Title>= = Analyst Predicts Decline to 17.07 =SEE REPORT=</Title><Username>blackscott588</Username><Timestamp>1361404069367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:47:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great update. Thx.</Msg><Username>blackjohn168</Username><Timestamp>1362167522162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:52:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362167566036-89</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>blacknick671</Username><Timestamp>1361906263256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:17:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great update. Thx.</Msg><Username>blackjohn168</Username><Timestamp>1362167566036</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:52:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362167873531-90</Id><Topic><Title>voulme picking up!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1362156826154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 11:53:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can short at the BID price now and apply pressure downward. A company buy-back has to (generally) put their order at the BID also. Both parties know the rules and have a good idea what the other will do. BUYING just has more restrictions than shorting. It is not really a fair "fight".</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1362167873531</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:57:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362167976677-91</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (INTC)</Title><Username>frankbryant786</Username><Timestamp>1361483522525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:52:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting information. Thank u.</Msg><Username>nickgreen403</Username><Timestamp>1362167976677</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:59:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362168379519-92</Id><Topic><Title>Omnivision article bullish on Ultrabooks</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362161713078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:15:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sensors. To be specific video sensors which are coupled with an ISP (Image Signal Processor, resulting in front, and world facing cameras for today's mobile and handheld platforms.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1362168379519</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 15:06:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362168463184-93</Id><Topic><Title>Omnivision article bullish on Ultrabooks</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362161713078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:15:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>imaging sensors would be more accurate than 'video sensors'</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1362168463184</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 15:07:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362170295942-94</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Customer Review on Amazon: BATTERY LIFE / FAN / STORAGE / APPS These are the big negatives I've read about most. I haven't timed the battery life yet, but I've used it a bunch of times while unplugged and have not found myself running to a power outlet because the battery drained out. I've been working this thing pretty hard, and the battery has not seemed at all unreasonable, though like with anything, it could probably be better. Like I've said, I haven't been easy on the Surface, and I have yet to get the fans running. It does get warm, and you can feel a slight breeze of hot air coming from the side vents, but I still haven't triggered the fans. Not sure what I have to do to get them going, I'm hoping they aren't broken. I had 89.4 GB of free space right out of the box. I have yet to uninstall anything, or remove the recovery partition, but I'd estimate that once I do I'll have an extra 12 or so GB's of space, plus 64 from an SD card, and pretty much an infinite amount from USB drives. For my purposes I don't think I will ever need more than the original 90-ish GB. I don't even understand the app argument. Maybe for Windows Phones, or the Surface RT, but with the Pro you have access to literally the entire software world. I don't need a 99 cent photo editing app, I have Adobe Photoshop. I don't need some Angry Birds type of game, I have Skyrim and Black Ops. Not sure how apps even got into the argument against Surface.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1362170295942</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 15:38:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362170438259-95</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another Amazon review. Of the 27 reviews, 22 of them are 5-star. LOL 5.0 out of 5 stars The Future of things to come!, February 11, 2013 Tablet (Personal Computers) OK. So here it goes. All the critics out there that are dissing the new Surface Pro can complain all they want. Because all I need to say is I got one and they don't!! Any one that doesn't have one can comment all they want about how bad Microsoft is, and how they are playing catchup to Apple. But let me tell you this... There is nothing that this Surface Pro can't do better and faster than ANYTHING that Apple, Linux, Unix, Blackberry, Android has to offer. Just imagine... The most powerful practical portable device ever. Because it is a Windows 8 operating system, I set up an SIP softphone, an FTP server, two Oracle Virtual Box systems running a Windows 2008r2 and SUSE. Anyone that is complaining about space, I dumped an extra 64GB microSD chip to handle the extra load. I can print to every shared printer on my network, run my Quickbooks and Skype all while I watch the new "Lincoln" on JustinTV. Tell me... What tablet can do that? I took all my notes this morning by writing in OneNote. Not typing, but writing! I did most of my Google searches with voice commands, just because I could. Believe me, a new era has arrived in computing. The desktop and laptops are going to go away. Because if this is what the future has in store for us, why do we need a desktop any longer? Let me tell you that the Surface Pro has raised the bar on all future products. Anything less than this will be, well, less. I can see future products, by other companies like ACER, ASUS, SAMSUNG etc. making faster products with greater battery life, smaller screens, lighter weight, more memory, with 4g. But what they will have as the backbone is Windows 8. And folks, that is where good `ol Microsoft will reign again. Because let</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1362170438259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 15:40:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362171215975-96</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeeps! Just read this entire thread and it's a new low for GETANID61. The man has no shame. Typical internet troll that claims victory no mater what happens in the market. Best to put goobers like him on ignore.</Msg><Username>euro.spam</Username><Timestamp>1362171215975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 15:53:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362171680212-97</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It weighs half of a lb more and it is significantly heavier? Whoever wrote this must needs some serious muscle up training at a local gym?</Msg><Username>herbwll</Username><Timestamp>1362171680212</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 16:01:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362173896975-98</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bottom line is that Surface Pro is selling very well. Folks who actually buy it and use it, like it even if a few pundits don't.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1362173896975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 16:38:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362174044702-99</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the line just above the bottom line is that Surface RT was a dud!</Msg><Username>herbwll</Username><Timestamp>1362174044702</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 16:40:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362174090848-100</Id><Title>INTC Up, NVDA Up, AMD...</Title><Msg>...DOWN. AGAIN! Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!</Msg><Username>jimkellerisblinderthanhelen</Username><Timestamp>1362174090848</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 16:41:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>26</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362174205061-101</Id><Topic><Title>What price is Apple a good buy at?</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362165496656</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 14:18:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I posted about this on the Apple board. I believe today was the start of the capitulation period. The last level of support was broken today and I expect a brutal week for Apple next week. Capitulation should take it somewhere between 350 and 400. That has been my target price for quiet a while.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1362174205061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 16:43:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362175034262-102</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Up, NVDA Up, AMD...</Title><Username>jimkellerisblinderthanhelen</Username><Timestamp>1362174090848</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 16:41:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and, despite Ashraf pumping it in his latest Seeking Alpha article. I think he should stick to Intel.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1362175034262</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 16:57:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362175369823-103</Id><Topic><Title>The TRUTH about Intel Corporation...</Title><Username>wayne.garza</Username><Timestamp>1361975360186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good work!</Msg><Username>fishj15</Username><Timestamp>1362175369823</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:02:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362176281525-104</Id><Topic><Title>The TRUTH about Intel Corporation...</Title><Username>wayne.garza</Username><Timestamp>1361975360186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>sanfordcharles820</Username><Timestamp>1362176281525</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:18:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362176693579-105</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/mbview/threadview/;_ylt=ArBLRXGvLl993.n3PX3nmz3eAohG;_ylu=X3oDMTB1cDZkbG52BHBvcwM4BHNlYwNNZWRpYU1zZ0JvYXJkc1hIUlVsdA--;_ylg=X3oDMTBvaWppbXYzBGxhbmcDZW4tVVMEdGVzdANUZXN0X0FGQw--;_ylv=3?&amp;bn=70e9dbe2-4ba3-33f2-925a-c34d3ae945c5&amp;tid=1345914310000-bd2bf9bb-16c0-37dc-a616-9595301f6ddf</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1362176693579</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:24:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362176966784-106</Id><Title>Future PCs threat to Apple? Yes, says Citibank analyst</Title><Msg>New hybrid laptop-tablet devices based on Intel's fast but power efficient Haswell chip may threaten Apple's tablet dominance, says a Citibank analyst Apple's "limited innovation" in tablets this year will make it vulnerable to newfangled PCs -- so says a Citibank analyst. Yes, you heard that right, PCs. While financial analysts write lots of research notes about Apple every week, this one from Citibank analyst Glen Yeung -- sent out early in the week -- got my attention. We believe Apple will launch an iPad Mini Retina and a thinner/lighter iPad5 (both likely sporting newer processors) in 3Q13...iPad innovation of this nature is insufficient to reverse share loss. Whereas we see limited innovation in tablets in 2H13, we see growing innovation in PCs. The growing presence of touch-based, ultrathin, all-day notebooks at improving price points (e.g., Intel requires all Haswell-based Ultrabooks to have touch and envisions price-points as low as $599) could create competition for 10" tablets not fully anticipated by the market. So, after getting their keisters kicked by the iPad for the last three years, PC makers may finally get some payback. Citibank, like other analyst groups, is pegging a lot of this prognosticated PC success on new designs based on Intel's upcoming Haswell processor and Intel's stipulation that Haswell-based ultrabooks must have touch screens. In other words, expect more designs like Microsoft's Surface Pro and Samsung's ATIV Smart PC Pro, but thinner and lighter with better battery life (though I suspect battery life won't approach that of the iPad). And, lest we forget, Apple doesn't put touch screens on its MacBooks. That, of course, is reserved for iOS devices, which have limited use as full-productivity devices (i.e., I'm writing this on my laptop, not my iPad). So, will PC makers be more successful at combining a laptop with a tablet, obviating the need for two devices? Yes. From Brooke Crothers at CNET</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362176966784</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:29:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362177041115-107</Id><Title>Marsazian kicks GETANID61's butt, part 437</Title><Msg>LOL! Marsavian laughs at Getanid61's taunts, his denials and posts the link to shove it down his throat. Want me to post Acer, HP, Samsung, etc. dissing RT you feable little man? ROFL@ YOU. Marsavian kicks Getanid61 in the TOOTH, again. LMFAO!</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362177041115</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:30:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362177084011-108</Id><Topic><Title>Future PCs threat to Apple? Yes, says Citibank analyst</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362176966784</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:29:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[Um, like I said - we've reached the tipping point...] Whereas we see limited innovation in tablets in 2H13, we see growing innovation in PCs. The growing presence of touch-based, ultrathin, all-day notebooks at improving price points (e.g., Intel requires all Haswell-based Ultrabooks to have touch and envisions price-points as low as $599) could create competition for 10" tablets not fully anticipated by the market. So, after getting their keisters kicked by the iPad for the last three years, PC makers may finally get some payback.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362177084011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:31:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362177546691-109</Id><Topic><Title>On the hunt for the Surface Pro’s missing battery life</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362157405769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 12:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Comments from the review ... 'Surface RT’s copy performance is terrible. Throughput is limited to 12.5MB/sec, less than half of Clover Trail’s. RT complements its poor performance with high power draw; its MB/s throughput-to-power consumption ratio is 1.39 compared to the Samsung’s 3.8. Surface Pro is twice as fast as the Ativ, thanks to USB 3.0, but that speed comes at a cost — file copying draws 18W of power, nearly 2.5x as much as Clover Trail. Surface Pro’s throughput-to-watt ratio is correspondingly lower, at 3.08. If you’ve been considering a Surface RT but don’t want to re-encode a library of MKV files, we’ve got good news for you. There’s an app available from the Windows Store (PressPlay) that converts MKV files into a format that the tablet can play. The bad news? Files have to be converted every time you view them, there’s no option to save in the converted format, and the playback stutters. Files that played flawlessly via Media Player Classic on Surface Pro and the Samsung Ativ stuttered when opened using PressPlay. We decided to test the file conversion and power consumption using a 8.75GB MKV file as a baseline. The video output couldn’t play back smoothly on any platform, but benchmarks available across all three platforms are few and far between. Surface RT performs remarkably poorly here. It draws more power than Clover Trail, and takes more than twice as long to perform the same task. Real compatibility with MKV files remains a pipe dream for RT users, though the appearance of PressPlay gives us hope that a real solution will present itself.'</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1362177546691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:39:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362177706137-110</Id><Topic><Title>The TRUTH about Intel Corporation...</Title><Username>wayne.garza</Username><Timestamp>1361975360186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:29:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report</Msg><Username>cartermarc24</Username><Timestamp>1362177706137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:41:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362177861483-111</Id><Title>Looks like its going to 24 finally</Title><Msg>However after that last temporary dip who knows where this is going over 21 same as CSCO</Msg><Username>mcannaly</Username><Timestamp>1362177861483</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:44:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362178358244-112</Id><Title>Apple Hits 57 Week Low</Title><Msg>This gives rise to a couple of thoughts: 1.) How is it that Wall Street sees no link between Apple and ARM? Some day they will wake up and discover that ARM's P/E ratio has no visible means of support. 2.) Steve Jobs died 68 weeks ago. It seems that there is little doubt that he is sorely missed and that Tim Cook is no Steve Jobs and apparently neither is anyone else at Apple. 3.) Again, I think that the Acronix and Altera deals must have suspended whatever fabrication plans Apple had in process. 4.) Apple needs touchscreens. 5.) Apple needs the iWatch or something that big in potential. And they need it now. 6.) If they squander that huge hunk of cash and don't get anything game-breaking from it (like an inferior technology fab of their own or run by TSMC), it could be a very, very long time before they climb back into the race. One more stumble and Samsung is going to be eating their lunch (and dinner). 7.) Time Cook thought he could just make small, incremental improvements and still grow the stock price. Wow, was he wrong. The Apple situation gets more interesting every day. We know where Intel is going. The question is whether Apple wants to come along...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362178358244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:52:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362178989250-113</Id><Topic><Title>Marsazian kicks GETANID61's butt, part 437</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362177041115</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:30:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Marsavian, you've got a fan club...:) "Marsavian laughs at Getanid61's taunts," sometimes... other times gets too caught up in them... "posts the link to shove it down his throat. " just a link to an article... still NOT my words... "Want me to post Acer, HP, Samsung, etc. dissing RT" Yes... hope you actually follow thru on something...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362178989250</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 18:03:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362179767248-114</Id><Title>Why is INTC moving up after hours</Title><Msg>not typical for this stock to mover so much</Msg><Username>racebanner2</Username><Timestamp>1362179767248</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 18:16:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362180323508-115</Id><Topic><Title>Marsazian kicks GETANID61's butt, part 437</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362177041115</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:30:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>getanid61 was burnt with his NVDA shares badly and still can't get it. just ignore the potz.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1362180323508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 18:25:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362180443790-116</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Hits 57 Week Low</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362178358244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:52:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks like a bad weekend for getanid61 in the works. oh well, expect irational 'revenge' getanid61's posts next week.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1362180443790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 18:27:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362181077910-117</Id><Topic><Title>Marsazian kicks GETANID61's butt, part 437</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362177041115</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:30:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep and by his own words he NEVER pumped ARMH's stock price and didn't even own it......yet when it was over 40 suddenly he claimed to be along for the whole ride. Yeah right! He's taken over the village idiot of this board and THAT is a hard trophy to attain. lol</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1362181077910</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 18:37:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362181880908-118</Id><Title>Het Hitakid61.......Surface Pro with HASWELL</Title><Msg>DAGGER!</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362181880908</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 18:51:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362181937198-119</Id><Title>Surface Pro with Haswell spells R.I.P. for GETANID61 AKA HIT-A-KID61</Title><Msg>Curtain closes.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362181937198</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 18:52:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362182832524-120</Id><Title>Acer CEO regarding ARM Windows RT</Title><Msg>Acer CEO tells MS to 'think twice' about Surface tablets updated 06:59 am EDT, Tue August 7, 2012</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362182832524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 19:07:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362182881309-121</Id><Title>HP Ditches ARM Windows RT</Title><Msg>.HP ditches Windows RT tablet plans, Microsoft Surface to blame By Dan Graziano | BGR News – Fri, Jun 29, 2012..</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362182881309</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 19:08:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362183080041-122</Id><Title>Windows RT (ARM Holdings Product) circling the drain</Title><Msg>February 05, 2013 Windows RT is circling the drain It's hard to be optimistic about the platform's future when you look at the Windows RT tablets on offer and on the immediate horizon</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1362183080041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 19:11:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362185515000-123</Id><Title>Haswell Mainboards are ready</Title><Msg>Mainboards for Intel Core i “Haswell” Are Ready: Asrock Set to Demo Intel 8-Series Platforms Next Week. Asrock to Show Off LGA1150 Mainboards for Intel “Haswell” Processors at CeBIT Trade-Show [03/01/2013 03:11 PM] by Anton Shilov Intel Corp. plans to formally launch its next-generation Core i-series “Haswell” central processing units only in June, but mainboard makers seem to be ready for the new chip well ahead of the official launch. Asrock, one of the world’s largest makers of motherboards, plans to demonstrate its platforms with LGA1150 sockets already next week at CeBIT trade-show. At the world’s largest IT exhibition, Asrock intends to show off mainboards powered by Intel’s upcoming 8-series chipset, such as Z87 Extreme6, Z87 Pro4-M, H87 Pro4 and B85M. Unfortunately, due to restrictions by the chip designer, the mainboards will only be present statically and will not demonstrate work of code-named Haswell microprocessors. Nonetheless, given that the design of actual motherboards is ready, Asrock may start sales of the platforms as soon as it is allowed to. Based on the lineup of LGA1150 mainboards that Asrock intends to show at CeBIT, it is clear that the company wants to target performance-enthusiasts, multimedia-interested users as well as business customers with its platforms for Intel Core i-series 4000-family “Haswell” microprocessors. Other makers of mainboards will likely follow Asrock and demonstrate their Intel 8-series chipsets-based motherboards with LGA1150 sockets at the upcoming trade-show next week.</Msg><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1362185515000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 19:51:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362185685499-124</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Hits 57 Week Low</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362178358244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:52:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple without Steve Jobs is like the Doors without Jim Morrison. Tim Cook is actually the right man for the job for what the company is going to be, a large consumer electronics label. They are beyond leading market innovation, they don't have the company culture to drive the next big idea. All they really have to do is stay current with technology. That will keep their client base happy. The money will help them stay afloat and help with R &amp; D and who knows, maybe something cool can come out of them over the next five years. As for ARMH they got a head start in a foot race that they will eventually lose. They have established themselves in phones to the extent that they will never be removed from them entirely. By now it's looking clear that what they want to do is offer a certain SoC for as long as they can to get maximum ROI. They also see a big future in embedded applications. Low dollar/high volume business will keep them happy for a very long time. Like Apple ARMH will have current but not bleeding edge technology. They can't scale up faster than Intel can scale down. Yet, yet, yet, I don't know if that's such a big deal. Look at what phones are "hot" right now. Larger screens like the Note II. It seems like the market is less concerned about pure performance than they are usability. This may help them stretch out their 40nm, 32nm, and 28nm if consumers rate other factors than CPU performance higher. This was the case with the iPad. The screen and GPU were more important than the actual CPU. There was a time that cell phones were nearly exclusively in cars. Then they became mobile, and that was chic. Then they got smaller and people didn't care as much. They stayed that way for many years, just something you traded in every two years with a new contract for something a little nicer. That will be the future of smartphones. Modest improvements over time, innovation waning.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1362185685499</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 19:54:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362188392341-125</Id><Topic><Title>Why is INTC moving up after hours</Title><Username>racebanner2</Username><Timestamp>1362179767248</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 18:16:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't that nice!!! I could get use to it.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1362188392341</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 20:39:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362188507269-126</Id><Topic><Title>Why is INTC moving up after hours</Title><Username>racebanner2</Username><Timestamp>1362179767248</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 18:16:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After hours buyback?</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362188507269</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 20:41:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362188751528-127</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell Mainboards are ready</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1362185515000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 19:51:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haswell is the only CPU that will play in the new sockets. Haswell has the onchip voltage regulator unlike any previous Intel CPU. Did they pop the CPU before showing the board or did they show it with Haswell installed? It will be too bad that PaulO can't be at the intro. Maybe they will time it for the shareholder meeting and his retierment. It is very close.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1362188751528</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 20:45:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362189557696-128</Id><Topic><Title>10 inch tablets are fading fast. CNET says that Ipad mini will outsell Ipad's</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362100646761</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 20:17:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Their problem? This is the least compelling Microsoft commercial since... I don't know.. their previous one? At least it's understandable. People see it and think "Oh, Microsoft now makes an iPad. I can tell because they did a bad copy of an Apple commercial." Not like some of the Microsoft TV ads from five and ten years ago where even the tech savvy went "huh?"</Msg><Username>watergatefive</Username><Timestamp>1362189557696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 20:59:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362191358134-129</Id><Title>Intel's Dividend?</Title><Msg>Is it sustainable? Can it grow to 2 dollars? Thoughts. Might buy some for my grandkids.</Msg><Username>stevierayvaughn4life</Username><Timestamp>1362191358134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 21:29:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362194679616-130</Id><Topic><Title>10 inch tablets are fading fast. CNET says that Ipad mini will outsell Ipad's</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362100646761</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 20:17:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not if you edit iMovie like my wife.</Msg><Username>optermoron</Username><Timestamp>1362194679616</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 22:24:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362194868522-131</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Hits 57 Week Low</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362178358244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:52:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple without Steve Jobs is like the Doors without Jim Morrison. Woh!!! Mr. Mojo rising.....</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1362194868522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 22:27:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362195778852-132</Id><Topic><Title>10 inch tablets are fading fast. CNET says that Ipad mini will outsell Ipad's</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1362100646761</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 20:17:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually one of the reasons that I am so negative on Apple. You can really feel the margin compression over at Apple. Interesting is that larger tablets don't seem to be the trend. It is either supersized cell phones or shrunken tablets that are the rage right now. Microsoft is rumored to be working on a smaller tablet and it seems that folks want larger screens then the iphone is delivering.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1362195778852</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 22:42:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362195971151-133</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Dividend?</Title><Username>stevierayvaughn4life</Username><Timestamp>1362191358134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 21:29:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am expecting 10% rise per annum. That is a double in 8 years. So yes and it is sustainable based on the payout ratio. I am hoping that it gets pretty large by the time I retire.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1362195971151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 22:46:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362196119582-134</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell Mainboards are ready</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1362185515000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 19:51:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are already sampling Haswell out. No one is allowed to say anything about the spec's but this one is going to rock the graphics world. :-)</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1362196119582</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 22:48:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362197449305-135</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Hits 57 Week Low</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362178358244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 17:52:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This may help them stretch out their 40nm, 32nm, and 28nm if consumers rate other factors than CPU performance higher. This was the case with the iPad. The screen and GPU were more important than the actual CPU." [Yet the new iPad ran into problems because it was fat and over-heated. It was said that Jobs would never have allowed the iPad to have become fatter. So, already Apple's fabrication problems are serious and it's only going to get worse. Altera moving to Intel is a solid indication that companies are looking at and wanting Intel's advanced fabrication technology. In a year, we'll look back and say this was the tipping point. It's happening now...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362197449305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 23:10:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362197788427-136</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell Mainboards are ready</Title><Username>lucifer_numbnuts</Username><Timestamp>1362185515000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 19:51:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel Corp. plans to formally launch its next-generation Core i-series “Haswell” central processing units only in June, but mainboard makers seem to be ready for the new chip well ahead of the official launch. Asrock, one of the world’s largest makers of motherboards, plans to demonstrate its platforms with LGA1150 sockets already next week at CeBIT trade-show." [Yep, CeBIT starts next Tuesday and it's a very nice opportunity to build on the great MWC 2013 and Altera/Acronix news, especially Haswell. Haswell is a mere 3 months out and it's time to get excited. Good news is coming in waves...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1362197788427</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 23:16:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>