<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363666025303-1</Id><Title>Is Intel Going Back Into The Memory Business?</Title><Msg>"Now my speculation is: Intel has developed a 14nm NAND cell that would shrink the 128Gb chip size to 100 square millimeters. A 450mm fab would produce over twice the square inches of silicon that a 300mm facility would. Thus a 1.2 million wafer 450mm plant would produce about 1.4 billion 128Gb 14nm NAND chips. That would be one $10 billion factory with the output of four $5 billion 300mm plants. Can Intel make money in the NAND business? Let's just figure a $7000 cost for those 450mm wafers. The 128Gb chips would have to sell for about $14 to Intel itself or the world at large in order to deliver a SSD at $1 per GB. Those big wafers could produce about 1200 100 sq mm chips. At $14 each, the wafer is worth about $16,800 against a $7000 cost is 58% gross margin. When the depreciation is out of that factory, the gross margins would reach into the high 60% range. There are a lot of numbers to be digested here, but the bottom line is that Intel can make a lot of money on the NAND memory that they are going to need for those SSDs in Ultrabooks. And, no small thing, Intel would be first to 450mm wafer production. Just another reason to own Intel." [I found Russ Fischer's speculation on the memory business very interesting - primarily because of the discussion relating to 450mm wafers. This is yet another area in which Intel's leadership will allow them economics that no one else in the business will have for a long time...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363666025303</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:07:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363666568853-2</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Cuts Manufacturing Costs With Big Data</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363665116820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 23:51:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A lot of what we're doing is pulling log files out of manufacturing and test machines," said Kasabian. "Across our entire factory network, we're talking about 5 terabytes an hour. So it's very big volume." By capturing and analyzing this information, Intel can determine when a specific step in one of its manufacturing processes starts to deviate from normal tolerances.... SPC Statistical process control (SPC) is a method of quality control which uses statistical methods. SPC is applied in order to monitor and control a process. Monitoring and controlling the process ensures that it operates at its full potential. At its full potential, the process can make as much conforming product as possible with a minimum (if not an elimination) of waste (rework or trash). SPC can be applied to any process where the "conforming product" (product meeting specifications) output can be measured. Key tools used in SPC include control charts; a focus on continuous improvement; and the design of experiments. An example of a process where SPC is applied is manufacturing lines.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363666568853</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363668235048-3</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel Going Back Into The Memory Business?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363666025303</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:07:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Now my speculation is: Intel has developed a 14nm NAND cell that would shrink the 128Gb chip size to 100 square millimeters" Intel NAND business focuses on Enterprise SSD - specifically SLC because of reliability . I think the author is off track. Intel 's plate is more than full and they should fully concentrtate on logic and not get sidetracked by NAND</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363668235048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:43:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363668558362-4</Id><Title>Example of Dual Boot tablet PC</Title><Msg>ignDOTcom/articles/2013/03/08/asus-dual-booting-transformer-aio-launching-q2-for-1299</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363668558362</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:49:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363668599478-5</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Cuts Manufacturing Costs With Big Data</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363665116820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 23:51:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPC is nothing really new - but Intel refined it and enhanced it. Six Sigma is a set of tools and strategies for process improvement originally developed by Motorola in 1985.[1][2] Six Sigma became well known after Jack Welch made it a central focus of his business strategy at General Electric in 1995,[3] and today it is used in different sectors of industry.[4] Six Sigma seeks to improve the quality of process outputs by identifying and removing the causes of defects (errors) and minimizing variability in manufacturing and business processes.[5] It uses a set of quality management methods, including statistical methods, and creates a special infrastructure of people within the organization ("Champions", "Black Belts", "Green Belts", "Orange Belts", etc.) who are experts in these very complex methods.[5] Each Six Sigma project carried out within an organization follows a defined sequence of steps and has quantified financial targets (cost reduction and/or profit increase).[5]</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363668599478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:49:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363669014289-6</Id><Title>Merrifield coming this year</Title><Msg>It seems sometimes 'Bay Trail' term is used synonymously for Merrifield...but anyways, 22nm for phones definitely coming this year. See the following you tube videos: v=ogneimca9ko (Intel CES presentation) v=O520s1e7Czw</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363669014289</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:56:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363669047050-7</Id><Title>Still nothing in the stock price for...</Title><Msg>Nothing in the stock price for Intel's significant lead in getting to 450mm wafers. Nothing in the stock price for the new smartphone just announced from Asus. Nothing in the stock price for an Apple deal that could eventually result in Intel doing all of Apple's fabrication. Nothing in the stock price for Intel's highly profitable, cash cow deal with Altera, and the deal with Acronix. Nothing in the stock price for Haswell which will be arriving sooner than expected. Nothing in the stock price for Intel 14nm FinFET arriving at the end of the year. Nothing in the stock price for Clover Trail or Bay Trail. Nothing in the stock price for the new deal with ZTE. Nothing in the stock price for the new smartphones by Lenovo and Xolo. Nothing in the stock price for the FonePad by Asus. Nothing in the stock price for the success of the Surface Pro. Nothing in the stock price for the Cisco deal. Nothing in the stock price for ARM's delays at 20nm. Nothing in the stock price for ARM not having FinFET for years and years and years. Nothing in the stock price for Intel's web TV project. Nothing in the stock price for a potential iWatch deal. Nothing in the stock price for more big foundry deals. We know one big one is in the works. Nothing in the stock price for dual booting of both Windows 8 and Android. Nothing in the stock price for Intel's partnership with Samsung on Tizen.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363669047050</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363670020264-8</Id><Title>News media gets it wrong</Title><Msg>These news media just seem to repeat one another without any kind of analysis. Here's an example: "It (Intel's TV service) will compete with heavyweights like Apple Inc, Amazon Inc and Google Inc " Wait a second here...Does Apple, Amazon or Google offer live TV streaming? NO. Intel will be the FIRST company to offer Live streaming TV. Let's get that straight. Intel will not be competing with these companies. Intel is offering an alternative to the cable operators who are refusing to work with Apple, Amazon and Google. Intel intends to work with these companies by providing the Live TV service to them in exchange for using Intel hardware.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363670020264</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 01:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363672897739-9</Id><Topic><Title>Merrifield coming this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363669014289</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:56:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Merrifield is 22nm phone based SoC based on "Silvermont" CPU core. Related to, but not quite, Bay Trail. I'd guess that Merrifield is just cut-down Bay Trail :)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363672897739</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 02:01:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363675189108-10</Id><Title>Samsung is building a smart watch</Title><Msg>The race is on.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363675189108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 02:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363675426245-11</Id><Topic><Title>Still nothing in the stock price for...</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363669047050</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also, Nothing in the stock price for Samsung using Intel Atom for detachable ultrabook/tablet combo even though Samsung builds its own processors. The detachable tablet part look just like the noteably successful Galaxy Tab.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363675426245</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 02:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363675798079-12</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Wallis:</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363643307942</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 17:48:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's funny how the market raises HP's stock price by over $6 in one month right after the company gives a so so estimate beat. Yet many still refuse to believe that Intel stock could have a huge rally after its earnings announcement. Two other catalysts coming up, aside from the huge advancements in mobile chips for smartphones, are the new CEO announcement and the May investor meeting. I've actually realized some gains finally from HP stock and have reduced my holding by about 2/3. So I'm in the market to possibly add more INTC positions tomorrow if stock remains weak.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363675798079</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 02:49:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363678658634-13</Id><Title>ARMH CEO Warren East Retiring</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/news/arm-holdings-plc-announces-ceo-073300355.html</Msg><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1363678658634</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 03:37:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363678728971-14</Id><Topic><Title>ARMH CEO Warren East Retiring</Title><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1363678658634</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 03:37:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Get while the gettin's good"?</Msg><Username>zags97</Username><Timestamp>1363678728971</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 03:38:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363681819563-15</Id><Topic><Title>Importan info about INTC future!!!</Title><Username>seanlacroix518</Username><Timestamp>1363042083166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 18:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great one</Msg><Username>andremcdonall</Username><Timestamp>1363681819563</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:30:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363681825968-16</Id><Title>ROFL @ GETANID61</Title><Msg>Your boy East SHOUT his mouth off and then........Intel revealed its road map and he slithers away like the snake that he is. Very telling!</Msg><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363681825968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363682355859-17</Id><Title>Warren East retiring? At only 51 years of age?</Title><Msg>What's that about? Pressure from Intel getting too much for the rookie? If there was a great future and excitement for ARM, a 51 year old would not quit.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363682355859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:39:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363682526543-18</Id><Topic><Title>Warren East retiring? At only 51 years of age?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363682355859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they were going to set the world on fire with Servers, he would ABSOLUTELY not quit at 51. Windows RT is VERY telling. Wow, this is a MASSSIVE shot in GETNID61's gut. Talk about having your teeth kicked in. East shot his mouth off and now quits at 51? Hilarious! Like LackeyGarret said on the ARM board: Is ARMH the closest thing to a legalized Ponzi scheme that there is??????</Msg><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363682526543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363685246754-19</Id><Topic><Title>Warren East retiring? At only 51 years of age?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363682355859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why not? I am 44 and I would retire if I could afford it</Msg><Username>andresfandom</Username><Timestamp>1363685246754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 05:27:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363687339625-20</Id><Title>How does the MS Surface RT compare to other tablets.</Title><Msg>Best buy currently has the Surface RT with 64GB SSD with keyboard for 699. It has an ARM based processor. They also have the ASUS tablet for 499. The Samsung tablet for 649. The Lenovo tablet for 549. The HP Envy tablet with much better keyboard for 649. The Acer tablet for 529. All of which have 64 GB SSD, full Windows 8 OS compatible with all MS software, and most importantly use an Intel Atom processor. Now which would consumers buy? Certainly not the Surface RT with ARM processor. It would be incredibly stupid for anyone to but the Microsofts Surface RT tablet.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363687339625</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 06:02:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363688982896-21</Id><Topic><Title>ROFL @ GETANID61</Title><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363681825968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:30:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL!</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363688982896</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 06:29:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363691349773-22</Id><Topic><Title>ROFL @ GETANID61</Title><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363681825968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:30:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That being said...wouldn't you retire in his place? ARM can be driven on autopilot given its business model.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363691349773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363691694099-23</Id><Topic><Title>Will $20 hold tomorrow after the Europe news?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1363575087266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 22:51:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are going to explain to Eric, you are going to have to use MANY, SMALL words. He thought you were talking about his mom.</Msg><Username>getanad61</Username><Timestamp>1363691694099</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:14:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363691903118-24</Id><Topic><Title>ROFL @ GETANID61</Title><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363681825968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:30:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM, after Apple made them successful, attracted agressive subordinates. East is being evicted by all the new sharks they hired.</Msg><Username>getanad61</Username><Timestamp>1363691903118</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 07:18:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363694653107-25</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Cuts Manufacturing Costs With Big Data</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363665116820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 23:51:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPC was first used on a sustaining basis by Western Electric in the late 1920's and 1930's, led by Dr. Walter Shewart. When Motorola started having quality problems in the 80's, some smart people decided to research and see how phone people made high quality phones back in the "old days", and low and behold they found the methods used at Western Electric (the people who make the phones and equipment for the ATT system - a government granted monopoly, by the way) were pretty smart about it. SPC has great application at Intel - high volume production that requires extraordinary tight tolerances - exactly what SPC is best at. The danger with SPC is getting people to change processes once they get processes "in control" - use of SPC can reinforce a natural resistance to change. This is a problem with all businesses to one degree or another, but in spades with tech - "controlled" production processes in the context of an industry where change is frequent.</Msg><Username>clcellve</Username><Timestamp>1363694653107</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:04:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363696866547-26</Id><Title>seriously, will this thing ever see $25 this year?</Title><Msg>All the hype on tablets, mobile, etc., is ultimately only worth a few percent of bottom line. The mobile mkts are commodotized and don't really represent a large revenue stream..maybe $6 Billion total to the chip makers. Tablets may be better, but probably low margin. This is, at best, offsetting the very real implosion of PC's. I have to travel this week and dread lugging my dell inspiron around (what a pos that company and its products are...almost a MSFT in shoddiness) . So we're taking 5 steps forward and 4 back..or is it the other way around? And, fact is, that's been the Intel story for the past decade. Yes, they are the best, but always margins are shrinking. I just don't see any explosive catalyst here, and always the present danger from a Samsung, or a QCOM, or ? Give me $25 and I'm outa here.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363696866547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363697012724-27</Id><Topic><Title>seriously, will this thing ever see $25 this year?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363696866547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy a slimmer Ultrabook and stop whining.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363697012724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:43:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363697015884-28</Id><Topic><Title>Still nothing in the stock price for...</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363669047050</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like I said..show me the money. And, btw, there's nothing in the stock price for all of your hot air. Sorry, you do good work, but I am having a bad INTC day...don't like the outlook. No explosive catalyst..just a bunch of bread crumbs.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363697015884</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:43:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363697079527-29</Id><Topic><Title>seriously, will this thing ever see $25 this year?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363696866547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Might I suggest one of the newly released Lenovo T431s? Or perhaps an ASUS Taichi? Very slim &amp; portable.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363697079527</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:44:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363697134055-30</Id><Topic><Title>seriously, will this thing ever see $25 this year?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363696866547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You do good work, ashraf, but do you see any real catalysts for the INTC pps? It just drones on...</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363697134055</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:45:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363697561280-31</Id><Title>Ashraf..saw your last piece, and</Title><Msg>It really reflected my own state of mind about INTC...it was rather ho hum. In fact, when your queried the board, I said that I didn't see a divvy increase with the current biz climate. I still think that's still the case, and it is really a bad thing. One of the major things that attracted me into INTC was the divvy rate of growth, d (div) /dt is about 10+% (div). If that halts, then this is "topped out" to use the term you applied to some INTC execs. And, frankly, TV is the stinking fish in the house. So, ho hum and no divvy increase and you have to start to wonder why? I think it's just commoditization of their products and the long term fight to try to maintain the top-line with decent margins. To me this is where all the risk is, and I just don't see any real mo here.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363697561280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:52:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363697604811-32</Id><Topic><Title>seriously, will this thing ever see $25 this year?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363696866547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure... 1. DCG growth should come in at ~10-15% this year. Very high operating margin here, which drives some very nice earnings leverage. 2. PC refresh cycle "reset" has pretty much hit, so I expect that after the bottom we saw put in during Q3 and Q4 2012, the PC segment should resume its normal, low single digit growth. 3. Opportunity in smartphones is quite large, especially as Intel provides both modem/baseband silicon and has begun offering competitive apps processors. Even if Intel grabs ~20% market share, that's several hundred million units of both apps processor + modem, so think ~$20-$30+ per phone. Across ~200M+ phones, this is not chump change. 4. Opportunity in tablets is even larger. Intel will own the windows 8 tablets, and it will also be a major player in the Android space. Lots of unit volume here to drive growth, especially as I do not believe that tablets are replacing PCs - this is all upside. 5. Longer term, Intel Custom Foundry should add nicely to the top and bottom lines. Lots of growth drivers ahead, but investors here need to be patient.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363697604811</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:53:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363697659460-33</Id><Topic><Title>seriously, will this thing ever see $25 this year?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363696866547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pardon my ignoramus, but what is DCG?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363697659460</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:54:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363698081766-34</Id><Title>I. LOVE. MY. COMPANY....but I think I'll bolt at 51</Title><Msg>I'll turn up somewhere else in a few years. LOL!</Msg><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363698081766</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:01:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363698107777-35</Id><Topic><Title>ROFL @ GETANID61</Title><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363681825968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:30:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WEAK !</Msg><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363698107777</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:01:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363698180362-36</Id><Topic><Title>seriously, will this thing ever see $25 this year?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363696866547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Data center group</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363698180362</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:03:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363698230849-37</Id><Topic><Title>seriously, will this thing ever see $25 this year?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363696866547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ALERT: Flumoxed, the guy that knows "big things coming from Intel but he's 'very important and can't tell us simpleton"..........is out of Tampons AGAIN this morning. He must buy them one at a time.</Msg><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363698230849</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:03:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363698586023-38</Id><Topic><Title>seriously, will this thing ever see $25 this year?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363696866547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're starting to remind me of backbay. Yes, you should move on. The whining, moaning and complaining is getting old...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363698586023</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:09:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363698863917-39</Id><Topic><Title>I. LOVE. MY. COMPANY....but I think I'll bolt at 51</Title><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363698081766</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:01:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't wait for the people to start speculating on whether he will end up at Intel or not.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363698863917</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:14:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363699099177-40</Id><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Msg>ARM will start the day down 92 cents which is 2.2 percent but it was down 3.3 on the London exchange. The news of East's retirement without any prior notice or speculation looks like a PR disaster. The fact that they don't have a replacement candidate ready and have to elevate Segars the president into the position indicates that this was not a planned event. It will be interesting to get some more color on the retirement. If the pattern of the previous days holds, then we will see further declines during the day. Another 50 cents would break the $40 barrier and then it becomes a much more slippery slope. All in all, it looks like a pretty ham-handed handling of a CEO change. It looks like something or somebody or a group of somebodies blew up. At this point we can only speculate as to why. Stay tuned for today's exciting action...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363699099177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:18:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363699349850-41</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363699099177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:18:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM can be run on autopilot because all they do is license an instruction set and maybe license a few cores. Its partners do all the heavy lifting. ARMH is a $15 stock.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363699349850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:22:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363699536174-42</Id><Title>Warren East is NOT a Rubber Stamp</Title><Msg>lolololol</Msg><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363699536174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:25:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363699625496-43</Id><Topic><Title>Will $20 hold tomorrow after the Europe news?</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1363575087266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 22:51:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your bearish tone is so misguided.</Msg><Username>hankg1030</Username><Timestamp>1363699625496</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:27:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363699680298-44</Id><Topic><Title>Steady as she goes</Title><Username>hankg1030</Username><Timestamp>1362577269690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:41:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Such as it is</Msg><Username>hankg1030</Username><Timestamp>1363699680298</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363699738725-45</Id><Title>Old Warren sees the DISASTER coming with TSMC</Title><Msg>.......and his pride won't let him stick around to fail miserably.</Msg><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363699738725</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:28:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363700500734-46</Id><Topic><Title>Warren East is NOT a Rubber Stamp</Title><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363699536174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:25:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will their next ceo talk as much trash ?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1363700500734</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363700673193-47</Id><Topic><Title>Warren East retiring? At only 51 years of age?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363682355859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>paul o is not a lot older and has not seen a runup in intc, paul o is quitting</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1363700673193</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:44:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363700725276-48</Id><Topic><Title>Warren East retiring? At only 51 years of age?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363682355859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>same can be said about Paul here</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1363700725276</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:45:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363700732879-49</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>linkosarah</Username><Timestamp>1362149300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:48:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just read your article. Nothing else.</Msg><Username>messeheftlou</Username><Timestamp>1363700732879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363700812610-50</Id><Topic><Title>Still nothing in the stock price for...</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363669047050</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I watch 12 stocks on my ticker, intc 1st to go red today.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1363700812610</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:46:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363701375808-51</Id><Topic><Title>Warren East retiring? At only 51 years of age?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363682355859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul is 62 and was with Intel for 40 years.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363701375808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:56:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363701522937-52</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>linkosarah</Username><Timestamp>1362149300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:48:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████LOADS A KEY STROKE LOGGER!!! ████████████████████████████████████████████████████████ ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>thatsmrmorontoyou</Username><Timestamp>1363701522937</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:58:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363701572734-53</Id><Title>Samsung Smart Watch: Apple Needs to Bust a Move Now!</Title><Msg>Samsung continues to box Apple's ears and is now looking for the opportunity to send Apple to the mat. Um, what exactly is Tim Cook waiting on? Retirement? Maybe he can get a nice place next to Warren East. And why is Apple up today? Nothing like Wall Street stupid...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363701572734</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:59:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363701753422-54</Id><Topic><Title>Still nothing in the stock price for...</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363669047050</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You obviously don't follow ARM. I see you like to stay well-informed...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363701753422</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:02:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363701797099-55</Id><Title>Stock doubles, CEO Bolts</Title><Msg>Typical EUROTRASH.</Msg><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363701797099</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:03:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363701871581-56</Id><Topic><Title>Still nothing in the stock price for...</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363669047050</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC 27, ARMH 27, a year ago or so, which do you follow/cheer? LOL. all the wrong info is what you spew</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1363701871581</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:04:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363701967606-57</Id><Topic><Title>Warren East retiring? At only 51 years of age?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363682355859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so he has seen the last 13 years take intc from 20 to 20. If intel was on the verge of greatness(phone chips) would he leave? obvious answer.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1363701967606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:06:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363702049144-58</Id><Topic><Title>Still nothing in the stock price for...</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363669047050</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 00:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was going to ask the same question. The Intel trading patterns have changed. There seems to be a sell off at opening and then accumulation during the day. Rope-a-dope buyers up to 3:50pm when stock buyback engine has to shut down and then some selling. What has been interesting is the after hours up trend the last couple weeks.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363702049144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363702238042-59</Id><Topic><Title>Warren East retiring? At only 51 years of age?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363682355859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, noooooooooooooooo.... You're one of those exhausted ARM investors. Now, that's funny...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363702238042</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:10:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363702501298-60</Id><Title>End of the ARM Era</Title><Msg>Hope you enjoyed it. It's over. Move along now, nothing here to see. Well, except for the ascendance of Intel into ARM's mobility position...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363702501298</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:15:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363702862282-61</Id><Title>East trashed Intel and pumped ARM so he could get rich and leave</Title><Msg>How would you look at his actions ANY other way?</Msg><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363702862282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:21:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363702941667-62</Id><Topic><Title>Warren East retiring? At only 51 years of age?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363682355859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He knew he would be humiliated by the public boasts he made about ARM's "inherent" advantages over Intel that he can no longer defend. ARM's Windows RT is a failure. ARM server competition never materialized and now Intel's 32 nm Clovertrail rivals the best ARM ships today for mobile. Note how silent East has been lately. He does not want to be around when the $&amp;#* hits the fan.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1363702941667</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:22:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363703620658-63</Id><Topic><Title>Warren East retiring? At only 51 years of age?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363682355859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe he'll take the INTel CEO job...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363703620658</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:33:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363703966205-64</Id><Title>Wallis:</Title><Msg>That does it...you are a complete idiot and you have been proven wrong on every idiotic hype you have put out. WARNING to anyone who strays in here: Do not listen to Wallis the shill. And, Getanid16 or 61 or Warreneast61, or whatever, all of them are a trogolydytic pedophile named ATT4GLTE. Beware..this place is a stinking swamp. It all speaks very ill of INTC.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363703966205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:39:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363704055370-65</Id><Topic><Title>seriously, will this thing ever see $25 this year?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363696866547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suspect Covello has this one right. $16 within a year.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363704055370</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:40:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363704083705-66</Id><Topic><Title>seriously, will this thing ever see $25 this year?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363696866547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you and att4glte...permaignore.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363704083705</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:41:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363704237280-67</Id><Title>att4glte:</Title><Msg>aka, warreneast61 and getanid16, or 61.... have you taken my advice and talked to a professional about your horrific family life? The abuse you suffered at home and on the school yard is unmentionable. Those lude acts you were required to perform out of fear have left you scarred for the rest of your life. You do need help. get some soon.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363704237280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:43:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363704493822-68</Id><Title>Insiders sell and more shorts every month, Looks like INTC is going lower</Title><Msg>Insiders sell and more shorts every month, Looks like INTC is going lower</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363704493822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363704573879-69</Id><Topic><Title>East trashed Intel and pumped ARM so he could get rich and leave</Title><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363702862282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>East will exit before Intel releases Baytrail. You think he doesn't know when ARM's party is over?</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1363704573879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:49:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363704652233-70</Id><Topic><Title>seriously, will this thing ever see $25 this year?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363696866547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm going to say yes, however I sold out yesterday at a profit and could buy back in at a lower average today than I was in when I sold out yesterday... and yes, I'm looking to get back in... but was able to take a profit and hope to be able to get back in at a lower average.... was averaged in at $21.32 yesterday and sold out at $21.45... if it maintains its current price I'd be able to lower my average in price right now, but I'm hoping of a little closer to $21...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1363704652233</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:50:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363704697946-71</Id><Topic><Title>East trashed Intel and pumped ARM so he could get rich and leave</Title><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363702862282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is a very smart man. He left at the top. Now he can cash his stock a very rich man.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363704697946</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363704925660-72</Id><Title>Please palace at___bubida</Title><Msg>Get some happiness at ____bubida</Msg><Username>kanarmir</Username><Timestamp>1363704925660</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363705366140-73</Id><Topic><Title>att4glte:</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363704237280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:43:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you forgot mystk, chump, and hundreds of other aliases I have on ignore...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363705366140</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:02:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363705684977-74</Id><Topic><Title>Insiders sell and more shorts every month, Looks like INTC is going lower</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363704493822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:48:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Down 1 cent, big whup. Loser ....</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363705684977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:08:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363705705633-75</Id><Title>How many of you are still holding on to INTC after CNBC Pete the con man told you to Buy INTC at 29.25. MAN he cost you a lot of money</Title><Msg>That Call to BUY INTC was so Warren Buffett to get out. Don't you fill like a sucker. Warren sold on that call SEC should look into that</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363705705633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:08:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363705769333-76</Id><Topic><Title>seriously, will this thing ever see $25 this year?</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363696866547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 08:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My opinion is that you should sell now and move on doesn't sound like you have the patience for this stock. INTC will change the game in mobile. Right now tablets are more or less toys. You can't do real work on them unless you buy something like a $1000 Surface Pro which has questionable battery life. I have a Galaxy Tab and it is a great but very limiting on what I can do with it I watch movies on it and play music and that is about it. When the new generation of mobile chips come out it will become a better market. The explosive catalyst is going to be Bay Trail. Also, don't discount the improving server market and better then expected PC sales in the second half of the year.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363705769333</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363705890737-77</Id><Topic><Title>Insiders sell and more shorts every month, Looks like INTC is going lower</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363704493822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:48:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Prove me wrong and put you money up BUY,BUY ,BUY, so I can watch you lose your money</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363705890737</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:11:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363706189315-78</Id><Title>INTC revenue to fall 8% quarter-over-quarter, Piper.</Title><Msg>this is the lower end for the march qtr,</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1363706189315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:16:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363706308772-79</Id><Topic><Title>Insiders sell and more shorts every month, Looks like INTC is going lower</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363704493822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:48:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already am long. Why don't you short it, instead of posting all your trash? Be a man for once. No one cares about your lazy cut/paste baloney.</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363706308772</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:18:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363706336788-80</Id><Title>INTC revenue lower , Earnings lower , Margins lower not a good picture is it</Title><Msg>INTC revenue lower , Earnings lower , Margins lower not a good picture is it</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363706336788</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:18:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363706781717-81</Id><Topic><Title>Insiders sell and more shorts every month, Looks like INTC is going lower</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363704493822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:48:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is an idiot who believes he affects the stock price. His attitude changes dramatically as soon as he buys and then again as soon as he sells. His posts are generally worthless.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1363706781717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363706878912-82</Id><Topic><Title>att4glte:</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363704237280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:43:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL@ both of you, Warren East, and your mammies.</Msg><Username>galba_tamponerator</Username><Timestamp>1363706878912</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:27:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363706901883-83</Id><Title>I am woman !</Title><Msg>Here me roar (whine).</Msg><Username>galba_tamponerator</Username><Timestamp>1363706901883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:28:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363707115498-84</Id><Topic><Title>I am woman !</Title><Username>galba_tamponerator</Username><Timestamp>1363706901883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:28:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's funny as #$%$ !</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1363707115498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:31:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363707120538-85</Id><Topic><Title>Insiders sell and more shorts every month, Looks like INTC is going lower</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363704493822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:48:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree except to say his posts are "always" worthless. He is a sick b*a*s*t*a*r*d*. He thumbs up his own posts with an alias.</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363707120538</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:32:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363707273445-86</Id><Topic><Title>I am woman !</Title><Username>galba_tamponerator</Username><Timestamp>1363706901883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:28:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah..not only are you a pedophile..but you are also a misogynist...they are dual symptoms of deep disorders. You belong in the lock-up.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363707273445</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363707408714-87</Id><Topic><Title>East trashed Intel and pumped ARM so he could get rich and leave</Title><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363702862282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"He is a very smart man. He left at the top. Now he can cash his stock a very rich man." [Let's hope so, It would mean that he will liquidate his big share holding as soon as possible before further declines in value. Which, of course, will drive the ARM stock price down even further. I love seeing the big Wall Street firms trying to work their way out of their erroneous conclusions about Intel and ARM. The Altera news totally undermined them and pointed out their complete mindlessness about Intel. Much more to come...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363707408714</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:36:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363707532471-88</Id><Topic><Title>A post from Khitchdees other personality regarding Surface Pro</Title><Username>intc_daily</Username><Timestamp>1363349088151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 08:04:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great post, khitchdee. I guess Warren East agrees, too.</Msg><Username>galba_tamponerator</Username><Timestamp>1363707532471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:38:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363707644886-89</Id><Topic><Title>Warren East retiring? At only 51 years of age?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363682355859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i have never owned armh, nothing funny about you, pathetic #$%$.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1363707644886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:40:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363707983772-90</Id><Title>Time to sell I taking INTC down today</Title><Msg>You can't win.</Msg><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1363707983772</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:46:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363708044680-91</Id><Title>One Month Chart: Intel verses ARM</Title><Msg>Even with the Wall Street analysts pulling out all the stops, Intel has opened up a serious gap over ARM for the last eleven days. With Haswell due in less than 30 days and new Intel smart phone announcements coming almost every day. This is what the tipping point looks like...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363708044680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363708356091-92</Id><Title>T.Woods Can Now Have A Flying Screw</Title><Msg>and I cant even get a regular one cause I am broke with INTC shares hitting the $#its everyday. What Luck. Maybe Woods has a mole on his #$%$.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1363708356091</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363708400774-93</Id><Topic><Title>Time to sell I taking INTC down today</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1363707983772</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:46:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BID/ASK 21.20/21.21</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363708400774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:53:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363708437449-94</Id><Title>Longs disappointment is palpable</Title><Msg>Having a chuckle. Take her to 16 Scotty. Aye aye captain ! The earnings release and explanations are gonna be really amusing. Wait til they explain the margins on mobile....OMG.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1363708437449</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:53:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363708692576-95</Id><Topic><Title>INTC revenue lower , Earnings lower , Margins lower not a good picture is it</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363706336788</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:18:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CNBC suckered me into BAC, sure glad I am not in INTC</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363708692576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:58:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363709431966-96</Id><Title>This, and its shills, is a pos.</Title><Msg>There's a reason why INTC hasn't gone anywhere in a decade. Go find a shill who can spin that.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363709431966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363709603274-97</Id><Title>BCCI GO TO NASDAQ--FACTS HUGE PROFITS $</Title><Msg>MONSTER MOVE</Msg><Username>sintelquatimod</Username><Timestamp>1363709603274</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:13:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363710233484-98</Id><Topic><Title>This, and its shills, is a pos.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363709431966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:10:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With a 4% yield I'll be happy if it just keeps chugging along. Not in this for hypergrowth,.</Msg><Username>mister_investor</Username><Timestamp>1363710233484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:23:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363710854832-99</Id><Topic><Title>INTC revenue lower , Earnings lower , Margins lower not a good picture is it</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363706336788</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:18:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CNBC now talking about a 2008 correction , because of copper . FN great</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363710854832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363711002851-100</Id><Topic><Title>SELL INTC and BUY HPQ or CSCO</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1362084810402</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 15:53:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you listen to Lucy or did you listen to Wallis? TOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1363711002851</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:36:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363711012023-101</Id><Topic><Title>Warren East retiring? At only 51 years of age?</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1363682355859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should have reinvesteded the dividend. The guy put in 40 years - back than Intel was still in DRAM business.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363711012023</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363711839503-102</Id><Title>Warren East would not like to hang around for Bay Trail announcement !!!</Title><Msg>so it seems !!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1363711839503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:50:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363712289863-103</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>linkosarah</Username><Timestamp>1362149300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:48:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was really looking for some great news. Now I found it.</Msg><Username>klangzeirosa</Username><Timestamp>1363712289863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363712402325-104</Id><Topic><Title>This, and its shills, is a pos.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363709431966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:10:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>galba_imperator, not sure what price your in at, but you might look into lowering your average price by selling some long covered calls... I'm back in again at less than I was before, you can play the bounces too... I will if I can... I'll buy more if we drop to $20.50 and more at $20... but as for right now I'll hold and sell future covered calls on up days....</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1363712402325</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:00:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363713038161-105</Id><Topic><Title>This, and its shills, is a pos.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363709431966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 12:10:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a grade-A loser. A 70 year wuss.</Msg><Username>galba_tamponerator</Username><Timestamp>1363713038161</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:10:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363713177592-106</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Will enter US smartphone market this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363543954511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:12:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The FACT is we have 2 foundries (Samsung and Global ) that have tapped out FinFET test chips. Clearly, the FinFET side of things has been resolved. We don't know how good/bad these transistors are to Intel's version and how well (or not) the process will scale. Less Clearly, the FinFET side of things has been resolved. Really? I think you should ask ALTR. There is plenty of publications of Intel TriGate (data, cross sections etc) I have seen NOTHING from Samsung, Glofo or TSMC. No "silicon" just schematics that show show how it should work. Do they have a process? Anyway it's a 20nm chip - it seems ARM foundries have problems with backend which will reduce the ability to shrink. It might not bother the ARM fans but it did bother ALTR.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363713177592</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:12:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363713265566-107</Id><Topic><Title>SELL INTC and BUY HPQ or CSCO</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1362084810402</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 15:53:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said to trade Intel at 20 for Cisco at 20, two years ago. Cisco promptly went from 20 to 14 and Intel promptly went from 20 to 29. LOL@ you and your vaginal warts.</Msg><Username>galba_tamponerator</Username><Timestamp>1363713265566</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:14:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363713355773-108</Id><Title>Bank of America Merrill Lynch - Price Target for Intel - $28 with some Haswell/Bay Trail details</Title><Msg>Meanwhile, Vivek Arya, analyst at Bank of America Merrill Lynch expect that the first quarter sales of Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) would come in a low-end of down 2% -10% guidance vs. current expectation of -6% decline due to the weakening PC demand in Asia particularly after the Chinese new year in February. The analyst expects the PC demand to decline by 15% QoQ. Arya also noted that the timing of Intel’s Haswell ramp could be a critical swing factor. “We expect Haswell to enable sub 10W convertible ultrabooks and tablets with 8-10 hrs battery life, in line with ARM Holdings plc (NASDAQ:ARMH) (LON:ARM), but at performance levels closer to full-featured PCs. Haswell also adds a connected stand-by power state (SOi) to the x86 ecosystem, which brings mobile features to PCs and lowers idle power by 10x and addresses Intel’s Achilles heels vs. ARM. While Intel’s Haswell pricing remains unclear, ultra thin (</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1363713355773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363713463123-109</Id><Topic><Title>Bank of America Merrill Lynch - Price Target for Intel - $28 with some Haswell/Bay Trail details</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1363713355773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:15:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Contd... While Intel’s Haswell pricing remains unclear, ultra thin (</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1363713463123</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:17:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363714068958-110</Id><Title>teeny bopper !!!! teen angel !! teeenie weenie !! teens !!</Title><Msg>Ok it is under 21, now must be discarded, I mean carded.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1363714068958</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:27:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363714239732-111</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Will enter US smartphone market this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363543954511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:12:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This makes sense. Appears Intel preferred to enter the U.S. market when it had demonstrably superior performance and efficiency over ARM based devices and support for LTE.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1363714239732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:30:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363714516407-112</Id><Topic><Title>INTC revenue lower , Earnings lower , Margins lower not a good picture is it</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363706336788</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:18:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wall Street is sell all they can , NOT a good picture</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363714516407</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:35:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363714564900-113</Id><Topic><Title>East trashed Intel and pumped ARM so he could get rich and leave</Title><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363702862282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallisweaver, Warren East has been aggressively liquidating during this bull run. He's way ahead of the hapless ARM shareholders who kept buying his shares from him.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363714564900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363714899096-114</Id><Topic><Title>ROFL @ GETANID61</Title><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363681825968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 04:30:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>teeenie weenie !!</Msg><Username>getanad61</Username><Timestamp>1363714899096</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363715350657-115</Id><Topic><Title>Longs disappointment is palpable</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1363708437449</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>someone moved the cheese. Prices on thin PCs coming down again too !!</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1363715350657</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:49:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363715661683-116</Id><Title>cyprus</Title><Msg>read some of the articles about Russia, Germany and why Cyprus is getting the evil eye by the EU. Sounds like a movie. Anyway Ben may hint on a slowing of the punch bowl soon. I love a good drama.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1363715661683</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:54:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363715739068-117</Id><Topic><Title>East trashed Intel and pumped ARM so he could get rich and leave</Title><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363702862282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, he has long term incentive stock options that cannot be sold until he leaves the company. I am short ARMH and happy about it but I am a bit suprised at how fast it is starting to fall.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363715739068</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:55:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363715770606-118</Id><Title>psychpath alert! att46lte and his id's.</Title><Msg>Do you know where your kids (the young males) are? Also, better keep an eye on your livestock..lambs and pigs in particular. att4glte is on the loose!</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363715770606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:56:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363715772052-119</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>linkosarah</Username><Timestamp>1362149300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:48:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok thanks. I will take a look at this.</Msg><Username>nufrijaadeline</Username><Timestamp>1363715772052</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:56:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363715783802-120</Id><Topic><Title>INTC revenue lower , Earnings lower , Margins lower not a good picture is it</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363706336788</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:18:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure glad I don't have any INTC stock. The picture is very BAD</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363715783802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:56:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363715818693-121</Id><Topic><Title>INTC revenue lower , Earnings lower , Margins lower not a good picture is it</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363706336788</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:18:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your comments have no effect on the price- you dip$hit.</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363715818693</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:56:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363716267340-122</Id><Title>Folks Folks Folks</Title><Msg>Yes when yall read the report of a slowdown in PC. Laptop, Ultrabooks yes its very true, trust me that is right. Europe is in deep crapola but the African makets are doing better and the middle east is just moving along, nothing big. The emerging mkts have slowed down tremendously other than india and Russia the rest of the BRIC countries are in the crapola as well. So intel needs to hurry and get into the tablets and smartphone if they need to be a growth company. They are a cash cow and will have plenty of cash flow like MSFT and CSCO. Their divi is attractive hence if he mkts go down folks will clamor into this stock and other divi stocks.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1363716267340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:04:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363716920253-123</Id><Topic><Title>INTC revenue lower , Earnings lower , Margins lower not a good picture is it</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363706336788</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:18:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC is just tracking the SOX, SMH, SP500, NDX and all the other indices down. The semi indices SOX and SMH are both down exactly the same as Intel. About 0.8%</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363716920253</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:15:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363717109885-124</Id><Title>MONSTER CONTRACTS COMING FOR **CERP** HUGE GAINS COMING</Title><Msg>YAHOO NEWS HEADLINES</Msg><Username>schoollboysstock</Username><Timestamp>1363717109885</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:18:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363717339159-125</Id><Title>aladiesright, coinmaker, too funny, pcrandallfinance, lucy _nuff, etc</Title><Msg>Aliases of the same. Going to ignore. Wish Yahoo could get rid of the idiot pest.</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363717339159</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:22:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363717544281-126</Id><Title>Eww that smell, Cant'ya smell that smell.. It's the smell that surrounds you.</Title><Msg>Lynard Skynard knew about Intel long before they started making Semis.... Long live Skynard.. Flush this turd..</Msg><Username>pcrandallfinance</Username><Timestamp>1363717544281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:25:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363718006067-127</Id><Topic><Title>INTC revenue lower , Earnings lower , Margins lower not a good picture is it</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363706336788</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:18:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1 month comparison TSMC / Into the ALTRel TSMC down almost 12%...</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363718006067</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:33:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363718071267-128</Id><Topic><Title>East trashed Intel and pumped ARM so he could get rich and leave</Title><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363702862282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too bad Waldo wasn't bright enough to liquidate INTC at 29, or 27.50, or 23 or even 22</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1363718071267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363718077496-129</Id><Topic><Title>INTC revenue lower , Earnings lower , Margins lower not a good picture is it</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363706336788</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:18:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks like option are pricing INTC at about 17-18 range by JULY</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363718077496</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:34:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363718424836-130</Id><Topic><Title>aladiesright, coinmaker, too funny, pcrandallfinance, lucy _nuff, etc</Title><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363717339159</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:22:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's another: wdblawgrow</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363718424836</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:40:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363718463071-131</Id><Topic><Title>East trashed Intel and pumped ARM so he could get rich and leave</Title><Username>warreneast61</Username><Timestamp>1363702862282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 10:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Warren East has been aggressively liquidating during this bull run. He's way ahead of the hapless ARM shareholders who kept buying his shares from him." [He probably understand a lot more about ARM's fading fabrication that the nennies on this board. And the evidence is in his liquidation of his shares. My only question is whether he really got fired. The abruptness of his departure is curious...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363718463071</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:41:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363718994760-132</Id><Title>Intel markets imploding.</Title><Msg>The analysts were right. PC's are disappearing like pay phones. 70% of Intel's markets are going away. This one is rotten timber. Let Wallis sing all he wants. This one is going down.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363718994760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:49:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363719133590-133</Id><Topic><Title>Folks Folks Folks</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1363716267340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:04:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think your information is a little old. Ok, so here is the scoop. Computers and chips sales in general started slowing down in the third quarter of last year. MSFT and INTC sold off because of this. These are both strong buys because of that. Remember, buy low sell high. So essentially you are 2 quarters late. INTC just finished selling the last bit of their excess inventory from the slowdown for the last 2 quarters. Now, INTC is at an earnings trough. Essentially the quarter to be announced earnings will be as bad as it gets. Of course analysts are going to drum beat "that PC sales are slowing down" as much as they can before now and then to get INTC stock as low as it can go. They make money when you churn the stock. IF you listen to this and sell then you are selling at the bottom. Intel missed the whole smart phone thing that is true. They are working hard to catch up but went from to behind to essentially caught up in 2 years time. That while using an outdated core. By the end of the year, Intel chips will be superior to any ARM chip out there. Yes, INTC is quite aware that they need to move aggressively in the mobile space and the are doing it. Buy big tech here, MSFT, INTC, and CSCO this year and you will be very happy at the end of the year.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363719133590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:52:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363719683848-134</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Cuts Manufacturing Costs With Big Data</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363665116820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 23:51:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>keep pumping Waldo, maybe some day INTC might get back to 24.00, pity the markets got overbght and are taking INTC the dog with it.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1363719683848</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:01:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363720174995-135</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>linkosarah</Username><Timestamp>1362149300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:48:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow free of charge. I love it. Thanks</Msg><Username>ravelabonita</Username><Timestamp>1363720174995</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:09:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363720445634-136</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Will enter US smartphone market this year</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363543954511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:12:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is kind of scary for ARM that Intel took an ancient core and made it at least competitive. In fact, in terms of graphics in many ways it is better. With ARM it is do you want great graphics or do you want battery life. The real scary is that Intel will shrink to 22 nm by the end of this year and when Airmont comes out in 2014 Intel will be at 14nm. They are shrinking the process every year! No other manufacturer is going to be able to keep up.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363720445634</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:14:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363720488003-137</Id><Topic><Title>Intel markets imploding.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363718994760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:49:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The analysts were right. PC's are disappearing like pay phones. 70% of Intel's markets are going away. This one is rotten timber. Let Wallis sing all he wants. This one is going down." [Absolutely. The world needs less processors every day. Use of the internet is on the decline. The Cloud shrinks every day. The Internet of Things is not really growing exponentially. Every day we have less and less video creation and storage. No one will ever install sensors, cameras or radio ID tags. No one watches TV. Communications are dropping in volume. The number of mobility devices is dropping like a rock. All foundries are cranking out volume production of 7mm FinFET's and all have 450mm wafers and EUV and none has an advantage over the other. The number of foundries increases daily. Why, oh why didn't I notice all of these things until you pointed them out. You truly are a genius, Gump... ]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363720488003</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:14:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363720637822-138</Id><Topic><Title>Time to sell I taking INTC down today</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1363707983772</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:46:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You can't win." You can't win indeed if you believe the lies posted by dimwit money loser Raystock. To give you an idea of how clueless he is about stocks he posted last October that he was buying aapl cheap when it was trading at $661.31 in this posting from the aapl message board "I am taking this stock down today so we can buy real cheap time to buy now by raystock48079 . Oct 2, 2012 1:31 PM . Permalink WE have started buying shares now" Stocks can only go up or down so a complete idiot should be able to guess right on a given day with 50 percent accuracy so how come Raystock averages 10 percent right?</Msg><Username>psychiatrist_of_rayst0ck</Username><Timestamp>1363720637822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363720648269-139</Id><Topic><Title>Intel markets imploding.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363718994760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:49:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I take back what I said about you being as bad as backbay You're not. You're worse...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363720648269</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:17:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363720959305-140</Id><Title>ARM down 83 Cents, Intel down 14 Cents</Title><Msg>Yet Mr. Dana F Blankenhorn (can't imagine what the F stands for) celebrates by once again steeping himself in ordure. And Cisco is down 22 cents...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363720959305</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:22:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363721134874-141</Id><Title>It May Be Time For Microsoft To Cancel Surface RT</Title><Msg>[I think Microsoft should cancel the RT in July to coincide with Mr. East's departure. Fitting they should leave together...] Cancelling RT and Focusing on Pro To achieve this seemingly uphill battle, Microsoft might need to do away with RT. Initial sales of the RT are weak, while the Pro appears to have sold at a more rapid rate. Consumers do not want a scaled-down tablet running on an ARM-based (ARMH) processor. The opinion of cancelling RT is not unique: IDC mentioned this notion too. The RT Tablet is also powered by NVIDIA (NVDA). The scaled-down operating system appears to weaken the tablet’s strengths: the ability to run x86-based Windows software. Microsoft may have believed that it needed a lower-priced device to compete in the market place. Canceling RT and going “all-in” with Pro would restore Microsoft’s relationship with Intel (INTC). The focus would also bring leadership to hardware manufacturers in building Windows 8-based solutions. From thestreet</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363721134874</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:25:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363721305107-142</Id><Topic><Title>ARM down 83 Cents, Intel down 14 Cents</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363720959305</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:22:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good thing you sold INTC at 29, eh Waldorf/</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1363721305107</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:28:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363721773636-143</Id><Topic><Title>ARM down 83 Cents, Intel down 14 Cents</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363720959305</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:22:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hoping ARM, CSCO, BAC and AMD all go under. These are all $hitty stocks.</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363721773636</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363723095572-144</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>linkosarah</Username><Timestamp>1362149300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:48:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love this article. Keep it coming.</Msg><Username>nahnahshaandrea</Username><Timestamp>1363723095572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:58:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363723147367-145</Id><Topic><Title>INTC revenue lower , Earnings lower , Margins lower not a good picture is it</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1363706336788</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:18:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am surptised at INTC strength at the end of the day. Lots of buying (covering?) which is a lot different than on the way down from $29. Especially in the last 10 minutes when buyback is turned off.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1363723147367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:59:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363723543598-146</Id><Topic><Title>It May Be Time For Microsoft To Cancel Surface RT</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363721134874</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:25:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like so many chip upstarts before ARM they came gunning for Intel's business and got handed their head. Microsoft probably won't officially kill RT for a while in hopes of saving face, but the jury of public opinion has already declared it dead.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1363723543598</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:05:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363723665036-147</Id><Topic><Title>ARM down 83 Cents, Intel down 14 Cents</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363720959305</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:22:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why bother juggling aliases all day? everyone already knows who you are nuff, you IDIOT Troll!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1363723665036</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:07:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363724581885-148</Id><Title>Marsavian</Title><Msg>As our resident TA expert, what's your current take on ARM?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363724581885</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:23:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363725963900-149</Id><Topic><Title>It May Be Time For Microsoft To Cancel Surface RT</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363721134874</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:25:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will die quietly. It was conceived before Intel really started getting serious about mobile chips. The market is really hungry for a tablet that can run their favorite Windows software. ARM is not going to do that. Calling it anything "Windows" was just a marketing disaster for Microsoft.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363725963900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:46:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363726171794-150</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363724581885</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:23:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's a pretty big gap at $30 that needs to be filled</Msg><Username>resu0ouf</Username><Timestamp>1363726171794</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:49:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363726482296-151</Id><Title>TWO DIFFERENT BUSINESS MODELS :: INTEL VS ARM HOLDINGS</Title><Msg>IN HOUSE FABS ..REQUIRE BILLIONS TO SUSTAIN AND WHEN THIS MODEL IS DISRUPTED AND MARGINS VANISH , IT BECOMES UNSUSTAINABLE VS FABLESS AND ONLY LICENSING CPU/GPU CORE BUSINESS ARMH now dominates Smart Phones,many other consumer devices and now entering 64BIT Server market frontier more and more Margin hell for Intel and revenue decline severity takes hold too now..................</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1363726482296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:54:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363726492428-152</Id><Title>Who handles Intel SEP-IRA accounts?</Title><Msg>Hi everyone and thanks for any help you can give me. Computershare is so tough to reach by phone. I called Intel investor relations and got an answering machine. I'm interested in establishing a SEP-IRA with Intel but I don't know who handles SEP-IRA's for them. If you know who to contact to set-up a SEP-IRA with them, I'd appreciate it! Good luck to all!</Msg><Username>braincandy62</Username><Timestamp>1363726492428</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:54:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363727455554-153</Id><Topic><Title>Intel markets imploding.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363718994760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:49:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I take back what I said about you being a paid shill. You're no paid shill...you're stupid enough to do this on your own. Geeez..a supposedly grown man hyping a stock on a yahoo message board all day...pathetic...I repeat: PATHETIC.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363727455554</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:10:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363727876517-154</Id><Topic><Title>Intel markets imploding.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363718994760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:49:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's an open forum what in H are ytou doing here?</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1363727876517</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:17:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363728545982-155</Id><Topic><Title>Intel markets imploding.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363718994760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:49:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey idiot..it's an open forum..then why are you doing in here? You seem to think you're the mind-control-police---your self and your shadow (your fat #$%$) .</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363728545982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:29:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363729592500-156</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363724581885</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:23:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The stock broke below it 50 DMA at around 42 and the 20 DMA is starting to roll over. Essentially the technicals look very bad and that is why I am short. There is very little support until around the 32 level. On a technical basis, the stock is not safe to invest in unless it can rally above the 43 level. The technical picture for INTC is a bit more difficult to divine. It is sitting right along support so I think we can rally off this point but the pattern shows more of a basing pattern then a bullish one. The technicals on INTC are neutral.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1363729592500</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 17:46:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363730633274-157</Id><Title>East on manufacturing a couple months ago...</Title><Msg>... he started to contradict himself a couple months ago... and he seems in complete disconnect to the manufacturing aspect though he figured out that cost for ARM SoCs will go up. He does not seem to fully comprehend Moore's law - at least that's what it sounds like In the Intel worldview, a kind of “Transistor Cliff,” if you will, is one very possible end game. To East, it is nonsense. He offers that the things that sell individual chips are “How much does the chip cost, how fast does it go, and how much power does it consume,” considered in concert. If chips can do that in any existing technology, “Why even move to the next node?” “The only benefit of a new geometry is to get more chips out of a wafer,” adds East. But if wafers end up costing twice as much because double patterning — the application of multiple additional “mask layers” — is needed to get to smaller geometries, than the additional cost may outweigh any benefits.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363730633274</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:03:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363731440183-158</Id><Topic><Title>Intel markets imploding.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363718994760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:49:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You fight the Fed in the manner that the Barbarians fought the legions. Just to clarify Attila as well as Arminus were well educated (by the Romans) - Arminius slaughtered the legions in the Teutoburger forest. The Americans applied similar tactics when battling the British empire. Now that Greece is out of the picture they digging up Cyprus... Mar 4, 2013 – Greece's primary surplus in January reached €1.64 billion. In January ... Greece sells 1.3 bln eur 3-month T-Bills, yield steady · Draghi says ....</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1363731440183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:17:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363731713578-159</Id><Topic><Title>Who handles Intel SEP-IRA accounts?</Title><Username>braincandy62</Username><Timestamp>1363726492428</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:54:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I usually just call Fred.</Msg><Username>resu0ouf</Username><Timestamp>1363731713578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:21:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363732557762-160</Id><Topic><Title>aladiesright, coinmaker, too funny, pcrandallfinance, lucy _nuff, etc</Title><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363717339159</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:22:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's even another: singhlion2001. It's like killing cockroaches.</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363732557762</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363733281591-161</Id><Title>Nvidia CEO - Says Windows RT Is Disappointing</Title><Msg>Huang said. "I know there are smart people up there who are going to unleash the dragons of Outlook onto millions of consumers who are just waiting with bated breath for a very, very thin PC with long battery life that is Outlook compatible." Nvidia's CEO's prayers have been answered. It's an Intel tablet based on Clovertrail+ or any Intel processor released after it.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1363733281591</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:48:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363733599888-162</Id><Topic><Title>Intel markets imploding.</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363718994760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:49:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel Is the Biggest Bargain Out There: Fort Pitt’s Forrest For anyone who has held shares of Intel (INTC) for more than a decade, chances are the stock has not only been a loser, but also a disappointment. While the world's largest maker of semiconductors has offered traders at least a dozen chances in as many years to try to make money on its price swings between $15 and $25 a share, its long-term story is still a daunting one, including the $75 high-water mark from September of 2000 that still stands today. And yet, analyst Kim Forrest, at Fort Pitt Capital says this time it's going to be different. "At this point in time, I couldn't be happier owning this stock because I really think 2013 is going to be the year in which they begin to show some traction," Forrest says in the attached video. "I think people have really underestimated what this company can produce." Forrest believes Intel can overcome its power efficiency problem sooner than its rivals at ARM (ARMH) can overcome its computing power disadvantage. "My bet is that the engineers at Intel will win this" she says. To gauge how that fight is going, Forrest recommends that investors keep an eye out for any signs of Intel pushing into the lower end smartphone business. Of course, there are plenty of skeptics out there who aren't impressed with the company's 4.3% dividend yield that is high, and rising. In fact, just 35% of the 51 analysts who follow Intel rate it a "buy" right now, which means the stock is the least loved it has been in at least 20 years, FactSet data shows. "Contrarian signals. You gotta love 'em," Forrest says with a smile. From Yahoo Finance</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363733599888</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:53:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363734482099-163</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia CEO - Says Windows RT Is Disappointing</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1363733281591</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:48:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As bullish as I am on Nvidia, I think that Windows RT is on its way to the morgue.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1363734482099</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:08:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363735509957-164</Id><Topic><Title>aladiesright, coinmaker, too funny, pcrandallfinance, lucy _nuff, etc</Title><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363717339159</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:22:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yhoo needs to rip nuff's ugly head off &amp; shet down the hole!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1363735509957</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:25:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363736786617-165</Id><Topic><Title>Marsavian</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363724581885</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:23:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>poor Waldo fails to see a similar situation for his beloved INTC.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1363736786617</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:46:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363737239009-166</Id><Title>Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) Is the Biggest Bargain Out There</Title><Msg>Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) Is the Biggest Bargain Out There March 19th, 2013 For anyone who has held shares of Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) for more than a decade, chances are the stock has not only been a loser, but also a disappointment. While the world’s largest maker of semiconductors has offered traders at least a dozen chances in as many years to try to make money on its price swings between $15 and $25 a share, its long-term story is still a daunting one, including the $75 high-water mark from September of 2000 that still stands today. And yet, analyst Kim Forrest, at Fort Pitt Capital says this time it’s going to be different. “At this point in time, I couldn’t be happier owning this stock because I really think 2013 is going to be the year in which they begin to show some traction,” Forrest says in the attached video. “I think people have really underestimated what this company can produce.” Have you ever wondered how billionaires continue to get RICHER, while the rest of the world is struggling? "I study billionaires for a living. To be more specific, I study how these investors generate such huge and consistent profits in the stock markets -- year-in and year-out." CLICK HERE to get your Free E-Book, “The Little Black Book Of Billionaires Secrets” Forrest believes Intel can overcome its power efficiency problem sooner than its rivals at ARM Holdings plc (ADR) (NASDAQ:ARMH) can overcome its computing power disadvantage. “My bet is that the engineers at Intel will win this” she says. You can see the full “Breakout” interview below:</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1363737239009</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 19:53:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363737946301-167</Id><Topic><Title>INTC Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>linkosarah</Username><Timestamp>1362149300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 09:48:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got it for free. Thank you</Msg><Username>knapkoekenvelma</Username><Timestamp>1363737946301</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:05:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363738729666-168</Id><Topic><Title>aladiesright, coinmaker, too funny, pcrandallfinance, lucy _nuff, etc</Title><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363717339159</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 14:22:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or they could take volunteers but the line would be too long. .</Msg><Username>jj88810</Username><Timestamp>1363738729666</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:18:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363738920215-169</Id><Title>Stop replying to Galba_Imperator (Flumoxed) and backbay_bstn</Title><Msg>Both are long Intel for the Dividend, neither are selling, but BOTH are gutless wimps that post crybaby messages in hopes that someone will come along and hold their hands and make them all comfy so they can sleep at night. Leave both of their messages untouched and let them rot.</Msg><Username>galba_tamponerator</Username><Timestamp>1363738920215</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:22:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363739368521-170</Id><Title>Hey Teabagg trashnuttyts? OB won so shut your loud #$%$ crying. The Dow is up huge.</Title><Msg>Of course, if you do continue to cry, it is funny so keep it up. You look so angry and pathetic that it gives me a good laugh. But really--how did you get sofreaking stupid teabagger? Do not blame it on your family because you have a brain but just choose to have shiiet in it. God did it to you? Welll gawdddaaammmed are you lucky. The weak shall inherit the earth and you are indeed weak of mind.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1363739368521</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:29:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363740084293-171</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Teabagg trashnuttyts? OB won so shut your loud #$%$ crying. The Dow is up huge.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1363739368521</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:29:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here are some of his other aliases. Poor guy is a lonely homosexual liberal dirtbag. Anything Hector Anything Cornhole Anything AMD monkey Miltonusa On and On and On. Let him rot.</Msg><Username>galba_tamponerator</Username><Timestamp>1363740084293</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:41:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363740176612-172</Id><Topic><Title>Stop replying to Galba_Imperator (Flumoxed) and backbay_bstn</Title><Username>galba_tamponerator</Username><Timestamp>1363738920215</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:22:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here are some of his other aliases. Poor guy is a lonely homosexual liberal dirtbag. Anything Hector Anything Cornhole Anything AMD monkey Miltonusa On and On and On. Let him rot</Msg><Username>galba_tamponerator</Username><Timestamp>1363740176612</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:42:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363740275027-173</Id><Title>Picked up another 5K shares at $21.02 today</Title><Msg>Nothing beats 4.5% dividend. My model says we are basing here for a while.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1363740275027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363741245911-174</Id><Title>Intel's main competition for it's upcoming set-top box</Title><Msg>The Roku 3 and Apple TV: youtubeDOTcom/watch?v=d69wCtKCATI But these devices don't have what Intel's box will have: - Live TV streaming - Cloud-based DVR Basically, Intel's set-top box will have combined features of a Roku and a TiVo. Big question for me is, will Intel use Android for their UI or will it be their own? I also think Microsoft will have support for Intel's Live TV service on their upcoming Xbox 720. There is also rumor of a Xbox Surface tablet, with Intel inside, that will be used to interact with the game console.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363741245911</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:00:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363741919313-175</Id><Title>Intel launches Media Server Reference Design to speed up set-top box creation</Title><Msg>engadgetDOTcom/2013/03/19/intel-launches-media-server-reference-design/ It seems Intel wants set-top box to be a new device category. So, similar to smartphones and tablets, set-top boxes can be developed using an OS like Android or Windows or Tizen ...and then additional features can be added by each hw maker.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363741919313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:11:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363742601450-176</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>The market is bracing for more volatile moves over the next several sessions. First, the FOMC rate decision is due out tomorrow afternoon. The problem with the Fed is that it probably can't get any more dovish than the market currently expects. That leaves the Fed with a choice either to stand pat or to phase out its QE programs. The market could get some short term disappointment. However, should the Fed upgrade its economic forecast, more buyers might come into the stock market. Second, the Cyprus banks will be reopening on Thursday. Regardless what decision or plans the ECB or the Cyprus government come up with, a bank run looks inevitable. These events could keep the volatility high and prices depressed in the stock market. Technically, short term momentum has turned bearish suggesting more pullbacks in the near term.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1363742601450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:23:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363743738000-177</Id><Title>Weaker PC shipments numbers in China due to Chinese New Year</Title><Msg>This is a factor to consider.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363743738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:42:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363745938451-178</Id><Topic><Title>Intel launches Media Server Reference Design to speed up set-top box creation</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363741919313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel normally releases a reference design when they don't intend to make the device themselves. If this is the device that's supposed to be used for Intel Web TV releasing a reference design now may mean the service is far from being ready, especially if they are just now looking for vendors to make it.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1363745938451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363746199676-179</Id><Topic><Title>Intel launches Media Server Reference Design to speed up set-top box creation</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363741919313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel's vision is for every home to have a Media Server (with Intel inside). The Media Server can be in the form of a set-top/streaming box (like Ruko or Apple TV), or a game console (like Xbox or Wii), or built into the TV (Smart TV). Intel's Live TV service was meant to accelerate this vision since cable operators are happy with the status quo and will not work with any other hw maker. Intel can also generate additional revenue by selling the Live TV service to hardware makers such as Ruko, MS (for the xbox), Sony (nintendo) or Samsung (smart tv). Intel can also use this service as leverage to encourage hardware makers to build their set-top boxes with Intel inside.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363746199676</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:23:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363746381154-180</Id><Topic><Title>Intel launches Media Server Reference Design to speed up set-top box creation</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363741919313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel's set-top box will be used to introduce their Live TV service and also to get the 'ball-rolling' for Media Servers.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363746381154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363746467172-181</Id><Topic><Title>Intel launches Media Server Reference Design to speed up set-top box creation</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363741919313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmm. General Instruments defined the set top box in 1982 or thereabouts. Doesn't it seem as if INTC is a little behind these days? I mean, seriously, dozens of companies have done hundreds of set top boxes in the past twenty years. Do you really think they overlooked something? And, the BOM for these things is in the fifteen to twenty five dollar range.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1363746467172</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363746725889-182</Id><Topic><Title>Intel launches Media Server Reference Design to speed up set-top box creation</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363741919313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe 'set-top box' is the wrong term to use nowadays. What I think Intel wants to do is have 'Media Servers' in every home..read my other post....</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363746725889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:32:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363747178044-183</Id><Title>ATT4GLTE is a psychopath</Title><Msg>Keep him away from your kids! This guy is really disturbed.. Mother rejected him. Serious abuse on the playground. Perma-ignore highly recommended</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363747178044</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363747663415-184</Id><Topic><Title>Intel launches Media Server Reference Design to speed up set-top box creation</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363741919313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you saying that the vendors considering making a box with Intel's reference design will be competing against Intel's box in the marketplace? That's a tough sell to vendors. Additionally, there are plenty of free &amp; open source media server packages that already run on generic Intel PC's. These packages function as DVR's and will stream music &amp; photos throughout the home. With an added HDTV receiver adapter they'll also record live TV. These are called HTPC's and they've been around since the introduction of HDTV.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1363747663415</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:47:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363747776313-185</Id><Topic><Title>ATT4GLTE is a psychopath</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1363747178044</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kids? Keep him away from your livestock!</Msg><Username>getanad61</Username><Timestamp>1363747776313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363748263038-186</Id><Topic><Title>Intel launches Media Server Reference Design to speed up set-top box creation</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363741919313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If vendors don't want to then Intel will continue to sell and enhance their own set-top box. That's the beauty of Intel's strategy here....they win however it plays out</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363748263038</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 22:57:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363748463816-187</Id><Topic><Title>Intel launches Media Server Reference Design to speed up set-top box creation</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363741919313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:11:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But I think the idea is to have their Media chip inside Smart TVs. That's where the TV is going. Set-top boxes are sort of temporary devices...eventually Smart TV will have the set-top box functionality built in....and Intel wants to be inside Smart TV.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363748463816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 23:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363748712970-188</Id><Title>Nobody retires at age 51.</Title><Msg>I won't read Warren East's retirement as a sign of trouble at ARMH. But just the same nobody ever retires at age 51. Yes there are people who try and after a summer at home with the wife they do something else. My thinking is that he is setting himself up as a corporate superstar. You'll see him slide into some other role sometime in the next year or two as the CEO of another tech company. It's all about timing and what the resume says. Right now his resume looks great. The stock growth story is fabulous and it recently reached record high. He can leave now with an amazing track record and walk into another company while demanding a very lucrative package. The downside in staying is if the stock drops then he has to answer to shareholders. There must be something in the future that has him a bit concerned. He can either leave now while on top or get forced out a couple years from now . I don't see this as a sign that ARMH will be slowing down anytime soon. What I do see is that he's about to get found out that the stories taking over Intel's market won't really come true and the stock will drop because people won't pay sky high premiums for it though the earnings will improve. Warren East isn't the Wizard of Oz but he is the Wizard of Cambridge His resignation ranks up there with the Pope resigning. You won't get the real story but the resignation does make you scratch your head. The real question isn't that he's leaving, but why now?</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1363748712970</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 23:05:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363749365191-189</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody retires at age 51.</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1363748712970</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 23:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100% agree.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1363749365191</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 23:16:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363749613328-190</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1363699099177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:18:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf, I have to say this: you have oversimplified ARM's strategic outlook as you have on other issues, ie. NVDA. I have you will close your ARM short soon...or it will bury you. Looks like you have collected enough information from this board. So....you should be hard at work to dumb down the stuff and feed it to your SA readers (before J7 gets to it).</Msg><Username>ibexx</Username><Timestamp>1363749613328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 23:20:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363751771004-191</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody retires at age 51.</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1363748712970</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 23:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>marsavian retired before that.... age 49 as I recall...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1363751771004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 23:56:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>