<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-29"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372479562027-1</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>semi_equip_junkie, Pardon me for sounding naive, but why does this suggest mid/end of 2014?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1372479562027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372479700887-2</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>semiwiki, I don't understand what you mean. The software ecosystem is primed for X86 on Android, and of course on Windows ARM is DOA, so there would be little benefit for Intel to license the x86 ISA to enable competitors. It makes more sense for Intel to design, build, and sell its own chips. You make a lot more money selling products than selling IP; just ask TSMC how much more money than ARM they make.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1372479700887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:21:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372480110775-3</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should follow up on your die size analysis die size 22nm versus 14nm Intel die size TSMC 20nm planar versus 16nm/14nm FinFet TSMC/GF/Samsung according to chipworks ARM can do some minor tweaks to interconnects but there won't be a significant shrink going from 20nm planar to 20nm 3D .....I am not sure the market comprehends</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372480110775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372480578421-4</Id><Title>Another Analyst is licking his chops, waiting to bad mouth the pig on Monday.</Title><Msg>Too many of these semi Analysts following Intel IMO. We have just one Mr Weaver.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372480578421</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372480939784-5</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Vows to Pick Up Mobile Pace</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372462712057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:38:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will begin using the company's most advanced manufacturing processes sooner to produce the .. ----------------------------------------------- Easily the best in the world</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1372480939784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:42:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372481101330-6</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>semi_equip_junkie, I am working on a very comprehensive piece, but I want to get my facts straight. What from that conference call excerpt tells you that 20nm will not be until mid/late 2014? What do you think is a reasonable time-frame for "16nm"? I am thinking 2H 2015, but what are your thoughts?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1372481101330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:45:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372481403846-7</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shipped to our customers by the end of 2013 across the industry. they are shipping the equipment ... install + qualification qualification? run split lots prior to release to production?</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1372481403846</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:50:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372495059873-8</Id><Topic><Title>B.K. is right</Title><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1372459480912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 18:44:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weak words coming from such a huge company. Look at Google, they started out with just search and then look at the heights they've scaled since that point. An efficient org can work on anything.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1372495059873</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 04:37:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372504365467-9</Id><Topic><Title>B.K. is right</Title><Username>t_e_n_k_a_y</Username><Timestamp>1372459480912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 18:44:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>challenging and doable</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1372504365467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 07:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372504468777-10</Id><Title>Intel Looks Ahead to the Wrist, the Ear and the Eye</Title><Msg>T new leaders are already setting sights on gadgets that they expect to sell in still-higher numbers.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1372504468777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 07:14:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372511141967-11</Id><Title>Two dishonest, large derivative players!</Title><Msg>Look at the tell signs on both the NASDAQ/NYSE. What is happening is stagnation in the major indices. This happens when the large derivative players are shifting their positions. They are now moving money and are going to bet against both markets. In the past this is when large corrections take place (over 10 percent). The large derivative players are the ones that run the indices. For example look at Warren Buffet; he is a heavy derivative player that has, over the last five years, substantially decreased his position in stocks and gone the derivative route. Smart, rich player. Derivative are an easy way to hide money.......so large losses can be covered up. The SEC does not understand this and they cannot track this. The result is no regulation. It will only take one major, dishonest derivative player to send our financial systems into ruin.</Msg><Username>geraldomcginty</Username><Timestamp>1372511141967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:05:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372511232328-12</Id><Topic><Title>Two dishonest, large derivative players!</Title><Username>geraldomcginty</Username><Timestamp>1372511141967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:05:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's going to get bad!</Msg><Username>geraldomcginty</Username><Timestamp>1372511232328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:07:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372511263339-13</Id><Topic><Title>Two dishonest derivative players!</Title><Username>geraldomcginty</Username><Timestamp>1372417574160</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 07:06:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its bad!</Msg><Username>geraldomcginty</Username><Timestamp>1372511263339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:07:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372512680796-14</Id><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Msg>"While expecting to stick mainly with Intel's longtime-processor technology, Mr. Krzanich said he would not rule out building chips for major foundry customers who prefer ARM technology." It was only a matter of time.......... Good call Mr Krzanich.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372513276955-15</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, I still can't believe it.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372513276955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372513496891-16</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are being disingenuous and not providing the full quote. It would need to be a VERY strategic partner (ala Apple) for them to consider it. Even so, I think Apple will go with TSMC and not Intel.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1372513496891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:44:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372514386319-17</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Sees Faster, More Flexible Future</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372445757324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:55:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And it would mean that Apple or Samsung gets to keep their huge base of designers to keep their business advantage and unique value add, while still leveraging the best of Intel's assets, and Intel gets to charge a premium for their process PLUS their IP. -------- right on</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1372514386319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:59:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372516160091-18</Id><Title>Intel hints at getting cold feet over TV plan</Title><Msg>It is encouraging that Intel's new CEO recognizes that technology alone, no matter how impressive it may be, is not a business plan. It also signals that he will not let the project become a drain on Intel's profitability and that's good. So it turns out those that questioned the viability of Intel's proposed Web TV are in fact in agreement with Intel's CEO. This certainly highlights the difference between those that are intellectually honest and view Intel's projects objectively and those do not.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372516160091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372516422590-19</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Foundries Rush 3-D Transistors Nearly two years after Intel, the world's leading foundries scramble to get FinFETs into the hands of chip designers By Rachel Courtland Posted 28 Dec 2012 | 16:00 GMT "They aim to introduce FinFETs at the 14-nanometer-manufacturing-process node—a step, more or less, behind Intel’s 22-nm introduction.   To get there, both GlobalFoundries and TSMC have revealed they’ll take a half step. They will replace planar transistors with a denser array of FinFETs, but they won’t advance the manufacturing process used to build the wiring that connects the devices on the “back end” layers of the chip. As a result, although there will be more transistors in any given area, a good number of them won’t be connected and therefore can’t be used. The chips won’t be much smaller than the 20-nm generation, which is going into production now. That means the foundries won’t be able to create more of them on a single wafer to reduce costs. Nonetheless, GlobalFoundries expects the chips it will produce could be as much #$%$ percent faster or 40 percent less power hungry than the 20-nm generation.   For GlobalFoundries, more than 7000 design rules that were developed for the 20-nm planar chip, while changing just 60 or so that are needed to describe the fin, says Subramani Kengeri, vice president of advanced technology architecture at GlobalFoundries. “First- generation FinFET is a huge challenge. There’s no question about it,” says Kengeri. “Adding more risks to that by adding other complexi ties that were not necessarily fin- related was not prudent.” " ------------------------------------------ ["the advantage of this halfway approach is that it will let the company keep more than 7000 design rules that were developed for the 20-nm planar chip, while changing just 60 or so that are needed to describe the fin"] [How many design rules will TSMC need to achieve 14nm HALF-finfet?] [How much more will 14nm add to the already skyrocketing cost of 20nm?]</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1372516422590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:33:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372517151092-20</Id><Title>Bloomberg: Intel nearing TV service deals with Time Warner, Viacom and NBC</Title><Msg>It's a very poorly kept secret that Intel is looking to bust in the pay-TV business. Rumors have been circulating since at least December that the chip giant is working on its own set-top box and hopes to pair it with a "virtual cable" service that offers unbundled channels. Of course, content creators are reticent to give up the lucrative package deals they've struck, which require providers to serve up smaller outlets alongside popular ones. But the tides are starting to shift, and many are demanding that these channels be offered à la carte. According to Bloomberg, Intel is getting close to offering such a service and is reportedly closing in on deals with Time Warner, Viacom and NBC that would allow them to offer both live and on-demand content over the internet. Sources are reporting that the broad terms of the deal have been agreed to, and its only a few fine details and some financial terms that need to be finalized. Intel is also allegedly in talks with Disney, CBS and News Corp. Though, those negotiations are in the preliminary stages. If Intel can successfully land deals for CNN, Comedy Central, MTV and other properties owned by its supposed new partners then its TV experiment could stand a legitimate chance at success.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372517151092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:45:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372517408381-21</Id><Topic><Title>Intel hints at getting cold feet over TV plan</Title><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372516160091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"So it turns out those that questioned the viability of Intel's proposed Web TV are in fact in agreement with Intel's CEO." [It's laughable that you got this out of the CEO saying that Intel needed to be careful. There's a huge difference between being careful and questioning the viability. Those who are intellectual honest would admit this...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372517408381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:50:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372517762499-22</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg: Intel nearing TV service deals with Time Warner, Viacom and NBC</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372517151092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:45:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One comment on the article: tkbrit69 Mar 26, 2013 lob apparently you dont understand what they are offering. You honestly think one of the most profitable american tech companies is going to invest billions on a whim? They have done, most likely more, market research then you would be able to read through in your lifetime regarding this. You are what? Some random person with a skewed opinion (shocking on the internet...i know) 1. Any TV you buy now, you are limited to app provided content. You dont need quad core arm lol. Your content isnt dependent on processing power, its dependent on graphics capability. Haswell + new atom is the answer here that intel will use. 7w consumption yet can do anything the average user will use + average gamer. The current atoms already match power consumption and performance for the most part. Wait until they release the new stuff ... 2. There is a HUGE market for a la carte channels. No one watches all 100 channels. Most people would pay for 6 channels individually. If you dont understand this...maybe you shouldnt comment on topics. There is no product or service on the market that does a la carte tv channels or a la carte tv shows. This is taking those 50 apps or websites you use to watch your content and combining it to ONE. Imagine netflix, hulu, HBOgo, ESPN + your specific channels you want to buy all combined. Makes life hell of a lot easier. Google next time before posting ;) It helps with your interwebs cred!</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372517762499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:56:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372518130731-23</Id><Title>CNET: For Microsoft, it's Haswell that ends well</Title><Msg>Intel's power-efficient Haswell chip could enable a range of devices with the battery life of Surface RT with the power and -- more importantly -- backward compatibility of the Surface Pro. More recently, faced with increasing competitive pressure from ARM, Intel has become even more fanatical about extending its processors' power efficiency. This has been dramatically proven by its latest Haswell processors found inside the new MacBook Air. In the 13-inch model, battery life has been extended from seven hours to 12 hours (some tests have found it to last longer), finally enabling a longstanding industry holy grail of all-day battery life in a sleek form factor. But while Apple clearly gains from these improvements, Microsoft and its partners may gain even more, at least on a relative basis, The promise of 10-plus hours on a screen of 10-plus inches enables an ultrathin notebook, tablet, or mutation running Windows to rival the running times of today's tablets while retaining backward compatibility. These PC industry stakeholders have been betting big that the PC can adapt to cover the range of usage scenarios that Apple's MacBook and iPad lines do, but in a single device. In other words, Haswell could enable something with the battery life of Surface RT with the power and -- more importantly -- backward compatibility of the Surface Pro.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372518130731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:02:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372518144308-24</Id><Title>GigOptix has a molecular computer with 500million layers ready in 2015</Title><Msg>36cubic inch small, transistors are hundreds times smaller than smallest silicon possible</Msg><Username>the_dudster_2014</Username><Timestamp>1372518144308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:02:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372518433504-25</Id><Title>Haswell chipset leading to some powerful, tiny PCs</Title><Msg>By all accounts, the new Intel Haswell processing chips are revolutionary. Their low power consumption and high performance are leading to the development of some new form factors in PCs, with increasingly tiny boxes able to drive increasingly more powerful programs. The latest entry in this realm is the D2308 from Giada Technology. The D2308 marries a fourth-generation Intel Haswell Core i7 CPU with the powerful Nvidia GTX650 GPU. Despite the small 9-inch-by-7-inch frame, and being only 2 inches thick, the new little system boasts some impressive power and features. The Giada D2308 is equipped with two SO-DIMM slots, which allows for the installation of up to 16G of DDR3-1333/1600 RAM with an additional 1G of VRAM onboard. The motherboard also features two Mini-PCIe slots that allow for the use of extra peripherals (1 x mSATA SSD; 1 x PCIe/USB). The 5.1 channel audio codec is based on the ALC662, and there is a Gigabit Ethernet port. The inside of the system allows for the installation of a 2.5-inch SATA drive. The D2308 supports Ultra HD 4Kx2K content with two HDMI outputs, and the unit comes with a Bluray/DVD player out front. Security is handed with a Trusted Platform Module (TPM), which allows for full data encryption. The Giada D2308 is equipped with a Wi-Fi and Bluetooth module to support IEEE 802.11 a/b/g/n and Bluetooth networks without the need to for an Ethernet port. And it does it using three wireless antennas for signal reception and a wireless maximum throughput speed of 450 megabits/sec. The new fourth-generation Intel Core processors feature a powerful DirectX 11 core, which is compatible with a wide range of today’s 3D applications and supports the majority of available data rendering technologies. HDMI and DVI ports with support for HDCP as well as an optional analog VGA interface are provided for video signal output. From gcn</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372518433504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:07:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372518549367-26</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell chipset leading to some powerful, tiny PCs</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372518433504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:07:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"By all accounts, the new Intel Haswell processing chips are revolutionary." Why is Wall Street always the last to know? D'oh - as Homer Simpson would say. The big Wall Street firm analysts make Homer look like a genius...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372518549367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372518562938-27</Id><Title>Samsung's Galaxy Tab 3 to hit store shelves on July 7.</Title><Msg>The 10 inch version will of course have Intel's Atom chip inside.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1372518562938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:09:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372519734439-28</Id><Title>Intel Warning?</Title><Msg>When do they normally warn in the earnings cycle? I would have guessed by end of Q2 for next earnings report.</Msg><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372519734439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:28:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372520292036-29</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Warning?</Title><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372519734439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:28:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would guess the same thing. A warning is wishful thinking on the short side...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372520292036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:38:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372520918121-30</Id><Topic><Title>Intel hints at getting cold feet over TV plan</Title><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372516160091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Caution and reluctance are the best way a buyer has to force sellers to lower their price.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1372520918121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:48:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372521315864-31</Id><Topic><Title>Intel hints at getting cold feet over TV plan</Title><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372516160091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said Wallis. "[It's laughable that you got this out of the CEO saying that Intel needed to be careful. There's a huge difference between being careful and questioning the viability. Those who are intellectual honest would admit this" I could not have said it better. Would a CEO about to make deals with multiple providers announce the deals before they are signed? Of course not. Before the fall is done, the deals will be announced and Intel TV will be launched.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372521315864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:55:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372521422164-32</Id><Topic><Title>Intel hints at getting cold feet over TV plan</Title><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372516160091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes indeed billy ray. Great point.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372521422164</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372521611412-33</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Warning?</Title><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372519734439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:28:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah..I just figured if there was a downside surprise it would come in this quarter. If we meet or beat I think its probably blue sky this year. I am a little concerned about new management...they are showing a lot of cards...aggressive marketeers...That sort of philosophy change for a great traditional company can precede a long-term decline.</Msg><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372521611412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:00:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372522901495-34</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Warning?</Title><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372519734439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:28:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This century, I can only find 5 warnings: For quarter ending Sep. 31, 2012, Intel issued a press release on Sep 7, 2012. For quarter ending Dec. 31, 2011, Intel issued a press release on Dec 12, 2011. Hard drive floods. For quarter ending Sep. 31, 2010, Intel issued a press release on Aug 27, 2010. iPad Apr 2010. For quarter ending Mar. 31, 2006, Intel issued a press release on Mar 3, 2006. For quarter ending Jun. 31, 2002, Intel issued a press release on Jun 7, 2002. Follows 9/11, Afghan War The Intel pattern seems to be to issue the press release 3 weeks before quarter end. Intel orders are weighted to the last month of the quarter. Internally, a company has early cutoff dates for submitting expense reports and purchase orders, .... I don't know when Intel closes their order books but it is even possible for them to close the books before the end of the calendar quarter. One week into the CALENDAR quarter, Intel has 25% CALENDAR visibility. for the last month. They also have visibility for any days they routinely close the books for. They have only warned early on revenue if they have a chance of missing the target revenue range. That is their key metric. For Q2/2013, they would have issued a press release in early June. At this point, Intel will issue their earnings. They still could miss, but that has never happened before. Intel could move down their FULL YEAR targets. All the negative analysts have been forecasting a lowered full year. IMO, at this point, the greatest Intel specific risk is a lowered full year. Intel will be affected by any market wide impacts. Even if Intel maintains their full year, the sell side analysts will say Intel is "delusional" and will do what they want.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372522901495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:21:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372523252571-35</Id><Title>Why Intel's Set-top box / Web TV service is important</Title><Msg>Search for the article "Motion Tennis brings Wii-style motion gaming to iOS, Apple TV". The Apple TV box is nothing more than a miniature set-top box. Apple is slowly but surely adding gaming to it. And you can also see from the developments of the Xbox One and the new PlayStation, that those game boxes have added set-box functionalities to their repertoire. The game-box and set-top box are merging into one device. The battleground in the living room is slowly emerging. Intel doesn't have presence in the set-top box/game box space. They need to be a player in that space (or risk missing out like with smartphones). Intel can try to sell a Ruku type device, but it would probably not sell very well. That is why they need to add the Web TV service along with the set-top box to differentiate from the rest.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372523252571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372524063088-36</Id><Topic><Title>Where oh where is coinmaker and his buddies</Title><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1372448844798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not time to play again yet , but soon</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372524063088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:41:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372524769337-37</Id><Topic><Title>What is up with this stock?</Title><Username>ultravis66</Username><Timestamp>1372446526385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's hugging the 50 day moving average which is on the cusp of support and resistance so it is acting like a gravitational point until the market decides which one it is going to be.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372524769337</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:52:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372525052288-38</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Warning?</Title><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372519734439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:28:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This century, I can only find 5 warnings:" [Five warnings in a century yet ApologyBoy issues about 100 warnings of warnings a year. This is the sorry state that the shills have descended into - resorting to techniques that have a .05 percent chance of success. Well, what else are they going to do? They don't have any traction issues. And short of a global economic meltdown, the shorts have no ability to construct an exit strategy. Stick a fork in the shorts. They're done... ]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372525052288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:57:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372525355254-39</Id><Topic><Title>Where oh where is coinmaker and his buddies</Title><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1372448844798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's not time to play again yet , but soon" [CoinBoy acts like a 2-year old and speaks like a 2-year old. He "plays" without realizing that everyone thinks he's a joke and not a player. The silliest of the fake ID personality creations to date...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372525355254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:02:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372527519733-40</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel will do custom ARM manufacturing for Apple ONLY IF they have a contractual agreement that they will rapidly taper off the ARM chips and move to Intel's. In half-life of 9 months? Intel has the upper hand here. Apple has no choice. Thanks to Barret, Ottelini, and Krzanich for making Intel's silicon process indisputably years ahead of others.</Msg><Username>butexcuseme</Username><Timestamp>1372527519733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:38:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372528666840-41</Id><Topic><Title>GigOptix has a molecular computer with 500million layers ready in 2015</Title><Username>the_dudster_2014</Username><Timestamp>1372518144308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:02:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also GigOptix has the most powerful wireless amplifier, 10gigabit/second &amp; faster in future, multimile range, Northrop Grumman is reselling, sampling q3 mass production q4, these wireless amps work at 90Gigahertz.</Msg><Username>the_dudster_2014</Username><Timestamp>1372528666840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:57:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372529006137-42</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Warning?</Title><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372519734439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:28:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting that none of the warnings was timely given the price peaks occurred at entirely different times, March 2000 $80.00, then 2004, $34.then October 2007, then 2010 Wally's famous $24., then March of last year, then, to be determined. the recent 26.00? interesting little article from Paul Farrell (98 percent chance of market crash in 2014). Will Waldo have an exit strategy?</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1372529006137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372529144578-43</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[You say this like it's a good thing when it is not. It's a clear sign that the ARM fabless model is totally broken. At 28nm there is really only one choice for ARM shops. One shop with insufficient capacity. It's okay by me. It just provides Intel with many new opportunities to take business away from the ARM ecosystem. This illustrates just one of the 16 reasons why ARM's fabrication is toast...] According to the new Intel CEO Intel is now part of the ARM Ecosystem. Intel is an ARM foundry. Intel IS part of the fabless semiconductor ecosystem now. So I guess the ARM fabless model is not so broken after all? Not that Intel has a choice. They need to fill their fabs and ARM is the only way to do it.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372529144578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:05:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372529359984-44</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"TSMC's 20nm will happen in late 2014 (maybe). They are still working on 28nm HPM." Wrong. 28nm HPM is shipping in volumes. And that has nothing to do with 20nm anyway. Your data is incorrect and your logic is flawed.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372529359984</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:09:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372529986512-45</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It would need to be a VERY strategic partner (ala Apple) for them to consider it." You are speaking out of turn here since you do not know this for a fact. This is your opinion so why not be clear on that? My opinion, Intel needs to fill their fabs and ARM is the only way for them to do it. In order for Intel to manufacture ARM based products they have to sign an ARM licensing agreement. It's coming, believe it, I will let you know when the ink is dry.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372529986512</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:19:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372530105682-46</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are other 28nm foundry processes in mass use although G-F's 28nm is gate-first and unlikely to be used at lower processes. The 28nm FD-SOI it offers via ST-Micro is also a pretty good process too as shown by the dual-core 3 GHz A9 demonstrated on it earlier this year. In conclusion TSMC is not the only foundry game in time but Intel's 14 and 10nm will weed out the weaklings and laggards in time as its mobile products clash with the foundry customers head-on on price. "We have chosen Globalfoundries as our strategic source partner of 28-nm HKMG because their state-of-the-art 28-nm HKMG process has allowed us to ramp our products with very high yields in a relatively short timeframe," said Chen Feng, vice president of Rockchip, in a statement issued by Globalfoundries.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372530105682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372530447257-47</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[How many design rules will TSMC need to achieve 14nm HALF-finfet?] [How much more will 14nm add to the already skyrocketing cost of 20nm?] I presented this at EDPS in March: 700 rules @ 90nm 800 rules @ 65nm 1,200 rules @ 40nm 1,900 rules @ 28nm 3,000 rules @ 20nm 3,400 rules @ 16nm TSMC design rules at 28nm and 20nm are much more restrictive than GF. NRE Cost of 16nm is equiv to 20nm.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372530447257</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:27:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372530502537-48</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Inte can and will fill its FABs without ARM, it just needs to convert the nm process mix in them and every two years it gets another go to change the formula. reutersDOTcom/article/2013/06/28/us-intel-ceo-idUSBRE95R0XK20130628 "If there was a great customer that we had a great relationship with laptops and other mobile devices, and they said look, we'd really love you to build our ARM-based product, we'd consider it. It depends on how strategic they are," Krzanich said.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372530502537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:28:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372531128242-49</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, 'strategic' was the CEO's exact words google reuters Intel's new CEO focused on mobile chips, cautious on TV</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372531128242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:38:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372531221096-50</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your desperation is palpable. Intel is saying they'll be happy to work with, say Apple starting with ARMH innards and then sunsetting them once the Intel innards provide a better solution. In short: This is good longterm for Intel as it gets them in the door and terrible longterm for ARMH as they'll eventually get shown the door.</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372531221096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372531470689-51</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Warning?</Title><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372519734439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:28:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What?? Long term decline? Give me a break.</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372531470689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:44:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372531978619-52</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I f t h e r e w a s a g r e a t c u s t o m e r t h a t w e h a d a g r e a t r e l a t i o n s h i p w i t h l a p t o p s a n d o t h e r m o b i l e d e v i c e s, a n d t h e y s a i d l o o k, w e ' d r e a l l y l o v e y o u t o b u i l d o u r A R M - b a s e d p r o d u c t, w e' d c o n s i d e r i t. I t d e p e n d s o n h o w s t r a t e g i c t h e y a r e," K r z a n i ch said.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372531978619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:52:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372531978689-53</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets not forget what Intel said when they first went into the foundry business. Google around and see. It went something like this: We are not going into the foundry business We will only do foundry work to promote Atom We will only foundry for strategic customers We will not manufacture ARM based designs We might manufacture ARM designs CEO's change, times change, messages change, and certainly customer demand changes...... Bottom line: Intel will do whatever it takes to fill their fabs. They have no choice. Intel is now part of the fabless semiconductor ecosystem. Just my opinion of course.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372531978689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:52:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372532128985-54</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Intel deal on phones coming. Apple has no choice.</Title><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1372434045281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Wrong. 28nm HPM is shipping in volumes. And that has nothing to do with 20nm anyway. Your data is incorrect and your logic is flawed." [This from the guy who represented that there weren't any delays or problems on TSMCs 28nm production... ]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372532128985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372532170134-55</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has enough of its own product to fill its FABs. If it has excess it will just convert old unused capacity to new technology as it is doing now to 14nm. ARM is not needed at all no matter how much you wish it to be,.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372532170134</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:56:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372532425742-56</Id><Topic><Title>TSMC and Apple Rumor</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372250086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 08:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"According to the new Intel CEO Intel is now part of the ARM Ecosystem. Intel is an ARM foundry. Intel IS part of the fabless semiconductor ecosystem now. So I guess the ARM fabless model is not so broken after all?" [You remind me of Baghdad Bob. Now instead of being the Minister of Propaganda for ARM/TSMC, you have now become the Minister of MisInformation. If you think Intel putting the ARM foundries out of business is an endorsement of the ARM fabless model, then two out of your three remaining brain cells have bit the dust...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372532425742</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:00:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372533024511-57</Id><Title>Is MarketWatch's Paul Farrell Patently Insane?</Title><Msg>One of the shills mentioned Paul Farrell - primarily because of his predictions of doom and gloom which shills cling to as the only hope to bail them out of disastrously bad judgments on Intel. So, Google the topic above for a laugh. If the shills are listening to this guy, then we know why they are so whacked. Here's more on Farrell from a Forbes article: Did Marketwatch Columnist Paul Farrell Incite Crime? "Marketwatch columnist and frothing madman, Paul Farrell, twisted in knots for having predicted a financial Armageddon this year that hasn’t happened, and won’t happen, now asks computer hackers to help salvage his prophecies. He wants computer hackers to commit felonies against Wall Street banks, cripple them, bring on financial chaos, and hopefully start the next civil war. Civil War. I’m not kidding. I’m not a First Amendment expert, but inciting crime and hoping for violence is a push. I hope Marketwatch is taking crazy Farrell seriously. Forget Farrell. Here are seven reasons to feel optimistic about the American economy:"</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372533024511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372533026362-58</Id><Title>Daniel Nenni (semiwiki) - I have reported you to Intel</Title><Msg>You are spreading lies. As a Intel investor, I am most disgusted. You call yourself a professional and yet you come on here and spread lies? Shame on you. What you are saying about Intel are legally actionable. I hope Intel sues you for all you have. You are truly pathetic.</Msg><Username>dianebouchard75</Username><Timestamp>1372533026362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372533268242-59</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel is now part of the fabless semiconductor ecosystem." [Just a minor correction, Baghdad Nenni: "Intel is now part of the END of the fabless semiconductor ecosystem." That's more than a little understated but it will do...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372533268242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:14:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372535171688-60</Id><Topic><Title>Is MarketWatch's Paul Farrell Patently Insane?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372533024511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:10:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTEL,is not and can never be and never cab be part of the :fabless: 'eco system'</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1372535171688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372536334223-61</Id><Topic><Title>Daniel Nenni (semiwiki) - I have reported you to Intel</Title><Username>dianebouchard75</Username><Timestamp>1372533026362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He needs to be reported to the authorities for driving a Porsche and wearing a Beau tie. He could blind someone on the road, OR they could start a 50 car pile up from laughing at him too hard. Just my opinion of course.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372536334223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 16:05:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372538158365-62</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"No, 'strategic' was the CEO's exact words" I know. I was just busting Ashraf for calling me disingenuous. He changed the CEO quote: "It would need to be a VERY strategic partner (ala Apple) for them to consider it." Looks a bit disingenuous to me. ;-)</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372538158365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 16:35:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372540575975-63</Id><Topic><Title>Intel to Become ARM Foundry!</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372512680796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 09:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>semiwiki, The fabs are filled now.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1372540575975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 17:16:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372542665540-64</Id><Title>In Consumer electronics its all about price. Thats why Intel will displace ARM in a few years.</Title><Msg>Intel can produce and sell their chips for less than anyone else on the planet. PERIOD. Even Allwinner and Mediatek will have a hard time keeping up with Intel because they have to first pay TSMC 60%+ margins on their 28nm ARM chips. Now Nenni will start his die size diatribe to try and argue that Intel's chips are more expensive. What the dude hasn't figured out yet, is that die size is only one of the variables that goes into cost. Yields, depreciation, volume and other factors go into cost.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1372542665540</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 17:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372543364549-65</Id><Title>Time to switch to nextgen molecular computer maker GigOptix, smallcap, ready in '15</Title><Msg>15 chemists busy in Washinton lab making pure blocks of the molecule</Msg><Username>the_dudster_2014</Username><Timestamp>1372543364549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 18:02:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372543499760-66</Id><Title>Y'all heard of molecular computer being the next big thing, GigOptix has it</Title><Msg>ready in 2015 Now you can invest in it,&amp; it's a smallcap Shares trade as GIG</Msg><Username>the_dudster_2014</Username><Timestamp>1372543499760</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 18:04:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372543604404-67</Id><Title>GigOptix has 36 cubic inch molecular computer that has 500million layers ready in '15</Title><Msg>GIG</Msg><Username>the_dudster_2014</Username><Timestamp>1372543604404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 18:06:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372544689859-68</Id><Topic><Title>Intel hints at getting cold feet over TV plan</Title><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372516160091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and all your aliases are delusional. All year the long the press releases have suggested Intel's Web TV service was imminent. Now at what is near the 11th hour Intel's CEO says they are "still evaluating the idea". "Still evaluating the idea" is and "cautious about moving ahead" are not the comments a CEO makes about a service they are committed to. This is a polite way of announcing Intel is seriously dialing back the plan and looking for an alternative strategy.</Msg><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372544689859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 18:24:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372546135907-69</Id><Topic><Title>Intel hints at getting cold feet over TV plan</Title><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1372516160091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Still evaluating the idea" is and "cautious about moving ahead" are not the comments a CEO makes about a service they are committed to. This is a polite way of announcing Intel is seriously dialing back the plan and looking for an alternative strategy." [These are your projections based on your bias. If you were correct they wouldn't be hiring support staff and we wouldn't be seeing articles in Bloomberg saying that Intel is close to having serious content commitments. ] [Your accusing me of using aliases is just more of the name calling you are resorting to because of your frustration. I don't use aliases and never will. If you have arguments then post them up. The attempted character assassination just makes you look like another shill...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372546135907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 18:48:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372546974448-70</Id><Title>Intel is T-Rex</Title><Msg>Dr. Ian Malcolm: Anybody hear that? It's a, um... It's an impact tremor, that's what it is... I'm fairly alarmed here. Dr. Alan Grant: T-Rex doesn't want to be fed. He wants to hunt. Can't just suppress 65 million years of gut instinct. -Jurassic Park, 1993</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1372546974448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 19:02:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372547206842-71</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is T-Rex</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1372546974448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 19:02:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC is looking for some fresh ARMH meat.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1372547206842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 19:06:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372547280586-72</Id><Topic><Title>Intel is T-Rex</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1372546974448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 19:02:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>short armhs</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372547280586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 19:08:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372548568806-73</Id><Topic><Title>CNET: For Microsoft, it's Haswell that ends well</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372518130731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:02:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do these journalists have any idea that Bay Trail exists?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1372548568806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 19:29:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372553992728-74</Id><Topic><Title>Daniel Nenni (semiwiki) - I have reported you to Intel</Title><Username>dianebouchard75</Username><Timestamp>1372533026362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm truly sorry my observations and opinions upset you. Yahoo has an ignore feature for just this reason. If you look on SemiWiki there are dozens of pro Intel articles by former Intel employees. Hundreds of Intel employees are registered users of SemiWiki. Traffic from the Intel domain to SemiWiki is in the top 10 according to Google analytics. Best of luck to you and your investments.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372553992728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 20:59:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372555118842-75</Id><Topic><Title>Daniel Nenni (semiwiki) - I have reported you to Intel</Title><Username>dianebouchard75</Username><Timestamp>1372533026362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>semiwiki, You are spreading FUD re: Intel's foundry deals. Insinuating that Intel isn't filling its own fabs with its own chips (and that it can't) is not based in reality (and inaccurate considering factory utilization was at healthy levels as of the last Q call). Also, it's quite clear that Intel isn't going to be a general purpose ARM SoC foundry, but would do so perhaps for the likes of Apple who buys plenty of Intel's main, high margin chips to begin with.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1372555118842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:18:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372556753619-76</Id><Topic><Title>Daniel Nenni (semiwiki) - I have reported you to Intel</Title><Username>dianebouchard75</Username><Timestamp>1372533026362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ashraf, I will reply to you on SemiWiki so I don't upset Diane. It will be up tomorrow at 5pm.</Msg><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1372556753619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:45:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372557480072-77</Id><Title>Will Nenni be able to gain back his loss on his ARMH investment?</Title><Msg>from ARMH above 50 to now 36 and change that's a big hill to climb, I think he has to take a loss and move on. I don't see ARMH getting there any time soon, INTC will eclipse ARMH at some point as early 2014 is my guess.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1372557480072</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:58:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372557991834-78</Id><Title>Yahoo msg and Semiwikki move Intel stock. LOL!!</Title><Msg>I can't believe the nonsense you guys are debating. If there are lies out there about the company, it sorts itself out and you get great buying opportunities; remember you got earnings next month. Investors are in it to make money and big money flows move the stock, not some message boards. A msg board over a period of a few minutes, hours, or days is nothing more than very short term noise, even if that! C'mon get serious.</Msg><Username>paul_speculator</Username><Timestamp>1372557991834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 22:06:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372558823841-79</Id><Topic><Title>Daniel Nenni (semiwiki) - I have reported you to Intel</Title><Username>dianebouchard75</Username><Timestamp>1372533026362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>semiwiki, I look forward to it. If you could construct a good argument for why Intel will need all of this outside help to fill its fabs, then I'm more than wiling to sit up and listen.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1372558823841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 22:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372559566180-80</Id><Title>wind of change</Title><Msg>" as Qualcomm consistently appears in many hedge funds’ top 10 holdings (joining names like AIG, Google, and eBay). Besides garnering the telecommunications player with bullish one-year price targets, analysts from the likes of Northland Securities, Raymond James, and Tigress Financial Partners have given Qualcomm bullish ratings since mid-March." ------------------------------------------------ already we see signs that this is going to change as the new player Intel appears on the stage</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1372559566180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 22:32:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372559796869-81</Id><Topic><Title>Daniel Nenni (semiwiki) - I have reported you to Intel</Title><Username>dianebouchard75</Username><Timestamp>1372533026362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Nenni is a man that's never amounted to anything, has nothing but some hack website and hates his life and only finds solace in creating chaos so he can gain the attention that nobody gives him.</Msg><Username>onemanshillshow</Username><Timestamp>1372559796869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 22:36:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372559853069-82</Id><Topic><Title>CNET: For Microsoft, it's Haswell that ends well</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372518130731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:02:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But while Apple clearly gains from these improvements, Microsoft and its partners may gain even more ------------------ Apple broke below 400$ again this week is not a good sign, investors fail to show confidence in Apple management recent moves</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1372559853069</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 22:37:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372562183701-83</Id><Topic><Title>Daniel Nenni (semiwiki) - I have reported you to Intel</Title><Username>dianebouchard75</Username><Timestamp>1372533026362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>semiwiki, it is so obvious that you are purposely spreading misinformation to the masses. You are now even trying to sell readership to your website. This tells me you are nothing more than a con man trying to get clicks to your website. Don't cop out of the discussion with "I will reply to you on SemiWiki so I don't upset Diane". Ashraf has provided you with known facts to refute your misinformation and now you are obviously copping out. Typical of a con man. If you have any good arguments for your claims, lets hear it here. I certainly won't be going to your website.</Msg><Username>dianebouchard75</Username><Timestamp>1372562183701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 23:16:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372562765545-84</Id><Topic><Title>Will Nenni be able to gain back his loss on his ARMH investment?</Title><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1372557480072</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:58:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[INTC will eclipse ARMH at some point as early 2014 is my guess.] Well, that could happen at Covello's $18. If INTC can't make $36 in 2014 then something is wrong.</Msg><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372562765545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 23:26:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372562819066-85</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo msg and Semiwikki move Intel stock. LOL!!</Title><Username>paul_speculator</Username><Timestamp>1372557991834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 22:06:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is like a saloon where little guys get to feel big.</Msg><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372562819066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 23:26:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372562939911-86</Id><Topic><Title>Y'all heard of molecular computer being the next big thing, GigOptix has it</Title><Username>the_dudster_2014</Username><Timestamp>1372543499760</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 18:04:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ever stop and think before you post? In any case, molecular computers have been around for a few billion years. They're called brains, and it might easier to train a pigeon than to build a molecular computer from the get go. Of course, reading your post it's clear molecular computers have a long way to go.</Msg><Username>orco_apocalypto</Username><Timestamp>1372562939911</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 23:28:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>