<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-05"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372997040245-1</Id><Title>Futures are up +191. Asia and Europe are up significantly two days now</Title><Msg>Which will we get to today? A reiterated upgrade or downgrade? No one believes INTC will miss earnings, this board has already shown that warnings (all five since 2000) come before the end of the quarter. Have the bear analysts covered their short positions? Is it time to make INTC a Wall Street darling once more and ride her to 30+ by end of year? We have less than two weeks before earnings and renewed guidance for the 2H 2013. Less than two weeks just for INTC, earnings season begins before July 17th. This means that shorts and analysts, who are aware of the technical superiority, have about one week to cover before it gets messy. Or, they can convince themselves that technical superiority, superior product, superior roadmap, and over 50 current design wins will not translate into higher EPS and EPS growth. On the other hand, denial is strong.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372997040245</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 00:04:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372997359420-2</Id><Topic><Title>Faster, more efficient than ARM</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372974073411</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seriously, Bay Trail has no competition!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372997359420</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 00:09:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372997769323-3</Id><Topic><Title>Apple just made a huge mistake by signing with TSMC</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372895929756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They may have signed with tsmc, but that doesn't mean they won't use Intel's chips. I expect Apple to use Bay Trail in one form or other when it comes out. There is a big price gap in between the iPad ($499) and MacBook Air ($999). Rumors of iPhones getting different screen sizes and price points, I expect a Merrifield-based iPhone when it comes out.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1372997769323</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 00:16:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373000433531-4</Id><Topic><Title>Futures are up +191. Asia and Europe are up significantly two days now</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1372997040245</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 00:04:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Up to the jobs report. A meet or beat will send us much higher...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373000433531</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 01:00:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373001152994-5</Id><Topic><Title>Two of them!</Title><Username>geraldomcginty</Username><Timestamp>1372941890233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 08:44:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will happen very quickly now!</Msg><Username>geraldomcginty</Username><Timestamp>1373001152994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 01:12:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373006593772-6</Id><Topic><Title>Two of them!</Title><Username>geraldomcginty</Username><Timestamp>1372941890233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 08:44:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not true. Does not make any sense. No supporting data. It has not happened the 50 times you have copy/pasted this "story". Copy/paste. Copy/paste. Copy/paste. Copy/paste. Copy/paste. No matter how many times you Copy/paste this fairy tail, it will not become more true.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1373006593772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 02:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373006831777-7</Id><Title>Nvidia sees limited shipments of Tegra 4</Title><Msg>Monica's words, not mine ..... NVDA seeing weak Tegra 4 shipments. Although Nvidia has successfully landed Tegra 4 orders from brand vendors such as Toshiba, Asustek Computer and Hewlett-Packard (HP) for their high-end products, because shipment volumes are still limited, sources from the upstream supply chain believe Nvidia may need to wait until the release of its next-generation Tegra 4i processor with integrated 4G LTE support to turn the tables Nvidia's Tegra 4 has advantages in terms of performance, but because of its high price, most brand vendors have turned to choose solutions from China-based makers or MediaTek, which offer strong performance/price ratios. Currently, the Tegra 4 is mainly focusing on mid-range and high-end markets. Toshiba has launched a Tegra 4-based tablet in Japan, using a 10.1-inch PixelPure LED touch panel with a resolution of 2560 by 1600. With an electromagnetic stylus and Bluetooth keyboard, the tablet is priced at JPY89,800 (US$899). HP is set to release a Tegra 4 tablet, the SlateBook x2 in the US in August, adopting a detachable keyboard design with a 10-inch 1920-by-1080 IPS touch panel, 2GB RAM/16GB ROM and support for microSD memory. The system is set to be priced at US$499. In addition to Android, HP also recently release a Tegra 4-based all-in-on PC, priced at US$399, featuring a 21.5-inch 1920-by-1080 touch panel. Meanwhile, Asustek is using the Tegra 4 for its latest Transformer Pad Infinity, which is priced at US$599.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1373006831777</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 02:47:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373009681616-8</Id><Topic><Title>Nvidia sees limited shipments of Tegra 4</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1373006831777</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 02:47:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NVidia's in trouble. Here's Daniel Charlton's commentary: "And the Tegra 4i - you know, the chip that was promised way back at CES 2011 - will be entering mass production some time in early 2014. And in devices some time in Q2 of 2014. That is, if NVIDIA can find anyone willing to buy one. They aren't having much like with the regular Tegra 4. Meanwhile, Qualcomm will be releasing whatever comes after the 800 at that point. So, concerns about the 4i vs. the 800 are about as relevant as concerns about the Snapdragon S4 vs the Exynos 4 Dual. But since NVIDIA acknowledges that the 4i will not even be as powerful as the 4, and early reports suggest that the 800 will outperform the 4, I still don't think the 800 will have trouble standing up against the 4i when it hits market 9 months later" and: "NVIDIA hasn't been able to get Icera modem production up and running. This is why they announced all the details of what came to be the 4i (at the time just calling it project grey) way back at CES 2012 and then failed to deliver the chip that year. They will fail again to put it to market this year. Just like they failed to hit their Q4 2012 release timeframe for the 4." [By the time 4i comes out, it will face not just the 800, but will face Intel's Merrifield, which will have the same kind of advantage for smartphones as we are seeing Bay Trail for tablets]</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1373009681616</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 03:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373010694059-9</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS GOING ON?????</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368550155862</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:49:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YTGV</Msg><Username>adampenske</Username><Timestamp>1373010694059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 03:51:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373013333523-10</Id><Topic><Title>Apple just made a huge mistake by signing with TSMC</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372895929756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing to watch out for is if Apple sticks with the 40nm node from TSMC. And if it's truly a year out then the next node Apple may want from TSMC may be 28nm. I have faith that by next year TSMC can finally make 28nm in sizable enough yields to satisfy Apple. ---- Apple is currently using Samsung's 32nm node, and there is no way they can go 'back' to 40nm. There was talk of the A5 in the latest version of Apple TV being the first (Samsung) 28nm part, but it looks like this is still 32nm, but a complete redesign which resulted in a smaller die. TSMC doesn't have (general) yield issues on the LP 28nm node, the biggest issue is capacity. I doubt Apple will use TSMC for 28nm. My bet, you'll see this years Apples A* processors staying with Samsung, but dropping to 28nm. As for , "iPhone will feel a bit sluggish compared to Intel based Android phones". Apple has a huge advantage in that their environment is native. Basically you are talking native code V Java so Apple could be quite far back on (real) CPU performance but the app will still perform better on their platform (Android's Java stack is poor) . Also, Apples GPU's are far ahead of anyone else which is a big driver for the fluid UI.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1373013333523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 04:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373022217061-11</Id><Title>We're going to see some crazy, low-volume movement today.</Title><Msg>All the analysts and big traders are at the beach. Asia had two spectacular days the the Jobs Report comes out. ECB holds rate steady. Futures are up. Europe is down. Gold is down, crude is up for the week. European bonds are a mixed bag. Just watch CNBC and Bloomberg talking heads throw their hands up and say, #$%$!" And of course, bashers and pumpers will come in after the fact, and with 20/20 hindsight say, "I told you so." I will go on record: (Easy call part) Today and next week will be volatile as shorts finally give in to an avalanche of data from multiple sources regarding INTC technical superiority. Big money will push. Put and Call options will go nuts to put floors and insurance on purchases. INTC will finish next week above $25.50 (Hard call part) Who wants odds?</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1373022217061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 07:03:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373023918485-12</Id><Topic><Title>Walliswaver made to look like a total dweeb.......yet again</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1372988104376</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can say TI 1,000 times straight for all I care as I've never owned it in my life. You are chasing your tail. I'm not Lucy, I'm a happy long term investor that sees you for the twit that he is. You gonna Do you teach your kids that God is "stupid"? Guys like you are the problem. Brain-dead adults raising future brain-dead adults.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1373023918485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 07:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373024083745-13</Id><Title>Hey Intel Fanboy aka LTI Steve...</Title><Msg>do your kids know of Daddy's mischief on the internet? I bet they'd be proud.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1373024083745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 07:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373027708664-14</Id><Title>Job Report Numbers:</Title><Msg>Released On 7/5/2013 8:30:00 AM For Jun, 2013 Prior Prior Revised Consensus Consensus Range Actual Nonfarm Payrolls - M/M change 175,000 195,000 161,000 145,000 to 200,000 195,000 Unemployment Rate - Level 7.6 % 7.5 % 7.4 % to 7.6 % 7.6 % Average Hourly Earnings - M/M change 0.0 % 0.1 % 0.2 % 0.1 % to 0.3 % 0.4 % Av Workweek - All Employees 34.5 hrs 34.5 hrs 34.4 hrs to 34.6 hrs 34.5 hrs Private Payrolls - M/M change 178,000 207,000 175,000 150,000 to 200,000 202,000 INTC is going old school Q3 and Q4.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1373027708664</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 08:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373028976129-15</Id><Title>Intel’s Justin Rattner on New Laser Chip Business</Title><Msg>technologyreviewDotcom/news/516311/intels-justin-rattner-on-new-laser-chip-business . . . . It’s a 100-gigabit-per-second transceiver [a device that sends data between computers along an optical fiber]. We use conventional CMOS [chip] fabrication techniques to actually build the lasers into the chip. We showed a 50-gigabit-per-second link a few years ago that was built in the lab (see “Computing at the Speed of Light”); the current chip can do 100 gigabits per second, but the connector, which we teamed up with Corning to build, has the ability to go to 1.6 terabits per second. In the data center—[meaning] more bandwidth at much lower cost, and what looks like a big win on the energy-efficiency side. The data center guys love all this capacity but with cables that are teeny-tiny. Right now most data centers are running at 10 gigabits per second; a few people have deployed 40 gigabits per second. People at Facebook [have] begun to think about other applications for silicon photonics [inside server] racks. . . . .</Msg><Username>jctailman</Username><Timestamp>1373028976129</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 08:56:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373032145108-16</Id><Title>Buy NDLS now</Title><Msg>easy double</Msg><Username>drhollars</Username><Timestamp>1373032145108</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:49:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373032231441-17</Id><Title>It won't sustain these prices</Title><Msg>Can't even hold 24. Pathetic.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1373032231441</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:50:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373033203616-18</Id><Title>Should be red soon...</Title><Msg>Lagging again</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1373033203616</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373033373031-19</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will see 18 before it sees 22 again</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1365430004086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 10:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Worst call ever.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1373033373031</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:09:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373033869230-20</Id><Title>NDLS seems going to $100</Title><Msg>in few days</Msg><Username>drhollars</Username><Timestamp>1373033869230</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373034125921-21</Id><Title>Red and lagging</Title><Msg>Par usual for this filthy stock.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1373034125921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:22:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373034234061-22</Id><Topic><Title>Filth Falls on Friday</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1372874252130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:57:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They got you buying again didn't they? Now you are stuck with that high 23 and those of you who bought all the way up to 30 will not see that price again for years.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1373034234061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:23:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373034598467-23</Id><Topic><Title>Apple iWatch Rumors: Release Date Expected In Late 2013 As Trademark Gets Filed In Japan</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372726449484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 20:54:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>iWatch will be big seller</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1373034598467</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:29:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373034604790-24</Id><Topic><Title>ANALysts really have it wrong</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372731133141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 22:12:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good points..Intel will easily make their target for the year</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1373034604790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:30:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373034609648-25</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Bay Trail benchmark appears online, crushes fastest Snapdragon ARM SoC by 30%</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372852272552</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 07:51:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bay Trail has no competition!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1373034609648</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:30:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373034618841-26</Id><Topic><Title>First Intel Bay Trail benchmark score appears online, squashes ARM scores like an insignificant bug</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372858269116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>arm is an insignificant bug haha</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1373034618841</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:30:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373034624974-27</Id><Topic><Title>'Lenovo K900 has been a top 5 selling device in the Chinese smart-phone market '</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372871982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>smartphones will add significant revenue this year. Next Year will be year of the smartphone for Intel with Merrifield. Revenue will go parabolic</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1373034624974</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:30:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373034634019-28</Id><Topic><Title>Olivetti Olipad W808, W809 and W810: Windows 8.1 tablet with Intel Bay Trail in October</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372974586947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:49:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>these are teasers...wait until the big boys announce...Samsung, Lenovo, Asus, Acer, Sony, Dell, HP, Microsoft....My bet is Apple will announce a product based on Bay Trail too...there's a price gap between iPad ($499) and MacBook Air ($999)</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1373034634019</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:30:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373034640016-29</Id><Topic><Title>Faster, more efficient than ARM</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372974073411</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seriously, Bay Trail has no competition!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1373034640016</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:30:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373034657241-30</Id><Topic><Title>Apple just made a huge mistake by signing with TSMC</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372895929756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They may have signed with tsmc, but that doesn't mean they won't use Intel's chips. I expect Apple to use Bay Trail in one form or other when it comes out. There is a big price gap in between the iPad ($499) and MacBook Air ($999). Rumors of iPhones getting different screen sizes and price points, I expect a Merrifield-based iPhone when it comes out</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1373034657241</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:30:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373034702779-31</Id><Title>WILL END OVER $24 TODAY</Title><Msg>COVER UP NOW SHORTIES HAHAHA</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1373034702779</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373035251966-32</Id><Title>THIS IS WHY SAMSUNG GOING WITH INTEL</Title><Msg>the Exynos 5 Octa, the chip may not be all it’s cracked up to be. by justfine790 • Jun 2, 2013 11:56 AM From the Android Authority; The Exynos 5 Octa and the State of Samsung SoCs by Daniel Charlton "All of this leads up to the Exynos 5 Octa and the Galaxy S4. The Octa is used in the GT-I9500 variant of the Galaxy S4 and is supposed to solve the problem of Cortex-A15 power consumption by using ARM’s big.LITTLE architecture. big.LITTLE allows the use of two core clusters, one for high-performance tasks and one for low-performance tasks. In the Octa, this is a quad-core Cortex-A15 cluster and a quad-core Cortex-A7 cluster, all built on 28nm. In big.LITTLE, there are supposed to be three modes for managing threads across all of the cores in both clusters. Evidence thus far suggests that the Octa really only supports one of these modes – the least efficient. Even worse, it appears that this limitation is due to crippled hardware in the SoC and not something that can be fixed in software" "According to Samsung, there is no hardware problem at all and the company chose cluster-migration because it “show[s] increased performance/efficiency.” But the statement does not match up with most people’s understanding of ARM’s big.LITTLE architecture. Moreover, ARM demonstrated core-migration working on a pre-release version of the Octa. And Samsung’s released kernel source code for the Octa includes the drivers for core-migration. But that code does not work in the final release version of the Octa and Samsung has been coy in giving a straight answer. Based on this, Linus Torvalds wrote:“quite frankly, the fact that the Exynos 5 currently only works in ‘either or’ configuration almost certainly means that there is something fundamentally wrong with the hardware design, to the point where no amount of ‘complex patches’ can fix it.” While this certainly makes it seem that Samsung has done something wrong in the Octa, the chip is still entirely based on desigfrom ARM."</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1373035251966</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373035451073-33</Id><Topic><Title>Apple just made a huge mistake by signing with TSMC</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372895929756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The odds are that Apple is smarter than you. Even though Intel's processors are faster, other considerations may be at play. LIke price/performance, programming ease, legacy systems, etc.. I'm disappointed like everyone on this board, but I don't go crazy. Sure ARM stock price is going down, but that doesn't mean that Intel's is going up. Wait for earnings and the conference call. Then we'll have a better idea of what's what.</Msg><Username>angstromatic</Username><Timestamp>1373035451073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:44:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373035870534-34</Id><Topic><Title>Apple just made a huge mistake by signing with TSMC</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372895929756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, Wally is the smartest person in the world. after all he's been holding INTC since it was 24 3 years ago and has made a fortune over the last 3 years.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1373035870534</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:51:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373036106672-35</Id><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Msg>Today is yet another example of Wall Street being able to manipulate and sit on the Intel stock price with the extensive use of downgrades, lowered price targets, opinion pieces, money and leverage. Come earnings this is going to disappear. I believe that earnings will bring significant and overwhelmingly positive news. Why do I think this? Well, for the simple reason that we already know about most of this news: Intel Silvermont: Huge success Haswell: Huge success Bay Trail: Huge success FinFet: Huge success with 14nm volume procduction just around the corner Airmont: A total game changer that is not that far off Tablets and new form factors: Tablet sales are doubling each quarter Smartphones: Growth is beginning to accelerate Dual Boot: Another huge advantage in the marketplace XP Replacement Wave: Should accelerate into the second half Growing relationship with Samsung Significant Mac refresh will drive sales Smartwatch release due by the end of the year ARM Major drop in the stock price due to looming competition with Intel Damaged and uncertain roadmap: Arrival of 20nm in volume quantities is unknown 20nm is planar with limited performance increases and damaged economics ARM FinFET is a half-step and may never come to market due to the immense complexity Shrinking margins and profits RT failure to launch No success in addressing the server markets No dual boot Conclusion: It's clear what has happened, what is happening and what will happen. Earnings will provide the granular information necessary to drive a stake through the heart of Wall Street's denial...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373036654217-36</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will see 18 before it sees 22 again</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1365430004086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 10:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You wish!!!</Msg><Username>northvisitor34</Username><Timestamp>1373036654217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:04:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373036717877-37</Id><Title>Intel headed up</Title><Msg>Surprised coinmaker isn't frantically driveling out his dog and pony show. Have printed out his vast array of comments to load onto my toilet paper dispenser.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1373036717877</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:05:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373036859887-38</Id><Topic><Title>Apple just made a huge mistake by signing with TSMC</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372895929756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, there are three things that most people are ignoring when it comes to the potential of Apple making a major move to Intel: 1.) The market is changing rapidly, especially with Intel. The speed with which Intel is moving has probably caused Apple to have to totally reconsider its roadmap going forward. I think the Altera switch was really their wake-up call and that wasn't very long ago. It takes a huge amount of work to consider a change and project out the effects. 2.) It takes a very long time to engineer a change once a decision is made- literally years for a move to x86 from ARM. I don't think Intel is going to make ARM chips for the simple reason that they don't need to. They will fill their capacity without Apple. Intel is in the driver's seat because of the clear superiority of their technology and manufacturing. 3.) Even if Apple had made the decision to change, they wouldn't tell anyone until they absolutely had to. We have known for a long time that 14nm was the sweet spot for Apple to make a change. That would mean late 2014 or more likely 2015 for the change. If that were the case, no one would know yet and Apple would still be a very long way from any announcement. Bottom line: We still don't really know anything about where the Intel-Apple relationship is going except in the short-term. I think the iWatch will be an exception. We should find out if that is an Intel deal in 3-6 months...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036859887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:07:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373037024447-39</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Denial is strong. It's kept P/E under 13 and the stock under 30 for a decade. It's going to take a huge upside surprise to change everyone's mind quickly. Realistically, INTC will have to crush the high estimate of 0.42 if we are changing any minds, quickly. We need mid-0.50s. It's a "show me the money" quarter.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1373037024447</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373037416111-40</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Practically everything (excpet Haswell) you have cited on the INTC side will have no impact on Q2 earnings. So a realistic expectation is... a negative reaction to the Q2 numbers. Only a major, unknown, catalyst reveal will propel the stock from here and overcome the numbers (probably in-line). Full dislosure: I have a large bullish options position (in the black) and think my best move would be to liquidate next week.</Msg><Username>mrekrek1</Username><Timestamp>1373037416111</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:16:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373037454973-41</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's a "show me the money" quarter." [A bit early for showing the money but instead I believe that Intel will show Wall Street the guidance and the future. And I think it's going to be pretty clear. There was no huge individual event that sent the ARM stock price down by 14 bucks and I don't think one is required to send Intel's stock price up by 14 bucks. Just the palpable proof that the tipping point has been reached. I think the Bay Trail performance metrics were that proof...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373037454973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373037613912-42</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As long as I would love to see it, I don't think this is the quarter. Windows 8 has screwed the pouch for Intel .It's going to take a few large wins in phones with new capacity coming on line. In the meantime, this is the year that you tell your friends to buy Intel while it's still cheap.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1373037613912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:20:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373037938552-43</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Practically everything (excpet Haswell) you have cited on the INTC side will have no impact on Q2 earnings. So a realistic expectation is... a negative reaction to the Q2 numbers. Only a major, unknown, catalyst reveal will propel the stock from here and overcome the numbers (probably in-line)." [This is realistic only if Wall Street ignores guidance and the impact that everything I have cited will have on guidance. Again, we only need the palpable proof that the tipping point has been reached. I think the Bay Trail performance metrics were that proof. If you have 2014 calls I can't see why you would be particularly worried about this earnings announcement...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373037938552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:25:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373038070875-44</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope you're right. But any large movement in guidance without a huge design win (Google, Apple, more Samsung), or multiple small wins, will be seen as delusional. INTC will have to prove a huge, full pipeline to move big without higher-than-expected EPS. Although, with everyone #$%$ on this stock, a small win could change sentiment. It could be the #$%$ moment we're waiting for. Either way, we need a significant surprise up, not the two/three cents everyone will be expecting.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1373038070875</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373038112118-45</Id><Topic><Title>Apple just made a huge mistake by signing with TSMC</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372895929756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Blue, Yes, that was exactly what I was thinking but you are a bit more developed in your analysis. Anyway, that argument reminds me of the days when Apple said it's RISC processor was twice as fast as Intel's X86. It turned out it was maybe 15 to 30 percent faster at the same speed, but a 1.5ghz Mac wasn't comparable to a 3ghz Intel processor. I think Apple will once again jump to Intel not so much on speed issues but their upgrade cycle being once again faster than RISC. But as we saw before it took years to make this jump. If Intel makes the A line of processors this would speed up the transition. Intel and Apple always come up with good stuff when they work together such as Thunderbolt 2. Can you imagine what tweaks they could put on the A line of processors?</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1373038112118</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:28:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373038208950-46</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street says they support our VETS , but it sure doesn't look like it, Letting Congress furlough our DOD VETS the week after the 4</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1372791664788</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 15:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DOD VETS and all VETS move your IRA, 401k's and TSP to CASH send Wall Street and Congress a message that's its wrong to treat our DOD VETS and there Families that way, furloughed the week after the 4th of July is just wrong.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1373038208950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:30:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373038711245-47</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gee, Wally saw all kinds of downgrades, lowered price targets, and opinion pieces today. never fear, pc's are selling like hot cakes at a Sunday church breakfast meeting.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1373038711245</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:38:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373038722816-48</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"As long as I would love to see it, I don't think this is the quarter. Windows 8 has screwed the pouch for Intel .It's going to take a few large wins in phones with new capacity coming on line. In the meantime, this is the year that you tell your friends to buy Intel while it's still cheap." [Windows 8.1 is another reason why guidance should significantly improve. Windows 8 and tablets go hand-in-hand. That's why the Bay Trail metrics are so important. This is going to be the year of the Intel tablet and it's a big market. Major growth in smartphones won't likely come until next year although there will be incremental progress. Let us not forget that Wall has arbitrarily and capriciously shaved 2 or 3 bucks off the stock price while ARM was dropping by 14 bucks. We should have been up by 3 bucks. So just meeting expectations on earnings should merit a 5 buck increase in the stock price. We need to see the recognition of the tipping point in the P/E ratio more so than in earnings. That's what the ARM drop told us. ARM's dropping P/E ratio should have been Intel's gain. This focus on earnings in the upcoming earnings date is absolutely the wrong focus. The focus should be on Intel getting a fair P/E ratio. It should be on guidance and it should be on the future. The tipping point has been reached and the ARM era is over. Let's see Wall Street come out of denial and give Intel it's due - a significantly higher P/E ratio that accurately reflects the future... ]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373038722816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:38:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373038822419-49</Id><Title>DOD VETS and families furloughed the week after the 4th of JULY is wrong, just wrong. Sent Wall Street and Congress</Title><Msg>a message that it is wrong , MOVE to CASH . Wall Street has not said anything that it's wrong and Congress should NO BETTER, but looks like we have to tell them it's wrong. All DOD VETS move your TSP to G fund and other VETS move your IRA's and 401K's to cash, Support our DOD VETS and there families by sending a message to Wall Street and Congress that its wrong to furlough them the week after the 4th of July</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1373038822419</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:40:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373038979847-50</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Palpable proof is not performance metrics. It is an increase in the Top Line. I do have Jan 2014 options.</Msg><Username>mrekrek1</Username><Timestamp>1373038979847</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373039220870-51</Id><Topic><Title>Intel headed up</Title><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1373036717877</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:05:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Surprised coinmaker isn't frantically driveling out his dog and pony show. Have printed out his vast array of comments to load onto my toilet paper dispenser." [The Used Toilet Paper Coalition has issued a statement saying any association with Mr. Coinmaker would degrade the reputation of their product...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373039220870</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:47:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373039322039-52</Id><Topic><Title>DOD VETS and families furloughed the week after the 4th of JULY is wrong, just wrong. Sent Wall Street and Congress</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1373038822419</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:40:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you not support our DOD VETS and there families CONGRESS and Wall Street, Just slap them in the face furloughing them the week after the 4th of July.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1373039322039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:48:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373039565840-53</Id><Topic><Title>DOD VETS and families furloughed the week after the 4th of JULY is wrong, just wrong. Sent Wall Street and Congress</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1373038822419</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:40:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We all know that Wall Street runs Congress</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1373039565840</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:52:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373039756887-54</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Palpable proof is not performance metrics. It is an increase in the Top Line." [I don't agree. It's an excessive and unnecessary benchmark said to be needed because the braindead on Wall Street will refuse anything less. The drop in ARM's stock price indicates that the new world order is being recognized. Wall Street can't have it both ways. I'm going to hold my 2014 options. Even if I'm wrong we still have a lot of time for Wall Street to get the idea pounded into them. Q1 was the real risk period. It's hard for me to believe that you held through that level of risk and want to blow out for Q2. The level of risk is substantially reduced from Q1. Silvermont and Haswell accomplished that. The Bay Trail performance metrics are icing on the cake...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373039756887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:55:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373039979430-55</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would agree with you, WW if QCOM also dropped 30%. Until then, I want to see the top line and bottom line growth. Don't get me wrong, the future and guidance are important, but if we want 30 by the end of the year we need sales, not possible sales... even if the new TAM is 2.35 billion screens. We have over 10 years of momentum to overcome.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1373039979430</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373040049694-56</Id><Title>Shill Misdirection</Title><Msg>Wow, who knew that the shills cared about veterans or were patriotic? For years they have bashed one of America's best companies while working daily to try to damage the US economy. And now they are wrapping themselves in the flag in order to divert attention from Intel's success. Such hypocrisy takes my breath away...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373040049694</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:00:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373040325560-57</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree Q1 was the real "business" risk period. However this position was taken in the low $20 range during Q1. The real "investment" risk period is now.</Msg><Username>mrekrek1</Username><Timestamp>1373040325560</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:05:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373040327674-58</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just because we won't see a full quarter of the Haswell effect in Q2 doesn't mean we shouldn't be able to quantify it. Or at least Intel should be able to quantify it. That's what I'm looking forward to come earnings. That granularity projected out for the rest of the year. I'll be quite content with an increase in full-year guidance. In my mind that clearly would justify a 5 buck move up in the stock price...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373040327674</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:05:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373040515524-59</Id><Topic><Title>DOD VETS and families furloughed the week after the 4th of JULY is wrong, just wrong. Sent Wall Street and Congress</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1373038822419</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:40:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What don't you like Congress, Wall Street or supporting our DOD VETS</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1373040515524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:08:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373040587720-60</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I agree Q1 was the real "business" risk period. However this position was taken in the low $20 range during Q1. The real "investment" risk period is now." [No, the investment risk was the 2-3 bucks we just lost due to Wall Street BS and manipulation. But I understand your point. If you want to drop out, be my guest. I don't make decisions based on what I think Wall Street might be able to do with its manipulation of the market. If you can make that work for you then you have skills I don't possess...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373040587720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:09:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373040802086-61</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think we're all saying the same thing, just with different weights on each variable. Either way, I hope Paul O. dumped as much as he could in Q1 and Q2 comes out clean, with a clear, quantifiable 2H guidance.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1373040802086</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373040957443-62</Id><Topic><Title>DOD VETS and families furloughed the week after the 4th of JULY is wrong, just wrong. Sent Wall Street and Congress</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1373038822419</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:40:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What don't you like Congress, Wall Street or supporting our DOD VETS" [Dana, what I don't like is the totally fake outrage coupled with volume garbage posting. You hate Intel and the US economy because you would be happy to see the US economy go down if it takes Intel with it. Your ability to find new levels of dishonesty to push your psychological dysfunction make me want to blow chunks. That you would use a Veteran's issue in your misdirection campaign means that you have sunk to a new low even for you. Dude, get some help. You're a sick man...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373040957443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373041178064-63</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I think we're all saying the same thing, just with different weights on each variable. Either way, I hope Paul O. dumped as much as he could in Q1 and Q2 comes out clean, with a clear, quantifiable 2H guidance." [Yep, I'm in total agreement with that.] [Honest debate is a good thing. Too bad that the loyal opposition doesn't believe in it. Or isn't capable of it...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373041178064</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:19:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373041387172-64</Id><Title>Amazing</Title><Msg>Amazing that the doom and gloom crowd was able to sit on the market for so long given the good jobs report...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373041387172</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373042900177-65</Id><Topic><Title>DOD VETS and families furloughed the week after the 4th of JULY is wrong, just wrong. Sent Wall Street and Congress</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1373038822419</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:40:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am almost 90% cash working to 100 % cash to support our DOD VETs and there families</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1373042900177</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373043306680-66</Id><Topic><Title>DOD VETS and families furloughed the week after the 4th of JULY is wrong, just wrong. Sent Wall Street and Congress</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1373038822419</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:40:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I am almost 90% cash working to 100 % cash to support our DOD VETs and there families" [Why do you persist in this stupidity? No one is buying it. It just makes you look more and more like you have had a psychotic break with reality. It's time to retire the Coinmaker character along with all of the rest of your fake IDs...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373043306680</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373044062299-67</Id><Topic><Title>DOD VETS and families furloughed the week after the 4th of JULY is wrong, just wrong. Sent Wall Street and Congress</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1373038822419</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:40:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still selling and moving to CASH to support our DOD VETS and there families</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1373044062299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:07:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373044658868-68</Id><Title>Buy a flash kit maker now, Seagate... good ones will be gone soon</Title><Msg>Interesting article on flash storage from the Register. Excerpt: Blocks and Files With Western Digital buying sTec and SanDisk buying SMART Storage Systems, Seagate is looking like the last player standing in the game of flash musical chairs. These days, a lot of serious storage suppliers are keen to get into enterprise flash storage devices - meaning component devices and not complete arrays such as those supplied by Nimbus Data, Pure Storage, Violin Memory and Whiptail. There are basically three NAND storage device form factors: SSDs using Fibre Channel; SAS and SATA interfaces; and PCIe interface cards. In very broad strokes, the current state of the main enterprise SSD and PCIe players and wannabe players is this:</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373044658868</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:17:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373044695556-69</Id><Topic><Title>We're going to see some crazy, low-volume movement today.</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1373022217061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 07:03:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did someone say "We're going to see some crazy, low-volume movement today?" We may finish at 24+. Monday will be a huge volume day.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1373044695556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:18:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373045025164-70</Id><Topic><Title>Buy a flash kit maker now, Seagate... good ones will be gone soon</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373044658868</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:17:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SSD is a stop-gap measure until PCIe. When boot to PCIe becomes more common, SSDs will go the way of the CD, and quickly.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1373045025164</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:23:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373048450403-71</Id><Title>CSCO and INTC</Title><Msg>What ever happened to the rumor of INTC fabbing CSCO chips?</Msg><Username>m00nsh1ner</Username><Timestamp>1373048450403</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 14:20:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373048604858-72</Id><Title>Mr Weaver will win today against the Analysts, as his pumps are working</Title><Msg>Next week is another story, as a couple of Analysts could come out and play.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1373048604858</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 14:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373052784368-73</Id><Topic><Title>Apple iWatch Rumors: Release Date Expected In Late 2013 As Trademark Gets Filed In Japan</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372726449484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 20:54:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>carpetbumper</Username><Timestamp>1373052784368</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:33:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373052793254-74</Id><Topic><Title>ANALysts really have it wrong</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1372731133141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 22:12:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpbump</Msg><Username>carpetbumper</Username><Timestamp>1373052793254</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373052801415-75</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Bay Trail benchmark appears online, crushes fastest Snapdragon ARM SoC by 30%</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372852272552</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 07:51:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpbumpbump</Msg><Username>carpetbumper</Username><Timestamp>1373052801415</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373052808110-76</Id><Topic><Title>First Intel Bay Trail benchmark score appears online, squashes ARM scores like an insignificant bug</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372858269116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:31:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpbumpbumpbump</Msg><Username>carpetbumper</Username><Timestamp>1373052808110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373052820999-77</Id><Topic><Title>'Lenovo K900 has been a top 5 selling device in the Chinese smart-phone market '</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1372871982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpbumpbumpbumpbump</Msg><Username>carpetbumper</Username><Timestamp>1373052820999</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:33:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373052829101-78</Id><Topic><Title>Olivetti Olipad W808, W809 and W810: Windows 8.1 tablet with Intel Bay Trail in October</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1372974586947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:49:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpbumpbumpbumpbumpbump</Msg><Username>carpetbumper</Username><Timestamp>1373052829101</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:33:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373053346205-79</Id><Title>Apple is rated "AVOID " Intel gets its commupance as Apple "AVOIDS" IT</Title><Msg>Intl NEVER delivers on its promises. A disappointment for us shareholders. I just want to get back even and then I will "AVOID" this dog.</Msg><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1373053346205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373053626278-80</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P UPGRADES OPINION ON SHARES OF INTEL TO BUY FROM HOLD</Title><Username>jctailman</Username><Timestamp>1372861108408</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:18:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>carpetbumper</Username><Timestamp>1373053626278</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:47:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373054253170-81</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P UPGRADES OPINION ON SHARES OF INTEL TO BUY FROM HOLD</Title><Username>jctailman</Username><Timestamp>1372861108408</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:18:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wel good then give me my 28 a share and I'm history JACK!</Msg><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1373054253170</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:57:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373054315937-82</Id><Topic><Title>Intel’s Justin Rattner on New Laser Chip Business</Title><Username>jctailman</Username><Timestamp>1373028976129</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 08:56:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpbump</Msg><Username>carpetbumper</Username><Timestamp>1373054315937</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:58:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373057037480-83</Id><Topic><Title>Apple is rated "AVOID " Intel gets its commupance as Apple "AVOIDS" IT</Title><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1373053346205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:42:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$40 is a quite a climb from here Nuff. You are understandably bitter being down that much. Those margin calls have gotta be a killer dufus.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1373057037480</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 16:43:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373057170850-84</Id><Topic><Title>Apple is rated "AVOID " Intel gets its commupance as Apple "AVOIDS" IT</Title><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1373053346205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:42:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you feel that way, you should sell, short, buy puts and take that action now. One of the worst investment strategies is to wait for a stock you view as a DOG, to "come back" while you could be making TONS of money on other stocks. You should find your courage to take your losses and move on to something that will perform better, recoup your losses and allow you to sleep better. If you have a big loss, I would not want to follow your advice and then follow in your footsteps. If you have a small loss, then what's the big deal? Sell and move on. Alternatively, you sell call options on your position, (assuming more than 100 shares) and generate some extra income while you are waiting. BTW, You don't speak for "us shareholders". Many of "us shareholders" have a profitable position and are quite happy.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1373057170850</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 16:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373057467988-85</Id><Topic><Title>Apple just made a huge mistake by signing with TSMC</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1372895929756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe Cook shorted Intel with off shore un-named accounts. He wants Apple down to 2.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey72</Username><Timestamp>1373057467988</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 16:51:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373057868399-86</Id><Topic><Title>Apple is rated "AVOID " Intel gets its commupance as Apple "AVOIDS" IT</Title><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1373053346205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:42:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intl NEVER delivers on its promises. A disappointment for us shareholders. I just want to get back even and then I will "AVOID" this dog." [Yes, you should only invest in stocks that always go up and never dip or go up and down. Because you are obviously incapable of dealing with anything else. And since there aren't any such stocks just find yourself a nice tin can, keep your investment money in it and bury it in your backyard. Oh, wait - for a moment there I thought you might be a real investor but the idea that you might be a disgruntled shareholder is ridiculous. You have never done anything but bash the company and the stock...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373057868399</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 16:57:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373057868547-87</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P UPGRADES OPINION ON SHARES OF INTEL TO BUY FROM HOLD</Title><Username>jctailman</Username><Timestamp>1372861108408</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:18:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sell your shares and then WRITE (sell) a Jan $28 put option for $4.65/$4.75. You can pocket the 65 cents per share and when Intel reaches $28, the put options expire worthless. If Jan arrives and Intel is still below $28, just roll the put option out 3 months for another credit. If you get LEVEL 3 option qualified by your broker, you can free up the cash of the underlying Intel position for use elsewhere.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1373057868547</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 16:57:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373060319697-88</Id><Title>Arm and its buyers are ROADKILL! I think Apple bails out and goes to Intel in 2014 in Phones and tablets.</Title><Msg>22nm Haswell, next new microarchitecture using a new cache hierarchy and adding FMA3 SIMD 2013 14nm Broadwell, shrink of Haswell 2014 14nm Skylake, post-Haswell microarchitecture 2015 10nm Skymont, shrink of Skylake late 2015/early 2016??? (Intel states 10nm is coming in 2015)</Msg><Username>amdroaddkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1373060319697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 17:38:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373063550419-89</Id><Topic><Title>Apple is rated "AVOID " Intel gets its commupance as Apple "AVOIDS" IT</Title><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1373053346205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:42:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you have never done anything but pump it, 3 long years and now up .06. Great investment, lol</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1373063550419</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 18:32:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373064610751-90</Id><Title>Tizen on the backburner?</Title><Msg>From Forbes: :Samsung may have hit some problems here. Its project to build a new open source operating system for potentially cheaper mobile devices with Intel INTC +1.21%, called Tizen, has reportedly been delayed from the third-quarter to the end of the year, allegedly due to problems getting developer support for its app store. In the second quarter of 2013, developers showd more interested in producing apps for Windows Phone and Firefox OS than Tizen, according to a recent study of more than 6,000 developers by Appcelerator and research firm IDC" At first it looks like bad news for Intel. Tizen may be downgraded in importance. But the key take-away from this article is that Samsung and Intel are working closer together on some Android related project. Today app developers seem to be able to pick and choose who and what they want to work with. Microsoft and now Apple are pleading with them for attention. The smartphone market is too mature now to take on new operating systems and many wonder if Microsoft is too late. I don't expect Firefox OS to go anywhere. When looking at the smartphone market I am glad Intel is putting more eggs in the basket of the well established operating systems instead of confusing the market with more choices. It's going to be iOS and Android with Windows Phone leading the pack of the unknowns. Intel will probably put Tizen to work with things like embedded devices where it can be boiled down to just the basics. Less</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1373064610751</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 18:50:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373067563484-91</Id><Topic><Title>Apple is rated "AVOID " Intel gets its commupance as Apple "AVOIDS" IT</Title><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1373053346205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:42:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>does it anger you that a stock that is where it was 13 years ago was simply stated that way?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1373067563484</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 19:39:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373067790097-92</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you mean you don't believe $30 is in the bag? or $3 eps is on the way as WW said 2 years ago? are you saying WW is FOS?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1373067790097</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 19:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373067886049-93</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poised to Explode Upward on Earnings</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1373036106672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh and I thought it was missing mobile and a lack of earnings. All it will take is earnings.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1373067886049</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 19:44:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373067916610-94</Id><Topic><Title>Apple is rated "AVOID " Intel gets its commupance as Apple "AVOIDS" IT</Title><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1373053346205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:42:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sell it, short it or whatever- diqu- wad / #$%$ drinker.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1373067916610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 19:45:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373069343593-95</Id><Topic><Title>Tizen on the backburner?</Title><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1373064610751</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 18:50:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel going full scale into Android and downplaying the Tizen sideshow means that Intel is ready to strike ARM deep in it's Android stronghold. It's these little news stories that don't get much press that is how you can tell where larger moves are being made. The groundwork is being laid right now and Intel is looking a bit more confident.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1373069343593</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 20:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373069409928-96</Id><Title>Jerry Blown needs a good blown job from cruncher jaws Kathy</Title><Msg>You have INTEL which hasn't done a dammnn thing since the 286 processor. Wake up Gibbons Babboon that you are! Now SCRAM!</Msg><Username>dowface</Username><Timestamp>1373069409928</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 20:10:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373072054091-97</Id><Title>Some Analysts will bad mouth the pig next week. Mr Weaver and</Title><Msg>Mr Essa need to quit their sniffin and get to work pumping this stock. Some material for Mr Weaver would be Intel is just starting out in smartphones, and with baytrail could capture a significant amount of marketshare.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1373072054091</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 20:54:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373074568044-98</Id><Topic><Title>Some Analysts will bad mouth the pig next week. Mr Weaver and</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1373072054091</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 20:54:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Intel is just starting out in smartphones, and with baytrail could capture a significant amount of marketshare." Yes, with a very low market share Intel has nowhere to go but up. But since you're more about the counterpoint tell us how you think ARM will fight off Intel from stealing the marketshare they worked so hard to build. It almost doesn't seem fair, does it? ARM built the Smartphone market and Intel is going to exploit it.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1373074568044</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 21:36:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373078762247-99</Id><Title>Evan Niu, CFA</Title><Msg>Anybody know about this guy? He talks a lot about ARM on MF.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1373078762247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 22:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>