<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369370222748-1</Id><Topic><Title>Canaccord: ARM upgraded to $56</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1369344064198</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:21:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good catch. And pretty funny. And just as funny is raising the earnings target...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369370222748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 00:37:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369370481098-2</Id><Topic><Title>INTC will see 18 before it sees 22 again</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1365430004086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 10:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boy I botched that prediction! Will you guys stop laughing at me? I want to be taken seriously. Please?</Msg><Username>itakebackrnyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369370481098</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 00:41:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369371031851-3</Id><Title>Any engineers, or people in the know, on this board? I have a NAND question.</Title><Msg>Can INTC use its excess capacity to build SSDs and PCI-e SSDs? The HDD is on it's way out. I believe PCI-e SSDs will replace SSDs in the future. INTC SSDs are rock solid, so say the experts at Tom's Hardware. Can INTC do a leap frog on Seagate, use its excess capacity to make serious inroads into the PCI-e SSD market? INTC already stopped making motherboards. Motherboards are becoming a commodity (Taiwan makes excellent, cheap Mobos) but the SSD market is still in its infancy. Thanks in advance for your help.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1369371031851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 00:50:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369371038983-4</Id><Title>Haswell processor, eliminating as many as seven external third party chips.</Title><Msg>5/23/2013 7:29 PM EDT The process names are actually P1270 and P1271. Perhaps you mis-heard your ... More... More Comments Intel Haswell packs integrated voltage regulator Rick Merritt 5/23/2013 2:53 PM EDT SAN JOSE, Calif. – Intel will pack a voltage regulator on to its next generation Haswell processor, eliminating as many as seven external third party chips. The news was one of a few details Intel revealed in a Haswell briefing the same day its archrival Advanced Micro Devices announced three mobile processors. Intel sketched out several steps it took to lower power consumption in Haswell, its next generation x86 processor geared for everything from 7W tablets to 75W servers. The techniques included integrating a voltage regulator, enhancing its 22nm process and using new power planes and states. It previously disclosed Haswell also will use a new on-chip DRAM. Power is a major focus for Intel given its rising competition especially in tablets and servers with generally lower power chips based on ARM cores. Intel likely gave up the possibility of higher data rates in Haswell to capture the power savings. The first Haswell chips are expected to ship later this year. Some Haswell chips will put two die in a package. The second die will be an integrated north and south bridge chip connected to the main CPU using a new low power interconnect. All Haswell chips will sport an on-chip voltage regulator. It will combine what was in previous CPUs as many as seven external voltage regulators made by third parties, lower the bill of materials and motherboard footprint, said Rani Borkar, general manager of the Intel Architecture Group which designs the company’s main processors. Gartner Inc. pegs the market for Intel Vcore regulators at roughly $325 million. It is slowly declining due price erosion of the components and declines in the overall PC market, said Stephan Ohr, Gartner analys</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1369371038983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 00:50:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369371712398-5</Id><Topic><Title>Any engineers, or people in the know, on this board? I have a NAND question.</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1369371031851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 00:50:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel has an arrangement with Micron for that specific purpose.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369371712398</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 01:01:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369374798332-6</Id><Topic><Title>Any engineers, or people in the know, on this board? I have a NAND question.</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1369371031851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 00:50:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What excess capacity?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1369374798332</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 01:53:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369376437067-7</Id><Topic><Title>46k in 2 months? net PROFIT</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1366433177700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i signed up with them!</Msg><Username>millionairetrader861</Username><Timestamp>1369376437067</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 02:20:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369377606664-8</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>Although Fed chief Bernanke received much of the blame for the sell-off, several pieces of economic data overseas added to concerns that global growth remained mundane and the market was ahead of itself. The market is at a place where 'good news' is 'bad news'. Reducing stimulus will obviously be tricky as the Fed will struggle to slow the flow of money and keep volatility at a minimum. Around the globe interest rates fluctuated on Bernanke's speech which added to pressure on stocks. The action of the last two days did little to change the direction of the major trend in the market. A drop to near their respective 50-day moving averages would put the DJIA and the S&amp;P 500 back to where they started the month of May. It seems there are plenty of buyers looking to get into this market at lower prices. For that reason it would appear that a 3-4% dip is the more likely scenario rather than the start of a serious correction.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369377606664</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 02:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369383165144-9</Id><Topic><Title>Any engineers, or people in the know, on this board? I have a NAND question.</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1369371031851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 00:50:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's my understanding that INTC is running at 50% capacity at its fabs. Is this old information? Or, am I confusing apples and oranges?</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1369383165144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 04:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369388826281-10</Id><Topic><Title>Any engineers, or people in the know, on this board? I have a NAND question.</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1369371031851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 00:50:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I also enjoy reading your articles. Keep 'em coming...</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1369388826281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 05:47:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369394681836-11</Id><Topic><Title>Any engineers, or people in the know, on this board? I have a NAND question.</Title><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1369371031851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 00:50:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt that Intel could use the costly advanced processes for NAND or would chose to use it for NAND if they had excess capacity. As Ashraf pointed out, Intel will be at their "FULL CAPACITY" level or higher with new Haswell, PHI and *Trail production. Everything hits the fan at once. If you look at the Navin Shenoy London They talk about HDD. Analyst meeting presentation on PAGE 9, Intel will be putting eDRAM on the high end Haswell chips. eDRAM is different that NAND but it is non-volatile storage. Intel is very interested in non-volatile storage. There was at least one analyst question about SSD fab capacity being an Ulrabook limiter. One PAGE 24, he indicates that there is a 500m unit refresh possibility looming. NAND storage has a "wear" problem like the CCDs for cameras. All SSD's have and ARM controller build in to manage SSD wear. The hiccups in response times are caused by wear pattern algorithms moving data around the SSD to make the write pattern activity uniform across the drive. SSD controllers have build in error detection and correction logic. The Intel SSD will sell at a premium to the server companies because of their reliability and UNIFORM response times.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369394681836</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 07:24:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369395208063-12</Id><Topic><Title>Canaccord: ARM upgraded to $56</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1369344064198</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:21:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARMH analyst earnings range for THIS year is low $.36 to high of $1.01 with $0.88 average. NEXT year, low of $0.47 to high of $1.36 with $1.09 average. It is unclear which year the Canaccord report was talking about but I would expect this years earnings. If so, their "upgrade" to 86 cents is still below the average of 88 cents. ARMH appears to use the calendar year for their FISCAL year so this upgrade would be relevant to the next 3 quarters. A real mix up by the financial writer.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369395208063</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 07:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369395262235-13</Id><Topic><Title>Laughing at the Shills</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369337273839</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 15:27:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>from a guy who has lost a ton on Intel ....you can't make this up ..Wally you are a disgrace to humanity.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1369395262235</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 07:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369396826665-14</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell processor, eliminating as many as seven external third party chips.</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1369371038983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 00:50:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lowers total cost to consumer while potentially increasing the BOM to Intel for each item shipped. This is especially true when using Haswell's integral graphics instead of a discrete graphics part.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369396826665</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 08:00:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369398359526-15</Id><Topic><Title>WOW did I read it right INTC lost to AMD for both, The new Xbox 1 and the New playstation 4, WOW thats not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369327845407</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah that is how they lost out on the Iphone ...it was a low margin biz. They could have got in the home with these consoles and developed it from there. Too bad.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369398359526</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 08:25:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369398645040-16</Id><Topic><Title>WOW did I read it right INTC lost to AMD for both, The new Xbox 1 and the New playstation 4, WOW thats not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369327845407</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Low margin is better than no margin.</Msg><Username>angstromatic</Username><Timestamp>1369398645040</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 08:30:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369401672014-17</Id><Title>Ironic, if Armh drops may well bring Intel down too...</Title><Msg>Sentiment is a funny thing.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1369401672014</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369402738065-18</Id><Topic><Title>Ironic, if Armh drops may well bring Intel down too...</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1369401672014</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:21:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"may well" and also "may well not". Uncertainty is a funny thing. The portion of drop that ARMH experiences based on sympathetic movement with a down market will also affect Intel. The portion of drop that ARMH experiences based on its own gravity will not affect Intel. Negative ARMH news about design losses will likely affect Intel positive to the extent the design win projects revenue and earnings impact. Consensus ARMH earnings this year is 88 cents and next year is $1.09. That is a 23% increase YoY. 23% growth and a $46 share price gives ARMH a PEG of 2. A PEG of 2 is not outrageous as long as they hit the $1.09 next year. If ARMH misses, they will lose a lot of confidence.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369402738065</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:38:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369402960251-19</Id><Topic><Title>Ironic, if Armh drops may well bring Intel down too...</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1369401672014</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:21:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sectors often trade together ..fairly or not.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1369402960251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:42:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369403232690-20</Id><Topic><Title>WOW did I read it right INTC lost to AMD for both, The new Xbox 1 and the New playstation 4, WOW thats not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369327845407</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Intel iPhone decision was based on the assumption that it was negative margin business when their fabs were operating at full capacity. The market would have not looked kindly on Intel substituting Apple negative margin business in place of profitable wafers. Why was the Intel cost forecast wrong? The iPhone retail sales forecasts were off by 100x. If the forecasts were more accurate, the costs could have been properly estimated. That would be the only difference I could see between game consoles and the iPhone. It is unlikely that game console forecasts are off by 100x.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369403232690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:47:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369403320565-21</Id><Title>Buy SOL for 5000% gain</Title><Msg>in next 1-2 yr</Msg><Username>drhollars</Username><Timestamp>1369403320565</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:48:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369403441564-22</Id><Title>Hold for one week and double your money</Title><Msg>5 soon on news</Msg><Username>drhollars</Username><Timestamp>1369403441564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:50:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369403523980-23</Id><Title>Pumpershills, down she goes where she land nobody knows</Title><Msg>laughing at the pumpershills. Evaporation of gains.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369403523980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369403533338-24</Id><Topic><Title>Ironic, if Armh drops may well bring Intel down too...</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1369401672014</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:21:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly what I said. There will some of the ARMH drop/rise that will be due to the sector (market) and ARMH/Intel will trade in the same direction. There will also be some extra ARMH drop based on decelerating ARMH growth. That drop, ARMH will have to experience on their own.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369403533338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:52:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369403765988-25</Id><Title>Load as many you can</Title><Msg>and say me thank you next week</Msg><Username>drhollars</Username><Timestamp>1369403765988</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:56:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369403834032-26</Id><Title>this dog wants to go back in the dog house</Title><Msg>here comes 22</Msg><Username>philip_914</Username><Timestamp>1369403834032</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:57:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369403856008-27</Id><Topic><Title>Hold for one week and double your money</Title><Username>drhollars</Username><Timestamp>1369403441564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Five? That would be an 80% loss. You might try going to the right board.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1369403856008</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:57:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369403931099-28</Id><Title>Deal with EU</Title><Msg>and Buyout</Msg><Username>drhollars</Username><Timestamp>1369403931099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:58:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369404158232-29</Id><Title>INTC breaks key support - island reversal</Title><Msg>Next test is low $23s. Intel has promised a lot for 2nd half revenue - if PC sales dont pick up soon, they will have to revise lower. Horrible management of expectations. Also, doesnt look like any dividend increase this year. The new CEO looks as bad as Otellini.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369404158232</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:02:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369404163165-30</Id><Title>Normally</Title><Msg>mkts end the day in the green on a Tuesday and Friday. I hope it does today as well. have a fun day.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369404163165</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:02:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369404317824-31</Id><Topic><Title>this dog wants to go back in the dog house</Title><Username>philip_914</Username><Timestamp>1369403834032</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should stoop down and then walk head first into an electric table saw.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369404317824</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:05:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369404499399-32</Id><Topic><Title>INTC breaks key support - island reversal</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369404158232</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you read the positions that got booted you realize they are having serious issues with getting this mobile thing movin.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369404499399</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:08:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369404533436-33</Id><Topic><Title>Normally</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369404163165</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:02:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>any effect of 3-day holiday?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369404533436</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:08:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369405001434-34</Id><Topic><Title>INTC breaks key support - island reversal</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369404158232</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy another 10k shares :)</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1369405001434</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:16:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369405037361-35</Id><Topic><Title>WOW did I read it right INTC lost to AMD for both, The new Xbox 1 and the New playstation 4, WOW thats not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369327845407</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and INTC will have no margins soon , because they think there to good for anyone else, Soon no one will do business with them , They have not learned from there past mistakes and it is showing up in lower revenue, lower earning, lower margins, The board needs to be cleaned out and the good old boy system needs cleaned out</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369405037361</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369405048414-36</Id><Title>Hammered!!!!!</Title><Msg>Bye bye INTC.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369405048414</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:17:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369405111789-37</Id><Topic><Title>INTC breaks key support - island reversal</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369404158232</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My grandmother just sold her 100 shares based on the these two comments by Nuff aliases. Thank you Nuff, you're a freakin' genius!</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369405111789</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:18:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369405185949-38</Id><Title>The good old boy system at INTC is still not working needs a very big change and shake up,</Title><Msg>The good old boy system at INTC is still not working needs a very big change and shake up</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369405185949</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:19:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369405314988-39</Id><Topic><Title>The good old boy system at INTC is still not working needs a very big change and shake up,</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369405185949</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:19:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Retest of yearly lows coming</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369405314988</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:21:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369405358627-40</Id><Topic><Title>Normally</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369404163165</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:02:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hi alex gud morn, yep bro normally folks like to cash in before the long weekend but I still feel we will close in the green today. bought some dis morn at 23.75 will buy in steps if it falls more. goodluck</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369405358627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:22:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369405388348-41</Id><Title>Analysts should be looking to raise estimates soon</Title><Msg>Especially due to their presumed lack of entry into mobile.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369405388348</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:23:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369405420119-42</Id><Topic><Title>The good old boy system at INTC is still not working needs a very big change and shake up,</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369405185949</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:19:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget to bring up insider selling, lower margins/growth and possible div. cut. Coinmaker is at his finest when repeating these over and over and over and over and over.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369405420119</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369405726862-43</Id><Title>Intel Poops on Boy Scouts of America</Title><Msg>Intel was instrumental in yesterday's decision forcing the Boy Scouts to admit openly homosexual members. Intel threatened to remove its major financial support if the open homosexuals were not admitted. Homosexuals cheered and said that next they demand homosexual scout leaders be admitted. A national poll of 200,000 scouts and parents showed a 2 to 1 majority opposing the change.. I'm selling the small amount of Intel stock I own and encourage the formation of a new "Real Boy Scout" organization comprised by boys who continue to be "morally straight". Intel management deserves the contempt of those who want to see boys develop in a healthy environment of honor, morality and democratic ideals.</Msg><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1369405726862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369405792220-44</Id><Topic><Title>The good old boy system at INTC is still not working needs a very big change and shake up,</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369405185949</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:19:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should use the word "WOW". That has an extremely dramatic effect on people. With every utterance, my finger reaches for the sell button on my computer.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369405792220</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369405961838-45</Id><Topic><Title>Ironic, if Armh drops may well bring Intel down too...</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1369401672014</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:21:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sector and market are not the same thing.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1369405961838</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369406102276-46</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poops on Boy Scouts of America</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1369405726862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it is intel's money. Scouts don't have to take it.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369406102276</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:35:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369406198554-47</Id><Topic><Title>WOW did I read it right INTC lost to AMD for both, The new Xbox 1 and the New playstation 4, WOW thats not good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369327845407</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW INTC missed the boat again, Good old boy system not working. INTC board needs to get its head out of each others A $ $,</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369406198554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369406206114-48</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poops on Boy Scouts of America</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1369405726862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are a deeply disturbed closeted homosexual who got rear-ended by a priest way back in 6th grade. You no doubt carry guns and are very tough on your son whom you sometimes call the "girly-guy." Ever tap dance in the men's room?</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1369406206114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:36:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369406252369-49</Id><Title>Hey Aintezbeingreen aka lucy_nuff</Title><Msg>No amount of venom will change the fact that you had to throw your prized aliases in the trash due to horrific stock picks and you are really just a miserable little putz in disguise.. LOL! Keep posting to remove all doubt.</Msg><Username>aladieistight</Username><Timestamp>1369406252369</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:37:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369406304963-50</Id><Title>Walleye was thinking this would be at about 28 right about now. LOL</Title><Msg>He just never learns how things work. oh well..</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369406304963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:38:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369406306800-51</Id><Title>Gotta love WS...gummint is off their backs.</Title><Msg>SEC has already taken the weekend off...recovering from their hangovers from yesterday's 4 martini lunch at the GB club.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1369406306800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:38:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369406404685-52</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Aintezbeingreen aka lucy_nuff</Title><Username>aladieistight</Username><Timestamp>1369406252369</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:37:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now wally I know you are having to eat a lot of crow today, so I will let it go.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369406404685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:40:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369406452478-53</Id><Title>Laughing at Shorts</Title><Msg>So, what is this? The latest attempt to construct an exit strategy? Get real. Haswell a week from Monday. ARM in freefall. Go find a nice fork and stick it in yourselves. You're done...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369406452478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:40:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369406464068-54</Id><Topic><Title>INTC breaks key support - island reversal</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369404158232</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup, Dadi basically getting the boot. He failed miserably in getting Intel chips into mobile. Paul O. made so many strategic blunders, I dont know where to start. I would hope the new CEO would reset expectations. I just dont see any organic growth coming. CFO needs to work his magic with financial engineering to get EPS growth. BTW, Intel should be about 20-30K employees lighter. Inexecusable for a no-growth company to keep this much fat.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369406464068</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:41:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369406604191-55</Id><Topic><Title>INTC breaks key support - island reversal</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369404158232</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are profoundly stupid.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1369406604191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:43:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369406647427-56</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poops on Boy Scouts of America</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1369405726862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel removed its support in July 2012 because Intel has an anti-discrimination policy. Intel was the LARGEST corporate donor to the BSA. If this issue is so important to him, why did he wait so long to sell his shares? If he believed that discrimination was OK, he should have sold Intel shares in July when Intel suspended BSA support.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369406647427</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:44:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369406765180-57</Id><Title>WOW INTC just keeps giving away business, first phones INTC was to good for it low margin , 2nd tablest INTC was to good for it low magin</Title><Msg>Now gaming INTC was to good for it low margin, Doesn't anyone else see there is a BIG problem here? The business is changing and INTC is not changing with the times.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369406765180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:46:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369406955393-58</Id><Topic><Title>WOW INTC just keeps giving away business, first phones INTC was to good for it low margin , 2nd tablest INTC was to good for it low magin</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369406765180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they consoles would have been a great vehicle to get in the house ...they blew it. They have admitted via the shake up the mobile strategy is not what it should be. Notice who got replaced !</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1369406955393</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369407018454-59</Id><Title>Told you sell INTC and buy AMD</Title><Msg>this stock is alawys trading weak</Msg><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369407018454</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:50:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369407021801-60</Id><Topic><Title>Ironic, if Armh drops may well bring Intel down too...</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1369401672014</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:21:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh. Then ..... I will change the word "market" to the word "sector". The portion of drop that ARMH experiences based on sympathetic movement with a down sector will also affect Intel. The portion of drop that ARMH experiences based on its own gravity will not affect Intel. Negative ARMH news about design losses will likely affect Intel positive to the extent the design win projects revenue and earnings impact.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369407021801</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:50:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369407050571-61</Id><Topic><Title>WOW INTC just keeps giving away business, first phones INTC was to good for it low margin , 2nd tablest INTC was to good for it low magin</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369406765180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Otellini was a failure, plain-and-simple. The new guy at least is reorganizing around new product areas, as opposed to chip type. Otellini was a COO, disguised as CEO. Horrible visionary.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369407050571</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:50:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369407102957-62</Id><Title>Sad to see INTC trading so poorly</Title><Msg>I hope is rises with weekly options expiration. It is oversold now.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369407102957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:51:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369407174279-63</Id><Title>FINAL SHAKE-OUT BEFORE BIG MOVE UP</Title><Msg>I FEEL SORRY FOR THE FOOLS selling today</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369407174279</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:52:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369407182057-64</Id><Topic><Title>Normally</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369404163165</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:02:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well .... since I am long. I like your thinking. If you said "red" then I wouldn't like it but .... life has its ups/downs. you have a good, long weekend. I think I have a weekend planned for me at the handle end of a shovel.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369407182057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369407207251-65</Id><Topic><Title>Deal with EU</Title><Username>drhollars</Username><Timestamp>1369403931099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:58:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What sort of deal? Anything less than the $1.3b should go directly to bottom line/earnings. Would be a nice way to kick start the run up in Q3-4 we should see.</Msg><Username>luv2_bike</Username><Timestamp>1369407207251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:53:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369407217581-66</Id><Topic><Title>Sad to see INTC trading so poorly</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369407102957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:51:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually it is at what it should be. Where it goes no one knows, not even big mouths me or Wally.</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369407217581</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369407270372-67</Id><Title>Texbook Wallisweaver, absent when it's red here pumping hard when it's green</Title><Msg>Gutless, moral-less Liberal degenerate.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1369407270372</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:54:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369407328180-68</Id><Topic><Title>Told you sell INTC and buy AMD</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369407018454</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When AMD pays as good a dividend I might consider.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1369407328180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369407360738-69</Id><Title>Asus Fonepad review</Title><Msg>'Best 7in tablet on the market, but far too big to make calls' theinquirerDOTnet/inquirer/review/2269455/asus-fonepad-review</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1369407360738</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:56:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369407425422-70</Id><Title>where is the support 22 or 20</Title><Msg>not looking good</Msg><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1369407425422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:57:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369407476683-71</Id><Title>INTC is flat since 2000</Title><Msg>even PO$ MSFT went up to $35.00</Msg><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369407476683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:57:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369407557598-72</Id><Topic><Title>Sad to see INTC trading so poorly</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369407102957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:51:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ORCL and HPQ have almost identical trading patterns to INTC today Short interest through 5/15 will be released after market. it will be interesting to see how much short interest was burned off during the recent rise.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369407557598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369407583458-73</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is flat since 2000</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369407476683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So sell it &amp; leave, bye bye</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1369407583458</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:59:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369407619957-74</Id><Topic><Title>WOW INTC just keeps giving away business, first phones INTC was to good for it low margin , 2nd tablest INTC was to good for it low magin</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369406765180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TO me INTC good old boy system needs to go and INTC needs a big shake up or INTC will kill themselves off , because they just keep missing the boat and then say we didn't want that business it was low margin, BIG BIG problem</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369407619957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369407624711-75</Id><Topic><Title>Sad to see INTC trading so poorly</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369407102957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:51:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its like a giant ship lost in the sea and doesn't know where to go</Msg><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1369407624711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:00:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369407726155-76</Id><Topic><Title>Texbook Wallisweaver, absent when it's red here pumping hard when it's green</Title><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1369407270372</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:54:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's here as Williamdavis, hiding under the table and yelling at people. You'll never see anyone more spineless.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1369407726155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:02:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369407772373-77</Id><Title>FINAL CHANCE TO BUY INTC BEFORE HASWELL FEVER BEGINS NEXT WEEK</Title><Msg>$40 BY END OF YEAR</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369407772373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:02:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369407795267-78</Id><Topic><Title>FINAL CHANCE TO BUY INTC BEFORE HASWELL FEVER BEGINS NEXT WEEK</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369407772373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2015 ?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1369407795267</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:03:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369407821572-79</Id><Topic><Title>Sad to see INTC trading so poorly</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369407102957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:51:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>alexander, what if you run a few years?</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1369407821572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:03:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369407987301-80</Id><Topic><Title>WOW INTC just keeps giving away business, first phones INTC was to good for it low margin , 2nd tablest INTC was to good for it low magin</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369406765180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, BIG BIG BIG problem. Sounds horrendous. (good use of caps). Your insightful comments could literally bring down a behemoth like Intel. Way to go!</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369407987301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369408193602-81</Id><Topic><Title>Sad to see INTC trading so poorly</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369407102957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:51:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure what you mean. If you mean compare the charts over 2 years, INTC and ORCL take different paths but end up flat. HPQ down about 30% (it would have been down 40% earlier in the week).</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369408193602</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:09:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369408303217-82</Id><Topic><Title>where is the support 22 or 20</Title><Username>phil42_ny</Username><Timestamp>1369407425422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:57:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd say around $5 or less. Ya think?</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369408303217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369408316710-83</Id><Topic><Title>WOW INTC just keeps giving away business, first phones INTC was to good for it low margin , 2nd tablest INTC was to good for it low magin</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369406765180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, no div increase as there was in past 2 years, sinking mammoth ship. Titanic II</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1369408316710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:11:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369408616256-84</Id><Title>Intel Given “Outperform” Rating at RBC C</Title><Msg>They currently have a $29.00 price target on the stock.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369408616256</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:16:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369408800918-85</Id><Title>Get in on INTC while you still can</Title><Msg>I'm being a hypocrite because i sold everything at 24.52, but I plan on buying options either today or early next week. Haswel will increase stock price. I predict $26 by mid June. Based on revenue this is still an very under priced stock.</Msg><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1369408800918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:20:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369409190712-86</Id><Topic><Title>WOW INTC just keeps giving away business, first phones INTC was to good for it low margin , 2nd tablest INTC was to good for it low magin</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369406765180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not bring INTC down , INTC's board and management is bring INTC down .because they think there to good and keep missing the boat. First they didn't want the phone business low margin, 2nd didn't want the tablet business low margin and now a very dumb move we didn't want the gaming business low margin. INTC has a very BIG problem , Business is changing and INTC is not The bigger problem for you is I am not even short .if INTC doesn't fix themselves soon they will DIE</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369409190712</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:26:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369409234009-87</Id><Topic><Title>WOW INTC just keeps giving away business, first phones INTC was to good for it low margin , 2nd tablest INTC was to good for it low magin</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369406765180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Intel raises the next dividend (which I don't expect) it will match the run at 21 cents won't it? Intel has not been exactly consistent and they don't appear to be the slave to timing that I thought. 22.5 cents 4 quarters raised in ????? 21 cents 4 quarters raised in Aug 2012 18.1 cents 2 quarters raised in Aug 2011 15.8 cents 4 quarters raised in Feb 2011 14 cents 7 quarters raised in Feb 2010 12.8 cents 1 quarter raised May 2008 11.3 cents 4 quarters raised in Feb 2008</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369409234009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:27:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369409417730-88</Id><Topic><Title>Sad to see INTC trading so poorly</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369407102957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:51:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC is always like this - very miserable trading pattern.</Msg><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369409417730</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369409481119-89</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is flat since 2000</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369407476683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i like his answer but really you should be doing the opposite. This stock is very ready fora climb. If it hits 23.00 I'm going to bet big on Intel</Msg><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1369409481119</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:31:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369409757523-90</Id><Topic><Title>Laughing at Shorts</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369406452478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:40:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Waldo, too bad one can't fixed stupid. you were warned of the danger of continuing to hold INTC, bearish reversal patter was clear as day to those who do more than incessantly pump INTC.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369409757523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369409852862-91</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is flat since 2000</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369407476683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I really don't care what anybody does because I'm not a trader &amp; already own a boatload, I'm satisfied with the good dividend.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1369409852862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:37:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369409916975-92</Id><Title>INTC look what happens when you think your to good to change until its to late , The good old boy system will kill you off.</Title><Msg>Look at Kodak's history, They had years to fix themselves , but never did until it was to late. Business was changing for Kodak, but they through they were to good and didn't try to change until it was to late. Now look were the good old boy system got Kodak got them. Kodak used to pay a very good and increasing dividend also. INTC change or DIE FACT history is tilling you that you need to change and when you think your to good for business your in very big trouble</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369409916975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369409918283-93</Id><Topic><Title>Normally</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369404163165</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:02:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not generally a good idea to buy into a falling macd, and we now have a rolloever on the QQQ. Market in correction mode.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369409918283</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:38:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369410279088-94</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is flat since 2000</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369407476683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even bubble PCLN went up from $80 to $800 (it may bubble further to $1000)</Msg><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369410279088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:44:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369410732973-95</Id><Topic><Title>WOW INTC just keeps giving away business, first phones INTC was to good for it low margin , 2nd tablest INTC was to good for it low magin</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369406765180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is English your second language?</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369410732973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:52:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369410828123-96</Id><Topic><Title>Hammered!!!!!</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369405048414</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:17:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was thinking INTC to run $30 or $35 (like MSFT).</Msg><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369410828123</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369410883451-97</Id><Topic><Title>Hammered!!!!!</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369405048414</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:17:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>have patience. It will</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1369410883451</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:54:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369411065490-98</Id><Topic><Title>Hammered!!!!!</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369405048414</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:17:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hedgies are betting on semis.</Msg><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369411065490</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:57:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369411570587-99</Id><Title>Haswell Chip announcement on June 6th</Title><Msg>folks...this will rocket the stock to $30</Msg><Username>oceanbeachvictor</Username><Timestamp>1369411570587</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:06:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369411873559-100</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell Chip announcement on June 6th</Title><Username>oceanbeachvictor</Username><Timestamp>1369411570587</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:06:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No it won't, INTC has given away all the new business and future business , phones, tablets and now gaming</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369411873559</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:11:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369411982501-101</Id><Topic><Title>INTC look what happens when you think your to good to change until its to late , The good old boy system will kill you off.</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369409916975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at IBM. It is hard to follow your sputtering message but .... You chose Kodak. I chose IBM as the example. You can construct whatever argument you want. I defend your right to express your "facts" and opinions. I think it is wrong when you go into hyper-posting mode saying the same thing over and over to disrupt the board. I think your old boy comments are silly. I think your declining revenue and earnings comments are silly. I think your backbay Intel management comments are silly. I gave you some credit when you posted about a purchase and sale of Intel stock. That trust and credit leaked away as you reverted to these sputtering rants. IT IS MY OPINION that much of your material is YOUR OPINION and presented as FACT and repeating it does not make it any more true.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369411982501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:13:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369412390475-102</Id><Title>If INTC doesn't not change, It won't matter what new chip they come out with, They have given away all the future business already</Title><Msg>phones , tablets and now lately gaming, INTC thinks there to good and it's going to kill them off, INTC needs a very big shake up, The good old boy system is not working and history has shown in other companies that once the good old boy system is in a company it will die, unless you can change it before it to late</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369412390475</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369412398164-103</Id><Topic><Title>INTC look what happens when you think your to good to change until its to late , The good old boy system will kill you off.</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369409916975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel hasn't been real good about keeping on top of market trends, but they do have the world's most advanced digital semiconductor process and if they are at least half smart in capitalizing on that trump card, they are going to do very well in the next few years.</Msg><Username>bot_feeder</Username><Timestamp>1369412398164</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:19:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369412517055-104</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell Chip announcement on June 6th</Title><Username>oceanbeachvictor</Username><Timestamp>1369411570587</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:06:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nuff how many aliases do you have ? the better question why bother since everyone knows who you are anyway LOL.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1369412517055</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:21:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369412555621-105</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell Chip announcement on June 6th</Title><Username>oceanbeachvictor</Username><Timestamp>1369411570587</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:06:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with you that Intel will not rocket to $30 on June 6th. If there is some surprise about Haswell that is not know, INTC will take a pop but not to $30. Tablets will all be Atom based. Galaxy Tab is first big one to switch. They can see what Bay Trail will do to ARM devices. Phone vendors are starting to switch outside the 4G world and that changes with Baytrail with it is released. There is also HPC which has a market value to Intel that is 4x the mobile market according to Gartner and IDC.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369412555621</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:22:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369412639917-106</Id><Title>don't forget</Title><Msg>Leading edge semiconductor chips garner big profits, last generation ones are commodities that you buy by the pound. The fact that Intel has a technological lead over the rest of the semicondutor industry should not be taken lightly.</Msg><Username>bot_feeder</Username><Timestamp>1369412639917</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:23:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369412996413-107</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell Chip announcement on June 6th</Title><Username>oceanbeachvictor</Username><Timestamp>1369411570587</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:06:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must really hate Intel for some personal reason. It's the only explanation other than your being a loony bird. What did they treat you rudely during an interview, ... or worse fire you because you could meet performance expectations? You are really hard to figure.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1369412996413</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:29:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369413193314-108</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell Chip announcement on June 6th</Title><Username>oceanbeachvictor</Username><Timestamp>1369411570587</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:06:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I SAY IT BREAKS 52 WEEK HIGH : THUS AROUND 28</Msg><Username>gtscorp1</Username><Timestamp>1369413193314</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369413222916-109</Id><Title>How is INTC new CEO doing?</Title><Msg>hope he will put INTC back on track.</Msg><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369413222916</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:33:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369413319724-110</Id><Topic><Title>INTC look what happens when you think your to good to change until its to late , The good old boy system will kill you off.</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369409916975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes and IBM was in big trouble at one time, They had the good old boy system in place also ,but were able to shake it up and put the company on a new track before it was to late. IBM had the same problem at one time were they through they were to good to take on some kinds of business. Maybe a better company to use would have been AAPL, The good old boy system ran Jobs out of the company and AAPL almost DIE , but sometimes when you shake the good old boy system up you get greatness again just look what AAPL did after the good old boy system was shaken up.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369413319724</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:35:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369413465963-111</Id><Topic><Title>How is INTC new CEO doing?</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369413222916</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:33:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you look too worried ?</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1369413465963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:37:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369413494398-112</Id><Title>Invest $8B in Intel = Largest Shareholder Status</Title><Msg>control the Board !!! Seems a steal @ 8B .....the chinese are watching !!!!</Msg><Username>oceanbeachvictor</Username><Timestamp>1369413494398</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:38:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369413594632-113</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is flat since 2000</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369407476683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and federal national mortgage has run from .25 to over 2.80 this year alone</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369413594632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:39:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369413956799-114</Id><Topic><Title>How is INTC new CEO doing?</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369413222916</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:33:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not at all. In fact I like INTC the most (INTC is the best company in the world)</Msg><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369413956799</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:45:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369414086219-115</Id><Topic><Title>INTC look what happens when you think your to good to change until its to late , The good old boy system will kill you off.</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369409916975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My problem is I can see INTC having greatness again, but not if they keep thinking there to good to take on some of the business because its low margin. The boneheads just missed the boat again with gaming. Think if someone buys a gaming system and really loves it. Now they need to buy a new computer or phone or tablet what chip do you think there going to want in the computer , phone or tablet ? and its not INTC no matter how good the chips are. INTC's got the good old boy boneheads running the company</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369414086219</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:48:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369414220760-116</Id><Topic><Title>this dog wants to go back in the dog house</Title><Username>philip_914</Username><Timestamp>1369403834032</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 09:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is the dog house?</Msg><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369414220760</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:50:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369414418444-117</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell Chip announcement on June 6th</Title><Username>oceanbeachvictor</Username><Timestamp>1369411570587</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:06:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its all about "POWER" in the computing World: Haswell will take Computing to the NEXT LEVEL. Watch and Learn ...folks....CALM before the STORM.</Msg><Username>oceanbeachvictor</Username><Timestamp>1369414418444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:53:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369414692270-118</Id><Topic><Title>backbay_bstn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361752255702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 19:30:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Backbay_bstn is just another Nuff alias. His wet dream is to buy at $19. Nuff likes to make crazy comments for attention. Certain he doesn't believe half of what he writes. Lately, his comments sound like he's had a mini-stroke or maybe just getting softer in the head. At any rate, sounds like a veritable moron.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369414692270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 12:58:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369415565057-119</Id><Topic><Title>backbay_bstn</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1361752255702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 19:30:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This could be a decent message board again without that IDIOT nuff, get tired of all his lame nonsense.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1369415565057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 13:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369416670205-120</Id><Title>Intel claims Haswell will offer 50% more battery life in laptops</Title><Msg>he new processor design is important for PC makers as they try to battle tablets and smartphones Agam Shah May 23, 2013 (IDG News Service) Intel's upcoming family of Core processors, code-named Haswell, will offer 50% more battery life in laptops than did their "Ivy Bridge" predecessors, Intel said on Thursday. Haswell chips were designed with laptops and tablets in mind, and the main focus was on lowering power consumption, said Rani Borkar, corporate vice president and general manager of the Intel Architecture Group, in a media briefing</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1369416670205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 13:31:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369416964893-121</Id><Title>CPOW strikes deal with China ((((</Title><Msg>MONSTER GAINS !!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>t.fold309</Username><Timestamp>1369416964893</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 13:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369417058317-122</Id><Title>I really think INTC can have greatness again, Maybe I should have used IBM or better AAPL. I just didn't want some pupm and dump again</Title><Msg>Yes and IBM was in big trouble at one time, They had the good old boy system in place also ,but were able to shake it up and put the company on a new track before it was to late. IBM had the same problem at one time were they through they were to good to take on some kinds of business. Maybe a better company to use would have been AAPL, The good old boy system ran Jobs out of the company and AAPL almost DIE , but sometimes when you shake the good old boy system up you get greatness again just look what AAPL did after the good old boy system was shaken up. My problem is I can see INTC having greatness again, but not if they keep thinking there to good to take on some of the business because its low margin. The boneheads just missed the boat again with gaming. Think if someone buys a gaming system and really loves it. Now they need to buy a new computer or phone or tablet what chip do you think there going to want in the computer , phone or tablet ? and its not INTC no matter how good the chips are. INTC's got the good old boy boneheads running the company</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369417058317</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 13:37:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369417226255-123</Id><Topic><Title>INTC look what happens when you think your to good to change until its to late , The good old boy system will kill you off.</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369409916975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 11:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is not your problem. So you learned some new English slang and you want to use sentences. It does not apply to Intel nor did it apply to AAPL nor IBM. If you think that anyone using an Xbox, PS4, .... knows that there is an AMD chip inside, you do not understand the technical level of a typical console user. IF THEY ARE smart enough to know that there is an AMD chip inside the game console, they will know why it is there and will buy the Intel system they want.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369417226255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 13:40:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369417247593-124</Id><Topic><Title>I really think INTC can have greatness again, Maybe I should have used IBM or better AAPL. I just didn't want some pupm and dump again</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369417058317</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 13:37:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very eloquently stated and wise. You sound like a senior statesman, another Winston Churchhill. Should consider writing a financial column.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369417247593</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 13:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369417428472-125</Id><Topic><Title>I really think INTC can have greatness again, Maybe I should have used IBM or better AAPL. I just didn't want some pupm and dump again</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369417058317</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 13:37:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think he is qualified to write for the Motley Fool. They do not seem to require any knowledge.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369417428472</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 13:43:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369417704417-126</Id><Topic><Title>I really think INTC can have greatness again, Maybe I should have used IBM or better AAPL. I just didn't want some pupm and dump again</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1369417058317</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 13:37:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>coinmaker is so transparent. He has drastic opinions in either direction depending if he is short or long. I remember last time he was long he sold way too soon. He sounds like an old Soviet. ;^)</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369417704417</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 13:48:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369417735227-127</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poops on Boy Scouts of America</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1369405726862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I understand that 15 of 14 Roman emperors were homosexuals. Is it a coincidence that your id correlates to that? Your foul, left wing response shows you are almost certainly part of Obama's horde of stooges whose logical capabilities don't rise above the level of the idiotic .</Msg><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1369417735227</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 13:48:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369418253516-128</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poops on Boy Scouts of America</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1369405726862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's true, but obviously most of those who engineered this betrayal of the Boy Scouts sold out because they think that money and political correctness outweigh character, honesty and bravery.</Msg><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1369418253516</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 13:57:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369418936571-129</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poops on Boy Scouts of America</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1369405726862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just learned about this yesterday. Discrimination is not merely ok, it is essential to living. We discriminate (make a distinction among) thousands of things all the time and could not live without so doing. In particular we discriminate between lies and truth, up and down, in and out, good and evil, homosexual and normal. We should recognize each for what it is and give to each what is due based on civilized norms, rather than be dictated to by civilization wrecking liberals.</Msg><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1369418936571</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 14:08:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369420478063-130</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poops on Boy Scouts of America</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1369405726862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If this BSA admitting gays issue was important to you or those around you, you would have known about Intel last July when Intel suspended support. That is the primary reason you are posting on the Intel board, isn't it? That is the topic of your message, isn't it? I think it would be fine for you to sell your shares and go support a "Real Boy Scout" organization. I can think of no better role model for those Real Boy Scouts of your friends and neighbors. Rather than being dictated to by civilization wrecking liberals, you can be their dictator instead.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369420478063</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 14:34:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369421234035-131</Id><Title>Samsung, carriers tout first Tizen mobes for late 2013</Title><Msg>Samsung, carriers tout first Tizen mobes for late 2013 alert print comment HTML5 seen as key to open source smartphone success By Neil McAllister in San Francisco • Get more from this author Posted in Operating Systems, 24th May 2013 00:35 GMT Watch Now : Virtual Machine Movement with Hyper-V TDC2013 You could be forgiven for thinking there's not much going on with Tizen, the Linux Foundation's open source mobile OS. It's been two years since the project was launched and there still are no Tizen devices on the market. But that's about to change – and there has been a lot happening behind the scenes, as well. "Tizen-based products will come out very soon," Samsung executive VP Jong-Deok Choi, who cochairs the Tizen Technical Steering Group, told the audience at the second annual Tizen Developer Conference in San Francisco on Thursday. NTT DoCoMo global marketing director Roy Sugimura said the Japanese carrier plans to release its first Tizen-based smartphone in the second half of 2013. Similarly, Orange plans to launch Tizen devices "in the back-to-school period" – meaning the end of summer – according to the company's device technical director, Frederic Dufal. What makes this possible is the arrival of Tizen 2.1, the most mature and stable version of the platform to date. The source code and SDK for the update were released on May 17, and its developers say this version is finally fully baked. "It's ready to be built into products and it's ready for you to build your applications against," said Mark Skarpness, director of systems engineering at Intel, another prominent member of the Tizen Association. In addition to a variety of bug fixes and API improvements, Tizen 2.1 includes an enhanced web framework with support for the Content Security Policy 1.0 and Navigation Timing specs from the W3C; improved IDEs for web and native app development; and support for a new kind of small apps that can be embedded inside other apps, called Web Dynamic Boxes. Tizen's de</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369421234035</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 14:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369421426757-132</Id><Title>Images Surface of First Tizen handset</Title><Msg>thedroidguyDOTcom/2013/05/images-surface-of-first-tizen-handset/</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369421426757</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 14:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369421596847-133</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poops on Boy Scouts of America</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1369405726862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alexander, I thought I made it clear that I learned about this yesterday so your protest that I didn't do something earlier makes no sense. I have no interest in dictating to anyone; I am just expressing my opinion on important cultural topics, in particular, the wreckage caused by left wing ideology to 2000 years of civilization. I encourage you to think long term, especially if you have or will have children.</Msg><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1369421596847</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 14:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369422091561-134</Id><Title>Redwood GT-I8805: Samsung Device Running Tizen OS Spotted Online</Title><Msg>gizbotdotcom/mobile/redwood-gt-i8805-samsung-device-running-tizen-os-online-012260.html</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369422091561</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:01:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369422116554-135</Id><Title>Source confirms Intel’s big score: Samsung tablet using an Atom chip</Title><Msg>Intel’s long years investing in mobile processors are about to pay off with its biggest win to date. We’ve confirmed that the next Samsung Galaxy tablet, the Samsung Galaxy Tab 3, will have an Intel Atom chip based on the Clover Trail code name. A source familiar with the matter confirmed to us that Samsung has chosen the Intel chip over other competing ARM-based solutions, including Samsung’s own Exynos mobile processors. If it’s true, that could mean that Intel’s mobile processor business is finally getting some traction. Benchmark testing sits leaked that news this week. The GFXBench site and the SamMobile site noted the Intel chip appeared to be inside a device dubbed the Samsung Santos 103 tablet with the product name GT-P5200 running Android on an Intel Clover Trail chip. Various sites concluded that was Samsung’s third-generation Galaxy Tab slate, which has a 10.1-inch touchscreen. Test results say the device has a 1,280-by-800 display and is running Android 4.2.2 operating system. The processor can run between from 800MHz to 1.6GHz in terms of clock speed. That’s within the stated capabilities of the dual-core Atom Z2520 processor. The Intel chip is made in a 32-nanometer high-k metal gate manufacturing process. Read more at venturebeat</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369422116554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:01:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369422197931-136</Id><Topic><Title>Source confirms Intel’s big score: Samsung tablet using an Atom chip</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369422116554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:01:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel will release new information in a talk at the upcoming Computex trade show in Taiwan. That will include new designs and upcoming low-power chip microarchitectures including Silvermont (used in Bay Trail tablets for this holiday), Avoton (for micro servers) and Merrifield for smartphones.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369422197931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:03:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369422273578-137</Id><Title>PROBLEM FOR INTEL IS: MARGINS AND REVENUES WILL SHRINK SHARPLY GOING FORWARD IN 2014</Title><Msg>$20 soC COMPETITION VIA COMMODITY glut Hell Intel Monopoly gone....... AMD in very good position, WIll QCOM buy AMD??????????????????</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369422273578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:04:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369422291616-138</Id><Title>Tizen with GNOME 3 shell shown by Intel</Title><Msg>Tizen with GNOME 3 shell shown by Intel submit to slashdot StumbleUpon submit to reddit Tizen logo Tizen, the mobile operating system that has yet to see a device launched with it, is already widening its reach to laptops. Tizen, a Linux Foundation project with Intel and Samsung collaborating on development, is due to appear on smartphones in the latter part of the year with Tizen 2.1, which uses a Linux base layer with a user interface built using Enlightenment libraries to run HTML5-based apps. At the Tizen Developers Conference held this week though, Intel showed an early version of what will become part of Tizen 3.0 later in the year. Tizen Experts recorded a video of the Intel Tizen variant running on an i7 Ultrabook. The desktop "Tizen Shell" used by Intel's laptop variant is based on the GNOME 3 shell and desktop environment. The demonstration shows the platform running applications such as Shotwell, Rhythmbox and Steam, as well as being able to run Tizen Web Apps. Desktop widgets have been created for the Tizen Shell, though they are built in JavaScript as GNOME extensions, rather than Tizen web applications. At this stage of development, it therefore appears to be a more traditional GNOME 3 desktop with the ability to run Tizen Web Apps and the Tizen IDE. The code involved will be donated to the Tizen project and should be available later in the year. The vision for compatibility between the Tizen variants appears to be centred on being able to run Tizen Web Apps on the phone and desktop. Tizen itself has recently been updated with the publication of Tizen 2.1. Tizen 2.1 is billed as a minor update; the web runtime has now has Content Security Policy 1.0 support and various specification updates, along with Web DynamicBox which allows content to be embedded in viewer applications. Both the Nat</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369422291616</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:04:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369422993758-139</Id><Title>Unity promises to support Tizen OS</Title><Msg>Unity promises to support Tizen OS Zen Terrelonge by Zen Terrelonge about 9 hours ago . Print this page Email Unity promises to support Tizen OS Tools are currently in development. Tizen is an open source OS made from a cocktail of Linux-based MeeGo, WebKit and HTML5 elements, and is supported by the likes of Intel, Samsung, Orange and Panasonic. The dream is to empower all devices with an OS that can run across mobiles, TVs, and in-car entertainment systems. As development tools provider Unity continues its push to become truly multi-platform, the firm has pledged allegiance to Tizen and promises it's working on a tool kit for the operating system. The solutions will allow developers to build and publish games to Tizen smartphones and tablets via the Tizen Store later in the year. A selection of Unity titles will be available in time for the debut of Tizen-powered devices. David Helgason, CEO, Unity Technologies, said: "Unity and Tizen have a lot in common in that they both aim to make the creation and the deployment of games and other apps as easy as possible for developers. Tizen’s broad OEM support and big market potential will provide another excellent avenue for our amazing community of mobile developers to find success." Royichi Sugimura, chairman of Tizen Association, said: "Games are one of the driving forces behind smartphone and tablet adoption. "Unity support for Tizen OS ensures a huge number of talented developers making some of the most entertaining games have an efficient and powerful channel to publish their titles to Tizen Store." Earlier this week, Unity made its mobile publishing tools free, and the Tizen announcement demonstrates how valuable the company considers the mobile market.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369422993758</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369423380701-140</Id><Topic><Title>Laughing at Shorts</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369406452478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:40:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"So, what is this? The latest attempt to construct an exit strategy? Get real. Haswell a week from Monday. ARM in freefall. Go find a nice fork and stick it in yourselves. You're done..." [Another day, another failed short exit strategy. And here come Haswell and we have confirmation of Samsung using Intel Inside. ARM lost over 5 bucks this week. ARM investors now recognize the Intel threat. What is the matter with the brain dead on Wall Street???] 2013: Year of the Intel Tablet 2014: Year of the Intel Smartphone</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369423380701</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:23:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369423454663-141</Id><Title>Who give a flying turd about Silvermont or Haswell</Title><Msg>This POS will never rise because the biggest money plays this like an accordion. The tech that tech makes don't mean anything if greedy people only want to profit by manipulating the shares of companies.</Msg><Username>boiled_n_oil</Username><Timestamp>1369423454663</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:24:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369423605846-142</Id><Title>Tizen Linux demo on an ultrabook (video)</Title><Msg>Tizen Linux demo on an ultrabook (video) Email Tizen is a Linux-based operating system that’s backed by Samsung and which is expected to ship on Samsung smartphones this year. But the OS isn’t just for mobile devices like phones and tablets. The folks at Tizen Experts got a chance to check out an early demo of Tizen running on an ultrabook, and it looks like a pretty it offers a pretty decent desktop Linux-style user experience. But like the smartphone version of Tizen, there’s an emphasis on running web apps as well as native apps. Tizen ultrabook Tizen’s notebook/desktop environment is based on GNOME Shell 3, and it comes with the ability to run native Linux apps such as LibreOffice and the Chrome web browser. But Tizen is developing a custom version of the home screen and app launcher called Tizen Shell, and supports installing and running web apps so that you can run them as if they were native apps downloaded and installed to your computer. Tizen can also handle the Steam gaming platform for Linux as long as you have a computer with decent 3D graphics capabilities. Much of what makes Tizen exciting is the operating’s system on mobile devices including phones and tablets — something that other GNU/Linux operating systems such as Ubuntu are just getting started on. But it’s interesting to see that it’ll also be available for traditional PCs. The demo video shows the operating system running on an ultrabook with an Intel Core i7 Ivy Bridge processor, but the OS can run on devices with slower processors. The code for the notebook/desktop version of Tizen shown off in the video will eventually be released as part of Tizen 3.0. As of mid-May 2013, the latest stable version of the operating system is Tizen 2.1.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369423605846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:26:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369423710330-143</Id><Title>Intel, MediaTek and Elan taking up 60% of global touchscreen controller market</Title><Msg>Intel, MediaTek and Elan Microelectronics combined have taken up over 60% of global touchscreen controller ICs market, according to industry sources. The global touchscreen controller chip market has been expanding at a CAGR of over 20% in recent years, attracting at least 50 chipset suppliers, including more than 20 in Taiwan, to step into the segment, the sources noted. MediaTek and its associated companies MStar Semiconductor and Goodix Technology together have a production capacity of 10 million touchscreen controller ICs a month currently, the sources revealed. Intel has been increasing its presence in the touch controller IC segment through its investments in IC design houses, including FocalTech Systems and Egalaxy-empia Technology (EETI). From Digitimes</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369423710330</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369423793724-144</Id><Topic><Title>Laughing at Shorts</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369406452478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:40:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another day of short frustration and impotence. Ho, hum...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369423793724</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:29:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369423881205-145</Id><Topic><Title>Redwood GT-I8805: Samsung Device Running Tizen OS Spotted Online</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369422091561</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:01:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Article mentions 8805 and 8800. According to the article - the one pictured is using a Samsung processor; it is the 8800. Does the 8800 use an Intel processor.?. I'm not trying to throw cold water on the news because I think long term it is a positive for Intel and I'm glad for it. I'd like to get clarification on what's in the pipeline. Supposedly there will be more big announcements at the Tizen conference.</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1369423881205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:31:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369423896911-146</Id><Title>ARM Slide Continues</Title><Msg>And will probably get worse as the strength of Intel's roadmap becomes more and more apparent...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369423896911</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:31:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369423995629-147</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Slide Continues</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369423896911</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:31:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another 12 hour work day for WW as evidenced by nonstop posting 7 days a week. He works hard and pays his fair share.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1369423995629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:33:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369424167256-148</Id><Topic><Title>PROBLEM FOR INTEL IS: MARGINS AND REVENUES WILL SHRINK SHARPLY GOING FORWARD IN 2014</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369422273578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just realized something: Nuff is holding AMD and most likely down substantially.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369424167256</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:36:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369424237445-149</Id><Topic><Title>Laughing at Shorts</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369406452478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:40:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Wally, years of holding INTC and only dividends to show for it, less the price drop, and a poor trade on his ARMH put entered when armh was still a lowly 44.00. Could have "covered" at 40.00, but na,not waldo, no gains. Keep the pumping coming Waldo. Intc's no longer 24.00. Net, net, a zero sum game sitting on your hands. may as well go buy some CRUS, a nice low pe, just as it had when it was 45.00 on its way to the 17's.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369424237445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:37:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369424484257-150</Id><Title>dont laugh too hard you will pay being a long here</Title><Msg>Yep we have at least a 10 to 15% sell-off here easy. Thats how over priced over valued we are. Markets think all central banks printing holds stocks up no matter what. All easy money made with that pyramid scheme. Its time for shorts to take markets back to reality.</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1369424484257</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:41:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369425279163-151</Id><Topic><Title>Tizen Linux demo on an ultrabook (video)</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369423605846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:26:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's easy to envision why Samsung would want to push their own branded Linux for mobile devices. Tizen may have value if it offers an alternative to the application bloat Google forces on Android users. However, its difficult to envision Tizen offering much of anything novel on laptops that existing versions of Linux can't already do. In any case, it's all upside for Intel because it all runs on x86 out of the box.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369425279163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:54:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369425287441-152</Id><Topic><Title>dont laugh too hard you will pay being a long here</Title><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1369424484257</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:41:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I remember watching you post on the Oracle board one time after earnings. It was at 28 and you said it would dip to near 20. It ran to 33 and you vanished. You take no responsibility for your own ignorance and are a laughable disaster.</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1369425287441</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369425328925-153</Id><Topic><Title>Redwood GT-I8805: Samsung Device Running Tizen OS Spotted Online</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369422091561</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:01:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am certain the pipleline is diverse. Now that good processors are available. As stated: Recently, Mark Skarpness, director of systems engineering at Intel, stated "It's ready to be built into products and it's ready for you to build your applications against."</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369425328925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369425767113-154</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Poops on Boy Scouts of America</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1369405726862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you were clear. You learned about the BSA decision yesterday because that is when it was decided. You also learned about the July 2012 Intel support withdrawal from the BSA because their discrimination policy violated Intel's policy. My point is also simple. If the BSA policy of discrimination was important to you before yesterday, you would have known about Intel having to withdraw support and would have been outraged months ago. It appears to me that your complaint is not genuine. Just my opinion and I can be wrong. Thank you for your concern about the wreckage of civilization. I would encourage you to be on guard from extremist ideology from both the extreme left and extreme right. Both extremes have been very damaging and have rarely benefited civilization.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369425767113</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 16:02:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369426246638-155</Id><Topic><Title>dont laugh too hard you will pay being a long here</Title><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1369424484257</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:41:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you. Finally, someone calling it like it is.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369426246638</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 16:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369426512212-156</Id><Title>This pig is down again today. Mr Weaver probably posted another</Title><Msg>ton of posts, or some Analyst bad mouthed the pig.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369426512212</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 16:15:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369428169625-157</Id><Topic><Title>PROBLEM FOR INTEL IS: MARGINS AND REVENUES WILL SHRINK SHARPLY GOING FORWARD IN 2014</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1369422273578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 15:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL @ AMD. Are they still in business?</Msg><Username>jj_the_homo</Username><Timestamp>1369428169625</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 16:42:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369430736157-158</Id><Title>Will Obamacare Leave Your Spouse Behind?</Title><Msg>Will Obamacare Leave Your Spouse Behind? By Meghan Foley | More Articles May 23, 2013 The Affordable Care Act will begin rolling out in October, and it will bring sweeping changes to how Americans get healthcare coverage. In particular, superstore-like state health exchanges — that are meant to make shopping for health insurance easier and more affordable — will open for enrollment this fall. NEW! Discover a new stock idea each week for less than the cost of 1 trade. CLICK HERE for your Weekly Stock Cheat Sheets NOW! That Obamacare is controversial is undeniable. Republicans have attempted 37 times to repeal the bill or de-fund it, arguing that it will expand the powers of the federal government too far, or hurt small businesses, or put a heavy burden on the country’s finances. And where political objections end, economic objections begin. Industry experts have argued that the reform will not improve the healthcare system in America. This sentiment is best expressed by Democratic Senator Max Baucus — a key architect of the healthcare reform law — who told Health and Human Services Secretary Kathleen Sebelius at an April hearing that he is concerned that the implementation of the Obama administration’s signature healthcare law will be a train wreck One group that will surely see its coverage change, and probably not for the best: spouses. Despite the fact that Obamacare mandates that businesses with 50 or more employees provide health insurance for their workers and their dependents or pay a penalty, it will not require employers to cover spouses. The law only defines children as dependents. Before the Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act was enacted into law, approximately 150 million Americans received health insurance through their jobs and this insurance provided coverage to many husbands and wives as well. Many healthcare law authorities say that the change will not result in any big changes in the way that employers provide insurance for husbands and wives. But that may not necessarily be the case. NEW! Discover a new stock idea each week for less than the cost of 1 trade. CLICK HERE for your Weekly Stock Cheat Sheets NOW! The legislation’s provisions represent a significant divergence from current standards. “Right now there are virtually no employers that just offer coverage for the employee and their children,” healthcare law expert Tim Jost told Mother Jones. “Whether that will change or not, who knows. We will probably see at least some employers who will offer individual and child coverage, but not coverage for spouses.” He regularly consults with the Obama administration on the implementation of the Affordable Care Act. In the case of a higher earning family — say one that brings in more than $94,000 per year, an income greater than what 78 percent of households earn — health insurance costs could greatly increase. If a spouse is dropped from a husband’s or wife’s insurance, the household income would disqualify him or her from receiving a government subsidy to purchase insurance on the government-run insurance exchanges. The uncovered spouse would then have to purchase private insurance, which could costs hundreds of dollars per month. If the dropped spouse is a middle income earner or poor, he or she will be able to shop on the exchange with a subsidy. But even then, coverage is not free, although the idea is that it will be at least affordable. When people buy coverage on the exchange, the subsidy will be based on household income, measured before the household pays for the employer-provided health insurance. The law stipulates that employer-provided health insurance must cover a set of core benefits and be affordable — which the law defines as premiums costing no more than 9.5 percent of an employee’s income. Added on top of those insurance costs, the family will be paying for the spouse’s subsidy on the exchange, which will based on that much higher pre-healthcare-costs income level. NEW! Discover a new stock idea each week for less than the cost of 1 trade. CLICK HERE for your Weekly Stock Cheat Sheets NOW! “It’s a potential problem,” Ethan Rome, executive director of Health Care for America Now, a group that backs Obamacare, told the publication. “There could be some folks that get lost in the shuffle. And that is not insignificant…If you’re one of few people adversely affected by something, it doesn’t matter that everyone else on the planet is getting the benefit.” It should be noted that 30 million people, who are currently without insurance, will get coverage under Obamacare. Other industry experts believe that it is unlikely that too many employers will drop spouses. “Family coverage is valued employee benefit,” she told Mother Jones. “I don’t see that this provision is going to change what employers do.” Rome agreed with her stance, “If you are an employer and you provide good quality health care for your employees, including dependent coverage, it’s because you understand that a good benefits package is the best way to recruit and retain top-notch employees.” Follow Meghan on Twitter @MFoley_WSCS</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369430736157</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 17:25:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369438297907-159</Id><Title>I thought this was suppose to be at 28 by now ??? gotta laugh..or cry..</Title><Msg>what happened to all the Cisco, Google, Hasbeen, TV, watches, and all the other big pops ??? hilarious stuff really.</Msg><Username>dominateamerika</Username><Timestamp>1369438297907</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 19:31:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369439453637-160</Id><Title>Laughing Even Harder at the Shorts</Title><Msg>Intel shorts demonstrate their frustration over being five bucks down since November and ARM being in freefall by another batch of content-free posting. Shorts believe every argument can be addressed or rebutted with a content-free response. Undoubtedly they will respond to this post with yet another batch of messages with no arguments, no logic, no support, no due diligence and no intelligence. At least their responses are good for a laugh...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369439453637</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 19:50:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369439730965-161</Id><Title>Intel: Haswell will draw 50% less power than Ivy Bridge</Title><Msg>Intel has preempted its formal Haswell unveil to announce that its chips will draw “50% less power” than Ivy Bridge on “active” workloads, such as playing a game or watching a movie. This is a dramatic turnaround, considering the latest leaks and rumors had suggested that Haswell was struggling to reach its TDP targets. Perhaps more importantly, though, Intel also put a figure on its efforts to cut idle power consumption, which is one of key areas that was targeted by the architectural changes between Ivy Bridge and Haswell. According to Intel, Haswell’s idle power consumption is 20 times less than Ivy Bridge. ”This means that the fourth-generation Core-based products will provide the biggest battery life increase in Intel’s history,” the general manager of Intel’s architecture group, Rani Borkar, told reporters yesterday. From extremetech</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369439730965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 19:55:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369439790941-162</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Haswell will draw 50% less power than Ivy Bridge</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369439730965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 19:55:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Borkar went on to say that the lowest-power Haswell chips, which are probably destined for expensive tablets (such as the Surface Pro’s successor), have a TDP as low as 7W, down from 10W for the most conscientious Ivy Bridge parts. Perhaps betraying her Indian heritage, Borkar said that the new Haswell chips would power devices that have enough battery life to watch three Bollywood-length movies. It goes without saying, but these power savings don’t come at the expense of performance: Depending on the form factor, Haswell should be the same as, or faster than Ivy Bridge.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369439790941</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 19:56:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369439848710-163</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Haswell will draw 50% less power than Ivy Bridge</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369439730965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 19:55:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From what we do know already, from leaked slides and IDF briefings, a lot of these power savings stem from the fact that this is a tock in Intel’s tick-tock manufacturing model. Whereas Ivy Bridge used the same architecture as Sandy Bridge, but shrunk to 22nm, Haswell is an entirely new architecture that’s designed from the ground up to make use of Intel’s 22nm FinFET transistors. We also know that a significant focus of the Haswell architecture is improved power gating, lower-power modes, and getting into low-power modes quickly. Way back at IDF 2011, Intel also stated that it will also help manufacturers choose the right components to reduce overall system power, which is generally a much larger hog than the CPU, too. All told, we expect Haswell to be a beast of a chip. It probably won’t make huge waves on the top end (expect a 10% improvement over Ivy Bridge), but it really does look like Haswell will be incredibly power efficient.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369439848710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 19:57:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369440089603-164</Id><Title>Next week, INTC will go down again as the market corrects. Mr Weaver</Title><Msg>meanwhile will keep pumping her up.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369440089603</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 20:01:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369440263832-165</Id><Topic><Title>Sad to see INTC trading so poorly</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369407102957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:51:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2 years? why 2 years. too convenient.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1369440263832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 20:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369440460855-166</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Haswell will draw 50% less power than Ivy Bridge</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369439730965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 19:55:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Improvements this significant in performance, power efficiency, battery life, carrying weight and compelling pricing are the reasons so many owners of Vista era PCs and notebooks will be replacing their older systems.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369440460855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 20:07:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369452694736-167</Id><Topic><Title>Intel: Haswell will draw 50% less power than Ivy Bridge</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369439730965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 19:55:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This should be excellent for the high end tablet and notebook space.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1369452694736</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 23:31:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369453062844-168</Id><Topic><Title>Sad to see INTC trading so poorly</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369407102957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 10:51:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"what if you run a few years?" I did not know what you meant by your statement. You could have been talking about the chart comparison or the short interest. A few is more than one but less than many. 2 fits that definition doesn't it???</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369453062844</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 23:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369453455859-169</Id><Topic><Title>Laughing Even Harder at the Shorts</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369439453637</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 19:50:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are just too funny for words. You act like some hot shot making tons of money on INTC, yet here we are, almost 3 years after your you'll be fine in 6 months if you bgt Intc at 24.00 on it's way to the 17's, and INTC sits, yet again, under 24.00, failing to sell at 29, on it's way back to the 19's and not smart enough to capture gains on armh when it previously plummeted to 40. Your non stop pumping has yielded a total lack of capital gains in almost 3 years. Good thing you don't work for Donald Trump as that kind of performance would lead to no job.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369453455859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 23:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369453689114-170</Id><Title>INTC Short Interest: 5/15/2013 224,949,744 : down 8.5m shares</Title><Msg>On 2/28, the short interest was 216mil shares and trading at $20.69. On 5/15, the short interest was 224mil shares and INTC was trading HIGHER by 17% at $24.20. INTC is trading 17% higher with a larger short interest. 5/15/2013 224,949,744 closing price $24.20 4/30/2013 233,212,213 closing price $23.73 4/15/2013 235,467,126 closing price $21.18 3/28/2013 238,762,872 closing price $21.64 3/15/2013 233,896,426 closing price $21.18 2/28/2013 216,006,917 closing price $20.69</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369453689114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 23:48:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369453855093-171</Id><Topic><Title>Laughing Even Harder at the Shorts</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369439453637</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 19:50:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>donald trump is a tool! his daughter's hot though</Msg><Username>wallstsx</Username><Timestamp>1369453855093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 23:50:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>