<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369221005547-1</Id><Topic><Title>Intel planning new devices unit led by former Apple exec</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369177633020</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 19:07:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The big picture here is that Intel is funding innovation. Apple took itself out of the leadership role a couple of years ago. The industry has certainly needed investment and leadership in this area. While Intel really can't be the next Apple since its not a consumer products company the point is clear that a few mildly successful new products can change the fortune of Intel. For years Intel has been investing five years out or further in R&amp;D. Very few companies can afford to do this. The question is why has it taken Intel this long to be in this position? It wasn't too long ago that Intel was working at full capacity and perhaps had products on allocation. With all it's new volume Intel is signaling that it wants to be more than a me too commodity SoC player that others on here have predicted. Also, five years ago Steve Jobs was alive and in charge of the helm of Apple's destiny. Had he lived industry leadership in innovation would have been much harder with Apple able to seize on new innovations better than anybody else in the industry. What you are seeing right now is a leaderless industry with slightly modified versions of the same stuff we've had for the last three years. The industry is craving change.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1369221005547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 07:10:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369224337791-2</Id><Title>Looks like another pathetic day for INTC</Title><Msg>OTOH look at VNQ. For over two months I have been recommending you buy it. Buy Starbucks, Green Mountain, Costco and CVS. I made these recommendations months ago too and almost every day a new 52 week high.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369224337791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:05:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369224367684-3</Id><Title>Tizen: Meet the Asian Android-Killer From Intel and Samsung</Title><Msg>Tizen: Meet the Asian Android-Killer From Intel and Samsung By André Mouton Mar 18, 2013 9:00 am Tizen will retain Android's more desirable features, like the low price tag and the cross-compatibility between markets, but it will also leave room for regional adaptation. 37 37 PrintPRINT 2 Comments URGENT BUY ALERT: Top 12 Stocks for 2013 - FREE! Click Now! Stay Connected Twitter Facebook Google + RSS Feed Tizen, the new mobile OS from Samsung (KRX:005930) and Intel (NASDAQ:INTC), is a lot like Android (NASDAQ:GOOG). Both operating systems are open source and Linux-based. They look and feel about the same, and smartphone users won’t have any problem switching between the two. Their logos, however, suggest a difference. When Google chose a personable green robot to represent Android, it was selling the system’s intelligence, with its integrated "brain" of Google Web apps and services. Tizen, on the other hand, is portrayed as a pinwheel – a toy that spins in whatever direction the wind is blowing. In other words, it’s a platform that doesn’t discriminate. Android has had a remarkably successful run in the four years since it debuted. Today, it comes on about half of the smartphones sold globally. In emerging markets, though – and Asia in particular – this success has been an awkward one. Google might be the dominant search engine and Web services provider in the US and Europe, but across the Pacific, that position is held by the likes of Baidu (NASDAQ:BIDU), Naver (KRX:035420), and Yahoo Japan (TYO:4689). Google’s Web apps are not always available, and when they are, they’re not generally preferred. The fact that Android is free, and has a large application base, means that manufacturers have adopted it anyway, but they’ve been forced to offer customized versions that strip away the Google content and replace it with less native content. samsung tizen The situation has become particularly bad in Chi</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369224367684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:06:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369225706370-4</Id><Title>Gosh it would be fun to be Intel CEO</Title><Msg>Get to stand on the shoulders of giants, like Ottelini, who has positioned the company for global domination. Get to launch a bazillion new devices...this is the next AAPL. This stock is heading to $1000/share.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1369225706370</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:28:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369225862516-5</Id><Topic><Title>Intel planning new devices unit led by former Apple exec</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369177633020</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 19:07:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when did Otellini fire you?</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1369225862516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:31:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369227263516-6</Id><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Msg>I'm very curious to see what ARM does at the open to see if the big drop from yesterday continues. Just when we thought the stock was headed to 100, it now appears that the bottom is dropping out. Given its huge swings, I plan on just watching today. If it drops another buck or two I will consider adding to my modest put position. With Haswell due a week from Monday I can't imagine what ARM investors are thinking. The iWatch rumors are heating up again. And Intel has a new focus on mobility while tablet sales are doubling. Why isn't everyone selling ARM at this point???</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369227792538-7</Id><Title>6 Reasons Why The iPhone Will Soon Have Processors Built By Intel</Title><Msg>[Crazier things have happened. We will know more when we see which way the iWatch deal breaks...] Six reasons why the iPhone will soon have processors built by Intel: Apple (AAPL) needs to have the best technology to continue to provide cutting edge products and to be able to charge the premium it has charged in the past. Intel (INTC) needs to put its processors in smartphones. The smartphone market is growing rapidly. Intel will make more money by building the iPhone processor than not. Intel will soon have excess capacity in its fabs (semiconductor chip factories). Apple will pay less per processor buying from Intel, compared to its current supplier Samsung (SSNLF.PK), or its other alternative TSMC (TSM). Apple and Intel would both find strategic advantages in such a deal. Despite the widespread belief that Intel is a microprocessor company, its distinguishing characteristic is that it is a leader in the manufacturing of integrated circuits. Intel's microprocessor design division is really just a way to ensure its fabs are full of high value semiconductors. I have listed six reasons why this will eventually occur, but I have not specified the processor. Two scenarios exist: Scenario 1. Apple could put an Intel designed Atom processor in the iPhone, or Scenario 2. Intel could act as a foundry for the A series, and produce those Apple designed A series (A7 or A8) for the iPhones. The six reasons above apply to both scenarios. More details on the six reasons are listed below. By Jim Brody</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227792538</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:03:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369228835753-8</Id><Title>Just A Thought</Title><Msg>Nobody knows for sure when this rally will end but everybody seems to agree that stocks are very overbought. Another day of gains could push the RSI readings of the major indexes to the highest level since the rally started in November. The Russell 2000 once again backed off at the 1000 level yesterday, suggesting that the rally is due for a rest. However, sometimes the market doesn't follow the path that technical conditions say it should.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369228835753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:20:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369228866792-9</Id><Topic><Title>6 Reasons Why The iPhone Will Soon Have Processors Built By Intel</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227792538</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:03:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple needs time to prepare its ecosystem for this change. Best guess is that they make the switch with Intel's 14nm products by mid-2014. Without Intel's 14nm product it is difficult to imagine how Apple could expect the iPhone to be exciting or even competitive.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369228866792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369228897333-10</Id><Title>Intel Ready to Go with 10nm</Title><Msg>"Mayberry said that everything up to the 10-nm CMOS node – which is in development at Intel and will ramp production in 2015 - is effectively done. However, he said his job depends on being able to continue to double density and performance every two years beyond that, something for which the way forward is much less clear." From EETimes Article: Industry needs to up its research game, says Intel [Apparently I missed putting the IMEC Technology Forum on the calendar. Happened today in Belgium...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369228897333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:21:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369229021488-11</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now down 1.02 pre-opening...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369229021488</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:23:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369229120109-12</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like another pathetic day for INTC</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369224337791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:05:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NOTHING creates more geniuses than a strong BULL market with everything up. The insecure are seen running to the front of the parade so they can think they are "leaders". Intel will do fine.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369229120109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369229868690-13</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The word is getting out how many top tier vendors will be making devices with Intel's products and the change in industry behavior has to have an impact on ARMH's prospects. Margins will be impacted first followed by top line revenue. This is long overdue.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369229868690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:37:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369229892273-14</Id><Title>Will Apple build its own fab to help placate congress and chip supply ?</Title><Msg>They brought the chip design in house, will they bring the fab in house. ? I think they are considering it.</Msg><Username>repklikint</Username><Timestamp>1369229892273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:38:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369230128196-15</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>would have been a nice quick profit had you bought it there lol</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369230128196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:42:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369230308883-16</Id><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Msg>The short exit strategy blew up on the launching pad. The results will put the shorts in the House of Pain for an extended period of time...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369230308883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369230675921-17</Id><Title>Okay What Just Happened?</Title><Msg>Anyone? We just made a big move up...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369230675921</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369230703189-18</Id><Title>It will be in the red zone soon</Title><Msg>Just wait and be patient. This is unsustainable.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369230703189</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369230826178-19</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM moving up like a rocket. But still not in the green. LOL Let's see if there are enough sheep to move it back up today...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369230826178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:53:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369230907865-20</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARHM is green for now...</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369230907865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:55:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369230956398-21</Id><Title>Shorts Now Down $5.20 Since November</Title><Msg>And Haswell a week from Monday. But watch out. That content-free posting could kick in any minute...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369230956398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:55:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369231058213-22</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's laugh out loud funny. I love those ARM investors! And manipulators...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369231058213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:57:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369231067082-23</Id><Title>IT HAS BEGUN!</Title><Msg>PUSH TO $28 NEAR TERM AND $40 BY END OF YEAR!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369231067082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369231067494-24</Id><Topic><Title>It will be in the red zone soon</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369230703189</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:51:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if something happens soon, there is no need to wait and be patient...just stop confusing yourself</Msg><Username>ttcolo</Username><Timestamp>1369231067494</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369231111814-25</Id><Title>MORE BONE FOR THE SHORTDOG</Title><Msg>How do you like it shorty?Just keep shorting,we all love you.</Msg><Username>bigcraigc</Username><Timestamp>1369231111814</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:58:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369231167036-26</Id><Topic><Title>It will be in the red zone soon</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369230703189</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:51:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the good news is that if it gets back to 24.50, there will be some bearish negative divergence on the chart.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369231167036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:59:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369231235716-27</Id><Topic><Title>It will be in the red zone soon</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369230703189</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:51:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thoughts on changing your name to "I take back my opinion" ?</Msg><Username>mark.steffenhagen</Username><Timestamp>1369231235716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:00:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369231309926-28</Id><Title>WARNING TO SHORTS: COVER NOW!</Title><Msg>THIS THING IS GOING PARABOLIC!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369231309926</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:01:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369231397059-29</Id><Topic><Title>MORE BONE FOR THE SHORTDOG</Title><Username>bigcraigc</Username><Timestamp>1369231111814</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:58:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just so long as they don't pee on my lawn.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1369231397059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:03:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369231413769-30</Id><Topic><Title>IT HAS BEGUN!</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369231067082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YAHOOOOOOOOO</Msg><Username>bigcraigc</Username><Timestamp>1369231413769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:03:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369231456301-31</Id><Title>BRUCE raise the dividend now</Title><Msg>Its a good way to start off!</Msg><Username>a33stacybb</Username><Timestamp>1369231456301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:04:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369231534841-32</Id><Title>OK it is acting like a good stock now.</Title><Msg>and to think Wally is still way under water !!!</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369231534841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:05:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369231581977-33</Id><Topic><Title>Okay What Just Happened?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369230675921</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:51:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>people are figuring out that the developing world smart phone purchases are growing by triple digits. these phones are sub-$100 phones. INTC is in these phones. INTC is entering Tablets. INTC owns PCs, which are not dead by a long shot. Haswell will own tablets and phones. By early 2016, INTC will be in every PC, tablet, phone, watch, etc... while still being ahead by at least one generation in fabrication, not even counting the advantage 450mm wafers will bring. we will see a P/E adjustment soon along with a forward looking EPS, not ttm. IMHO.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1369231581977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:06:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369231615120-34</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Galaxy Tab win, if confirmed, is sooo important. It means Intel won't have to really fight to get into the best selling mobile vendor outside of Apple. just needs to keep producing the best mobile processor every new year and it could be used. The ARM mobile market is basically split amongst the cheap small die chips at the low end and the highest performance chips at the high end. The low-end market Intel can attack with its n-1 process chips, e.g. Clovertrail+ when Silvermont arrives, by selling at wafer cost and the n process chips like Silvermont can attack the high end. Every year the mobile device vendors demand a superior performing chip to last year's model, so far ARM has fulfilled this need by going A8, dual-core A9, quad-core A9, quad-core A15. What is it going to do for next year though ? Is either 20nm or A57 ready ? This leaves an opportunity for Intel to move in with quad-core Silvermont if neither are ready in volume. Maybe TSMC's 20nm might be ready for volume in 2014 but will Samsung's considering they need to switch to gate-last at the same time ? I would say there is a strong possibility that the Samsung Galaxy S5 will contain a quad-core Silvermont if a 20nm Extnos Octa is not ready in time which will be some volume !</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1369231615120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:06:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369231686359-35</Id><Topic><Title>Okay What Just Happened?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369230675921</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:51:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GREAT POST!!!!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369231686359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369231769823-36</Id><Topic><Title>BRUCE raise the dividend now</Title><Username>a33stacybb</Username><Timestamp>1369231456301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:04:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the AUG dividend will be raised, probably to $1. as to when they announce, who knows? seriously, who knows?</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1369231769823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369231829743-37</Id><Topic><Title>Okay What Just Happened?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369230675921</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:51:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a better theory, or at least one that's more fun. Someone influential person has advance knowledge of some announcement about to be made, and starts buying. Other people who watch the influential so-and-so start buying as followers. Demand increases enough to bump the price 1%.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1369231829743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:10:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369231967906-38</Id><Title>VNQ hits another 52 week high</Title><Msg>It is the no 1 performing ETF this year and pays a very nice dividend. Go ahead and hold onto this laggard. INTC is dead money boys.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369231967906</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369232087159-39</Id><Title>Don't buy the headfake</Title><Msg>They are fooling you into buying more and they watch as it finishes in the red today (or lower by the end of the week)</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369232087159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:14:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369232272546-40</Id><Topic><Title>Okay What Just Happened?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369230675921</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:51:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no one more amazed than Wally and he is still at a loss.. lol</Msg><Username>aintezbeingreen</Username><Timestamp>1369232272546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:17:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369232361779-41</Id><Topic><Title>Don't buy the headfake</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369232087159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:14:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go away you stupid silly troll. No-one has asked for your opinion or wants you here.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1369232361779</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:19:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369232734094-42</Id><Topic><Title>Okay What Just Happened?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369230675921</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:51:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>haha. that would be way better. i bought the jan14 30 calls for .19, yesterday. not a lot of money, but a big move would help turn it into a lot of money. 2.25 eps and a market average PE would be a great start. dare to dream.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1369232734094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:25:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369232771557-43</Id><Title>24.50 that's all the upside ?</Title><Msg>Watch the tanking begin as weak hands jump ship</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369232771557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:26:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369233263176-44</Id><Title>One-fourth of average daily volume in one hour</Title><Msg>11 million Intel shares traded with prices moving up. Average daily volume is 43 million. Bodes well for further upward movement.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1369233263176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:34:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369233359270-45</Id><Topic><Title>24.50 that's all the upside ?</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369232771557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:26:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nah, 24.52 so Wally can jump for joy about being up .50 since 2010 as the markets, sans INTC hit new highs again because the Bernake said what everyone already knew,</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369233359270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:35:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369233388589-46</Id><Topic><Title>VNQ hits another 52 week high</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369231967906</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:12:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are going to have to chose a better WHITE KNIGHT. This Year, INTC is up more and pays a higher dividend. Are all your best investment ideas performing worse than dead money? VNQ YTD up 16.4% Yield 3.37% INTC YTD up 23.7% Yield 3.7% 2-Jan Today %up INTC $20.62 $25.50 23.7% VNQ $67.74 $78.82 16.4%</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369233388589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369233696790-47</Id><Topic><Title>VNQ hits another 52 week high</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369231967906</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:12:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I sold 500 June 24 calls for a huge gain between 81 and 84 cents. ;^) Will buy some more July 24s and 25s if the price continues to go down.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369233696790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:41:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369233720641-48</Id><Title>HAHAHAHA red zone soon</Title><Msg>Just another headfake with many more to come</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369233720641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369233808327-49</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Almost $4 down from its $50 high. That is a pretty steep drop. Yes, the market is finally beginning to figure out that Intel is going to come out on top. And I think this is only going to accelerate with Haswell, multi-mode LTE, Bay Trail, and Merrifield. Haswell and multi-mode LTE should be out in June. Bay Trail should be shipping soon if the devices are to be available for back-to-school season. Would be great if they can pull in Merrifield by a quarter or two (Q3 or Q4 instead of early 2014).</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1369233808327</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:43:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369234337003-50</Id><Topic><Title>Okay What Just Happened?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369230675921</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:51:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spike..looks like it's now leaking air.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1369234337003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:52:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369234436692-51</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369230308883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are an expert about the house of pain for sure.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1369234436692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:53:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369234529564-52</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So much for the ARM green...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369234529564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369234599625-53</Id><Topic><Title>Okay What Just Happened?</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369230675921</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:51:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now thats some market volatility, a huge drop in the SQQQ down to new lows at 25.27 followed by a huge move up to 25.84 and rising again, very nice reversal. could today have been the short term peak in the markets?</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369234599625</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:56:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369234985672-54</Id><Topic><Title>Rumor: Apple testing 1.5" OLED displays for wearable 'iWatch'</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369095874595</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:24:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Intel is involved with the iWatch, the additional revenue would be icing on the cake as everything is funded by CPU business</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369234985672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:03:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369235011600-55</Id><Topic><Title>WARNING TO SHORTS: COVER NOW!</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369231309926</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:01:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you covered yet shortboy? Might just be your last chance.</Msg><Username>bigcraigc</Username><Timestamp>1369235011600</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:03:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369235055768-56</Id><Topic><Title>Structural Change In The Mobile Processor Marketplace: Intel Wins; ARM, AMD Lose</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369096348557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:32:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great article</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369235055768</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:04:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369235163286-57</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung To Use Intel Atom Processor In Its New 10” Tablet</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369107837268</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:43:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great info</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369235163286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369235243759-58</Id><Topic><Title>Symphony Teleca Booth #26 and Samsung Booth, Zone 2</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369164977760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 15:36:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tizen Developer Conference...starting today</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369235243759</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:07:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369235255785-59</Id><Title>MISM looks prime for a breakout</Title><Msg>I am getting all the MISM I can at these levels. Check their website and financials. This thing is so undervalued here.</Msg><Username>adamkelly804</Username><Timestamp>1369235255785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:07:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369235478840-60</Id><Title>Good summary by jflaherty</Title><Msg>jflaherty • 1 hour 3 minutes ago people are figuring out that the developing world smart phone purchases are growing by triple digits. these phones are sub-$100 phones. INTC is in these phones. INTC is entering Tablets. INTC owns PCs, which are not dead by a long shot. Haswell will own tablets and phones. By early 2016, INTC will be in every PC, tablet, phone, watch, etc... while still being ahead by at least one generation in fabrication, not even counting the advantage 450mm wafers will bring. we will see a P/E adjustment soon along with a forward looking EPS, not ttm. IMHO.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369235478840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:11:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369236194936-61</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung To Use Intel Atom Processor In Its New 10” Tablet</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369107837268</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:43:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUY THE RUMOR</Msg><Username>bigcraigc</Username><Timestamp>1369236194936</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369236526907-62</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What'cho talkin bout, up .11</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369236526907</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369237023860-63</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung To Use Intel Atom Processor In Its New 10” Tablet</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369107837268</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:43:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It isn't a rumor.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369237023860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:37:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369237405420-64</Id><Topic><Title>VNQ hits another 52 week high</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369231967906</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:12:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your comments on any subject have no value whatsoever. It's just a total waste of ink. Please consider doing away with yourself.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369237405420</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:43:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369238244702-65</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Touchscreen Notebook Shipments Increased by 51.8% in Q1 2013</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1369188204316</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 22:03:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great info!</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369238244702</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:57:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369238280820-66</Id><Title>It Will Be Nice</Title><Msg>if the fed keeps on printing and the mkts keep the rally going on for the next 10 years until I retire by then hopefully intc will be over 200 and I can enjoy my retirement.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369238280820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:58:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369238456219-67</Id><Title>Transitioning away from Blackberry</Title><Msg>My company is finally transitioning away from BB. It'll be interesting to see what they go to... There's probably a lot of companies doing this now...</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1369238456219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 12:00:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369238525767-68</Id><Topic><Title>46k in 2 months? net PROFIT</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1366433177700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>signed up</Msg><Username>jackmayor503</Username><Timestamp>1369238525767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 12:02:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369238684342-69</Id><Topic><Title>It Will Be Nice</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369238280820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:58:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the fed will produce yet another bubble that will burst apart in flames, just as all bubbles do. that said, even Roubini believes the rally can continue for some time before the bubble bursts, likely late next year. shades of October 1987</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369238684342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 12:04:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369239234365-70</Id><Topic><Title>Good summary by jflaherty</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369235478840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks. but i think the market is going to take a "wait and see" attitude. unless INTC has a big Q2, and maybe raises guidance, we will only see incremental advance. with a strong Q2, the shorts will be forced to cover and it will be a great summer lead into a strong autumn... unless the world decides to implode again.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1369239234365</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 12:13:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369239662039-71</Id><Topic><Title>It Will Be Nice</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369238280820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:58:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hi wdb, good morn, yes bro I read that article that roubini wrote and he thinks all this will blow up in 2015. he says this could go on for another year or two and then it will end in a massive flash. And yes if the mkt fundamentals cannot support the prices it will. The other reason is that the corporations even though they are making billions every qtr they are not sharing that with their people. We get a 1 percent raise and we are told you are lucky you have a job. With that attitude and with that kind of monetary sharing it does not even keep up with inflation leave alone saving and spending. I don't know which soup kitchen Bernanke goes to get his meals or which pantry he goes to get his weekly donated groceries hence he is out of touch with the real world and inflation. Take care bro.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369239662039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 12:21:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369240980783-72</Id><Title>Japanese banks buying US stocks bigtime</Title><Msg>And they are smart, so probably buying a lot of Intel.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1369240980783</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 12:43:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369241985388-73</Id><Title>just dumped all INTC options</Title><Msg>I sold all INTC options at 24.52....but I still think next 30 days will be very good to intel. Haswel will be a hit. I'm going to buy a lot more call options if this goes under 24 in the next week.</Msg><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1369241985388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 12:59:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369242077701-74</Id><Topic><Title>HAHAHAHA red zone soon</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369233720641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I dont know about red, but back down to 24.15 ~...probably</Msg><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1369242077701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 13:01:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369242407232-75</Id><Title>Intel's New Haswell Chip ; due next month !!!</Title><Msg>seems it will be a BLOCKbuster...moving intel stock over $40.</Msg><Username>oceanbeachvictor</Username><Timestamp>1369242407232</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 13:06:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369242464953-76</Id><Topic><Title>just dumped all INTC options</Title><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1369241985388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 12:59:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I did my laundry today. I think the whites came out better than usual because I switched to Tide. I'll do the colorfasts in the next load, and if there's time, run the dryer too.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1369242464953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 13:07:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369242513870-77</Id><Title>8 yr high 28.38. We are currently 15.8% off that high</Title><Msg>the shorts must be feeling some pain. 233m shares short with an average daily volume of 43m shares. Haswell is well received with critics and companies alike. when the shorts start to cover, we could push the 10 year high of 33.97 by year end.</Msg><Username>jflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1369242513870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 13:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369242602474-78</Id><Topic><Title>just dumped all INTC options</Title><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1369241985388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 12:59:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the markets are quite extended, rsi's extreme, INTC at the level you sold has formed a lower rsi than the prior rsi at the 24.50 level, that's bearish divergence, in most instances not a time to be buying. markets can sell off quite quickly, as the drop this morning at 10:25 shows, the QLD dropped over a dollar in about 30 minutes</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369242602474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 13:10:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369242635084-79</Id><Topic><Title>HAHAHAHA red zone soon</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1369233720641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where's that red zone j-hole? You're comments are re+arded</Msg><Username>brianwilson549</Username><Timestamp>1369242635084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 13:10:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369243440856-80</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's New Haswell Chip ; due next month !!!</Title><Username>oceanbeachvictor</Username><Timestamp>1369242407232</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 13:06:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, I dont know about 40, but it will do nothing but help increase the stock price</Msg><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1369243440856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 13:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369244239060-81</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM now down 7 percent over 5 days. I think the Samsung news was an important factor but also think the new CEO's moves are a part of it. And soon we will have just a flood of new Intel product releases. Some are starting to come out already. But on June 3rd the releases will be enormous. This will provide a lengthy continuation of the Haswell news past the announcement date...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369244239060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 13:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369244439426-82</Id><Title>Incoming Intel CEO Not Wasting Time – Sweeping Changes Coming</Title><Msg>New Intel CEO Brian Krzanich is wasting no time reorganizing the chip-giant Intel. Just a week in to his new position at Intel, Krzanich announced a “sweeping company reorganization” in an internal memo on Monday, according to Reuters. Among the changes is the creation of a “new devices” unit that will develop mobile chipsets quicker in order to become more competitive with Qualcomm, a chip manufacturer for smartphones and tablets. “The group will be tasked with turning cool technology and business model innovations into products that shape and lead markets,” Krzanich said in a statement. PCMag is reporting the head of the “new devices” department will be former executive of Apple and Palm, Mike Bell, who currently co-heads the mobile chip unit. The restructuring is part of Intel’s plan to become more dominant in the mobile device market, which it has had a difficult time breaking into. Rumors have been circulating that Intel will partner with Apple and become a producer of Apple’s A7 chips. If true, this could help bolster Intel’s standing in the mobile market, though market experts point out that ARM-based processors (not the A7) currently dominate the marketplace. Intel spokesman Chuck Mulloy told PCMag: “The primary objective is to move faster, not just with the Intel architecture, not just with mobile, but across the entire company and to be able to move faster into markets as we see them develop.” From highlightpress</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369244439426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 13:40:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369244674608-83</Id><Title>Why did INTC purchase MFE?</Title><Msg>Was it a worth investement?</Msg><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369244674608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 13:44:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369245093868-84</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Waldo, just keep pumping INTC waldo as the qqq goes red</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369245093868</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 13:51:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369245757732-85</Id><Title>Relentless program trading</Title><Msg>just computers....</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369245757732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369245846052-86</Id><Title>$10B investment in INTC = Largest Shareholder Status</Title><Msg>all it takes is $10b to become to the largest shareholder in intel : .... maybe Michael DELL should do it....</Msg><Username>oceanbeachvictor</Username><Timestamp>1369245846052</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:04:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369246392085-87</Id><Topic><Title>Relentless program trading</Title><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369245757732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:02:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very nice day for the sqqq finally broke the 26.38 resistance of the last 2 days, on the upside that it is, very nice reversal day as the bubble loses some of it's luster</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369246392085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:13:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369246794767-88</Id><Title>Momentum Stocls Getting Killed</Title><Msg>PCLN -23 GOOG -16 AZO -7 AMZN -7 ISRG -10 well if easy money flow stops these will be reduced to ashes.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369246794767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:19:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369246878182-89</Id><Title>Looks like Rally is OVER. Correction underway. INTC back to $20</Title><Msg>and Mr Weaver will keep pumping.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369246878182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369247176834-90</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM is now down 85 cents. Any ARM investor that didn't sell or hedge when the stock moved over $50 is totally nuts...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369247176834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369247263207-91</Id><Topic><Title>Why did INTC purchase MFE?</Title><Username>pakaushik</Username><Timestamp>1369244674608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 13:44:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, they get about a billion a year in revenue from it. What do you think?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369247263207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369247364636-92</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Worry about INTC now. Forget ARMH. INTC was just breaking out of a trading range. Then whacked by the market.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369247364636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:29:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369247475286-93</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like Rally is OVER. Correction underway. INTC back to $20</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369246878182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:21:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction, he will keep pumping INTC as he has daily for years.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369247475286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369247488754-94</Id><Title>New Short Victory Cry</Title><Msg>It only went up a little!!!!!!!!! Of course, since the NASDAQ is having a big down day, this still makes shorts losers...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369247488754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:31:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369247552904-95</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like Rally is OVER. Correction underway. INTC back to $20</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369246878182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:21:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and, you will keep making your inane/asinine comments til we all puke.</Msg><Username>jtrader30</Username><Timestamp>1369247552904</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369247601261-96</Id><Topic><Title>New Short Victory Cry</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369247488754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:31:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Of course, since the NASDAQ is having a big down day, this still makes shorts losers..." How??</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369247601261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369247612722-97</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like Rally is OVER. Correction underway. INTC back to $20</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369246878182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:21:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>aw, thanks, I wanted to put you on ignore but had forgotten your handle. now I can do it.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1369247612722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:33:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369247911488-98</Id><Title>anyone get fished in today?</Title><Msg>what a great head fake. I almost fell for it myself. You know, the government should create a regulatory body to oversee the financial markets and to police the blatantly criminal things that go on within it. This would give the citizens more confidence to invest, and thus create a market suited for raising capital to start new companies and develop new products. What a great idea, eh? Hey, what is that thing called the SEC? Is that a lunchtime martini drinking club?</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1369247911488</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:38:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369247917787-99</Id><Title>Former Apple Exec To Head Intel’s New Devices Unit</Title><Msg>Intel is in the process of shaking things up. One big change in the wings is the addition of a new devices unit. Today, AllThingsD is reporting that former Apple executive Mike Bell will be in charge of the new development department. Currently, Bell heads Intel’s mobile chip unit alongside Hermann Eul. When Bell switches to running the new devices unit, Eul will take over the mobile chip department. According to Intel’s new CEO, Brian Krzanich, the new unit will be researching emerging technologies and trending products. “The group will be tasked with turning cool technology and business model innovations into products that shape and lead markets,” Krzanich said in a statement. Reuters recently reported on Intel’s creation of the new devices unit. The reorganization comes only a few days after Krzanich took office. According to unnamed sources who spoke with Reuters, Intel’s new CEO said that the company will be more responsive to customers with an “intensified focus” on the mobile device market. Intel has had a difficult time breaking into the mobile device market. Recent rumors have pointed to a possible partnership with Apple. However, ARM-based processors currently lead the market. If the rumor is true that Intel will be contracted to produce some of Apple’s A7 chips, it could help increase the former’s presence in the market. “The new devices organization is responsible for rapidly turning brilliant technical and business model innovations into products that shape and lead markets,” Krzanich said. From appadvice</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369247917787</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:38:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369247955850-100</Id><Title>Mr Weaver has stopped dissing ARMH and the stock is going down. LOL.</Title><Msg>Mr Weaver is a bad news bear for sure.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369247955850</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:39:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369248224079-101</Id><Topic><Title>New Short Victory Cry</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369247488754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:31:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Um, because shorts expect Intel to trade in sync with the NASDAQ and so expect to have gains on any big NASDAQ down days. Expecting gains and not getting them - Losers...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369248224079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:43:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369248274792-102</Id><Topic><Title>New Short Victory Cry</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369247488754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:31:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They shorted from todays highs and continue. They made plenty.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369248274792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:44:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369248316874-103</Id><Topic><Title>New Short Victory Cry</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369247488754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:31:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's a waldoism, shorthand for a no content post with absolutely no truth to it. but the guess is that waldo is calling intc shorts losers cause it ain't down, but waldo probably wouldn't know a revesal day if someone hit him over the head with it.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369248316874</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:45:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369248364701-104</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM now down over 2 percent today (95 cents). Makes over 7 percent in two days. Downward momentum is building...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369248364701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369248522548-105</Id><Title>#$%$ R D Dip Buyers</Title><Msg>where is the sideline cash that is supposed to come in, guess waiting for a 5-10% correction.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369248522548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:48:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369248576530-106</Id><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Msg>If Apple's only problem was that forthcoming tablets and smartphones made with Intel chips were simply speedier, as in more MIPs or FLOPS I could agree with Eassa's argument,. Apple could conceivably employ a custom ARM with mediocre speed bolted with fast graphics capability and try to compete. But speed is not the only dimension Intel has gained advantage. Intel-based tablets and smartphones should also enjoy far better battery life and while most consumers are ignorant about MIPS and FLOPS they are very well aware of battery life and how long they can go between having to charge up. The other key differentiator is software. Tablets with Intel processors can run professional 64 bit Windows AND Android. This gives Intel tablets the enormous distinction of offering the user access to the millions of mature apps in the Windows ecosystem plus everything Android has to offer. While iPad is just iOS, with no access to MAC OS. The software distinction will be most visible on tablets initially but what Intel does for tablets this year, they will do to smartphones very soon. Every day Apple delays getting on board the Intel train they will find themselves becoming less and less competitive in a sea of faster, better, and cheaper products with superior battery life and far broader software capability.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369248621278-107</Id><Title>INTC tanks on Ashraf's article</Title><Msg>Surprisingly, he believes Apple will not switch to Intel chips. INTC tanked after the article published this afternoon. Not good.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369248621278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:50:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369248624157-108</Id><Title>Powerful Squeeze At Entropic (ENTR)</Title><Msg>RIPE For Squeeze!!!!!!!!! Insider Buying: Cluster Buying-Strongest Signal: SQUEEZE A particularly strong insider buying signal is what we call a “cluster-buy” where three or more different insiders make open market purchases within a short period of one another. ENTR Entropic Commun... BAILEY ROBERT L Director 2013-02-27 Buy 12,000 ENTR Entropic Commun... BECHARD KEITH Director 2012-11-27 Buy 10,000 $4.83 48.3 -12.84 0.00 83.90 370.822 Link ENTR Entropic Commun... MANIAN VAHID Sr VP, Global Operations 2012-11-16 Buy 5,000 $4.51 22.6 -6.65 0.00 83.90 370.822 Link ENTR Entropic Commun... PADVAL UMESH Director 2012-11-16 Buy 5,000 $4.47 22.4 -5.82 0.00 83.90 370.822 Link May 3, 2013 Lyle David CFO 2013-05-03 Buy 10000 $3.93 7.12 33809 Bridges Lance Senior VP and General Counsel 2013-05-03 Buy 20000 $3.93 7.12 96073 FARESE MICHAEL J. Sr VP, Global Engineering 2013-02-21 Buy 3000 $4.43 -4.97 5419 Short Interest (Shares Short) SMALL AMOUNT OF SHARES SHORT •Squeeze Alert POSTED Short Percent of Float DROPPED TO LOWEST POINT 7.91 % Ripe for Squeeze!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Great News Coming Entropic Communications, Inc. : Entropic Achieves MoCA(R) 1.1 Band E Golden Node Certification Entropic, Telepath Deliver First AVS+ High Definition Set-Top Box Platform for China Satellite, Cable/IP and Terrestrial Markets</Msg><Username>maplecherrypie</Username><Timestamp>1369248624157</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369248855466-109</Id><Topic><Title>INTC tanks on Ashraf's article</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369248621278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The whole Nasdaq is tanking. Why is that surprising? If Intel fab'd Apple's chips, they would be shooting their own mobile strategy in the face, and it would be low margin city forever. Long term investors want Intel to take huge market share with its own chips, not to be dependent on Apple.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1369248855466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:54:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369249023408-110</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>merlot_1, Why do you think I would never own Apple? Microsoft's Windows 8 tabs, as well as Android, will eat Apple's products alive long term. Intel will be a major winner in phones/tabs, but it won't be by slapping the faces of its own engineers and building Apple's designed chips ;)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1369249023408</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369249053714-111</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$ R D Dip Buyers</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369248522548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:48:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looking at the qqq daily chart, the macd stopped rising, the bars show waning during the price rise, rsi extreme, macd looked like it wanted to roll down, so we may finally gett more than a one, two day drop in the markets. The bearish divergence in INTC already noted. third time a charm on the SQQQ taking out 26.38. Not time to be buying long, well other than a bear play.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369249053714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:57:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369249258511-112</Id><Topic><Title>INTC tanks on Ashraf's article</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369248621278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If INTC were to take on manuf of AAPL chips it will have to be on INTC terms and NOT IN NO WAY AAPL terms. AAPL is worse than any jewish outfit. They count their pennies. AAPL can squeeze 6 cents out of a nickel. You can hear Tim Cook SQUEEK when he walks. No you don't want to deal with AAPL terms. They are worthless.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369249258511</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369249499050-113</Id><Topic><Title>INTC tanks on Ashraf's article</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369248621278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed. If you think the hype around "Apple could switch to ARM for Macs" is bad, think of how bad it would be for Intel if every other day we heard, "Apple may switch foundries, leaving Intel's fabs idle"? The Android ecosystem is going to eat Apple alive in this space, and I would much prefer Intel is on the winning team.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1369249499050</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:04:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369249560134-114</Id><Title>Time to short intc, buy HP</Title><Msg>Now</Msg><Username>adamwangwang47</Username><Timestamp>1369249560134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:06:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369249940427-115</Id><Topic><Title>Time to short intc, buy HP</Title><Username>adamwangwang47</Username><Timestamp>1369249560134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:06:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i would do exact opposite</Msg><Username>eodsolo</Username><Timestamp>1369249940427</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:12:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369250357031-116</Id><Topic><Title>Time to short intc, buy HP</Title><Username>adamwangwang47</Username><Timestamp>1369249560134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:06:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>should be doing neither. market corrections last more than a day, and often begin with reversal days, new high, with a close below the day before. more pronounced, sqqq, new low, yet the close is extremely likely to be higher than yesterday's high of 26.38</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369250357031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369250454847-117</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" I think the Samsung news was an important factor " It was part of the catalyst but Morgan Stanley explicitly telling its client to go short was the major factor. INTC with its volume and solid base can shrug off bad analyst sentiment but not a fluff stock like ARMH. I always thought it would be a combination of bad analyst sentiment, bad earnings/forecast and good Intel news that would bring it down to Earth. Well the first and last are starting the decline but when they have bad earnings or forecast that will really start the avalanche like it did with AAPL.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1369250454847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:20:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369250470286-118</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While I fully understand the "not invented here" syndrome I believe Apple has a greater responsibility to do what's best for its customers and shareholders. From my perspective switching to Intel is not an action designed to insult anyone, it's simply a necessary step to keep the company relevant. There are many ways to reward significant contribution by talented employees other than perpetual employment. BTW, I enjoy your articles.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369250470286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369250645152-119</Id><Topic><Title>Time to short intc, buy HP</Title><Username>adamwangwang47</Username><Timestamp>1369249560134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:06:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3:00pm 5/22 INTC $21.12 HPQ $23.23</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369250645152</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369250653503-120</Id><Topic><Title>Time to short intc, buy HP</Title><Username>adamwangwang47</Username><Timestamp>1369249560134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:06:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3:00pm 5/22 INTC $21.12 HPQ $23.23</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369250653503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:24:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369251033133-121</Id><Topic><Title>Time to short intc, buy HP</Title><Username>adamwangwang47</Username><Timestamp>1369249560134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:06:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Wally, rome burning and he's still pumping INTC. But never fear, if you paid over 24, 00 you'll be fine in 6 months</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369251033133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:30:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369251312643-122</Id><Title>Dividend</Title><Msg>Is Intel going to communicate to their shareholders what there plans on dividend policy. obviouly there is a change occurring at this time, but it would be nice for the company to respond to this request</Msg><Username>cweby</Username><Timestamp>1369251312643</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:35:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369251527130-123</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple is the type of company that will do what's necessary to succeed. If they become convinced that moving to an Intel designed processor will improve their product, they won't be worried about abandoning their processor design. I don't think Intel will go the other way (fab services for an Apple-tweaked ARM design). At least - I don't think they should (IMHO).</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1369251527130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:38:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369251599888-124</Id><Topic><Title>Time to short intc, buy HP</Title><Username>adamwangwang47</Username><Timestamp>1369249560134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:06:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If a position in any investment makes someone nervous, then they have made a mistake. At a minimum, they have exceeded their risk tolerance and should consider correcting it. With regards to INTC, you are probably right about being fine.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1369251599888</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369251728660-125</Id><Title>The Stks Cud Correct 10% &amp; NOT</Title><Msg>even touch their 200 day MA its so darn overbought.</Msg><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369251728660</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:42:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369251966651-126</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend</Title><Username>cweby</Username><Timestamp>1369251312643</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:35:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was thinking we would hear something in early May. At this point - I'm thinking there might not be an increase.</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1369251966651</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:46:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369254344594-127</Id><Title>HPQ Beat Raised Guidance w 70 Million Upgrades Coming</Title><Msg>HPQ stock up 11% afterhours. INTC Long</Msg><Username>frankly_buying</Username><Timestamp>1369254344594</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 16:25:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369255212336-128</Id><Title>anyone heard from khitchdee</Title><Msg>or Covello or Shah lately ? guess not</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1369255212336</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 16:40:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369255422180-129</Id><Topic><Title>anyone heard from khitchdee</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1369255212336</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 16:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This was the last msg on ARM board ... The importance of being rooted ARM is strongly rooted in mobile and at the low power end of the microprocessor market. That means its got all its weight on on foot in the paint and it can pivot from here if needed. Intel will likely challenge it in low power, but it can equally make inroads at the higher power end of the market. It's not going away anytime soon. It's staying power is what gives Intel nightmares. None of Intel's previous competitors had this vantage point when looking at Intel.</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1369255422180</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 16:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369255821132-130</Id><Title>Eassa needs to get his head out of his rump and do some talk over in the valley.</Title><Msg>Take a trip to Cupertino or Santa Clara right down the road. Apple was ready to go ALL Intel years ago and we know that for a fact now. It is not even a question of whether but just a qustion of when now. That story by Eassa is without any research and a good example of someone blowing wind out their rump onto print. Grow up you little #$%$ and get your story with some research.</Msg><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1369255821132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 16:50:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369256174574-131</Id><Topic><Title>anyone heard from khitchdee</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1369255212336</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 16:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His split personalities are currently arguing with each other as he can't make up his mind on whether to go long, short or sideways and on what stock. You see he's been preaching for some time that an Intel mobile chip would not find itself in a Samsung device so his fuses were blown on that news and are currently being replaced as we speak after which we will have to wait to see what personality wins the internal argument arising from this news ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1369256174574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 16:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369256770837-132</Id><Topic><Title>Wanna make 300% on your next stock trade??</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1366937596462</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:53:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i subscribed to them.</Msg><Username>jackmayor503</Username><Timestamp>1369256770837</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:06:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369257031465-133</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again Apples failure to innovate and adapt may end up being it's downfall. Just good enough ARM, will NOT be good enough. Apple ignores intel technology at its own peril. Apple should heed the lesson learnt by intel. Don't tell the market or consumer what they should have. Listen to the market and produce products that the market want. Clearly the market will want convertible Tablet PC's. I know this because a lady friend of mine, who is a huge Macbook fan and totally technology illeterate, said the other day there are new notebooks coming out that double as tablets. I was surprised by comments from her. Guess what, little does she know, apple has decided that iPad is just good enough for her needs?</Msg><Username>gooddigger</Username><Timestamp>1369257031465</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369257161934-134</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What makes you think Apple is not already working with Intel to switch to Intel processor possibly both Atom (in smaller devices) and Core in full-sized iPads, basically, similar to the MS Surface Pro, but better implemented by Apple than by MS as usual. I love it how people write in blogs and postings about how Apple needs to consider switching to Intel processors as if that is some huge insight that Apple never considered and is not already doing. We now know that Apple even wanted Intel to foundry the chips for the original iPhone, but Intel declined because what Apple was willing to pay per unit was deemed too little. Also, of course, at that time Apple had recently converted Macs to Intel. So, I am sure that using Intel chips for iOS devices has never been far from Apple's attention and that they have been working in secret with Intel to make that conversion by 2014 or maybe even Fall of 2013 with the next generation of iPads. That would be nice, but my expectation is to see the switch in 2014. Either way, good for Apple and HUGE for Intel. That is why I am long long term both AAPL and INTC. I have owned AAPL since 2006 when they converted to Intel processors in Mac and well before the iPhone was even a rumor. And I have owned Intel since 2003 taking the opportunity to buy after the crash and adding as Intel began paying larger and larger dividends. I expect nice increases in both INTC and AAPL in 2014 and maybe even later this year. But I can wait. I'll just bide my time counting the money I am collecting from INTC and AAPL dividends.</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1369257161934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369257302326-135</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend</Title><Username>cweby</Username><Timestamp>1369251312643</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:35:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What makes you believe they are changing their dividend policy?</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1369257302326</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:15:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369257543258-136</Id><Topic><Title>Eassa needs to get his head out of his rump and do some talk over in the valley.</Title><Username>hector_cornholed_amders</Username><Timestamp>1369255821132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 16:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Welcome to "ignore".</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1369257543258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:19:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369257573822-137</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend</Title><Username>cweby</Username><Timestamp>1369251312643</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:35:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually - before- I did not think they would change it myself. However - they usually announce the increase early May, but they didn't. Perhaps they will delay the increase for a quarter.?.</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1369257573822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369257630522-138</Id><Topic><Title>Making 100k a year trading!</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368346134909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 04:08:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i subscribed to them.</Msg><Username>jackmayor503</Username><Timestamp>1369257630522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369257672791-139</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is my highest conviction long position, and I think they will do very well in mobile devices. But Apple seems hell bent - from aggressive hiring of CPU teams, to what I've heard of them trying to poach Intel CPU engineers (I do have friends at Intel who have been contacted by Apple) - on keeping its CPU/SoC designs in-house.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1369257672791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369258119840-140</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend</Title><Username>cweby</Username><Timestamp>1369251312643</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:35:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not really early May. It seems more like mid to late May so I would not read too much into it. Additionally, if you look back over the last four years or so, they don't always announce increases on a regular annual schedule. Intel's dividend and buyback policy is based on returning a percentage of cash flow. I think it is targeted as 40% of cash flow. Unless the cash flow has stopped increasing, I would not expect the dividend payments to stop increasing.</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1369258119840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:28:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369258283248-141</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No-one wants to run PC apps on tablets or smartphones. The way you design an app for these form factors is completely different. For starters, you target the installed base which is mostly iOS or Android running ARM. It's going to be very difficult to suddenly change the installed base. Apple just needs to make their products incrementally better to stay in business which they are slotted to do without needing to change their underlying microprocessor.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1369258283248</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:31:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369258742168-142</Id><Title>HP could care less about PC/hardware</Title><Msg>Their PC numbers were horrible..down over 20%, yet the stock up 13% AHs. Thats the problem with Intel. They need PC/server volumse to increase, but the OEMs care most about services/software &amp; dont mind losing in hardware. Intel needs to sell direct to consumers/businesses.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369258742168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:39:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369259065567-143</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps. But I also think it is possible that Intel would foundry Apple's "A" chip design. Apple could work with Intel to optimize the design to best utilize the trigate advantages (or maybe not, I'm certainly no microprocessor architect). I disagree with those who say Intel would not foundry an ARM-based chip for Apple. If the money is right, why wouldn't they? Also, if Apple is hiring Intel CPU engineers, maybe that is an indication that Apple IS planning to switch to Intel designs. Who better to help with a transition to Intel x86 processors than former Intel engineers? And why hire those guys to design ARM-based processors. I know people at Intel and Intel has an "Apple Group" within the company. They only work on Apple projects and they keep what they are working on a secret even from other Intel employees outside the Apple group. The rumor is that they are working on an x86 based iPad. But even before I hear that, I knew it made sense. Apple and Intel have something cooking (no Tim Cook pun intended), you can count on it. Don't forget that they have successfully kept their collaborations a secret before. The announcement of Macs switching to Intel caught everyone by surprise. Then they surprised everyone again at MacWorld by demonstrating iMacs and MacBook Pros running on Intel Core processors (which were new then) a full six months ahead of the schedule they had announced at WWDC in the prior June. Then even the MacBook Air was a collaboration with Intel to make a custom chipset package to fit the super-thin design that was also kept a secret. So just because there is little more than speculation, that does not mean they have not been working on, at least, an x86 iPad. Both Intel and Apple have shown before that can keep these kinds of secrets.</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1369259065567</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:44:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369259422482-144</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple is in year two of it's post Jobs identity crises. Year one came without stockholders and the board of directors breathing down Tim Cook's back. Those days are past and Cook is feeling the heat. Apple has lot the title of being the innovation leader. If they blow it with phones they will struggle to keep relevant. Their previous plans of thinking that the user experience trumps hardware innovation just isn't working in their favor. I won't say that they "have not choice but to work with Intel." They have lots of choices. They can choose to watch their stock drop and Tim Cook could choose to be forced out. When you're battle plans include Samsung, no, TSMC as your partner to battle Intel it's time to seriously think about the future.</Msg><Username>intel_fanboy</Username><Timestamp>1369259422482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369259617300-145</Id><Topic><Title>HP could care less about PC/hardware</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369258742168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:39:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They already do. A couple of quarters ago I recall them mentioning on the conference call that more and more of there server business is with companies buying motherboards for rack-server systems directly from Intel to install in the servers themselves rather than buying servers from Dell, HP, and other OEMs. It seems unlikely that Intel would ever sell computers directly. The margins are too low. Making the processors is the most profitable part of the chain. Getting into building and selling finished computers just takes them into low profit areas. That is why HP does not care, as you said. But if HP's numbers are down, that does not mean total PC sales must go down. Lenovo and Acer will happily take over what HP does not want. And Intel will sell more to them.</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1369259617300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369259761025-146</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you know Apple is ignoring Intel technology? I guess they forgot to inform you that they are working with Intel on an x86 based iPad. How inconsiderate of them.</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1369259761025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 17:56:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369260184069-147</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just realized that you are the guy whose articles I read on Seeking Alpha. I like your analysis of Intel in those Seeking Alpha articles, but as I said, I disagree on this point. I think Intel and Apple have a BIG surprise in the works. And as I said, the poaching of Intel engineers by Apple that you mentioned may be an indicator that Apple really is going to switch to Intel designed chips. As I also said, who better to manage that transition than the guys who actually worked on those Intel designs and how much good would they be for working on ARM-based designs. You might reconsider how you are interpreting Apple poaching of Intel CPU engineers. Give it some thought. Thanks.</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1369260184069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 18:03:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369260243186-148</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for your response. It is very much appreciated. Great discussion :)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1369260243186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 18:04:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369260758531-149</Id><Topic><Title>INTC tanks on Ashraf's article</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369248621278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is worth noting that Apple has been Intel's most loyal x86 processor customer. Every other computer OEM uses AMD chips as well as Intel and they also use many of Intel's lower margin celeron processors. Only Apple uses 100% Intel processor in their computers and, more than that, they only use Core i5, i7, and i9 and they even use two Xeons per Mac Pro system. They don't buy any of Intel's cheap, low margin Celerons. Apple computers are 100% Intel and use only the most current top-of-the-line processor models. That sounds like a pretty good customer to me. Apple even asked Intel to make the iPhone processors, but Intel declined. So I see no evidence that Apple will not stick by Intel. And what the hell is the deal with this "AAPL is worse than any jewish outfit" garbage? Grow up. We don't need your kind here.</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1369260758531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 18:12:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369260818934-150</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're welcome.</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1369260818934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 18:13:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369262186723-151</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to Qualcom TriGate/FinFet requires complete redesign when switching from (20nm) planar to 3D. IOW Apple can't just plug a 20nm design into a 14nm manufacturing process. (that's why ALTR has to stick with TSMC @ 20nm but go with Intel @ 14nm) Apple would waste precious time sticking too long with TSMC - the only way to leapfrog Samsung would be to go with Intel</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1369262186723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 18:36:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369265114699-152</Id><Topic><Title>INTC tanks on Ashraf's article</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369248621278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you're an anti-Semite. Dunce.</Msg><Username>angstromatic</Username><Timestamp>1369265114699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 19:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369265398881-153</Id><Topic><Title>INTC tanks on Ashraf's article</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1369248621278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>littlestewie88, you seem to be anti-semite sh@t that you are.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1369265398881</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 19:29:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369266006248-154</Id><Topic><Title>The Stks Cud Correct 10% &amp; NOT</Title><Username>littlestewie88</Username><Timestamp>1369251728660</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 15:42:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not so much anymore. IBD calls today the 2nd straight distribution day, due to the volume selling outweighing the buying. qqq macd finally curved down, but no crossover of signal lines, yet. Looking for SQQQ 26.38 as support given the final break above that level after 3 tries in the last three days. ARMH last high showed a lower rsi, bearish, same scenario for INTC on the 24.50. what a fun day.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1369266006248</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 19:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369266017056-155</Id><Title>Only the chinese and Koreans can sell PC's now, like TV's. HP and Dell</Title><Msg>will get out of the PC business in the next few years.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369266017056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 19:40:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369266290785-156</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"No-one wants to run PC apps on tablets or smartphones." [This is the same nonsense you cited in saying how successful the RT would be. The market has proven you substantially wrong in its endorsement of the Surface Pro over the RT...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369266290785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 19:44:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369266950322-157</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"ARM now down over 2 percent today (95 cents). Makes over 7 percent in two days. Downward momentum is building..." [Make that 3 percent (1.42) today or an 8+ percent decline in two days...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369266950322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 19:55:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369267440229-158</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS GOING ON?????</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368550155862</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:49:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i signed up with them.</Msg><Username>bgates354</Username><Timestamp>1369267440229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 20:04:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369267808561-159</Id><Topic><Title>Making 100k a year trading!</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368346134909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 04:08:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i signed up with them.</Msg><Username>bgates354</Username><Timestamp>1369267808561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 20:10:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369268099885-160</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Unlikely To Move To Intel Chips For iPad Or iPhone?</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1369248576530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM Holdings PLC (ARMH, ARM.LN) added to Tuesday's loses, falling 3% to $45.82,</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1369268099885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 20:14:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369268761067-161</Id><Topic><Title>Only the chinese and Koreans can sell PC's now, like TV's. HP and Dell</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1369266017056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 19:40:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's okay with me just as long as they have INTEL INSIDE.. And I'm confident they will.</Msg><Username>tljarvis1968</Username><Timestamp>1369268761067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 20:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369269228137-162</Id><Title>Trade Idea: Short ARM Holdings on Samsung design loss</Title><Msg>Trade idea background ARM Holdings' stock is down in early London trading following news that Samsung may use Intel's Atom processor in their Galaxy Tab 3. This could mark the end of the "free lunch" ARM Holdings has had with Intel being behind the curve on mobile device processors. ARM Holdings is extremely overvalued based on the EV/TIC framework with the enterprise value being GBP 13.8 billion on GBP 1.1 billion in total invested capital. This premium valuation does not hold up with the profitability spread, defined as the ROIC vs. WACC, which is only around 1.5x. In other words, the valuation does not reflect the underlying profitability and expectations are too rosy. If the momentum reverses on the news of design loss to Intel then long investors might be willing to get out causing prices to correct downward over the foreseeable future. Trade management and risk description The trade is entered as a short market order with a stop at 1,075 and target at 900. The biggest risk to this trade is either counter news on the rumours of design loss or better than expected macro data. Tomorrow better than expected PMI figures for Europe could ignite a broad run-up in stocks yet again which would lift ARM Holdings despite the negative news stream. Trade idea parameters Entry: Short market order From Peter Garnry, Head of Equity Strategy, Saxo Bank</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369269228137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 20:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369269509929-163</Id><Topic><Title>Wanna make 300% on your next stock trade??</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1366937596462</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:53:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i signed up with them.</Msg><Username>bgates354</Username><Timestamp>1369269509929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 20:38:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369270159837-164</Id><Title>ARM: The View from London</Title><Msg>Price started dropping at 14:45 one hour after the end of the ARM investor session in London now down 6.6%. Hmmm! From iii co uk You know what to put inbetween each...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369270159837</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 20:49:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369272030905-165</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis, Victory is sweet, eh? Finally the air is being let out of this bubble. ARM should be priced like a utility and have a dividend yield commensurate with that industry.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1369272030905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 21:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369280571325-166</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down 90 Cents Pre-Opening</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369227263516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, it's nice to see the markets at least occasionally being driven by something other than manipulation, ignorance, greed, power and irrational exuberance...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369280571325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 23:42:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369280884153-167</Id><Title>Another Comment From the UK ARMH Message Board</Title><Msg>But I am now getting more nervous about Intel. The claims they're making for Silvermont are pretty remarkable - although the Intel slide on the following page is interesting. I've read in many places, as on this page, that Silvermont (the next Atom) will bring 3 times performance at 5 times lower power consumption. That's widely reported. But the slide actually seems to show 3 times performance or 5 times lower power consumption. That sounds more realistic - but is still very hefty. Given the current Atom is close to the performance of an A15, having that performance at 5 times less power would be very attractive. I've been surprised the market hasn't moved in reaction to this - maybe no one believes Intel. When the first independent benchmarks come out, be ready to sell (some, anyway). Having already seen a slide from 1000p to 100p, now we're back again I'm not sure I'm ready for another.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369280884153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 23:48:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369281120674-168</Id><Title>HERE'S THE BOTTOM LINE</Title><Msg>1) APPLE AND SAMSUNG ARE AT WAR with each other. 2) Intel is rolling out Silvermont - Bay Trail for tablets and Merrifield for smartphones. Bay Trail and Merrifield are the best performing SoCs with best battery life. 3) BOTTOM LINE: Either one or both will strike a deal with Intel to use Bay Trail/Merrifield in their products. Anyone who thinks otherwise is in denial.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1369281120674</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 23:52:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369281184205-169</Id><Title>ARM Holdings plc will be hosting ANALYST and INVESTOR presentations TODAY in London.</Title><Msg>ARM HOLDINGS PLC - "ANALYST AND INVESTOR DAY" That was yesterday. So, what would you conclude when the stock of a company drops 8 percent in the 2 days beginning with its Analyst and Investor Day presentation? The sky is falling. On ARM...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1369281184205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 23:53:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>