<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358658132965-1</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is not building FAB capacity based on expected phone chip sales lol. Did you not listen to/read the CC ? Find another strawman argument to bash with.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358658132965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:02:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358658251901-2</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Apple and Samsung' Don't get hung up on these two to be dominant forever, remember it used to be Nokia and Motorola once. Fashions change ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358658251901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:04:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358658441312-3</Id><Title>ST-Ericksson puts out a 28nm FD-SOI 2.5GHz dual-A9 development platform</Title><Msg>semiaccurateDOTcom/2013/01/17/st-ericksson-puts-out-a-2-5ghz-phone-chip</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358658441312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:07:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358658877032-4</Id><Topic><Title>If Intel's growth was more evenly distributed...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358644624312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:17:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>14 million iPad units. 2011 was a phenomenal year for Intel. Totally out of the ordinary. Growth in PC sales was way beyond anybodies expecations, including Intel's. This could happen again in the future at any time, benefitting Intel in a very big way. So let's go to the next level which is Q3 of 2010. Intel sold PC chips and chipsets to the tune of $8.055 Billion, while Apple sold 4.19 million iPad units. Apple grew the sales of iPad units, being a very new and inexpensive Apple solution, to 14 million units in Q3, 2 years later. While Intel still sold PC ships and chipsets that totalled $8.633 Billion. So even though 10 million more iPads were sold compared to Q3 of 2010 for Apple, Intel still managed to grow sales of PC by over 7%. Evidence does not point to cannibalization there. It points more to a huge interest in a new product by Apple and Apple alone. All other tablets have been very anemic in sales. The next best selling model, far behind Apple's iPad, is Samsung's Galaxy. Yet Samsung still has decided to offer Atom based tablets, one of which is more like a hybrid that turns into a slim laptop. Available already at Bestbuy and other electronic outlets. If tablets are expected to grow sales to a 200 million units a year, Intel could benefit very nicely in that area. This is because Intel based tablets or hybrid ultrabooks are the only true way competitors can differentiate themselves from Apple's iPad. Then the burden will be on Apple to join the quality tablet crowd and go with Intel chips themselves.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358658877032</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:14:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358659322141-5</Id><Topic><Title>semiaccurate gaming on intel's atom z2670</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358640156679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:02:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>semiaccurateDOTcom/2013/01/18/gaming-on-intels-atom-z2670 Tegra 3 would been no better trying to play PC games. Clovertrail+ (Z2580)'s gpu has 5x better performance.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358659322141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:22:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358671212739-6</Id><Title>INTC to split into 2 companies very soon</Title><Msg>INTC $13 very soon Good Luck</Msg><Username>dansmily2000</Username><Timestamp>1358671212739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 03:40:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358671865118-7</Id><Topic><Title>INTC to split into 2 companies very soon</Title><Username>dansmily2000</Username><Timestamp>1358671212739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 03:40:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"INTC $13 very soon Good Luck" [If all of your brain cells spit in two, you still wouldn't break double digits...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358671865118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 03:51:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358672178970-8</Id><Title>getanid61</Title><Msg>If you really need to bash something ever single day, I suggest your parents...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358672178970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 03:56:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358681626845-9</Id><Title>Facebook to ARM: give us traditional Server cores</Title><Msg>I guess a rubber stamp isn't sufficient in the real world ;-) cdnDOTeetimesDOTcom/electronics-news/4405195/ARM-SoCs--flash-don-t-match-Facebook-s-needs</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358681626845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 06:33:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358690297292-10</Id><Topic><Title>Facebook to ARM: give us traditional Server cores</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358681626845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 06:33:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel and Facebook collaborate on future data center rack technologies Posted on 17 January 2013. Intel and Facebook aim to define the next generation of rack technologies used to power the world’s largest data centers. As part of the collaboration, the companies also unveiled a mechanical prototype built by Quanta Computer that includes Intel’s new photonic rack architecture to show the total cost, design and reliability improvement potential of a disaggregated rack environment. The new architecture is based on more than a decade’s worth of research to invent a family of silicon-based photonic devices, including lasers, modulators and detectors using low-cost silicon to fully integrate photonic devices of unprecedented speed and energy efficiency. Silicon photonics is a new approach to using light (photons) to move huge amounts of data at very high speeds with extremely low power over a thin optical fiber rather than using electrical signals over a copper cable. Intel has spent the past two years proving its silicon photonics technology was production-worthy, and has now produced engineering samples. Silicon photonics made with inexpensive silicon rather than expensive and exotic optical materials provides a distinct cost advantage over older optical technologies in addition to providing greater speed, reliability and scalability benefits. Businesses with server farms or massive data centers could eliminate performance bottlenecks and ensure long-term upgradability while saving significant operational costs in space and energy. Silicon photonics and disaggregation efficiencies Businesses with large data centers can significantly reduce capital expenditure by disaggregating or separating compute and storage resources in a server rack. Rack disaggregation refers to the separation of those resources that currently exist in a rack, including compute, storage, networking and power distribution into discrete modules. Traditionally, a server within a rack would each have its own group of resources. When disaggregated, resource types can be grouped together and distributed throughout the rack, improving upgradability, flexibility and reliability while lowering costs. By separating critical components from one another, each computer resource can be upgraded on its own cadence without being coupled to the others. This provides increased lifespan for each resource and enables IT managers to replace just that resource instead of the entire system. This increased serviceability and flexibility drives improved total-cost for infrastructure investments as well as higher levels of resiliency. There are also thermal efficiency opportunities by allowing more optimal component placement within a rack. The mechanical prototype is a demonstration of Intel’s photonic rack architecture for interconnecting the various resources, showing one of the ways compute, network and storage resources can be disaggregated within a rack. Intel will contribute a design for enabling a photonic receptacle to the Open Compute Project (OCP) and will work with Facebook, Corning, and others over time to standardize the design. The mechanical prototype includes distributed input/output (I/O) using Intel Ethernet switch silicon, and will support the Intel Xeon processor and the next generation, 22 nanometer system-on-chip (SoC) Intel Atom processor, code named “Avoton,” available this year. The mechanical prototype shown today is the next evolution of rack disaggregation with separate distributed switching functions</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1358690297292</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:58:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358690836108-11</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358617729379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:48:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Wally, Good sound analysis. The question is, how much more downward manipulation of the stock price will Wall Street criminals be driving before flipping the switch and loading up on INTC for the big boy clients? At the end of the day it might make good financial sense to simply run a prison wall around all of the NYC financial district and call it 'justice served"</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1358690836108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:07:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358691254575-12</Id><Topic><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358617729379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:48:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd start by shipping all those Bernie Madfoff's at GS out to sea and using the ship for target practice. I think their "munchkins" might support this.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358691254575</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:14:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358692137834-13</Id><Title>What is the reason for no LTE for a year?????</Title><Msg>Someone please clarify...sounded like a used car sales pitch on the cc.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358692137834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:28:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358692745012-14</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is little need for more power and performance if software and internet demands stayed the same. They don't. Software continually grows more complex and demanding on computer resources. The demand for more performance in phones, pads and PCs will always continue.</Msg><Username>billy_ray_valentine</Username><Timestamp>1358692745012</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:39:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358693004187-15</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor INTC, caught up in what eventually happens in tech, market saturation and the commodization of chips.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1358693004187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:43:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358693728499-16</Id><Title>INTC bashing is part of the ARMH bubble psychology.</Title><Msg>No one on Wall Street actually believes the ARMH hype. It is part of the Wall Street bubble game is to give you something to sell while they give you something to buy. They think there are people holding INTC who would sell if prodded and buy into the ARMH bubble. INTC is insanely underpriced as Wall Street attempts to build up ARMH's stock price. ARMH is TRANSMETA all over again. Look it up. INTC is a great investment while the Street tries to convince you things are different this time. Can INTC go lower? Sure. And then it will go back over thirty. INTC's quarter was decent. The div is good. There is no real long term competitor. And INTC just bagged all of CSCO's chip business on Friday, which of course was not covered by the news. Take advantage of people like Cramer who said sell at 20 and GS who are consistantly wrong about everything. Now, with more QE coming, is the time to be an investor in good companies. Trading at these prices is for suckers.</Msg><Username>buddhatrader</Username><Timestamp>1358693728499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:55:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358696753963-17</Id><Title>Buyout</Title><Msg>Any chance for INTC to buy NVDA to be ahead of the game. Ant thoughts</Msg><Username>handsome868</Username><Timestamp>1358696753963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:45:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358696755841-18</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"... The demand for more performance in phones, pads and PCs will always continue." I think what is in question is the rate and cost of this demand. It's possible for everyone to accelerate, but is it worth the effort?</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1358696755841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:45:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358697011214-19</Id><Title>O)ff topic: The MLK Bible - Tavis Smiley</Title><Msg>The inauguration, President Obama will place his hand on Martin Luther King's Bible. Smiley characterizes the move as a clever political choice. It certainly is. It's as clever as a number of moves that don't hold true to the superficial viewpoint most people quickly accept and then, continue to accept over the long term. Did the administration actually "rescue" General Motors? In a fantasyland way it did. Just don't ask the shareholders of the GM shares that went to worthless. An ecological green economy, how about the list of those types of companies that went bankrupt which should include all those that are teetering on insolvency. I would never characterize the President for having anything but best intentions in mind. But the reality of life os om conflict with Smiley. He isn't aware, some goals are either unattainable or considerably way ahead of their time. Oil is still hugely cheaper than any green initiative and will continue to be for some time. Smiley in his blame game, pontificating that ending poverty is a something that should have already been accomplished, when in the real world lazy people will always be part of our culture, all cultures for that matter. Keep upping the tax revenue to fund foolish ideas, government waste and to boost the income of those that abuse the system. Yup, it plays to the masses for any politician racking up votes that run over those that embrace a true work ehtic.</Msg><Username>towncryer911</Username><Timestamp>1358697011214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:50:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358697093902-20</Id><Topic><Title>INTC bashing is part of the ARMH bubble psychology.</Title><Username>buddhatrader</Username><Timestamp>1358693728499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:55:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"And INTC just bagged all of CSCO's chip business on Friday" Do you have a link for that? I missed it as well.</Msg><Username>mysticalpotatohead48</Username><Timestamp>1358697093902</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:51:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358697136292-21</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Khitchdee believes that humans will never need a device that has more performance that the iphone5. He along with CEO Warren East believe that the human race has reached its technological peak. ________ I talked to a guy last night that was with a large group that we were with for a birthday party. He was playing with his Iphone 5 and I asked him how he liked it. His EXACT words were "it freezes up on me, I wish there were better phones as I'd get one. I could care less about Apple."</Msg><Username>intel_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1358697136292</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:52:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358697623296-22</Id><Title>Why do the anal bashers forget to mention the 4.25% dividend??</Title><Msg>Who is paying their publication bonus? How many dollars are they getting in the back alley? My friends,a 4.25% dividend is pretty hard to get from the bluest of the blue chips. Don't run too far. I read one article today in which the anal said earnings were very bad, and in the next sentence said 'the beat expectations' WHAT??? This is a cheap stock. And they are investing $13 Billion to EXPAND the business. Buy low, sell HIGH.</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1358697623296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:00:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358697839525-23</Id><Topic><Title>INTC bashing is part of the ARMH bubble psychology.</Title><Username>buddhatrader</Username><Timestamp>1358693728499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:55:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Found it. No specifics, other than cisco is now intel's largest foundry customer.</Msg><Username>dancingluminousfleshgiants</Username><Timestamp>1358697839525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:03:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358698227536-24</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Demonstrates Industry’s First Fully Patterned 450mm Wafer: Photos</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358629753635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:09:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You nailed it. A "good analyst" might have asked what Intel expected to accomplish with that investment and how it would improve their competition position. If Intel had said we believe this investment will give us a two year lead over everyone at 450mm that response would have shaken the industry. That none asked says a lot about the quality of the "analysts" usefulness.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1358698227536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:10:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358698299398-25</Id><Title>Is Intel a value trap?</Title><Msg>Good dividend; low PE; great balance sheet; stock buy-backs; always a "line of sight" to where management wants to go; stock price stuck in the muck for more than ten years.</Msg><Username>jceandthegirls</Username><Timestamp>1358698299398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:11:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358698351488-26</Id><Topic><Title>Why do the anal bashers forget to mention the 4.25% dividend??</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1358697623296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:00:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again, If you buy today and hold for five years, cashing and using each Dividend check, you will have an average of around 15 in five years. You'll also have made one single buy, paid one single commission and I just bet you'll have made quite a bit of profit to boot. Smart people already know this.</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1358698351488</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:12:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358698678672-27</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel a value trap?</Title><Username>jceandthegirls</Username><Timestamp>1358698299398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:11:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Market trends?</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1358698678672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:17:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358699385951-28</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel a value trap?</Title><Username>jceandthegirls</Username><Timestamp>1358698299398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:11:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC will soon blow the competition out of the water including nuff the IDIOT,Tic Toc.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1358699385951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:29:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358699485853-29</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel a value trap?</Title><Username>jceandthegirls</Username><Timestamp>1358698299398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:11:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. Great dividend. My analysis shows the largest negative as the number of shares outstanding. Like Cisco, they saturated the market with shares during the tech bubble. They are buying some back, but the basic saviour is the dividend yield. How many blue chips can you find that have a 10:1 PE and pay 4.25%.. ?? NONE.</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1358699485853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:31:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358700057137-30</Id><Title>INTC a great long term buy here</Title><Msg>Still THE premier global chip company, with the greatest number of patents, with the greatest engine of "intellectual property", and THE best company in this sector...by far. The dividend is going up, and INTC has a solid record not only of paying divis, but in growth of divis. GLTA, whatever you do. -Frieberg</Msg><Username>frey_guy17</Username><Timestamp>1358700057137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:40:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358700338962-31</Id><Topic><Title>INTC a great long term buy here</Title><Username>frey_guy17</Username><Timestamp>1358700057137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:40:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also, I might also offer up two other excellent dividend yielding cheap tech stocks: AAPL, WAY way undervalued @ 500 bucks, and MSFT, down....but FAR from dead. Buy 'em all, be patient, and simply hold them along with your INTC. Far better than owning bonds or treasury notes. -Frieberg</Msg><Username>frey_guy17</Username><Timestamp>1358700338962</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:45:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358700577943-32</Id><Topic><Title>Is Intel a value trap?</Title><Username>jceandthegirls</Username><Timestamp>1358698299398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:11:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree. I guess the market is concerned about what may happen to that PE. We shall see. In any event, I am definitely going to start to buy maybe 600-800 shares of INTC, 100 at a time, over the next several months. I have been waiting for this moment, so will now dive in. Also, T is getting cheap again, and yielding over 5%. INTC, AAPL, MSFT, T...all excellent buys, and great long term dividend payers. AAPL is the sleeper; I think they will grow its dividend (now about 2.1%) significantly over the coming years. -Frieberg</Msg><Username>frey_guy17</Username><Timestamp>1358700577943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:49:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358700660215-33</Id><Topic><Title>Facebook to ARM: give us traditional Server cores</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358681626845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 06:33:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. Thats was a big public #$%$ to the Arm server players from Facebook.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1358700660215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:51:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358701147491-34</Id><Topic><Title>17 Trillion in debt and Lady Gaga set to sing for Obama and Michelle tomorrow</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358624030530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:33:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PUMP A DEAD DOG WHY DONCHA</Msg><Username>cd2374</Username><Timestamp>1358701147491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:59:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358701687768-35</Id><Topic><Title>O)ff topic: The MLK Bible - Tavis Smiley</Title><Username>towncryer911</Username><Timestamp>1358697011214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:50:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, 90% of the gov't budget is Social Security, Medicare and Defense. Let's hear how you plan to cut them.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358701687768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:08:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358701719693-36</Id><Title>The world is porting to ARM</Title><Msg>Samsung confirms no Windows RT tablets for US The company's decision is based in part upon feedback from retail partners, which suggested that such a product would be only modestly successful in the marketplace. Samsung also pointed to the lack of education about Windows RT, and suggested that it would require too much of an investment to properly inform consumers of the differences between it and Windows 8.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358701719693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:08:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358702157694-37</Id><Topic><Title>The world is porting to ARM</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358701719693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:08:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chump, "The world is porting to ARM" Exactly... it's why ARMH went up when INTC's numbers brought the mkt down...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358702157694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:15:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358702454253-38</Id><Topic><Title>The world is porting to ARM</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358701719693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:08:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny how you used to pump the company but now you just pump the stock price with ABSOLUTELY NO evidence that 5 years from now ARM will be in laptops and servers in a "big way" as you've said. Your time is now but you and ARM won't be so cocky down the road, and I can't WAIT to bring back alllll your old posts. Keep chirping, you're providing us with GOLD material.</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358702454253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:20:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358703568362-39</Id><Topic><Title>The world is porting to ARM</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358701719693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:08:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DESPERATE !!!!!!</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358703568362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:39:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358704085919-40</Id><Title>Acer $ 199 dollar Chromebook with Intel inside</Title><Msg>..........advertised at the top of ESPN's site. So much for the notion $ 200 Chromebooks would decimate Intel.</Msg><Username>getanid16</Username><Timestamp>1358704085919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:48:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358704462996-41</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 RT Version is Better Than The Windows 8 Pro Version</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1345914310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol HP ditches Windows RT tablet plans, Microsoft Surface to blame</Msg><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358704462996</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:54:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358705256575-42</Id><Topic><Title>O)ff topic: The MLK Bible - Tavis Smiley</Title><Username>towncryer911</Username><Timestamp>1358697011214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:50:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I DON'T like social topics on a financial board ..... but, I did the math a couple times and it does not look good. Just my thoughts and I am unlikely to "debate" or "defend" them on this board. It seems like if their is 7% of the 2012 budget is interest on the debt, and that your 90% number is high. But your question is very good. There are lots of numbers but I get (in 2012) $3.6T SPENDING and $2.4T REVENUE. There is $1.2T or so difference between SPENDING and REVENUE. You can't cut $1.2T out of the $634 billion Non-defense discretionary. You cannot fix this without making some changes to major programs. You cannot fix this with the "yelling, taunting, insults and lack of cooperation" from both sides. ====================================== I THINK, and it is ONLY JUST MY OPINION (and I may be entirely wrong, but ... ), that the behavior of the extreme conservatives have earned them a strong distrust from the both the liberals AND those poor and sick struggling at the bottom of the economic ladder. I THINK, and it is ONLY JUST MY OPINION (and I may be entirely wrong, but ... ), that the conservative and wealthy who benefit most from their work and end up carrying most of the financial load will have to take a LEADERSHIP role in working through a REALLY, REALLY GRAND BARGAIN to address a restructuring of programs. I THINK, and it is ONLY JUST MY OPINION (and I may be entirely wrong, but ... ), that until the conservative/moderate leadership take this responsibility and a large majority agree, there will be little progress and the USA will be held hostage by the extreme fringe on both sides. ====================================== CBO's 2012 August Update Spending (I get $3.6T) Social Security: $769 billion 21% Medicare: $555 billion &amp; Medicaid: $259 billion 22% Defense Spending: $708 billion 20% Other Mandatory (Entitlement) Spending: $473 billion 13% Interest on the Debt: $238 billion 7% Everything Else: $634 billion (often known as "non-defense discretionary") 17% ====================================== Medicare: $555 billion (Medicare is national health insurance administered by the federal government for people 65 and over and disabled Americans. It is financed by payroll taxes, general tax revenues, premiums and copayments.) Medicaid: $259 billion (Medicaid, financed jointly by the federal and state governments, is administered by the states. It is the major health program for low-income Americans. A large portion of Medicaid pays for long-term care for low-income elderly.) CRS Medicaid Primer CRS Overview of Affordable Care Act, which expands Medicaid Cost Estimate of the Affordable Care Act (CBO, 2010) Cost Estimate of the Affordable Care Act (CBO, 2011 Update) Cost Estimate of the Affordable Care Act (following the Supreme Court Decision (CBO, 2012) Overview of Affordable Care Act (CRS, 2012) Nonpartisan Kaiser Family Foundation Resources on Affordable Care Act Nonpartisan Kaiser Family Foundation Summary of Affordable Care Act Everything Else: $634 billion (often known as "non-defense discretionary" -- Includes law enforcement, veterans health care, homeland security, education, prisons, NASA, disease and epidemic control, highways &amp; bridges, food and drug inspection, disaster relief, airports, health research, housing assistance, and many other functions of government. ====================================== REVENUE 2012 Individual Income Tax $1165 billion 47% Corporate Income tax $237 billion 9.5% Social Security $841 billion 34% Excise tax $79 billion 3% Customs duties $31 billion 1% Estate and gift taxes $11 billion 0% Deposits of earnings and Federal Reserve System $81 billion 3% Other miscellaneous receipts $24 billion 1% Total $2.469 trillion ======================================</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358705256575</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:07:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358707486100-43</Id><Topic><Title>The world is porting to ARM</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358701719693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:08:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>getanid61, used to pump NVDA when it was above 22$ range, look where it is now. ARMH will have similar fate. lol</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1358707486100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:44:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358708366608-44</Id><Title>Ivy Bridge Tablet -Kupa Ultranote X15</Title><Msg>Kupa UltraNote X15 Windows 8 tablet now available starting at $1,099 Summary: The premium tablet offers a modular design, full 1080p HD screen, and Intel Ivy Bridge processor choices. By Sean Portnoy for Laptops &amp; Desktops | January 20, 2013 -- 16:26 GMT (08:26 PST) A few months ago, I posted about the Kupa UltraNote, a Windows 8 tablet that promised a modular design that would maximize customization options for users. At the time, we didn't know any pricing or availability information, but now it appears the UltraNote X15 has showed up for pre-order from Dynamism's webiste, a site known for bringing gadgets unavailable in North America to these shores. There are four configurations available for the UltraNote, all of which will ship in March. They start with the $1,099 X15 Elite, which includes an Intel Core i5-3317U Ivy Bridge processor, 8GB of RAM, and 64GB of storage, and go up to the X15 Pro at $1,599, which comes with a Core i7-3517U, double the storage, Windows 8 Pro, and 3G connectivity capabilities. There are also $1,199 and $1,299 options, which keep the same Core i5 chip but add more storage and, in the case of the pricier X15 Lux, 3G functionality. All share the UltraNote's premium features, like a 10.1-inch IPS screen with 1,920x1,080 resolution, active digitizer, and removable battery. The modular design lets you add (via the external side panel) a card reader, scanner, or other accessory, though none appear to be ready at this time. Of course, there's also a keyboard docking station being readied with an extra battery and additional ports.</Msg><Username>lucysuxwang</Username><Timestamp>1358708366608</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:59:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358708500681-45</Id><Title>Look for another BIG down day for intc -</Title><Msg>Drops another 10% on average after an earnings miss!! Always 0- slow drip all week....................</Msg><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1358708500681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:01:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358709786797-46</Id><Topic><Title>Look for another BIG down day for intc -</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1358708500681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:01:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you dying to get in , aint you</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1358709786797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:23:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358709934464-47</Id><Title>WALLIS MUST RESIDE IN THE BIZARRO WORLD!</Title><Msg>First he tells you to buy Intel at $29, then he pumped Intel from $29 down to $20 and tells you that Intel's stock performance is good, then he tells you that the recent terrible earnings report was great and then that the fear and concern of the shorts is "palpable." Is Waldo a comedian, a poor lost soul, or a dolt? Whatever he is, he is definitely... TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358709934464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:25:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358710161415-48</Id><Topic><Title>WALLIS MUST RESIDE IN THE BIZARRO WORLD!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358709934464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:25:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would like to add that, at this point in time, Waldo probably doesn't know whether to sheeeet or wind his watch! HI-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358710161415</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:29:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358710791419-49</Id><Topic><Title>Look for another BIG down day for intc -</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1358708500681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:01:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ha ha - you wish - I may start a position at $19, NO catalyst to take INTC up. Earning already told you sales are down and out look is bad. So I will buy your shares a lot cheaper. I worked for INTC 18 years, this is an OLD dog and no growth. Spending money like crazy with NO returns.</Msg><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1358710791419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:39:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358711406237-50</Id><Topic><Title>WALLIS MUST RESIDE IN THE BIZARRO WORLD!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358709934464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:25:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>through Lucy eyes .... wallis is just a crotch to shove his nose. ARF!!ARF!!ARF!!ARF!! when wallis covers his crotch .... PROTECT YOUR REAR END !!!! HEREEEEE COMES LUCY !!!!!! TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNY!!!</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1358711406237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:50:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358711604155-51</Id><Topic><Title>Look for another BIG down day for intc -</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1358708500681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:01:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dream on and wet your bed</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1358711604155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:53:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358711696168-52</Id><Topic><Title>INTC a great long term buy here</Title><Username>frey_guy17</Username><Timestamp>1358700057137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:40:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ditto that</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1358711696168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:54:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358711739894-53</Id><Title>2 billion to be spent on 450nm factory.</Title><Msg>It is in the cfo comments right befors the risk factors in the balance sheet section.They are beginning to build a factory to produce the 450 silicon disc. As wally said the analist don't figure these into any value when estimating the value of intc,Yes I saidANAList</Msg><Username>kravcleve</Username><Timestamp>1358711739894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:55:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358712697451-54</Id><Topic><Title>ST-Ericksson puts out a 28nm FD-SOI 2.5GHz dual-A9 development platform</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358658441312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:07:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM manufacturing base is fragmented - AMD quit SOI. TSMC is certainly not using SOI - more or less they all seem to follow Intel's roadmap Freescale also reducing its mobile chip business - I posted it some time ago ST exiting mobile chip JV with Ericsson, but still committed to FD-SOI 12/10/2012 By James Montgomery News Editor December 10, 2012 - STMicroelectronics has come to a decision about its mobile chip JV with communications giant Ericsson: it's getting out of the business. The company's new strategic plan calls for an exit from ST-Ericsson as part of a broader strategic plan to focus on five product areas: MEMS/sensors, smart power, automotive products, microcontrollers, and application processors including digital consumer, stated Carlo Bozotti, ST's president and CEO. The new strategy will be based on two product-segment organizations. A "Sense &amp; Power and Automotive" division will include MEMS and sensors and power discrete and advanced analog products, plus everything the company does tied to automotive -- powertrain, safety, body, and infotainment. Another group, embedded processing solutions, will narrow its focus "on the core of the electronics systems rather than on wireless broadband access," according to the company. This includes microcontrollers, imaging products, digital consumer products, application processors and digital ASICs. "Our new strategy is centered on leadership in sense and power and automotive products, and in embedded-processing solutions," Bozotti explained,. The more focused, leaner structure is expected to be profitable and generate cash in both divisions, rapidly improving operating margins to 10% while addressing a combined $140B market in 2013 (citing WSTS statistics). The embedded unit in particular is anticipated to swing back to profitability thanks to its narrowed technology focus, expanded customer base, and manufacturing synergies between microcontrollers and digital offerings. That narrowed focus does not, however, leave room for ST's joint venture with mobile giant Ericsson. After a restructuring earlier this year including a workforce reduction, and calling in a strategic advisor just weeks ago (despite industry watchers' doubts that the loss-making unit would find any buyers), ST is currently in negotiations on exit options and plans to be fully out of the business "after a transition period" expected to be complete by 3Q13. ST says it will support ST-Ericsson as a partner in advanced process technology -- notably fully depleted silicon on insulator, or FD-SOI, to create power-sipping chips for future mobile platforms -- as well as a source for application processor IP and supply-chain. "As semiconductors continue to be more pervasive, we see a world where ST products are everywhere microelectronics make a positive contribution to people's lives," Bozotti said. "With our new strategic plan, we will grow faster, be more profitable and overall become an even stronger company."</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358712697451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:11:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358713323931-55</Id><Topic><Title>Look for another BIG down day for intc -</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1358708500681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:01:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nuff always creates the same signature STOOOOPID aliases.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1358713323931</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:22:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358713681573-56</Id><Topic><Title>Look for another BIG down day for intc -</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1358708500681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:01:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the mention, jackwad.</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358713681573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:28:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358715584382-57</Id><Title>True value is $12.04 a share - INTC = DELL</Title><Msg>INTC is dying and will soon take the path of DELL and HPQ. OLD OLD company,.,.,.,.,.,.,.,.,.,.,.,.,.,.,.,.,.,.,.,.,.,.</Msg><Username>longtrader123</Username><Timestamp>1358715584382</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:59:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358715797640-58</Id><Topic><Title>INTC bashing is part of the ARMH bubble psychology.</Title><Username>buddhatrader</Username><Timestamp>1358693728499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:55:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As of Friday.</Msg><Username>buddhatrader</Username><Timestamp>1358715797640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:03:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358717481015-59</Id><Topic><Title>Look for another BIG down day for intc -</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1358708500681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:01:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If things are so awful, why would you even consider buying at $19 Nuff? You are the biggest Bee Esser I've ever come across. You may get your chance to buy in the 19's about 3 weeks after ex date.</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1358717481015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:31:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358717782611-60</Id><Title>450 mm - about the size of a large pizza.</Title><Msg>Intel may have little choice in big manufacturing bet Reuters – Fri, Jan 18, 2013 4:54 PM EST Email Recommend0Tweet Print RELATED CONTENT View Photo The Intel logo is seen on a computer in New York May 13, 2009. REUTERS/Shannon Stapleton/Files RELATED QUOTES Symbol Price Change AMZN 272.12 1.64 2330.TW 101.50 2.20 INTC 21.25 -1.43 AMAT 12.65 0.25 ASML.AS 51.57 0.08 By Noel Randewich SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Intel Corp's(NSQ:INTC) decision to spend $13 billion in 2013 to develop and build future manufacturing technology has not gone down well on Wall Street but it may be necessary if it wants to stay on top of rivals in coming years. The top chipmaker's shares slumped nearly 7 percent on Friday, a day after executives said the company would increase 2013 capital spending from an already dizzying $11 billion. Some analysts decried the move, saying adding new capacity should be far from Intel's mind in a waning personal computer market. Increased spending may further pressure margins and leave Intel with even more idle capacity if PC sales keep falling. But others believe that Intel's top priority must be maintaining its technological edge, a costly but necessary endeavor that may even pay off in the long run with market share gains. Moving up the technology ladder can also deliver cost savings, helping safeguarding Intel's margins as it tries to catch up to rivals in smartphones and tablets. "That's the bet they're making and they're all in," said Sanford Bernstein analyst Stacy Rasgon. "If you stop, TSMC and Samsung close the gap - and you're toast." Of Intel's $13 billion capex this year, $2 billion will go toward expanding a fabrication plant, or fab, in Oregon where engineers will work on a long-term plan to manufacture microchips on silicon wafers measuring 450 mm - about the size of a large pizza.</Msg><Username>maveric_trader1</Username><Timestamp>1358717782611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:36:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358718470204-61</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Demonstrates Industry’s First Fully Patterned 450mm Wafer: Photos</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358629753635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:09:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC's 450mm schedule semiDOTorg/en/node/43256</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358718470204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:47:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358718995664-62</Id><Topic><Title>The world is porting to ARM</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358701719693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:08:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, the hype is porting to ARMH having finished with GLD and AAPL and NVDA ;-). Hype bubbles always crash though when reality eventually intrudes. I told you the NVDA $20+ price wouldn't hold and I am now saying the same about the ARMH $40+ price. Just a question of when not if.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358718995664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:56:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358719231232-63</Id><Title>You have to pay to play in semis. No one else can keep up</Title><Msg>Typical intc will be above and beyond with their manufacturing capability. AMD is broke. Last man standing 2013 till forever... Intc is not going outta busisness... Most others will or will sell their ip like isil. Gorilla in the house. Take your divi and watch longs. The WORLD must have chips.... Intc will be printing $ when the weak co are t a t t a s up. Wait fer it. The capper.</Msg><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1358719231232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:00:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358720467931-64</Id><Topic><Title>O)ff topic: The MLK Bible - Tavis Smiley</Title><Username>towncryer911</Username><Timestamp>1358697011214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:50:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raise elegibility age for Social security might make sense. Figure out how to lower the barrier for repatriating overseas profits might make sense. Address fraud. I don't know of anyone who would oppose this. Raise age on Medicare, "Repeal Obamacare", other medical issues .... the biggest emotional hot button and the least understood. Your suggested "start" roll back to a point, is where there is less medical support than before. "Repeal" will never happen for practical reasons. It will be tough to get through the Senate. At least one US Senator will put a "hold" on any "repeal Obamacare" bill. That is one reason why the 30 votes in the House is unproductive. New laws that "reorganize" the US medical programs are certainly possible. Many of the medical savings/costs get shifted to costs/savings in other areas without any real change. There is just some cost shifting. IMO, your "Lets start with the above!" type statement frames the big problem that faces the USA. There is no trust about where the end target is and what is a practical model for citizen living (what kind of country is desireable). There is a fear that surrendering a position of power will not be honored later. With that fear, there will be very little that is accomplished without a battle. I doubt that there will be much progress on anything without the 70% moderates in the center agreeing to make some big changes. Otherwise, the US will be just a sequence of battle of extreme positions.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358720467931</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:21:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358720573320-65</Id><Title>What we need to hear about TSMC's 20nm is not from TSMC but</Title><Msg>from companies like Nvidia and Broadcom who say TSMC 20nm is horse manure. Name 1 company that crows they have working samples of 20nm and its better than 28nm. Below 25nm, the going gets very tough, and TSMC has no one to copy from. Intel is on FinFet, and thats gonna take 4-5 years to copy.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358720573320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:22:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358720986780-66</Id><Title>jeez</Title><Msg>monster dumpage..look at the volume. gonna take months to recover. fricken hate this pig.</Msg><Username>po_sharp</Username><Timestamp>1358720986780</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:29:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358723163364-67</Id><Title>They cencored my black lazy brown peoples message</Title><Msg>Come on who is on the dole? Work my tail off while they get their checks is this America is it is it ? I think not they are losers and are a bunch o f paracites they wont post this either im done who ever is doing this needs a reality check.</Msg><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1358723163364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:06:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358723272201-68</Id><Topic><Title>They cencored my black lazy brown peoples message</Title><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1358723163364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:06:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good it posted......</Msg><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1358723272201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:07:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358723446880-69</Id><Topic><Title>450 mm - about the size of a large pizza.</Title><Username>maveric_trader1</Username><Timestamp>1358717782611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:36:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel Corp's(NSQ:INTC) decision to spend $13 billion in 2013 to develop and build future manufacturing technology has not gone down well on Wall Street but it may be necessary if it wants to stay on top of rivals in coming years. There were two reasons for INTC's stake in ASML: 1.) 450 mm (ASML was reluctant to support 450mm) NVLS system leader in deposition was reluctant too - Intel pulled some strings and LAM Research (leader in etch) bought NVLS and the "new" LRCX combined with NVLS are a key (450mm) supplier. Multi Patterning needs litho but also deposition and etch and that's why Intel pushed for LRCX/NVLS merger. So Intel's move becoming serious about 450 mm is the logic second step after making the equity investment in ASML. So I am baffled about WS chip "analysts" - they don't seem to get it 2.) EUV - will probably be late</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358723446880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:10:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358723555274-70</Id><Topic><Title>450 mm - about the size of a large pizza.</Title><Username>maveric_trader1</Username><Timestamp>1358717782611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:36:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intc stands amd goes out of buss</Msg><Username>hubcap1234_00</Username><Timestamp>1358723555274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:12:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358723608048-71</Id><Title>49ers pulled it off</Title><Msg>what a cliff hanger - they "destroyed" Matt Ryan in second half</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358723608048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:13:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358724255961-72</Id><Topic><Title>49ers pulled it off</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358723608048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:13:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Matt Ryan fumbling a perfectly good snap with the Falcons driving constitutes "getting destroyed" in your back, I'll have to laugh.</Msg><Username>smokinghotblitch</Username><Timestamp>1358724255961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:24:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358724803287-73</Id><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Msg>ARM's INFERIOR chips at a higher price CANNOT win in the marketplace over the long run. PERIOD. ARM is a severely hobbled architecture. It has now become a power hog with low performance with a high price tag compared to X86. Kludges such as Big little etc.. are done to compensate for its inferiority. In a few years, ARM will be relegated back to where it belongs, in the embedded market.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358724917688-74</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will_amd_yu You're wrong. Intel's going to take quite a bit of the embedded market, too :-)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1358724917688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:35:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358725181409-75</Id><Topic><Title>jeez</Title><Username>po_sharp</Username><Timestamp>1358720986780</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:29:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 143m share Friday volume raises the 5-day average volume to 62m shares. Intel can buyback 25% of that number so they will be able to buy 15m shares open market Tuesday (Monday holiday). It will take 5 days for the 143m shares to drain through the moving average and that allows Intel to buy 25% of that each day. Might not take too long.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358725181409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:39:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358725198302-76</Id><Title>10 years from now can I get at least 20/share for Intel?</Title><Msg>I'll sit back and take the dividend if so, but what are the odds that Intel will go under 15 and never return at some point in the next several years? 30 percent? 15 percent?</Msg><Username>stuckinintelfrom27</Username><Timestamp>1358725198302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:39:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358725337958-77</Id><Topic><Title>10 years from now can I get at least 20/share for Intel?</Title><Username>stuckinintelfrom27</Username><Timestamp>1358725198302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:39:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel borrowed $6b a couple months ago and the market charged them 70 basis points above treasuries. The credit swaps are priced to imply a near zero probability.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358725337958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:42:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358725858326-78</Id><Topic><Title>10 years from now can I get at least 20/share for Intel?</Title><Username>stuckinintelfrom27</Username><Timestamp>1358725198302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:39:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you saying that means the probability of it going under 15 and staying there forever is near zero?</Msg><Username>stuckinintelfrom27</Username><Timestamp>1358725858326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:50:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358727379787-79</Id><Topic><Title>10 years from now can I get at least 20/share for Intel?</Title><Username>stuckinintelfrom27</Username><Timestamp>1358725198302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:39:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The CDS pricing implies that there is near zero chance of Intel not being able to pay off the notes. It means that Intel would not have problems making dividend payments and operating normally, making profits and paying dividends. Intel has only been under $15 twice since 1996. Sept 2002: think Invasion of Iraq. March 2009: the market crash bottom when the SP500 hit a low of 666. Since Mar 2009, the Intel share count has dropped from 6.5b down to 4.9b shares. The Intel revenues are up from $35b in 2009 to $53b in 2013. On an adjusted units per share value, Intel priced today at $21 is very close to its all time low.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358727379787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:16:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358727610946-80</Id><Topic><Title>10 years from now can I get at least 20/share for Intel?</Title><Username>stuckinintelfrom27</Username><Timestamp>1358725198302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:39:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for taking the time to give your thoughts. You're a good soul. I'm going to hang in there as 20 would be fine with me forever as long as the current Dividend is not reduced or taken away permanently.</Msg><Username>stuckinintelfrom27</Username><Timestamp>1358727610946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:20:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358728367567-81</Id><Topic><Title>49ers pulled it off</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358723608048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:13:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't like either team but I dislike the Falcons and Ryan more. Happy to see them blow a 17-0 lead in the playoffs. They were a fraud and only win at home til now. I do like the SF QB these guys will change defensive game plans going foward.</Msg><Username>vincent90157</Username><Timestamp>1358728367567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:32:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358729079391-82</Id><Title>INTC is an ATM</Title><Msg>and not much more. I got in $21.03-$21.14 out at $21.24 before close. This might retest those $20 levels like it did a couple of months ago but who knows the market seems to be in a forgiving mood towards lackluster earnings these days.</Msg><Username>vincent90157</Username><Timestamp>1358729079391</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:44:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358731477159-83</Id><Topic><Title>49ers pulled it off</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358723608048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:13:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go 49ers - I will buy next week if the stock drops further.</Msg><Username>maveric_trader1</Username><Timestamp>1358731477159</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:24:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358733658525-84</Id><Topic><Title>49ers pulled it off</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358723608048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:13:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>California Trash...SMH Falcons fan stabbed in throat by 49ers fan outside Georgia Dome after loss - developing story.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358733658525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:00:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358736096735-85</Id><Topic><Title>49ers pulled it off</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358723608048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:13:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The California Trash was attacked first and was just defending himself. Should he have used his AK47 or Bushmaster AR-15 instead of his knife? Self defense is perfectly legal in Georgia. Not only is the California Trash in the right but the Georgia Trash will probably go to prison. The California Trash will probably sue the Georgia Trash for assault. We have to protect our guns and knives from people like you who just want to take away our protection and ignore our 2nd amendment rights.</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1358736096735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:41:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358736546956-86</Id><Title>21.25 -1.43 (-6.31%)</Title><Msg>Should open at $20.00</Msg><Username>larry_the_frog</Username><Timestamp>1358736546956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:49:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358736849193-87</Id><Topic><Title>49ers pulled it off</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358723608048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:13:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$. aholewad AKA........Wallisweaver. Lying, disgusting, moral-less pumper with a million aliases. ZERO life, ZERO integrity..........act like he has a job but doesn't and lives off of Obama handouts. California trash.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358736849193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:54:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358736931076-88</Id><Topic><Title>The world is porting to ARM</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358701719693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:08:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the hype is porting to ARMH having finished " Doesn't even start until ARM64... "wouldn't hold and I am now saying the same about the ARMH $40+ price. " OK Marsavian, Stops at $40... but I'll keep holding otherwise...</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358736931076</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:55:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358736932291-89</Id><Topic><Title>49ers pulled it off</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358723608048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:13:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. half 24 : 14 2. half 00 : 14 24 : 28</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358736932291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:55:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358737020447-90</Id><Title>California trash elects Arnold Schwartzenhagger as Governer</Title><Msg>You can't make this stuff up! California is the armpit of earth.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358737020447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:57:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358737375938-91</Id><Topic><Title>49ers pulled it off</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358723608048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:13:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$. att4glte AKA........Wallisweaver. Lying, disgusting, moral-less pumper with a million aliases. ZERO life, ZERO integrity..........act like he has a job but doesn't and lives off of Obama handouts. California trash. The only thing that att4glte likes to jump is his sister, mother, grandmother and pet boar hog. The only thing that att4glte can do is jump to conclusions, whine, complain and generally make life unpleasant for all those around him. Noone in the hogslopper's family can even stand the stench. WHEEEEEW!!! Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, .... run little piggy. See Mom run! Run Mom, run! TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYYY</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1358737375938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:02:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358737398551-92</Id><Topic><Title>49ers pulled it off</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358723608048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:13:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Falcons fan stabbed in throat by 49ers fan outside Georgia Dome after loss I thought they played @ Candlestick Park? att4glte: you should see a shrink - you are a basket case</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358737398551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:03:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358738780646-93</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Demonstrates Industry’s First Fully Patterned 450mm Wafer: Photos</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358629753635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:09:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2015/16 IS TIME LINE...CLOWNS 2013/2014 BRUTAL FOR INTEL ON MARGINS AND REVENUE SHRINKAGE NEXT</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1358738780646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:26:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358739344211-94</Id><Title>It's a bit of a feast-or-famine da</Title><Msg>It's a bit of a feast-or-famine day on Wall Street as earnings drive stocks today, but even big movers haven't stirred the markets as a whole. The Dow Jones Industrial Average is up just 0.11% as of 3:20 p.m. EST, and the S&amp;P 500 is flat. Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC)'s shares have tanked 6.7% today after the company reported earnings last night. Earnings per share of $0.48 beat estimates by $0.03, and revenue of $13.5 billion was in line with estimates, but investors are still worried about the future. Intel didn't have any bullish remarks about the state of the PC market, and it is planning to increase capital spending to $13 billion next year from $11 billion this year -- a bit of a shock to investors. The increase in spending has investors worried that Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) won't keep up its lofty 4.1% dividend yield, especially if it can't quickly make big inroads into smartphones and tablets.</Msg><Username>longtrader123</Username><Timestamp>1358739344211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:35:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358741899772-95</Id><Topic><Title>Look for another BIG down day for intc -</Title><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1358708500681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:01:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You think it can drop to $19. I dare you to short it now. The catalyst will be Intel's $6 Billion new debt, mostly to buy shares back. With 20 tablets out in the market already using Intel chips. One of them being Samsung. With 140 ultrabook design wins, with the hybrid versions all selling out as soon as they hit the store shelves. As for smartphones, Intel may not be in the U.S. market till 2014 due to LTE being fully ready in 2014, Intel is already in the two most populous countries, China and India. I would not bet against China. With Lenovo very close to being number one smartphone supplier in China. I would say that the Lenovo K900 is another catalyst. Goodluck going against that powerhouse.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358741899772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:18:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358742074483-96</Id><Title>No LTE til 2014?? Now that's is a disaster</Title><Msg>and they lied. Said razr I would be early 2013. I don't like this kettle of fish one bit.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358742074483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:21:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358742256978-97</Id><Title>First time buyer at 21.06</Title><Msg>With its nice dividends, very unlikely that it will drop anymore, especially next week when you have so many big companies reporting and with each of those who miss on earnings, you'll have investors looking for stocks with nice dividends and stocks that have already reported, like Intel.</Msg><Username>hey_rob69</Username><Timestamp>1358742256978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:24:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358742505076-98</Id><Topic><Title>First time buyer at 21.06</Title><Username>hey_rob69</Username><Timestamp>1358742256978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:24:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry to hear you invested you money in INTC they will be $19 in a few weeks............................. 20% will easily that this stock way done.</Msg><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1358742505076</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:28:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358742572285-99</Id><Title>20% correct on the way</Title><Msg>Look out - the markets are going down huge.</Msg><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1358742572285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:29:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358742575794-100</Id><Title>PC maker Asus reportedly eyeing Windows Phone 8 Microsoft-powered phones could join manufacturer's Windows PCs and tablets.</Title><Msg>Microsoft-powered phones could join manufacturer's Windows PCs and tablets.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358742575794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:29:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358742779616-101</Id><Topic><Title>The world is porting to ARM</Title><Username>chumpanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358701719693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:08:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intc fate is isn't anymore enviable.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358742779616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:32:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358742824908-102</Id><Topic><Title>No LTE til 2014?? Now that's is a disaster</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358742074483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:21:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now that's is a disaster Is it?</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358742824908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:33:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358743695480-103</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In a few years there won't be any lunch left for intc. There are too many companies invested in arm there is no way intc can win on all the fronts it's trying to fight. Once AMD finally folds the Intel will be the sole company supporting x86 while arm has numerous - that's a lot of r &amp;d to contend with. As for your technical assessment - you are clueless. If you want an examples of kludges take a close look at the evolution of the x86 - everything from its addressing schema to instruction sets.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358743695480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:48:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358744349806-104</Id><Topic><Title>Why Intel will prevail against ARM over the next few years.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358724803287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:33:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel will never take the embedded market. Can u give me one embedded example where it would be cost effective to use an x86?!? Anybody who'd use an x86 for a true embedded solution is nuts. I can use an nxp 32 bit arm proc for like $2 bucks.</Msg><Username>brokeagain73</Username><Timestamp>1358744349806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:59:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>