<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-21"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366516884627-1</Id><Topic><Title>Apple/Intel deal in the works way back in 2011</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1366516346558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:52:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did anyone listen to Doug Freedman, the RBC analyst on the conference call? Does he sound like the type of person that would make up a story? Remember, Doug Freedman, last November, said Apple and Intel are set to make a deal. Apple uses x86 chips in iPads (Bay Trail) while Intel fab Apple's chips for the iPhone. The deal is coming guys.</Msg><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1366516884627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 00:01:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366518359737-2</Id><Topic><Title>Apple/Intel deal in the works way back in 2011</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1366516346558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:52:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Russ Fischer had this to say: On the topic of the foundry initiative, Mr. Otellini, when asked about making ARM based products, said, "The second is that we would not enable a chip competitor." Most would interpret that as a hard "no," but the two words "chip competitor," while not admitting to doing ASIC chips for Apple (AAPL), did not exclude that possibility. What was excluded was foundry work for Qualcomm (QCOM), Nvidia (NVDA), and, of course, Samsung (SSNLF.PK). A very careful and clever answer from Mr. Otellini.</Msg><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1366518359737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 00:25:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366547841026-3</Id><Topic><Title>Can Otellini stay on?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366408969846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If so, why is he and Andy are in a big hurry to unload their stock? Do the shorts' alarmingly heavy bet (4.86 of float) mean anything? It is rather unusual to have such an intense activity in a stock that pays 4.00+% in dividends while Cramer continues to recommend the stock. What more bearish signals can one look for?</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1366547841026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 08:37:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366552471018-4</Id><Topic><Title>Rumor: Intel and Partners Working on Android Convertible Push</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366393035641</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:37:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Payback is a #$%$ Microsoft. I love it.</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1366552471018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 09:54:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366553421563-5</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, RE: Intel's investor meeting for 2013.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1366503702143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:21:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My earlier reply never came through.... If Otellini leaves as planned, the new CEO would need a few months to settle down and be ready for the Investor Meeting.</Msg><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366553421563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 10:10:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366555653216-6</Id><Topic><Title>Rumor: Intel and Partners Working on Android Convertible Push</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366393035641</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:37:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what are the office apps like on android? Is there a good alternative to Word an Xcel? I have never been satisfied with the Linux alternatives. But, I detest MsWord..every few years they have so monkeyd with it that you can't find any of the usual controls.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1366555653216</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 10:47:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366557730481-7</Id><Topic><Title>Test</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366410905209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:35:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you sound like George Bush II. "Bring it on" "Mission accomplished" Tough talk from the party of guns and dead children..the party of death for the masses, money for the few... such a wise party you come from.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1366557730481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 11:22:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366564477278-8</Id><Title>Comparisons of top 5 dividend payers in Dow 30.</Title><Msg>Intel is currently the number 3 highest yield in dividend payout in the Dow. But how does it compare in key fundamentals among top 5. Start with number one, MO. Dividend payout is highest at 5%. Trailing EPS is currently $2.21 with a PE of 15.83 Their dividend payout is about 80% of its trailing EPS. They have $2.9 Billion in cash with $13.88 Billion in debt. Numer two is AT&amp;T (T). Dividend payout is 4.7%. Trailing EPS is currently $2.33 with a PE of 16.43 Their dividend payout is about 77% of its trailing EPS. They have $4.95 Billion in cash with $69.84 Billion in debt. At number four, right behind Intel, is VZ. Dividend payout is 3.9%. Trailing EPS is $2.41 with a PE of 21.68 Their dividend payout is about 85% of its trailing EPS. They have $6.14 Billion in cash with about $52.88 Billion in debt. At number five, it's Merck (MRK) Dividend payout is 3.6%. Trailing EPS is $3.82 with a PE of 12.43 Their dividend payout is about 45% of its trailing EPS. They have $16.14 Billion in cash with about $20.57 Billion in debt. At number three is my favorite and safest dividend payer in Dow, Intel. Dividend payout is 4.0% Trailing PE is currently at $2.00 with a PE of 11.22 (the cheapest of the top 5. Their dividend payout is about 45% of its trailing EPS (tied with Merck as the lowest ratio) They have $17.07 Billion in cash (which is the highest of the top 5) with about $13.23 Billion in debt (which is the lowest of the top 5). Also their debt to cash ratio is at only .77 which is by far the lowest. Taking into account both the dividend yield payout and the fundamentals, Intel is currently the best dividend stock of the Dow.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1366564477278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 13:14:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366565460307-9</Id><Topic><Title>Test</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366410905209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:35:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Wallis; You are a coward!" [And you're ugly and your mother dresses you funny...] [Wow, these games are fun! Your turn...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366565460307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 13:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366565539160-10</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis, RE: Intel's investor meeting for 2013.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1366503702143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:21:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If Otellini leaves as planned, the new CEO would need a few months to settle down and be ready for the Investor Meeting." [Unless it's someone like Stacy Smith...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366565539160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 13:32:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366565612848-11</Id><Topic><Title>Comparisons of top 5 dividend payers in Dow 30.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1366564477278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 13:14:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice..but the reason I'm into INTC is the rate of growth of dividend, which has been spectacular over past decade. It's probably the best of the 5. .I don't know how sustainable, though. In May I hope they put their policy where Stacy's mouth is and raise it another $0.015/qtr.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1366565612848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 13:33:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366565634976-12</Id><Topic><Title>Can Otellini stay on?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366408969846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Tech wonk Wally, do you own AAPL?" [I don't but I confess I'm thinking about it. But they have to show me something first. I've been waiting and waiting and waiting. I'm still waiting...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366565634976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 13:33:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366565933370-13</Id><Topic><Title>Can Otellini stay on?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366408969846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The shorts heavy bet simply means that the shorts got it wrong on earnings and the "PC is dead" nonsense. It isn't something waiting to play out. It has already played out and shorts are in shock in response to Intel's strong move up when the NASDAQ was moving down. If you want to see an incredible gap, chart Intel verses the NASDAQ for the last 5 days. Shorts blew it. Now here comes Haswell and the Year of the Intel Tablet. And a number of new big announcements with maybe one this week...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366565933370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 13:38:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366566168004-14</Id><Title>Apple Earnings on Tuesday</Title><Msg>Apple has to tell the world something and it better be good. If they are going to do something with Intel, then this would be a great time to announce it. More of the same isn't going to re-ignite the stock. Another week of big risk for Intel shorts. Any kind of deal with Apple would crush them...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366566168004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 13:42:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366566744095-15</Id><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Msg>Another tough week for ARM longs as the stock dropped close to 2 bucks and finished under $40. Haswell is just around the corner and that massive P/E ratio looks like anvil around ARM's neck. Otellini's remark about the $200 Intel device price level got huge press. 2013: The Year of the Intel Tablet Apple dropped $35 bucks as it's slide continues. A very interesting week coming up...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366566744095</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 13:52:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366567094703-16</Id><Title>Tom's Hardware - Is Intel Pushing Android-based Notebook Hybrids?</Title><Msg>tomshardwareDOTcom/news/Androidbook-Paul-Otellini-Lenovo-Yoga-Hybrid-Bay-Trail,22140DOThtml "Sources claim these Intel-based Android hybrids will attract strong demand because (1) consumers are highly familiar with Android and (2) Google has brought Quickoffice to Android for editing Microsoft Office files. Of course, the latter is part of Google Apps for Business, but should make Android more competitive against a Windows 8 solution in the home or office. [IMO, this is a major development. OEMs are pre-loading hybrids with Android, instead of Windows, to bring down the price point. I am sure they will offer to preload Windows (or dual boot option) at a higher price. Advanced users can also add the dual boot functionality after purchase if they wish. But this move of selling PCs preloaded with Android is significant and can really spur excitement and demand]</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366567094703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 13:58:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366567983897-17</Id><Topic><Title>Tom's Hardware - Is Intel Pushing Android-based Notebook Hybrids?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366567094703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 13:58:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, Google acquired QuickOffice last year: googleblogDOTblogspotDOTcom/2012/06/google-quickoffice-get-more-doneDOThtml quickofficeDOTcom/google_acquires_quickoffice</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366567983897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 14:13:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366568318001-18</Id><Title>Intel/ARM Roadmap Comparison</Title><Msg>Intel 22nm: Haswell June 2013 14nm: Broadwell: End of 2013/Start of 2014 14nm: Skylake: 2015 10nm: Skymont: 2016 7nm: 2018 5nm: 2020 ARMH 28nm: Production has been increasing but is still insufficient to meet market demand. Substantially all of the production is coming from TSMC, which is a significant bottleneck. 20nm: Volume production in 2014/2015. TSMC has promised to ramp 20nm faster than 28nm but this appears to be nothing more than rhetoric as 20nm will be yet another level of complexity when trends have show each successive ARM die shrink to ramp significantly slower than the previous. 14/16nm: ARM foundries will pursue a half-step to FinFET by making it half FinFET and half 20nm. This clearly illustrates their lack of confidence in bringing a full step online in a reasonable time frame. There are so many unknowns with the half-step process, that any prediction of volume production cannot be reliably made. Conclusions 1.) Intel will continue to have significant opportunities for high margin foundry work, as illustrated by the Altera deal. 2.) Intel's fabrication economics will continue to improve just as ARM's are degrading. ARMs 20nm planar and the half-step to FinFET both have inferior economics to the Intel nodes. 3.) Intel will reach 450mm wafer implementation well ahead of ARM, giving them significantly improved economic benefits. Intel's lead in fabrication and manufacturing is increasing in virtually every area.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366568318001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 14:18:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366568804391-19</Id><Topic><Title>Intel/ARM Roadmap Comparison</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366568318001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 14:18:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and if you listen to TSMC's last conference call, they are totally unprepared for 450 mm: Randy Abrams - Crédit Suisse AG, Research Division The second question, on 450-millimeter, it's pretty far out, but we're seeing Intel already spend about $2 billion to $3 billion on a 450-millimeter shell, when do you expect... Morris Chang - Chairman and Chief Executive Officer On what? Elizabeth Sun - Director of Corporate Communication Division On 450-millimeter. Randy Abrams - Crédit Suisse AG, Research Division 18 inch. Yes, when is your expectation you'll have to start spending CapEx? And do you have any view on fab location at this stage? Morris Chang - Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Have we started to spend CapEx yet? Lora Ho - Chief Financial Officer and Senior Vice President of Finance Not yet, we have to start to spend R&amp;D. And we have a small team working on 450 but not really to start on the meaningful way in CapEx. Morris Chang - Chairman and Chief Executive Officer I think his question is when do we plan to start CapEx? Well, I think our schedule is 2016, isn't it? Lora Ho - Chief Financial Officer and Senior Vice President of Finance In the 2016 time frame. That will be the time we start to spend CapEx. Morris Chang - Chairman and Chief Executive Officer So it's too early yet. Well, yes.</Msg><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366568804391</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 14:26:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366569091632-20</Id><Title>Intel Mobility Roadmap</Title><Msg>Clover Trail platform (2012) Intel's fifth generation MID platform contains a 32 nm Intel Atom processor (codenamed Cloverview). Bay Trail platform (2013) Intel's sixth generation MID platform (codenamed Bay Trail) contains a 22 nm Intel Atom SoC (codenamed Valleyview). Airmont-based platform (2014) Intel's seventh generation MID platform contains a 14 nm Intel Atom SoC. [Airmont scares the bejesus out of the ARM world. It is the reason that 2014 will be the Year of Intel Smartphone...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366569091632</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 14:31:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366569229835-21</Id><Topic><Title>Intel/ARM Roadmap Comparison</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366568318001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 14:18:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, Morris sounds totally clueless on TSMC's 450mm wafer plans!</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366569229835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 14:33:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366571371730-22</Id><Title>Gamers Only</Title><Msg>Google this and check out the video: Team Fortress 2 on Oculus Rift with an Omnidirectional Treadmill Excellent for tubby gamers. LOL</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366571371730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 15:09:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366572408227-23</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Earnings on Tuesday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366566168004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 13:42:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More of the same would be having iphone 5s and ipad using samsung's 28nm then tsmc's 20nm next year. No one will buy apple products when Samsung and others will have better offerings. Apple need to switch to bay trail for their ipads and offer windows 8 thru bootcamp. Then have intel fab their phone chips. by 2014, apple will be on 14nm instead of 20nm and will have clear advantage over samsung.</Msg><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1366572408227</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 15:26:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366572462504-24</Id><Topic><Title>Apple/Intel deal in the works way back in 2011</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1366516346558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:52:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will apple announce deal on Tuesday or wait until later in the year?</Msg><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1366572462504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 15:27:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366575604613-25</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Earnings on Tuesday</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366566168004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 13:42:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, the more I think about the more I conclude that Apple needs Intel to get a leg up on Samsung. I don't see anything else that will give them the same bump. At the same time it would get rid of the risk of depending on TSMC which is a very significant risk going forward. Not just at 20nm but after that - if there is any after that. ARM foundry FinFET efforts are unknown at best. With Intel, Apple knows it would have fabrication solutions for the next 10 years. I think Apple is nuts if they don't tell somebody something on Tuesday. They have a chance to reverse the slide. Or to quicken it if they have nothing to project...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366575604613</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 16:20:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366576678714-26</Id><Topic><Title>Can Otellini stay on?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366408969846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There will be well over 30M shares for sale tomorrow as a result of exercised options which expired on Friday. Now then, where are the buyers?</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1366576678714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 16:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366577688234-27</Id><Topic><Title>Can Otellini stay on?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366408969846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're saying all of a sudden there's now 30m more shares for sale tomorrow because option expired ? it doesn't work that way bonehead.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1366577688234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 16:54:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366578338775-28</Id><Title>Shorts get fried again next week</Title><Msg>we are looking at $14.5 billion in revenue for Q3 and Q4. 2014 looks even stronger as Intel will not be hit with excess capacity charges. This is the bottom.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1366578338775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 17:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366579799117-29</Id><Title>Analysts will come out next week and bad mouth Intel.</Title><Msg>PC is dead and tablets are taking over the world. Intel's projections are unbelievable. ARM is eating Intel's lunch...</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366579799117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 17:29:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366579831409-30</Id><Title>Intel and Android</Title><Msg>Is Intel Pushing Android-based Notebook Hybrids? 12:00 PM - April 21, 2013 Unnamed sources from notebook vendors told DigiTimes that Intel is pushing hybrid notebooks that use Google's Android operating system, form factors that can be used as both a notebook and a tablet thanks to a detachable keyboard. China-based Lenovo is supposedly the first on the list to produce such a device, an 11-inch Android-based Yoga notebook slated for a May release. According to the report, many other OEMs are jumping on the Android-based hybrid bandwagon as well including HP, Toshiba, Acer and Asus with models hitting the streets in the third quarter. Sources claim that Intel has estimated the retail "sweet spot" to be around $500 USD, mirroring a statement made by Intel CEO Paul Otellini last week. The news shouldn't be surprising given all the recent talk about how disappointed OEMs have been with Windows 8. Microsoft's new touchy update has been partially blamed for the dramatic drop in PC sales over the last several quarters. Yet while Microsoft is making slow progress in the smartphone and tablet sectors, it's currently still not enough to fend off the more lucrative Android and iOS solutions. Earlier this week Otellini hinted during the company's first-quarter earnings conference call to Windows 8 devices with a smaller form factor and a smaller price point. These inexpensive designs will be based on Intel's upcoming quad-core "Bay Trail" 22-nm chip, the first complete redesign of the Atom micro architecture since it debuted in 2008. "If you look at touch-enabled Intel-based notebooks that are ultrathin using [Bay Trail] processors, those prices are going to be down to as low as $200," he said. Otellini also predicted that more standard Ultrabook designs sporting the upcoming Haswell chip will likely reside within the $499 price range.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1366579831409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 17:30:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366580095685-31</Id><Topic><Title>Intel and Android</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1366579831409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 17:30:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is not the first time we've heard about Android on notebooks this year. DigiTimes coughed up another story earlier this month claiming that "Androidbooks" may march into the market by the end of 3Q13 or the beginning of 4Q13. Given that Intel released the x86 image of Android 4.2 "Jelly Bean" last year for Atom-based chips, and that Google doesn't charge a licensing fee to use Android, the idea is far from being farfetched. Sources claim these Intel-based Android hybrids will attract strong demand because (1) consumers are highly familiar with Android and (2) Google has brought Quickoffice to Android for editing Microsoft Office files. Of course, the latter is part of Google Apps for Business, but should make Android more competitive against a Windows 8 solution in the home or office. Recently ZDNet reported that many PC OEMs are unhappy with Microsoft and what it has done with the Windows platform. One OEM source supposedly said that Microsoft is destroying the PC industry while another said that Microsoft has driven millions of customers over to Apple. Based on the DigiTimes report, OEMS are flocking to Android to produce lucrative solutions to make up for the revenue void that Windows 8 has seemingly left behind.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1366580095685</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 17:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366580571833-32</Id><Topic><Title>Analysts will come out next week and bad mouth Intel.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366579799117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 17:29:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're an idiot</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1366580571833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 17:42:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366580925892-33</Id><Topic><Title>Analysts will come out next week and bad mouth Intel.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366579799117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 17:29:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With an ID impersonating another vinnie, you are the smart one. LOL.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366580925892</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 17:48:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366581900439-34</Id><Topic><Title>Analysts will come out next week and bad mouth Intel.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366579799117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 17:29:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PC is dead and tablets are taking over the world. Intel's projections are unbelievable. ARM is eating Intel's lunch.. *** And how do you square the post above with this one you made just three days ago: "Too late for Apple. Apple is going with Intel. They have NO OTHER CHOICE." You've convinced me that this is just more of Dana's stupidity...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366581900439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 18:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366583102260-35</Id><Topic><Title>Can Otellini stay on?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366408969846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are people going to do with the in-the-money expired options? Really, do you ladies have any idea as to what options are being discussed?</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1366583102260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 18:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366583441597-36</Id><Topic><Title>Can Otellini stay on?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366408969846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whatever moron. you a moron because you said in your previous post that there'll be 30M shares for sale tomorrow. how do you explain that moron?</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1366583441597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 18:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366583485690-37</Id><Topic><Title>Tom's Hardware - Is Intel Pushing Android-based Notebook Hybrids?</Title><Username>bacbacker</Username><Timestamp>1366567094703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 13:58:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The open source office package is very effective and handles about 90% of what most people use an office package for. An Intel-based Android tablet will make a very useful product, however an Intel tablet with dual-boot or multi-boot W8 and Android is a big step up in versatility and probably well worth the extra cost.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1366583485690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 18:31:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366584405761-38</Id><Topic><Title>Analysts will come out next week and bad mouth Intel.</Title><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1366579799117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 17:29:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's well-known around these parts that Lucy posts as will_amd_you. He's the most bitter underwater Long in the world, and takes his anger out on Wallisweaver. Think!</Msg><Username>lucy_mutt</Username><Timestamp>1366584405761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 18:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366585382124-39</Id><Topic><Title>Can Otellini stay on?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366408969846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Budha of Bridgewater, NJ said best. "Company with a fool is pain and misery."</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1366585382124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 19:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366587027471-40</Id><Topic><Title>Can Otellini stay on?</Title><Username>ideal_invst</Username><Timestamp>1366408969846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What are people going to do with the in-the-money expired options? Really, do you ladies have any idea as to what options are being discussed?" [Anyone with a brain doesn't wait for an in-the-money option to expire. They sell them before expiration specifically so they don't end up with the shares...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366587027471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 19:30:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366591475060-41</Id><Title>Daniel Nenni</Title><Msg>When not riding around in his convertible hot rod, smiling at 20 year old women that are 35 years younger than him, he's on the yahoo board creating aliases like "wallis.weaver", trying to pimp his 4th rate newsletter and telling Intel longs to "suck it". He's a true professional, every guy's guy.</Msg><Username>lucy_mutt</Username><Timestamp>1366591475060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 20:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366591593162-42</Id><Topic><Title>Daniel Nenni</Title><Username>lucy_mutt</Username><Timestamp>1366591475060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 20:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that him on Linked In with that Beau Tie on? LOLOL....................OL.</Msg><Username>lucy_mutt</Username><Timestamp>1366591593162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 20:46:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366593146754-43</Id><Title>The Intel Years</Title><Msg>2013: Year of the Intel Tablet 2014: Year of the Intel Smartphone Intel/ARM Roadmap Comparison Intel 22nm: Haswell June 2013 14nm: Broadwell: End of 2013/Start of 2014 14nm: Skylake: 2015 10nm: Skymont: 2016 7nm: 2018 5nm: 2020 ARMH 28nm: Production has been increasing but is still insufficient to meet market demand. Substantially all of the production is coming from TSMC, which is a significant bottleneck. 20nm: Volume production in 2014/2015. TSMC has promised to ramp 20nm faster than 28nm but this appears to be nothing more than rhetoric as 20nm will be yet another level of complexity when trends have show each successive ARM die shrink to ramp significantly slower than the previous. 14/16nm: ARM foundries will pursue a half-step to FinFET by making it half FinFET and half 20nm. This clearly illustrates their lack of confidence in bringing a full step online in a reasonable time frame. There are so many unknowns with the half-step process, that any prediction of volume production cannot be reliably made. Conclusions 1.) Intel will continue to have significant opportunities for high margin foundry work, as illustrated by the Altera deal. 2.) Intel's fabrication economics will continue to improve just as ARM's are degrading. ARMs 20nm planar and the half-step to FinFET both have inferior economics to the Intel nodes. 3.) Intel will reach 450mm wafer implementation well ahead of ARM, giving them significantly improved economic benefits. Intel's lead in fabrication and manufacturing is increasing in virtually every area. e</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366593146754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 21:12:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366595644132-44</Id><Title>Intel's latest processor price list.</Title><Msg>Just released on 4/21. Again, after 3 whole months, not one of their over 200 CPU offerrings dropped in price. Looks like Intel is still having no problem at all selling their CPU's.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1366595644132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 21:54:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>