<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367899373732-1</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Each of these sentences represents a body blow to ARM in terms of competitive capabilities. Just take one: "Merrifield will probably be the first 64-bit smartphone SoC." Wow, what a huge deal just that one aspect is! And it's just one of many. The overall conclusion: "In conclusion, the 22nm Silvermont CPU is a tremendous step forward, particularly in mobile devices. It is a thoroughly modern microarchitecture that is both higher performance and more efficient than the previous Saltwell core." Note to analysts: If you still can't figure out what this means then let me know and I'll send you a translation in reverse-mirror print that you can have tattooed on your foreheads so you can see it every morning when you shave. It goes like this: "ARM is so toast!!!" Don't let your wake-up call be the trophy wife pulling out of the driveway in the limo pulling the U-Haul...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367899373732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:02:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367899495279-2</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Silvermont should be banned ... on the grounds of something that good just has to be illegal !! LOL" [Indeed! I just finished reading the article you posted up and I can't stop grinning and laughing...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367899495279</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:04:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367899869889-3</Id><Topic><Title>THE STREET DOESN'T GET IT YET!</Title><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367894239023</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 22:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I have to say I don't think Dadi did a very good job of delivering the message today." My guess this presentation was given by Intel to VIC like Apple/CSCO months ago - anybody who believes Apple is not evaluating Intel seriously lives in LaLa land. So who cares whether his English is not perfect - a heavy duty accent combined with knowledge can be a great asset - people who have the knowledge can fill in the blanks. Maybe do a rerun for the financial community. Varian Semiconductor ( bought out by AMAT) used to have investor days events and at the end Varian management would quiz the analysts to make sure they understood the message.....</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367899869889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:11:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367900173957-4</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Anandtech one is also a good read if you have not read it yet anandtechDOTcom/show/6936/intels-silvermont-architecture-revealed-getting-serious-about-mobile Notice how they are using improvements from the Core architecture to beef up the Atom ipc but they are still generations behind with this only using Westmere level so there is still more easy hanging fruit to pick in the future. Shame multi-threading got dropped for die space reasons but it is not really needed this time round and I suspect it will make a resurgence at the 2015 14nm tock spec to rudely greet A57 with ;-).</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367900173957</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:16:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367900387122-5</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone..has splained why its down?</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367891179974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:46:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Ashrraff? The Beaver? Why down? You guys have hyped..and I mean HYPED this thing. So why down?" [My guess two things: One is that a lot of effort was spent by the short crowd trying to keep the stock under control today. Intel opened big and then got beat on almost immediately. ARM looked terrible at the opening and then immediately moved up. The other is that Wall Street is dumber than a box of rocks and will take at least two or three days to have the impact of Silvermont explained to them.] [Analogy: ARM is the deer that got gut-shot with the Silvermont bullet today. Who cares that the deer then ran off into the trees? The outcome is not in doubt...] [And if you thought the run up hype was big, you ain't seen nothin yet. We hyped the run up because we thought Silvermont was good. Now we actually know that Silvermont is GREAT!!!]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367900387122</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367900597572-6</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>["Today Intel is in a different position..."] The most frustrating part about covering Intel’s journey into mobile over the past five years is just how long it’s taken to get here. The CPU cores used in Medfield, Clover Trail and Clover Trail+ are very similar to what Intel had with the first Atom in 2008. Obviously we’re dealing with higher levels of integration and tweaks for further power consumption, but the architecture and much of the core remains unchanged. Just consider what that means. A single Bonnell core, designed in 2004, released in 2008, is already faster than ARM’s Cortex A9. Intel had this architecture for five years now and from the market’s perspective, did absolutely nothing with it. You could argue that the part wasn’t really ready until Intel had its 32nm process, so perhaps we’ve only wasted 3 years (Intel debuted its 32nm process in 2010). It’s beyond frustrating to think about just how competitive Intel would have been had it aggressively pursued this market. Today Intel is in a different position. After acquisitions, new hires and some significant internal organizational changes, Intel seems to finally have the foundation to iterate and innovate in mobile. Although Bonnell (the first Atom core) was the beginning of Intel’s journey into mobile, it’s Silvermont - Intel’s first new Atom microarchitecture since 2008 - that finally puts Intel on the right course.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367900597572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:23:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367900672580-7</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Multi-threading was dropped? How come slide 34 has multi-thread comparison?</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367900672580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367900735034-8</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When they announced Medfield, it was supposed to be clearly superior to the available ARM offerings and they flashed up numbers to back that, yet when the benchmarks were done and the market looked at it, it was not so. Let's hope they were more honest with Merrifield.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367900735034</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:25:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367900962319-9</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>["The even better news is that Silvermont will only be with us for a year before it gets its first update: Airmont."] [Airmont (14nm Intel Atom SoC) is the word that truly strikes terror into the ARM world. But it's looking like the war may be over before it arrives. Silvermont is amazing...] Although Silvermont can find its way into everything from cars to servers, the architecture is primarily optimized for use in smartphones and then in tablets, in that order. This is a significant departure from the previous Bonnell core that was first designed to serve the now defunct Mobile Internet Devices category that Intel put so much faith in back in the early to mid 2000s. As Intel’s first Atom architecture designed for mobile, expectations are high for Silvermont. While we’ll have to wait until the end of the year to see Silvermont in tablets (and early next year for phones), the good news for Intel is that Silvermont seems competitive right out of the gate. The even better news is that Silvermont will only be with us for a year before it gets its first update: Airmont.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367900962319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:29:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367901148654-10</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A thread in those cases run on each core. To be fair multi-threading gives less advantage to an OoO design in terms of hiding latency than to an in-order design although it really helps in getting the most out of wide execution unit rich designs like Haswell.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367901148654</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:32:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367901199426-11</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[New improvements coming every year! The Intel Roadmap is fully loaded...] Intel made this announcement last year, but Silvermont is the beginning of Intel’s tick-tock cadence for Atom. Intel plans on revving Atom yearly for at least the next three years. Silvermont introduces a new architecture, while Airmont will take that architecture and bring it down to 14nm in 2014/2015. One year later, we’ll see another brand new architecture take the stage also on 14nm. This is a shift that Intel needed to implement years ago, but it’s still not too late. Before we get into an architectural analysis of Silvermont, it’s important to get some codenames in order. Bonnell was the name of the original 45nm Atom core, it was later shrunk to 32nm and called Saltwell when it arrived in smartphones and tablets last year. Silvermont is the name of the CPU core alone, but when it shows up in tablets later this year it will do so as a part of the Baytrail SoC and a part of the Merrifield SoC next year in smartphones.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367901199426</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:33:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367901355538-12</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"it’s extremely likely that with Silvermont Intel will be able to drive down to far lower power levels than anything we’ve ever measured..." [Wow, you don't see statements like that every day!!!]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367901355538</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:35:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367901899199-13</Id><Title>Mr. Alias recommends everyone take profits on INTC-</Title><Msg>repeated as 10 new posts since 5/3 - Wonder how many we get on Tuesday?</Msg><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367901899199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367902195340-14</Id><Title>LENOVO K900 AND ZTE GEEK DUKE IT OUT FOR CHINA PHONE MARKET</Title><Msg>BOTH HAVE INTEL INSIDE nvonewsDOTcom/2013/04/11/zte-geek-5-inch-intel-phablet-released-zte-geek-vs-lenovo-k900-by/</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367902195340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:49:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367902220980-15</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Silvermont is now OoO. All compilers have generated "ATOM" code and the code generates have been scheduling instruction sequences to optimize for in-order execution. Recompilation should use new instructions and instruction scheduling based on OoO. AVX, FMA, AES ..... will give big performance jumps after recompilation. On top of OoO. New instructions support AES (encryption/decryption) directly in transistors. Big deal? Geekbench INTEGER performance is 25% based on encryption/decryption. The results are combined using the arithmetic mean. It would take a 500% improvement in one of the benchmarks like blowfish to double the INTEGER performance. Oracle saw an 8x performance boost in encryption/decryption with Westmere over Nehalem.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367902220980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:50:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367902898023-16</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no complaints from Charlie: "And that sums up the Silvermont core itself from a user perspective, several big and fundamental changes like OoO, two pipelines, and the loss of HT. Many of the gains that lead you to the massive 4-5x efficiency improvements are small and obscure in isolation, massive in aggregate. They all add up to a very efficient core and the 22nm SoC process they are built on adds to that too. "</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367902898023</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 01:01:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367903826737-17</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When they announced Medfield, it was supposed to be clearly superior to the available ARM offerings and they flashed up numbers to back that, yet when the benchmarks were done and the market looked at it, it was not so. Let's hope they were more honest with Merrifield." [Guess you didn't read this part of the Anandtech article: "A single Bonnell core, designed in 2004, released in 2008, is already faster than ARM’s Cortex A9." Anandtech confirms that you have no idea what you are talking about...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367903826737</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 01:17:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367904757928-18</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like everyone is tired of the INTC good old boy system, Were they hand out free shares to the insiders and all they do is sell them</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367867824475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This alias guy will just keep posting this as a new topic over and over and over again. He doesn't really want an answer or discussion. He may pretend and give the impression that he's wanting a second opinion. But just wants to try and keep this out in the open as viable reality when in fact it's baloney. Best thing to do is ignore. Look back over the last month and you will see this same post repeated ad nauseum maybe 50 times. Other topics he repeats over and over: possible div cut, low margins, low revenues, bad earnings, trading days with only sellers and no buyers ? (never understood this one), outdated products, no growth, etc,</Msg><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367904757928</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 01:32:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367905318335-19</Id><Title>MSFT hit new 52wk highs. PC demand must be strong. LOL.</Title><Msg>Mr Weaver is still pumping INTC, so the stock should go down.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1367905318335</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 01:41:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367905467193-20</Id><Title>Windows XP upgrade cycle is coming up. MSFT could be moving because of this.</Title><Msg>Lots of PC's need to be upgraded, and won't be replaced with tablets.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1367905467193</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 01:44:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367907531488-21</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>re, AES instructions. The compiler 'wont' spot an encryption algo and use these instructions, they have to be explicitly used in new alogo implementations (FYI, ARM v8 also has AES instructions). So they wont help those geekbench scores:) Your point about atom code generation is a good one as most compilers use the lowest common denominator, silvermont is more like core that atom, so will be interesting to see what kind of code compilers start to spit out.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367907531488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:18:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367907949405-22</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In this respect the article is wrong. There are some Bonnell cores that can beat the A9, but these usually have different form factors (ie desk top parts). It's clear from all known benchmarks that Saltwell and the A9 have very similar performance profiles given a similar environment. Typically, Saltwell will beat on Integer, the A9 in float. Tegra 3 on RT excepted, as it's useless;)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367907949405</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367908917648-23</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aren't you that #$%$ bragger that goes around calling other guys 'sweetheart', and forever saying bay trail can't beat the A15? Are you still saying that now you f**u**c**k?</Msg><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367908917648</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367909067141-24</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>blueredmonk, why don't you go f**u**c**k yourself</Msg><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909067141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:44:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367909930027-25</Id><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Msg>theblueredmonk • Mar 15, 2013 2:20 PM :) I would put money on it that this chip (A15) will beat Atom@22nm in all known benchmarks (except Javacript). I suspect that Clovertrail+ will struggle against even the A9. We shall soon see when the real benchmarks start to arrive...:)</Msg><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367911028348-26</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The upshot of this thread is that Intel tends to hype its performance and in fact they don't really have as much performance as they claim which is part of the reason why they fail in the market afterwards. This is their time in the sun when they get to toot their own whistle.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367911028348</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 03:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367911190724-27</Id><Topic><Title>This stock is going to the MOON!</Title><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1363965968442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:26:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time to short INTC. I currently have 1500 shares shorts. Will cover at $21.68.</Msg><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1367911190724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 03:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367911429119-28</Id><Title>khitchdee = theblueredmonk</Title><Msg>so obvious..what a loser!</Msg><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367911429119</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 03:23:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367913283379-29</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Defend myself eh? There is only one person I call sweetheart - my alter ego - you perhaps?:) I only ever use this nick. As for my comments about the A15 V Silvermont, even Intel say that Silvermont should have roughly the same single threaded performance as ARM’s Cortex A15 (anandtech article) the difference being that Silvermont will be able clock higher and use less power doing so. Can I still defend that comment? No, not really, I was wrong and I'd lose my bet. The various gossip on the tech forums had Silvermont around the 25% IPC improvement mark, which would put it behind the A15 (the jump in IPC from the A9 to A15 was around 40%). Silvermont is a good design but it *had* to be to stay in the game.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367913283379</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 03:54:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367918728896-30</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>:) Aw, tsk, tsk, tsk, sweetheart *wink*</Msg><Username>thebluereddork</Username><Timestamp>1367918728896</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 05:25:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367929221305-31</Id><Title>Silvermont Recap: ARM is So Toast</Title><Msg>In the more abstract realm of CPU to CPU comparisons, Intel indicated that Silvermont is a much faster design than the Cortex A7 or the A15 at any given power level. Even if Intel’s projections are modestly optimistic, Silvermont should conclusively dispel the myth that the x86 instruction set is a barrier to power efficient microarchitecture. If Intel’s claims hold true, the Silvermont microarchitecture might be even more efficient than some ARM cores when normalized for Intel’s advantage in process technology. Products based on Silvermont will launch in the latter half of 2013. Ironically, Merrifield will probably be the first 64-bit smartphone SoC, a milestone for a company that has traditionally lagged in this area. Merrifield should be very competitive for Android phones; if Intel also delivers a discrete LTE modem, it will inject competition into a market where Qualcomm has been unchallenged for quite some time. Intel’s progress in tablets will accelerate with updated CPU cores, graphics, and SoC fabric. Windows tablets will be a particularly strong point, since Valleyview uses a variant of the Ivy Bridge GPU which is far better from a DirectX and OpenGL standpoint than pretty much every alternative. The Avoton server chip is already sampling to OEMs and should also be quite interesting. In conclusion, the 22nm Silvermont CPU is a tremendous step forward, particularly in mobile devices. It is a thoroughly modern microarchitecture that is both higher performance and more efficient than the previous Saltwell core. The new core and updated SoC fabric and should put Intel on an even technical footing with mobile competitors such as Qualcomm, Nvidia, and Samsung, and perhaps even grant a significant advantage. From anandtech</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367929221305</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:20:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367929440890-32</Id><Title>Don't forget that with Silvermont the ARM server revolution is official dead</Title><Msg>Buried.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367929440890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367929632962-33</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget that with Silvermont the ARM server revolution is official dead</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367929440890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel unveils low-power Silvermont chip design for ‘teraflops to milliwatts’ May 6, 2013 10:00 AM Dean Takahashi Intel announced its low-power Silvermont microprocessor architecture today, revealing the power-efficient design that will be the foundation of a new generation of PCs and mobile devices. Silvermont delivers a three-fold performance improvement over previous generations at the same power levels, the company said. The technology is a blueprint for future chip designs that will serve as the brains of devices ranging from smartphones to data center servers. Devices made with the Silvermont architecture will use the 22-nanometer Tri-Gate SoC manufacturing process. Silvermont will be the heart of a bunch of chips coming from Intel starting during the holiday season in 2013.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367929632962</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367929661346-34</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget that with Silvermont the ARM server revolution is official dead</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367929440890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Silvermont is a leap forward and an entirely new technology foundation for the future that will address a broad range of products and market segments,” said Dadi Perlmutter (pictured), executive vice president and chief product officer, in a press briefing at Intel’s headquarters in Santa Clara, Calif. “This is one of those years when Intel is coming out with one of the biggest innovations in its product lines.” Perlmutter said Intel’s mission is to create chips from “teraflops to milliwatts,” meaning from supercomputing performance levels to the most power-efficient devices. Early samples of new chips, code-named Bay Trail and Avoton, are generating good feedback from customers, Perlmutter said. Silvermont can enable three-times peak performance or the same performance at five times lower power over the current generation of Intel Atom processors. Intel said that some of the dual-core chips based on Silvermont will outperform quad-core chips from rivals. With Silvermont, the company has completely redesigned the processor, with a new “out-of-order execution engine” that enables top performance when processing one thread, or program code. Within this part of the design, Intel can fuse three instructions together and process them quickly as if they were a single instruction. In such calculations, the chip fuses instructions that present some data, perform a calculation on them, and then return the result to memory — in a more efficient manner than in the past.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367929661346</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367929683670-35</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget that with Silvermont the ARM server revolution is official dead</Title><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367929440890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The design can be scaled up to eight cores. Intel has added new instructions for support of better virtualization, power management, and security management. With Silvermont, a chip can enter sleep mode or wake up more quickly than it the past. Also, the range of performance at different power levels will vary more widely. Intel will use Silvermont in a variety of markets. Different chips that will use Silvermont include Bay Trail, Merrifield, Avoton, Rangeley, and an unnamed chip. Bay Trail, a new Atom-branded chip, will debut for the 2013 holidays in tablets that can more than double the performance of current Intel-based tablets. It can also be used in entry-level laptops and desktops in new forms. Intel’s code-named Merrifield will focus on increased performance, better battery life, and support for context aware and personal services. And Intel’s Avoton will be used as an Atom chip in the data center, for use in micro servers and other low-power devices. Rangeley is aimed at networking devices such as routers, switches, and security appliances coming in the second half of the year. Starting in June, Intel will be shipping its Haswell architecture, with a series of chips based on that architecture. Silvermont-based devices will come after that. Intel’s low-power chips will compete against the ARM architecture, which is used by many different chip makers. “We are on the path of breaking the myth that ARM can do things that Intel cannot,” Perlmutter said.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367929683670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:28:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367929809920-36</Id><Title>Silvermont Target Dates</Title><Msg>In the press briefing Rani Borkar, VP General Manager Intel Architecture Development Group A, explained that the company will be refreshing the Silvermount architecture annually. She also gave the target dates of the first generation processors. Bay Trail: A low-power, quad-core SoC designed for tablets that will be available in time for the holiday shopping season. Intel also expects manufacturers to tap Bay Trail for “entry laptop and desktop computers in innovative form factors.” Avoton: Designed for microservers. Available in the second half of 2013. Rangeley: Designed for infrastructure devices, such as routers, switches, and security appliances. Also available in the second half of 2013. Merrifield: A next-generation smartphone chip that Intel plans to ship by the end of 2013 for products hitting the market in the first quarter of 2014. From thedroidguy</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367929809920</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:30:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367930519477-37</Id><Title>Penchant for Understatement</Title><Msg>"I view this as a big occasion," Perlmutter added of Silvermont. "This is not just a small deal." FierceWireless [Yep, it marks the end of the ARM era...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367930519477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:41:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367931417750-38</Id><Title>ashraf the idiot</Title><Msg>keep telling you ashraf. but you are two stupid two under stand their is room for both itel and arm in the space.even your own writers are telling you idiot. keep pumping cry baby.arm is not going away any time soon. dip #$%$.</Msg><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367931417750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:56:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367931643663-39</Id><Topic><Title>ashraf the idiot</Title><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367931417750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your posts would be a little bit more effective if you took a course in English grammar. Now, I always forgive anyone whose native language is something else, but it's clear your native language is English, of sorts. You might want to work on a little mastery of it. Having mastered one language is worthy goal in life.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367931643663</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:00:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367931766651-40</Id><Topic><Title>ashraf the idiot</Title><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367931417750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well AE has had a lesson in how markets don't always agree with you and how dangerous shorting can be, he is hardly an idiot. He is young and does not have much experience in trading markets is all. Wallace now he is a dingaling.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1367931766651</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:02:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367931867521-41</Id><Topic><Title>Penchant for Understatement</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367930519477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:41:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh you have so much to learn Wally dingaling.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1367931867521</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:04:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367932382437-42</Id><Title>We need to penetrate $24</Title><Msg>We need some real altitude, $29, or this one WILL get sucked back down to $19 when the bubble bursts.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367932382437</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:13:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367932509926-43</Id><Title>New windows is going to cause computer sales to fall even more while people wait for the new windows, NOT good for INTC</Title><Msg>New windows is going to cause computer sales to fall even more while people wait for the new windows, NOT good for INTC</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367932509926</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:15:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367932747326-44</Id><Topic><Title>ashraf the idiot</Title><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367931417750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lol, ARM isn't going away, but you do realize that the valuation bakes in massive market share gains in PCs, hardly any market share loss in phones/tabs, share gains in servers, etc., right? ARM collects royalties on 10B processors and can hardly make $300M/yr after taxes. You don't think that a $22B+ valuation is just...erm...a tad optimistic for what is essentially a utility company? Take a look into the past, "idiot" - MIPS once rode sky high, as did AMD. Look at where those stocks went after people finally woke up? But hey, keep buying ARMH.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367932747326</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:19:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367933347839-45</Id><Title>Unsinkable market will propel Intel through 24 and higher</Title><Msg>Shorts will be screwed further. You will see people like puke Nuff in full panic mode. Can't wait. He thinks he can talk down a stock.</Msg><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367933347839</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:29:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367933384737-46</Id><Topic><Title>New windows is going to cause computer sales to fall even more while people wait for the new windows, NOT good for INTC</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367932509926</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:15:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember to take your profits, INTC is up over 25%</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367933384737</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:29:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367933413502-47</Id><Topic><Title>ashraf the idiot</Title><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367931417750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>al ready made a small fortune in arm and got out at 46.80 who's the idiot unlike you . that keeps pumping intel .a stock that has done zero. bottom line is to make money.idiot.</Msg><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367933413502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:30:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367933433185-48</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really thought that Intel, desperate to make inroads in new markets and with massive R&amp;D resources, would have let designs based on ARM's A15 "win"? Especially on a performance/watt comparison, where process technology alone gives a huge advantage?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367933433185</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:30:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367934008659-49</Id><Title>BIG MOVE ON (CERP) SOLID NEWS</Title><Msg>GROWING</Msg><Username>first.alert</Username><Timestamp>1367934008659</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:40:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367934032802-50</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Up next Apple's A7 on 20nm</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1367934032802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367934175101-51</Id><Topic><Title>Unsinkable market will propel Intel through 24 and higher</Title><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367933347839</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:29:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good start.</Msg><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367934175101</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367934272323-52</Id><Topic><Title>ashraf the idiot</Title><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367931417750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you have ANY idea how much I made on my Jan 2014 $20 LEAP calls on Intel? Also, made a tidy sum shorting your pals Applied Micro...;)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367934272323</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367934288539-53</Id><Topic><Title>ashraf the idiot</Title><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367931417750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>al ready made a small fortune. Not only did you spell "all" a three letter word incorrectly, the word is actually not two words, it is one word :- "already" And you tell us you have made a fortune. Pick your slack jaw off the floor.</Msg><Username>zisdead1</Username><Timestamp>1367934288539</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367934563806-54</Id><Topic><Title>khitchdee = theblueredmonk</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367911429119</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 03:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think so. theblueredmonk is a reasonable, balanced guy. khitchdee has multiple personality disorder.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367934563806</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:49:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367934667038-55</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Up next Apple's A7 on 20nm" [Hahahahaha. Don't hold your breath on that one. You're not going to be seeing any ARM 20nm any time soon. No matter what the press releases say...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367934667038</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:51:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367934922831-56</Id><Title>closing out INTC</Title><Msg>made some good money here from 21.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1367934922831</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:55:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367934938412-57</Id><Topic><Title>We need to penetrate $24</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367932382437</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:13:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We need some real altitude, $29, or this one WILL get sucked back down to $19 when the bubble bursts." [Intel's advantages aren't going away - they are going to get stronger. The only bubble to burst is ARM. The P/E is now a ridiculous 81. The price keeps going up but the earnings estimates don't...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367934938412</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:55:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367935040850-58</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple's A7 on 20nm, eh? An uncompetitive, relatively leaky process compared to Intel's 22nm FinFET? Don't make me laugh. Apple's A7 is probably 28nm to reduce risk, since TSMC thinks that ~2% of revenues will be 20nm by Q2 2014.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367935040850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:57:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367935072762-59</Id><Topic><Title>ashraf the idiot</Title><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367931417750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Well AE has had a lesson in how markets don't always agree with you and how dangerous shorting can be, he is hardly an idiot. He is young and does not have much experience in trading markets is all. Wallace now he is a dingaling." [Yeah, I'm the dingaling who is up 5 bucks since November. You the dingaling who is down 5 bucks...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367935072762</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:57:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367935073975-60</Id><Title>Greek Yogurt is where breakfast is at, Gentleman!</Title><Msg>Wallaby Organic is tasty! Strawberry, Raspberry or Honey.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367935073975</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:57:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367935176656-61</Id><Title>Dividend increase. When is it coming</Title><Msg>looks like we are do any day.</Msg><Username>a33stacybb</Username><Timestamp>1367935176656</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:59:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367935177412-62</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL DOWNGRADED $2 PRICE TARGET PC MARKET COLLAPSING</Title><Username>nasdaqczar2</Username><Timestamp>1365692696048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lower lows for intel pc is dead</Msg><Username>goldmansuxtrader</Username><Timestamp>1367935177412</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:59:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367935307863-63</Id><Title>More to Come...</Title><Msg>May 6: Intel to announce Silvermont - Buzz should last all year May 6: Lenovo K900 release in China May 10: Lenovo K900 in India May 15-17; Google I/O Developers Conference - Buzz depends on announcements. Good potential. May 16: Intel's Annual Stockholder Meeting June 3: Intel to release Haswell - Buzz should last all year June 4: Computex - Buzz depends on announcements. Good potential June 10-14: Apple's WWDC - Macs about to get a major upgrade thanks to Intel’s (NASDAQ:INTC) new “Iris” graphics processors? June 26-28: Microsoft's Build Developer Conference - Rumors of next Surface Pro announcement 2013: Year of the Intel Tablet 2014: Year of the Intel Smartphone</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367935307863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:01:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367935393040-64</Id><Topic><Title>INTEL DOWNGRADED $2 PRICE TARGET PC MARKET COLLAPSING</Title><Username>nasdaqczar2</Username><Timestamp>1365692696048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"lower lows for intel pc is dead" [What is dead is the future of content-free posting...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367935393040</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:03:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367935461307-65</Id><Topic><Title>ashraf the idiot</Title><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367931417750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least he's man enough to post under one ID &amp; backs up his conviction by writing articles about it instead of being some shut in freakshow.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1367935461307</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367935723576-66</Id><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Msg>ARM is now 50 cents off the day's high. So, in answer to what is holding the stock up - Nothing...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367935723576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:08:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367935767841-67</Id><Topic><Title>ashraf the idiot</Title><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367931417750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>williamdavis960, Thank you, sir.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367935767841</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:09:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367935791502-68</Id><Title>Looks like INTC is going to need to lower Q3 , New windows is going to make people want to wait to buy a new computer</Title><Msg>Looks like INTC is going to need to lower Q3 , New windows is going to make people want to wait to buy a new computer,</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367935791502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:09:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367935828596-69</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367935723576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:08:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When ARM was at 39, your ARM Technicals post said "it will take a miracle for ARM to stay above 40". Are you going to take responsibility for that nonsense? Apparently not.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367935828596</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:10:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367935839788-70</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like INTC is going to need to lower Q3 , New windows is going to make people want to wait to buy a new computer</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367935791502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:09:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not priced in INTC going lower</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367935839788</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:10:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367935842289-71</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Given what was 'leaked' on the techi forums, yes. Remember Intel need to hit the sweet spot of 'beating' ARM but not invading the higher margin (low end) core based SoC's which Krait/Swift/A15 are already starting to sniff it. I have no doubt that Intel can produce a more performant processor than an ARM one, but getting that balance right, with the right GPU at the right time and at the right price point is hard. Given that airmont is now a node shrink rather than a new arch as originally planned, Intel might have moved up arch changes to make sure they are competitive with (current) A15's, next gen Swift/Krait. Depending on who you listen to, the A15 has arrived early while swift surprised almost everyone. This is also new LP process, so we don't know enough about it to make comparisons on existing 28nm parts (even though Intel call this a 22 nm node, gate size is actually closer to 26nm) and with (usually) more restrictive design rules in Intel's fabs, SoC's using Silvermont might not be that much smaller than the foundries 28nm SoC's. Clearly FinFet will make a big difference:)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367935842289</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:10:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367935850987-72</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367935723576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:08:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Long term, it will take a miracle for this thing to stay above $30.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367935850987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:10:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367935857111-73</Id><Title>Headed for the red zone later in the day</Title><Msg>The pattern is just too consistent.Up early, then down. This stock lacks buying conviction and shorts aren't covering.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367935857111</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:10:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367935877410-74</Id><Topic><Title>ashraf the idiot</Title><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367931417750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wallace you could be up 10 and I could be down 20...you will always be a dingaling, it is who you are.</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1367935877410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:11:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367935972817-75</Id><Title>Get ready to say by by Profits</Title><Msg>Get ready to say by by Profits</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367935972817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:12:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936024386-76</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366864941994</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:42:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brilliant post! It's up 20% since you bashed it at 40 and almost 100 percent since you bashed it at 25. SMH.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367936024386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:13:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936028820-77</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TBRM, You are right about AES. I guess I was on a "down with Geekbench" rant. Blowfish source (vintage 1990's) has ifdef's for little and big endian and not much else. Oracle implemented Westmere AES support using the Intel IPP libraries. It looks like Silvermont will be supporting a Westmere subset instruction set. I suspect that Intel might take this opportunity to purge the pipeline of some of the legacy instructions. The new Atom which everyone will need to recompile won't support them. The new recompiled Silvermont Atom code will then run very nicely on Core also, from Westmere forward.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367936028820</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367936055585-78</Id><Title>stacy smith insider sell</Title><Msg>cause for concern?</Msg><Username>lorryclayes</Username><Timestamp>1367936055585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:14:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936061140-79</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367935723576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:08:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any decent human being would shut up if they said it was a sell at 25 up to 48.....</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367936061140</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:14:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936208664-80</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367935723576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:08:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and INTC dropped .20 off the day high, both have overbght daily charts. the question becomes, dip or correction?</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1367936208664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:16:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936250952-81</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367935723576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:08:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't say it was a sell at $25 ;)</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367936250952</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936346061-82</Id><Topic><Title>ashraf the idiot</Title><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367931417750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats right made a small fortune all the to the bank.and my jaw is very nice thank you.</Msg><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367936346061</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:19:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936357444-83</Id><Topic><Title>We need to penetrate $24</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367932382437</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 09:13:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, I agree Wallis. We need some more altitude.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367936357444</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936362652-84</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367935723576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:08:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wallis did, and thank for confirming that I'm right by getting defensive about 25 as you and I both know that he's a moron for not shutting up at this point.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367936362652</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936409697-85</Id><Topic><Title>stacy smith insider sell</Title><Username>lorryclayes</Username><Timestamp>1367936055585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:14:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he couldn't do it while he was in the running for CEO. Ever try to hold it til the next rest stop?</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367936409697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:20:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936465406-86</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Dilemma</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1367251651755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 12:07:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am my own link :)</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367936465406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:21:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936592432-87</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like INTC is going to need to lower Q3 , New windows is going to make people want to wait to buy a new computer</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367935791502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:09:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whoosh! That is the sound of the Intel factories pumping out Q3 Haswell chips for the 200 design wins! Whoosh! That is the sound of the Intel factories pumping out the Q3 BayTrail chips for the 50 design wins! Whoosh! That is the sound of the Intel factories pumping out the Q3 PHI 20,50 &amp; 70 core products! Whoosh! That is the sound of the coinmaker77 cash disappearing down the toilet like always!</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367936592432</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:23:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936928814-88</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Dilemma</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1367251651755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 12:07:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...and do you think ARM is prepared for a competitor in the space that is capable of under-cutting ARM on price for the same or better performance? (they better be cuz it's only a matter of time) ...or do you think customers will be loyal to ARM even if a world-class company like Intel could come in for less? I wonder who has the resources to win that war? (see AMD)</Msg><Username>kingsx_fan</Username><Timestamp>1367936928814</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367936944754-89</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I told you Charlie D was unreliable, you should have paid more attention to what I was telling you :). Silvermont was designed at least 3-4 years ago which is why it has Westmere level technology so it could not have been designed with A15/Swift in mind. It is basically a revamp of Atom correcting its weaknesses and then seeing where they ended up. As it happens they landed on their feet with a class leading processor. ARM chips are not going away but Intel now has a chance to carve out a premium $30-50 mobile chip market above them. Intel is only interested in making money not marketshare bragging rights in a race to the bottom so ARM can still keep its small die peanuts market as Intel is just not interested.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367936944754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:29:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367937312843-90</Id><Title>GOOD VOLUME, INTC GOING UP MUCH HIGHER</Title><Msg>ANALysts FINALLY GETTING THE SILVERMONT MESSAGE</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonilz</Username><Timestamp>1367937312843</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:35:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367937325268-91</Id><Title>So you want 4% dividend return</Title><Msg>then get into a REIT like VNQ. You get a better yield plus growth. In 6 weeks I am up about 20% in growth with about an 8% yield.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367937325268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:35:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367937430951-92</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like INTC is going to need to lower Q3 , New windows is going to make people want to wait to buy a new computer</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367935791502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:09:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you keep posting the same garbage over and over, sometimes within a few minutes? Your posts are cut/pasted sloppy childish drivel.</Msg><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367937430951</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:37:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367937463869-93</Id><Topic><Title>So you want 4% dividend return</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367937325268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:35:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So it will be up another 20% six weeks from now?</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367937463869</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:37:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367937523754-94</Id><Title>MKM Partners raises price target to $28 from $24; rating buy</Title><Msg>May 7 (Reuters) - Intel Corp MKM Partners raises price target to $28 from $24; rating buy</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367937523754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:38:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367937525318-95</Id><Topic><Title>ashraf the idiot</Title><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367931417750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>their is room for both Intel and arm Neither one of the two SA authors (the one who writes here and the other who published on ARM board) has had exposure to semiconductors. They scan the boards and pick up ideas/research and sell it as their own research. The guy hyped all about CSCO but not one word about MSCC and why Intel picked MSCC. Intel (new CEO) is going full blow after NON ARM foundry business or after foundry business that does not compromise its core business, Read the quote : mixed-signal designs....IBM’s Burlington fab is doing “extremely well” in RF "Market watcher Handel Jones of International Business Strategies (Los Gatos, Calif.) said FinFETs present real challenges for mixed-signal designs, potentially delaying the node’s ramp. Nevertheless, he said Globalfoundries and Samsung have a significant opportunity to grab market share from TSMC. In addition, IBM’s Burlington fab is doing “extremely well” in RF, he added." BTW: Opposite to TSMC GF stated that 20nm is marginal</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367937525318</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:38:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367937649300-96</Id><Topic><Title>So you want 4% dividend return</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367937325268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:35:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A lot better chances of that happening with REITs than with INTC. Higher interest rates will slow down their popularity but not by much. Japanese love American REITs.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367937649300</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:40:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367937737490-97</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like INTC is going to need to lower Q3 , New windows is going to make people want to wait to buy a new computer</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367935791502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:09:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now you know why all the PUMPING Wall Street need to get out of MSFT, INTC</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367937737490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:42:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367937886278-98</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like INTC is going to need to lower Q3 , New windows is going to make people want to wait to buy a new computer</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367935791502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:09:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wanna bet?</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1367937886278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:44:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367937941579-99</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Dilemma</Title><Username>semiwiki</Username><Timestamp>1367251651755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 12:07:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Only if Intel produces mobile SoCs so stunningly superior in performance..." That is one of the dumbest things I ever heard. Money is everything. Similar performance with lower cost is all that is needed.</Msg><Username>intoodeep99</Username><Timestamp>1367937941579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:45:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367938062639-100</Id><Topic><Title>ashraf the idiot</Title><Username>henrya1228</Username><Timestamp>1367931417750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 08:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"their is room for both Intel and arm" Sure, but ARM's valuation (and indirectly Intel's) is predicated on ARM "taking all of the marbles", so to speak. "The guy hyped all about CSCO but not one word about MSCC and why Intel picked MSCC." I "hyped" about Cisco primarily because I had found evidence that the deal was real...you know, not from a message board, but through some solid digging on LinkedIn. "They scan the boards and pick up ideas/research and sell it as their own research." You really think that my articles are picked up from the boards? That's interesting...well, unless I'm copying my own posts here, I s'pose.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367938062639</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367938109167-101</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It wasn't just Charlie D, but yes I should have listened to you - in this *one* instance;) Intel may have a good design, but they need to get it out of the door asap. Krait/A15 won't be standing still, you're looking at (probably) one silicon level revision of the A15 before Silvermont actually arrives and the optimizations are already starting to arrive for the abomination (ie, HMP scheduling for the linux kernel)</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367938109167</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:48:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367938331835-102</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>theblueredmonk, How many A15's are shipping today? You have Samsung's Exynos Octa which is a battery draining power hog, and then you have Exynos Dual which...is also a power hog...and then you have Tegra 4 which is where, exactly? Silvermont based SoCs will be right on time to fight Snapdragon 800/Cortex A15 devices, and then Airmont takes on the A57 class.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367938331835</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:52:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367938392157-103</Id><Topic><Title>So you want 4% dividend return</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367937325268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:35:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is another rehashed tired post from yesterday. Do you have alzheimer's?</Msg><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367938392157</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:53:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367938422845-104</Id><Topic><Title>MKM Partners raises price target to $28 from $24; rating buy</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367937523754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:38:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yawn. Another upgrade and the effect is laughable. That makes three companies selling their shares.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367938422845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367938514084-105</Id><Topic><Title>So you want 4% dividend return</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367937325268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:35:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like the stock performance of INTC. Flat with every rally.</Msg><Username>angermanagementracist</Username><Timestamp>1367938514084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:55:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367938539661-106</Id><Topic><Title>So you want 4% dividend return</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367937325268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:35:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have REIT's in my portfolio now (REIT mutual fund instead of ETF). I increased my REIT holdings in 2010 and participated nicely in the "20%" along with you. I participated in a highly leveraged Dec, Jan and Feb in the housing market which saw prices go up 10% (Case Schiller). There are some underlying problems with REITS in that many are issuing shares to pay the dividends. Part of our 20% is our own money. The REITs have been doing that since the collapse as they try to recover. REITs should be part of a diversified investment portfolio just like technology. In addition to REITs, I am long Intel and expect to do nicely. Short covering, share buy back, upgrades and institutional purchases will keep Intel in "OVERBOUGHT" territory and make it hard for chartists to buy. Intel will be stronger that the general market as long as the "PC is DEAD" crew have a following.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367938539661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:55:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367938833326-107</Id><Topic><Title>MKM Partners raises price target to $28 from $24; rating buy</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367937523754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:38:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get lost FREAKSHOW.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1367938833326</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:00:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367938969342-108</Id><Topic><Title>MKM Partners raises price target to $28 from $24; rating buy</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367937523754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:38:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since JPM, GS, Nomura, C, .... analysts have been quiet after the Silvermont discussion, I would not be surprised if they started announcing that they were "selling there shares" too. Covello has to nearly double his $16 target price when GS starts "selling". 8-) Enjoy!</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367938969342</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:02:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367939297314-109</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd wait unless you actually get decent (tech) reviews of Exynos Octa until you pass judgement:) A few blog posts whinging about overheating doesn't cut it (just google overheating on any major phone and you'll see the same "complaints") No idea when the Tegra 4 will arrive. Unless Airmont is clocked higher (or has more cores) than silvermont it won't have any more performance (at the IPC level) to go up against the A57 abomination.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367939297314</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:08:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367939311932-110</Id><Title>Intel’s Latest “Silvermont” Platform To Offer 3 Times Performance at 1/5th the Power</Title><Msg>Intel has been the leader in computer processing platforms over the years, and has only recently made a foray into the mobile processing space. The mobile arena though, dominated by the likes of Qualcomm with their Snapdragon chipsets, and Nvidia with the Tegra chips, has been a hard nut to crack. Intel’s initial Atom -based chipsets were seen as good alternatives, but didn’t really make too much of a dent in the pie dominated by Qualcomm and Nvidia, and to a lesser extent Taiwanese firm Mediatek. Earlier today, Intel announced a new SoC, code named Silvermont, in a bid to take the smartphone and tablet processor fight to the biggies. Silvermont is claimed to be a completely revamped, built from scratch, and vastly improved Atom chipset. Intel claims that the new chip will offer upto 3 times the speed and performance, over past generations of Intel Atom processors, while consuming just 20 percent of the power that its predecessors like Clover Trail did. Further, Intel intends to make the new processing platform available not only to smartphones and tablets, but also to a wide array of products such as other mobile devices, cars, infotainment systems et al. The Silvermont SoC will employ the latest 22nm processor fabrication process, resulting in high efficiency and much improved battery life, and if these claims are even close to being accurate, Intel’s new baby could pose a serious threat to the the newly announced Snapdragon 600 and 800 chipsets from Qualcomm and the Tegra 4 chipset from Nvidia. Intel has not met with an major success with its earlier chipsets, and hopes the new chip could change the game. Silvermont is likely to feature in Intel’s upcoming Merrifield mobile processors for smartphones and tablets. Whether some of these devices which use the new platform from Intel, will come to smartphones in the U.S or not, remains to be seen, as details on 4G LTE integration in the Merrifield platform are not exactly clear yet. The new chipset is expected to be seen in mainstream devices coming out towards the end of 2013. Hopefully, there would be more details coming up down the road.</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367939311932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:08:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367939395655-111</Id><Topic><Title>MKM Partners raises price target to $28 from $24; rating buy</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367937523754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:38:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Slowly but surely analyst's attitudes will change. When the new dual boot Windows-Android tablets from top tier vendors are on the shelves of BestBuy they'll get the message. The PC is NOT dead, it simply became thinner, more portable and has awesome battery life.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367939395655</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:09:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367939611346-112</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What makes you think that it won't have more performance at the IPC level? It'll be a "tick", but that doesn't completely rule out tweaks/enhancements. Plus, 14nm will allow for higher clocks, beefier GPU, etc. all at good cost. The 20nm parts shipping at the time will be hamstrung by cost and power.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367939611346</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367940171457-113</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like INTC is going to need to lower Q3 , New windows is going to make people want to wait to buy a new computer</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367935791502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:09:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now you know why all the insider selling , They already knew about the new windows and the PC sales are going to fall off a cliff waiting for the new version of windows. Margins are going lower , because there going to have to drop prices to move anything</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367940171457</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:22:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367940339162-114</Id><Topic><Title>theblueredmonk, this thread is yours to defend yourself</Title><Username>ruipeirara</Username><Timestamp>1367909930027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 02:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>true, there are some tweaks, but usually nothing major at the IPC level. Again, wait until (TSMC) actually delivers it's process (the same for Intel's 14nm) before you jump to conclusions:) We don't even know basic details; how big is silvermont (compared to A15/Swift/Krait) etc.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367940339162</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:25:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367940396372-115</Id><Title>Intel's Silvermont Gain = ARM's Loss</Title><Msg>period.</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367940396372</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:26:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367940495081-116</Id><Topic><Title>MKM Partners raises price target to $28 from $24; rating buy</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367937523754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:38:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Yawn. Another upgrade and the effect is laughable. That makes three companies selling their shares." [What's laughable is the content-free posting that you continuously waste your and our time with. Five bucks up since November and about a billion of your posts. Color you impotent...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367940495081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:28:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367940603814-117</Id><Topic><Title>MKM Partners raises price target to $28 from $24; rating buy</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367937523754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:38:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a sad misunderstanding (or misuse) of the difference between correlation and cause-effect. Many think that just because things correlate that there is some cause-effect relationship. That is why I am reluctant to give too much credit to my option volume controlling price theory. There is very good correlation between option activity and flat-line Intel share price. Today for example, when the share price started trading in a narrow range, the PUT option volumes for JUNE $24 and JULY $22 picked up. It looked like (based on the ASK SIZE) that there was selling of both. My theory is that AT or IN the money put option buying will encourage shorting by the option market maker. IMO, someone is trading options to either make money on the options or to provide a shock absorber for Intel share prices. Motive is tough to assess.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367940603814</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:30:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367940626258-118</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like INTC is going to need to lower Q3 , New windows is going to make people want to wait to buy a new computer</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367935791502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:09:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like a freaking moron. Are you a US citizen? Your english is broken.</Msg><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367940626258</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367940655525-119</Id><Title>ARM's Valuation of $23 B is unsustainable.</Title><Msg>Intel is aggressively going after mobile.</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367940655525</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367940676591-120</Id><Title>Coinmaker price target INTC by Sept under $22</Title><Msg>Coinmaker price target INTC by Sept under $22</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367940676591</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:31:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367941121833-121</Id><Topic><Title>Coinmaker price target INTC by Sept under $22</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367940676591</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:31:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good guess. I think your guess is too pessimistic unless the market makes a 15% to 20% correction which is entirely possible. The general market is probably fairly price but there are pockets of value that will increasingly attract investors. Today is Golden Cross day. The 50-day moving average is crossing above the 200-day moving average. In addition to the 3 recent upgrades/target raisings, this will send a signal to chartists. As a group, they will be watching share price movement to see if there is an entry signal. They do not try to peg the bottom.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367941121833</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:38:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367941152341-122</Id><Title>The money invested in this POS means lost opportuniies</Title><Msg>Think about how this is a once in decade rally and you are squandering it on stock going nowhere.</Msg><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367941152341</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:39:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367941166719-123</Id><Topic><Title>Intel’s Latest “Silvermont” Platform To Offer 3 Times Performance at 1/5th the Power</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367939311932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:08:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exciting (and perilous) times for Intel. If they can execute the current price looks like a bargain.</Msg><Username>kip_castle</Username><Timestamp>1367941166719</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:39:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367941515960-124</Id><Title>Always remember that when all the insiders are selling they know something you don't and now we know about windows</Title><Msg>Always remember that when all the insiders are selling they know something you don't and now we know about windows</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367941515960</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367941589577-125</Id><Topic><Title>Intel’s Latest “Silvermont” Platform To Offer 3 Times Performance at 1/5th the Power</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367939311932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:08:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How are these perilous times for Intel? The roadmap is clear, the global demand will exceed all expectations, and Intel delivers the goods. Looks mighty perilous for ARMH, Taiwan Semi, Samsung, AMD, even AAPL, etc. but I repeat, how is this perilous for Intel?</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367941589577</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:46:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367941652154-126</Id><Title>Short interest waning.</Title><Msg>Short interest in Intel waning-and all these outstanding short shares will have to be covered: http://wsj.com/mdc/public/page/2_3062-nasdaqshort-highlites.html</Msg><Username>kip_castle</Username><Timestamp>1367941652154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:47:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367941685724-127</Id><Topic><Title>The money invested in this POS means lost opportuniies</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367941152341</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got in 2 years ago during the flash crash. I keep the Dividend in my account instead of reinvesting, so my average share price at the end of this year will be in the 18's. LOL @ you.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367941685724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367941774083-128</Id><Title>PC makers are going to have to cut prices to move PC that should help AMD sell more chips, Not good for INTC, but its good for AMD</Title><Msg>PC makers are going to have to cut prices to move PC that should help AMD sell more chips, Not good for INTC, but its good for AMD</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367941774083</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:49:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367941797590-129</Id><Title>Silvermont: Intel's promise to power phones and tablets you'd actually want</Title><Msg>Today, nearly all modern smartphones use an ARM-based processor, along with every iPad and practically every Android tablet as well. Soon, though, Intel's x86 silicon might finally pose a challenge. Six years after laying out a roadmap for power-efficient processors for tiny computers, and several failed attempts to make a real dent, Intel impressed us last October with just how power-efficient its Medfield chip could be compared to the latest Qualcomm Snapdragon. That chip used the company's Saltwell core inside, but this year the company's introducing Silvermont, and Intel claims the new 22nm architecture will more than hold its own against the best ARM has to offer. Intel promises three times the performance, or the same performance at five times lower power than the current gen Atom core, a truly serious boost. In charts (see below), Intel showed us how its dual-core processor can theoretically trounce the competition's quad-cores at one watt, and how a quad-core Silvermont-based chip, like the Bay Trail that will appear in tablets and cheap notebooks late this year, should be able to wipe the floor with the competition with just 1.5 watts of power at its disposal. "If you have an efficient solution, you don't need to play the core count game," Intel Fellow Belli Kuttanana told reporters at a press conference.</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367941797590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:49:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367941964225-130</Id><Topic><Title>Always remember that when all the insiders are selling they know something you don't and now we know about windows</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367941515960</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a dirty little secret, right? Don't forget to post about taking profits, lower margins and a possible div. cut.</Msg><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367941964225</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:52:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367942132376-131</Id><Topic><Title>The money invested in this POS means lost opportuniies</Title><Username>itakebackmyapology</Username><Timestamp>1367941152341</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, thanks for the concern. If I could guarantee that INTC stock price was going to stay flat or in a range, I could collect the 4% dividend and sell covered calls on the stock (without fear of assignment) and generate another 30 cents per month. 30 cents x 12 = $3.60 add the dividend at 90 cents $3.60 + $0.90 = $4.50 on a $24 stock (not compounded). $4.50 on a $24 stock is 18% a year. Is my math wrong? Are any of my assumptions misaligned with yours? If INTC drops then my $4.50 per year still comes into my account. The percentage is just bigger but I still get it.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367942132376</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:55:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367942251857-132</Id><Title>The lunchbreak</Title><Msg>we may see red. Probably a green close, but red for lunch.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367942251857</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367942277473-133</Id><Topic><Title>PC makers are going to have to cut prices to move PC that should help AMD sell more chips, Not good for INTC, but its good for AMD</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367941774083</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:49:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are doing a great job. Got a bunch of folks sick of your #$%$.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1367942277473</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:57:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367942356453-134</Id><Topic><Title>Intel’s Latest “Silvermont” Platform To Offer 3 Times Performance at 1/5th the Power</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367939311932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:08:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My interpretation of Intel's data was a bit different. I understood the slides to say Silvermont would offer up to 2.3 times the performance of current ARM products at the same power envelope, or at a comparable speed use up to 5.8 times less power - but not both. Even the conservative interpretation is awesome. Imagine an Intel and ARM tablet offering roughly the same speed but the Intel tablet can go 3-5 days without recharging whereas the ARM tablet must be charged every day. Consumers have a difficult time appreciating technology but they certainly can appreciate the benefit of 3-5 times better battery life.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367942356453</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:59:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367942520705-135</Id><Title>Intel Core i7-4770K “Haswell” Overclocked to 7.01GHz - Report.</Title><Msg>Intel Haswell Demonstrates Overclocking Wonders Ahead of Release [05/03/2013 05:42 PM] by Anton Shilov It is not a secret that it is going to get easier to overclock future K-versions of Intel Core i5 and Core i7 "Haswell" microprocessors because of variable DMICLK/BCLK [base clock] coarse ratios. Therefore, it is not surprising that professional overclockers have already started to test the new chips in a bid to set-up clock-speed records. While no actual records have been set yet, Core i “Haswell” chips have already hit 7GHz core frequency. Haswell Hits 7.012GHz Ahead of Launch Journalists from Ocaholic web-site have discovered a record in the CPU-Z database that an unnamed overclocker had managed to boost the speed of an Intel Core i7-4770K microprocessor from 3.50GHz to whopping 7012.8MHz (91.07MHz BCLK*77). The overclocker used Asus Maximus VI Extreme Edition mainboard based on Intel Z87 core-logic. While the utility claims that the core voltage of the chip was upped to unprecedented 2.56V, it should rather be considered as a software bug, than a miracle since Core i-series 3000-family “Ivy Bridge” chips fail at 2.0V. Results submitted to CPU-Z database cannot be cheated, but they also cannot be tracked down to find out a particular person. It is unknown what kind of cooling system did the anonymous overclocker use to overclock the Haswell chip by two times over its default frequency. One thing is clear, though: Intel Haswell seems to be very capable of reaching high clock-speeds, even early in its lifecycle. Better Overclocking Intel Core "Haswell" desktop platform is going to offer unconventional flexibility when it comes to boosting performance. Core i "Haswell" chips will feature more "knobs" for relevant frequency and voltage domains of the chip [compared to today’s products] as well as higher core ratios for those, who want to set-up clock-speed records using extreme cooling methods like liquid nitrogen. The main improvement of Haswell platform over</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367942520705</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367942582426-136</Id><Topic><Title>Always remember that when all the insiders are selling they know something you don't and now we know about windows</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367941515960</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I learned to look for insider selling and when WALL STREET is pump hard its time to take profits They know something I don't and 99% of the time its not good, Just like today. You have to get out before WALL STREET does or you get burned 100% of the time.</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367942582426</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367942680605-137</Id><Topic><Title>Always remember that when all the insiders are selling they know something you don't and now we know about windows</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367941515960</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wall Street will try and hold it up before they tank INTC , but for sure they will tank INTC</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367942680605</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367942872701-138</Id><Title>GTHP: Billion Dollar Estimate</Title><Msg>GTHP can rise more than 200% when their medical device gets approved this month. Approval is expected this month. That's why people are buying GTHP.</Msg><Username>hilla2ro</Username><Timestamp>1367942872701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:07:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367943178672-139</Id><Topic><Title>Always remember that when all the insiders are selling they know something you don't and now we know about windows</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367941515960</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When I asked you for examples of Intel insider selling, you gave me two instances where the Intel insiders had sold to pay taxes on vesting RSU options. If that is your definition of "insider selling" then please give me the name of a company where the insiders are writing a check for the tax bill on RSU options. You either do not know what "insider selling" really looks like or you do know and are spreading misinformation. Please give me the name of a single company where a single insider has wrote a check to pay the taxes on a vesting RSU option. Please identify one company or one insider. I don't think one exists.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367943178672</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:12:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367943267607-140</Id><Title>Analysts slowly showering praise: Ellis expects Intel to have strong demand for Silvermont-based parts:</Title><Msg>Intel: B Riley Cheers Krzanich, James; ‘Silvermont’ Should Draw OEMs Email Print smaller Larger By Tiernan Ray B. Riley &amp; Co.’s Craig Ellis this morning catches up to Intel‘s (INTC) two significant announcements from the last two weeks, the appointment of COO Brian Krzanich as the company’s new CEO, announced last Thursday, and the formal unveiling of a new CPU “core” for Intel’s Atom line of mobile processors, called “Silvermont,” which came about yesterday. Ellis, who has a Neutral rating on Intel shares, is pleased with Krzanich’s appointment, and relieved the company didn’t go outside its halls: Our view had been that INTC would promote from within and we thought Krzanich’s extensive mfg background – where INTC’s crown jewels are a closely guarded secret, and early-C12 COO appointment made him the favorite. We have seen him interact well with investors since August, 2011 at events large and small and view him a realist. The James appointment is a bit more surprising, though following a dinner in early-January we walked away quite impressed with her strategic insights and mastery of INTC’s different businesses, first established as chief of staff for Andy Grove and then refined as head of Software &amp; Services (former #2 Doug Fisher now runs). We think she understands that INTC needs to make significant if measured changes to ultimately to win in Mobile while retain a dominant PC and server position. Our sense is both she and Krzanich are foundry proponents. Ellis expects Intel to have strong demand for Silvermont-based parts: For years we’ve said INTC tablet APU competitiveness required matching industry-leading clock speed and web page downloads with better active power which has lagged ARM-based rivals. INTC believes Bay Trail offers 3x and 5x better performance and power, respectively with up to eight-core capability, HD4000 graphics, out of order execution, and Windows/Android compatibility. An annual refresh shows commitment to greater mobile success. We expect traditional notebook vendors – with extensive legacy Atom architecture experience with netbooks in C08-12 but an absence of any real tablet success so far, will flock to Bay Trail and follow the reference designs INTC announced in January with Compal, Pegatron, and Wistron. As has been the case since 2010 with non-Apple, Samsung, and China white box tablets, the real question for late-2013 will be finished device sell through. As far as the stock, Ellis is holding off on recommending the shares because he’s concerned about how further cannibalization of the PC market will play out as “low-end smartphones and white box tablets” continue to capture some demand.</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367943267607</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367943518262-141</Id><Title>INTC is pure lies</Title><Msg>Do not buy into this crock of you know what. The slumbering giant is going to need more than promises and vaporware to overcome the fact their designs are garbage.</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1367943518262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:18:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367943575081-142</Id><Title>Now stop pumping Wall Steet wants out bad</Title><Msg>Now stop pumping Wall Steet wants out bad</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367943575081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:19:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367943593352-143</Id><Topic><Title>Intel’s Latest “Silvermont” Platform To Offer 3 Times Performance at 1/5th the Power</Title><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367939311932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:08:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is OVER, let it go. The stock hasn't moved in 10 years</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1367943593352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:19:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367943613258-144</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is pure lies</Title><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1367943518262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:18:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you "sir" are pure $#^T</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367943613258</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:20:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367943734293-145</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is pure lies</Title><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1367943518262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:18:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still have my american pride. And aulus is right ....you are #$%$.</Msg><Username>albchem</Username><Timestamp>1367943734293</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:22:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367943768128-146</Id><Topic><Title>GTHP: Billion Dollar Estimate</Title><Username>hilla2ro</Username><Timestamp>1367942872701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:07:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Guided Therapeutics, Inc. (OTC:GTHP) contains perhaps one of the most promising medical devices aiming for an annual global $1 billion dollar non-invasive cervical cancer market"</Msg><Username>hilla2ro</Username><Timestamp>1367943768128</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:22:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367944063481-147</Id><Topic><Title>INTC is pure lies</Title><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1367943518262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:18:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey think what you want the facts are Intel is fraud on society.</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1367944063481</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367944577454-148</Id><Topic><Title>Always remember that when all the insiders are selling they know something you don't and now we know about windows</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367941515960</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there was a new item out this am, cfo sold about 300,000 shares a little over 24.00</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1367944577454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:36:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367944776857-149</Id><Title>Intel Brings Silvermont to Mobile Competition vs. ARM</Title><Msg>Intel Brings Silvermont to Mobile Competition vs. ARM By Jeffrey Burt | Posted 2013-05-06 Email Print Intel officials argue that the performance and power-saving innovations in upcoming Atom SoCs will outpace anything ARM can offer. Intel officials, five years after introducing the first low-power Atom chips, are finally bringing a new microarchitecture to the platform, a move they say will introduce performance and power consumption advantages that will significantly exceed anything ARM and its partners can offer. Now they just have to see if the upcoming systems-on-a-chip (SoCs) with the new “Silvermont” microarchitecture will be enough to convince device makers and consumers to embrace the idea of Intel inside their tablets and smartphones. “We’re breaking the myth that ARM can do things that Intel cannot,” Dadi Perlmutter, executive vice president, general manager of the Intel Architecture Group, and Intel’s chief product officer, said during a May 6 Webcast introducing Silvermont. Silvermont will be an architecture that will be found in Intel chips that power everything from servers to PCs to embedded systems, but it’s the low-power and mobile spaces—in particular, smartphones, tablets and microservers, where the chip maker will compete most directly with ARM—where the architecture will succeed or fail. Intel for several years has been pushing its Atom platform—and to a lesser extent, its Core processors—as the technology that will take the company into the booming mobile space. The bulk of the smartphones and tablets on the market today are powered by SoCs designed by ARM specifically for mobile devices and built by the likes of Qualcomm, Samsung and Nvidia. Intel has been trying to drive down the power consumption of its x86-based Atom chips to compete with ARM, and doing so with the original “Bonnell” microarchitecture. That will change later this year and early next, when devices powered by the upcoming 22-nanometer “Bay Trail” Atom SoCs for</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367944776857</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:39:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367944836555-150</Id><Title>Microsemi</Title><Msg>I could not find one analysis in regards to MSCC foundry deal (although SA and fool are cranking out blurbs like chicken lay eggs) - some people say Micro who? or someone on EE times commented MSCC least expected. Brian Krzanich is far, far more aggressive to grow Intel's foundry business. They are not only cherry picking - they are going to grow it into a "serious" business (forget Apple for a moment - there is other business to be taken from TSMC) Intel has a HUGE advantage with a production worthy TriGate - not only in the CPU and Soc ARENA. See attached quote - of course you need to understand what MSCC business is about. The market is slow and has a hard time to "connect the dots". The new guy is good...push ARM to the wall while sucking business away from the ARM foundries "Market watcher Handel Jones of International Business Strategies (Los Gatos, Calif.) said FinFETs present real challenges for mixed-signal designs, potentially delaying the node’s ramp. Nevertheless, he said Globalfoundries and Samsung have a significant opportunity to grab market share from TSMC. In addition, IBM’s Burlington fab is doing “extremely well” in RF, he added."</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367944836555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:40:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367945064492-151</Id><Title>Intel won't stay undervalued for long. We might see a jump up</Title><Msg>similar to microsoft.</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367945064492</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:44:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367945148183-152</Id><Title>Now we know why Warren East was in a hurry to leave ...</Title><Msg>Before end or the year</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367945148183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367945273530-153</Id><Topic><Title>Microsemi</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367944836555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:40:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And your point is ? Because it is far from apparent with the two paragraphs you copied and pasted</Msg><Username>zisdead1</Username><Timestamp>1367945273530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:47:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367945436006-154</Id><Title>WOW whats the book value of INTC $10.45 a share trading at 2.5 X book NOT good</Title><Msg>WOW whats the book value of INTC $10.45 a share trading at 2.5 X book NOT good. There are a lot of stocks still trading under book value</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367945436006</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:50:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367945443494-155</Id><Topic><Title>Silvermont Is Coming</Title><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367855229297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now that the original Atom is being retired as a mobile success at 32nm here was its original story as told in 2008 ... Intel's Atom Architecture: The Journey Begins anandtechDOTcom/show/2493/</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367945443494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367945486593-156</Id><Topic><Title>Microsemi</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367944836555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:40:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I looked at MSCC profile / competitors and I put it into perspective to a quote from Handel who is an ARM advocate. The rest is up to you....either you get it or you don't</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367945486593</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:51:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367945957765-157</Id><Topic><Title>Microsemi</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367944836555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:40:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's nearly impossible to understand what you are talking about 88% of the time because you are lazy and just ramble instead of stating clearly what you are saying.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367945957765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367945960504-158</Id><Title>The Deal: Intel's McAfee Buys Helsinki's Stonesoft for European Expansion</Title><Msg>important deal in this day and age</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367945960504</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:59:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367946158317-159</Id><Topic><Title>WOW whats the book value of INTC $10.45 a share trading at 2.5 X book NOT good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367945436006</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not under valued</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367946158317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367946235959-160</Id><Topic><Title>Microsemi</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367944836555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:40:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you a native English speaker ? Maybe that is the problem ?</Msg><Username>zisdead1</Username><Timestamp>1367946235959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:03:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367946625509-161</Id><Topic><Title>WOW whats the book value of INTC $10.45 a share trading at 2.5 X book NOT good</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367945436006</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for pointing this out. Especially like it when you capitalize "NOT". This helps out those of us who are mentally challenged. Do you have any clue as to how completely ridiculous and obnoxious your comments are?</Msg><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367946625509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367946782147-162</Id><Topic><Title>Always remember that when all the insiders are selling they know something you don't and now we know about windows</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367941515960</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see a sale for 90,000 shares by Stacy Smith reported by Intel to the SEC on 5/6 but I don't see any 300,000 share transaction. I got my information from the Intel site related to SEC filings. I would say, yes, CFO made a 90,000 share sale. I could not find the 300,000 share sale by Smith. Where did you get your information? Yahoo: May 2, 2013 SMITH STACY J Officer 90,000 Direct Sale at $24.05 per share. 2,164,500</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367946782147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:13:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367946910464-163</Id><Title>Golden Cross - 50 over 200 MA</Title><Msg>50 DMA (21.83) crossed the 200 DMA (21.81) today. When the 50 DMA moves into the 23s then the stock will start rising again up to the next resistance $24.5-25.0 stockchartsDOTcom/c-sc/sc?chart=INTC,uu[800,a]daclyyay[pb50!b200!f][vc60][iue12,26,9!lc20]</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1367946910464</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367947345251-164</Id><Topic><Title>Always remember that when all the insiders are selling they know something you don't and now we know about windows</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367941515960</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i stand corrected, it was 90,000, dble checked the news</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1367947345251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:22:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367947359239-165</Id><Title>Intel presentation at Jefferies TMT Conference: William Holt</Title><Msg>the REPLAY of the Holt talk on technology is online at Intel events. Register and listen. It happened earlier today. Holt talks technical process topics to Jefferies group.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367947359239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:22:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367947425911-166</Id><Title>Why You Want Your Tablet To Run 64 bit Windows 8</Title><Msg>What is the significance of Windows on tablets? - While running Windows 8 everything just works - your network, your peripherals, your drivers, etc - You have access to the world's largest ecosystem of apps for work and entertainment - You leverage the time, money &amp; skill you already have using Windows apps and utilities - You don't have to leave your professional tools behind just because you carry a tablet - Administrative control is often a necessity to get things done - Your remote connectivity, authentication and VPN's will work just as they do on regular PCs - The Windows tablet is essentially a PC that's simply lighter, thinner and far more portable Android is a fine piece of work for what it was designed for but the tablet that can run professional class 64 bit Windows is in a completely different product category than an Android-only tablet. The tablet that can run Windows &amp; Android gives consumers the best of both for work &amp; play. Intel isn't just "entering" the tablet market, they are redefining the tablet space.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367947425911</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:23:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367947471654-167</Id><Topic><Title>Microsemi</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367944836555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:40:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you a native English speaker ? No but here MSCC business summary - looks like Intel is going after a very (new) lucrative market beside ASIC and FPGAs. Handel stated GF and Samsung could take business (Mixeded Signal) away from TSMC. Now it looks like Intel is trying to take that business. bottom line: Intel is expanding into foundry business more than I had anticipated Microsemi Corporation engages in the design, manufacture, and marketing of analog and mixed-signal integrated circuits (ICs) and semiconductors primarily in the United States, Europe, and Asia. Its products include radio frequency (RF) and power components, analog and RF ICs, standard and customizable system-on-chip solutions, and mixed-signal and radiation-tolerant field programmable gate arrays.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367947471654</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:24:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367947740448-168</Id><Topic><Title>Intel presentation at Jefferies TMT Conference: William Holt</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367947359239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:22:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EUV?</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367947740448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367947859597-169</Id><Topic><Title>Why You Want Your Tablet To Run 64 bit Windows 8</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367947425911</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:23:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows tables are 3 to 6 times the price of Android tables</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367947859597</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:30:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367947902732-170</Id><Topic><Title>Intel won't stay undervalued for long. We might see a jump up</Title><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367945064492</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:44:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't understand why it hasn't happened. You'd think this silvermont buzz would be good for $30. Only thing I can think of is the light volume, and a guy on Bloom this AM who was saying it's still a market of a lot of sidelined money....which is a good thing if there's no big war in the middle east.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367947902732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367948023159-171</Id><Topic><Title>Intel presentation at Jefferies TMT Conference: William Holt</Title><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367947359239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:22:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I did not hear him talk about EUV in presentation Questions @ 21min point</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367948023159</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:33:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367948176531-172</Id><Topic><Title>Why You Want Your Tablet To Run 64 bit Windows 8</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367947425911</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:23:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Asus CEO announced yesterday he expects to see Windows tablets below $300. It may well be that ARM tablets will have to be priced at $50 to sell.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367948176531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:36:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367948774972-173</Id><Topic><Title>Always remember that when all the insiders are selling they know something you don't and now we know about windows</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367941515960</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That makes sense. Thanks. The RSU option "immediate sell to pay taxes" makes it easy to say that all the insiders are selling. While technically accurate, that activity is really a routine and standard way to acquire the shares to pay the initial tax bill.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367948774972</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367948781100-174</Id><Topic><Title>Why You Want Your Tablet To Run 64 bit Windows 8</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367947425911</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:23:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surface is 700 1200</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367948781100</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367948838726-175</Id><Title>armh 49 49 49 49</Title><Msg>holy molie</Msg><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1367948838726</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:47:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949087372-176</Id><Topic><Title>armh 49 49 49 49</Title><Username>aladiesright</Username><Timestamp>1367948838726</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:47:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So are you saying Wally's ARM TECHINCAL's posts from 20 percent ago are content-free ????</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367949087372</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:51:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949138413-177</Id><Topic><Title>The lunchbreak</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367942251857</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:57:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lunchbreak is over.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367949138413</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949145378-178</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367935723576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:08:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Come again? It's over 49 now and you are the board boob.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367949145378</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:52:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949151593-179</Id><Topic><Title>Why You Want Your Tablet To Run 64 bit Windows 8</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367947425911</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:23:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazon leaks first 8-inch full Windows 8 tablet, priced at $379 Amazon has all but confirmed rumors about an incoming breed of smaller Windows tablets by accidentally listing an 8.1-inch Acer Iconia over the weekend, running the full version of Microsoft’s latest operating system. The listing has since been removed, but not before several sites caught a glimpse at some specs and its price. Specifically, Amazon’s listing described the Acer W3-810 as a $379.99 tablet powered by a dual-core 1.8GHz Intel Atom processor, 2GB of RAM, and an 8.1-inch 1280 x 800 display. The price tag is particularly interesting given that the slate is based on Windows 8, not RT, and will therefore run ‘legacy’ applications. Other specs include 32GB of storage, 2-megapixel front and rear cameras, one micro USB 2.0 port, and a micro-HDMI port. The tablet is said to weigh 1.1lbs and provide up to 8 hours of battery life.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1367949151593</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:52:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949194600-180</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366864941994</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:42:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another content-free post from Wallisweaver.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367949194600</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:53:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949225124-181</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366816509289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 11:15:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM over 49 now, lol.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367949225124</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:53:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949236547-182</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366781711845</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 01:35:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope ARM longs didn't listen to your con game.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367949236547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:53:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949271702-183</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366566744095</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 13:52:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL....</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367949271702</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:54:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949320913-184</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366307545399</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 13:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tested 49, not 39. You are a boob.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367949320913</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:55:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949348522-185</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Falls Off Cliff</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366211294635</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 11:08:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess again, chump.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367949348522</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:55:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949361588-186</Id><Topic><Title>ARM and 40</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366208162722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:16:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Priceless.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367949361588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:56:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949376313-187</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Drops Below 40 - Again</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366207441246</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only shill here is you.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367949376313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:56:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949405962-188</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Low of the Day: 39.90</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366206894653</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:54:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're the village idiot.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367949405962</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949505872-189</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, ARM Drops Below $40 and Apple Drops Below $400</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366226836452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 15:27:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARM flitering with fitty, lol.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367949505872</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:58:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949539852-190</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down Again on Another Big NASDAQ Day</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366144169779</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:29:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>50.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367949539852</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949593487-191</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down Over a Buck</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366053080588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 15:11:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It'l be a miracle if you ever admit how wrong you were.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367949593487</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:59:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367949749794-192</Id><Topic><Title>I Pity the Fools</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365785161334</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 12:46:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who needs pitying, again?</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367949749794</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:02:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367951084491-193</Id><Title>Yahoo: Please create a "superignore"</Title><Msg>where the message "Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post" does NOT appear on the screen. Also, please create a time limit on the redisplaying of a message that has been replied to, not to exceed one-week.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367951084491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:24:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367951197597-194</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo: Please create a "superignore"</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367951084491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:24:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They also should ban all posters that bash stocks that proceed to rise 100 percent.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367951197597</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:26:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367951405332-195</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo: Please create a "superignore"</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367951084491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:24:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.........and ban all posters that say they know of "big things" coming from Intel one minute, then say they are scared to hold in the low 20's the next...........and then change aliases once a week.......</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367951405332</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:30:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367951705937-196</Id><Title>Misinformation All Day Long</Title><Msg>From TheStreetDOTcom "The vast majority of the apps and software that run on iPhones, iPads, Galaxy phones, and other devices all are built off ARM-based intellectual property, so to change from that technology to Silvermont is an enormous task. " Of course, the opposite is true. All the software that has been written for X86 serves as a huge moat protecting INTC's PC and server business. This moat will simply expand to cover tablets this year. On the other hand, it is my understanding that few apps have been written that will run ONLY on Apple or Android machines. Virtually all of them can now or will soon run on X86. ARM has no moat. Apple has no moat except a lot of true believers. Android is agnostic. INTC has a huge moat and better technology. How long will it take to get this through some of these fat heads?</Msg><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1367951705937</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:35:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367951765510-197</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo: Please create a "superignore"</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367951084491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:24:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But, thank-you for the "ignore" feature that we presently have because it really comes in handy. It allows us to keep the visibles at a much higher average IQ. It also makes the chat room smell better.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367951765510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:36:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367951951868-198</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo: Please create a "superignore"</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367951084491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:24:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your IQ is so high that you ask people on Yahoo why the stock isn't any higher. LOL! What a maroon.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367951951868</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:39:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367952232232-199</Id><Title>High IQ post from one of the boards's most astute and elite investors</Title><Msg>Anyone..has splained why its down? by aulus_vitellius_germanicus • 16 hours ago Flag Ashrraff? The Beaver? Why down? You guys have hyped..and I mean HYPED this thing. So why down?</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367952232232</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:43:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367952451253-200</Id><Topic><Title>Misinformation All Day Long</Title><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1367951705937</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:35:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apples iOS environment is native, that is to say apps are compiled into ARM machine code. In Android most apps are Java and happily run under x86. There are some apps (typically games) that are native ARM code. Windows server environment is all native x86, while the linux server environment is native x86 but most apps happily compile to ARM native. Basically, running a linux software stack on ARM is no problem.</Msg><Username>theblueredmonk</Username><Timestamp>1367952451253</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:47:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367952754496-201</Id><Topic><Title>Misinformation All Day Long</Title><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1367951705937</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:35:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel to offer tools for easy porting of iPhone or Android apps to its hardware here is no doubt that the chipset manufacturer is pretty annoyed to see these little devices turning into the main computing units for many people, who would otherwise have to use Intel's hardware, found in laptops and desktop machines. To remedy the situation until the dual-core Atom family finds its way into tablets and smartphones, Intel is working on a tool that will allow applications developed for ARM chipsets, to be ported for Intel gear with maximum ease. Theoretically, this could allow all applications written for the Apple's App Store and Google's Android Market, to be transformed into software for Intel's Atom-based gizmos. Whether or not this strategy will prove successful, is anyone's guess, but at least Intel is doing something to entice developers. The company already has an AppUp Center for Intel-based netbooks that will also double as a store for MeeGo and Windows down the road. Intel's goal is to have a look at existing apps, try to port the relevant ones over, and have them on the AppUp Center for the end users.</Msg><Username>sujit_98</Username><Timestamp>1367952754496</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367952836756-202</Id><Topic><Title>Misinformation All Day Long</Title><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1367951705937</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:35:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the fat heads are those who have consistently bashed ARMH in favor of INTC and gotten their shorts handed to them. notably some poster who noted Wall Street finally takes notice when ARMH was at the low of the day on the way to a new high, something INTC was not able to achieve today. and the poster wasn't wally</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1367952836756</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:53:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367953127808-203</Id><Topic><Title>Misinformation All Day Long</Title><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1367951705937</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:35:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the fat heads are those who have consistently bashed ARMH in favor of INTC and gotten their shorts handed to them. notably some poster who noted Wall Street finally takes notice when ARMH was at the low of the day on the way to a new high, something INTC was not able to achieve today. and the poster wasn't wally" [Please buy copious amounts of ARM stock and post your buys here so we can track your success. Otherwise put a sock in it...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367953127808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:58:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367953334744-204</Id><Topic><Title>Misinformation All Day Long</Title><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1367951705937</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:35:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to take your own advice and put a sock in it. You have NO CLUE about Technicals or ARMH stock and have RUINED this board.......you know, this INTEL board. Everybody that's frustrated with this board can blame it on you.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367953334744</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367953381798-205</Id><Topic><Title>I Pity the Fools</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365785161334</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 12:46:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Who needs pitying, again?" [Anyone who paid over $15 for ARM. I will laugh last on this. ARM P/E is now 81.24. What a joke...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367953381798</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367953430037-206</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Down Over a Buck</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366053080588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 15:11:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It'l be a miracle if you ever admit how wrong you were." [You're 5 bucks down on Intel since November. Show me how it's done...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367953430037</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:03:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367953507016-207</Id><Title>Just put a bunch of aliases on ignore</Title><Msg>That's why Nuff has so many- he doesn't want to be ignored.</Msg><Username>johnsmitty109</Username><Timestamp>1367953507016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:05:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367953874564-208</Id><Title>Wallisweaver has completely ruined your message board</Title><Msg>His arrogance and attempts to influence investors has brought on daily chaos here. If he cared one bit about any of you, he'd become a man and stop thumbing his nose at everybody. But he doesn't care and can't stop because he's mentally disturbed. Disclaimer: Long Intel, never shorted Intel and never bought ARM.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367953874564</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:11:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367953999115-209</Id><Title>Going to all cash selling almost everything</Title><Msg>Going to all cash selling almost everything</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367953999115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:13:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367954032141-210</Id><Title>Weaver: Quit taunting these jerks</Title><Msg>You're ruining this board. I frankly don't want to hear about ARMH all the time. I want to hear about Intel. If you want to taunt ARMH droids, go to their board, BUT DON'T BRING THEM OVER HERE. Yahoo: create a keyword ignore feature so I can ignore any message that contains "Wallis", "Weaver," "WW", or "Wallisweaver."</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367954032141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:13:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367954082079-211</Id><Topic><Title>I Pity the Fools</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1365785161334</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 12:46:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The chance of Haswell being a big flop is pretty close to zero. The only question is whether or not they can break out of their traditional desktop, laptop, and server markets.</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1367954082079</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:14:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367954245249-212</Id><Topic><Title>Weaver: Quit taunting these jerks</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367954032141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:13:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I so agree. He posts so much about ARM that it's just not even close to cool. This is the Intel board.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367954245249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:17:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367954327690-213</Id><Topic><Title>Why You Want Your Tablet To Run 64 bit Windows 8</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367947425911</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:23:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel and several major vendor CEO's have said Bay Trail tablets with Windows 8 are expected to be below $300. To make this possible Microsoft will introduce new pricing plans for small screen tablets. Intel based tablets in the second half of this year will be vastly different from the beginning of the year.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367954327690</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:18:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367954328135-214</Id><Topic><Title>Going to all cash selling almost everything</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367953999115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:13:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really nice gain this year and I will be happy on matter what the market does. Can go on vacation and have a goo time</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367954328135</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:18:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367954391273-215</Id><Topic><Title>Going to all cash selling almost everything</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367953999115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:13:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I sold in May and I can go away</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367954391273</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:19:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367954547357-216</Id><Title>Interesting INTC chart here on Yahoo</Title><Msg>For each of the last five years, INTC has reached a yearly high in late April to early May, and a yearly low in October. What will be different about this year? Why not sell now and come back in October?</Msg><Username>firstofmany</Username><Timestamp>1367954547357</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:22:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367954551472-217</Id><Topic><Title>Misinformation All Day Long</Title><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1367951705937</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:35:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That statement you quoted is absolutely, positively false. Applications written for iOS are written in Objective-C and are already compiled NOW to run on X86. When you develop an iOS application you can run it in an iPad or iPhone simulator and the simulators run on X86 Macs. A simply choice from a drop-down list lets you build your application for either ARM or X86.</Msg><Username>intoodeep99</Username><Timestamp>1367954551472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:22:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367954555652-218</Id><Topic><Title>ARM Technicals</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1366307545399</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 13:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't care about ARM Technicals, especially when you are wrong as rain about them. Please stop.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367954555652</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:22:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367954657124-219</Id><Title>Why doesnt Intel have LTE implemented yet??</Title><Msg>Its the main reason why Intel is not in smartphones. Gimme a break. How many years does it take when you have the resources Intel has? What was the Infinion acquisition for Billions all about? Once again, Otellini has missed mobile.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367954657124</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:24:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367954731556-220</Id><Title>Smart glasses exploding - Vuzi is breaking out... last chance to buy the future of Cell service</Title><Msg>Its gonna be big</Msg><Username>whattime0000</Username><Timestamp>1367954731556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:25:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367954876255-221</Id><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Msg>Wow, you just have to love those ARM investors. There are so many reasons. They are totally fearless. They are afraid of literally nothing. Not Haswell, not ARM's fading fabrication. Not Clover Trail, not Bay Trail, not Airmont, and not being years away from FinFET production. Not afraid of Intel doubling tablet sales every quarter. Not Intel's new traction in smartphones. Now some might say that this is not fearless, it's stupid. But that would be rude. And non-factual. Surely none of these things will have any effect on ARM's future. Don't worry, be happy. And fearless. They have humble expectations. They are totally happy with just a dab of earnings. Almost no earnings at all will send them happily driving the stock to new 52-week highs. In fact, that have almost no expectations of ARM at all, other than it continue to stay in business. They are the essence of humility. They are in it for the long term. The fact that it takes over 80 years to earn back the price of a share of ARM stock doesn't bother them in the least. Hey, if they don't benefit from the purchase of ARM shares then their grandkids or great grandkids will surely reap the rewards. What other investors are able to take such a multi-generational approach??? None, I think. They are exuberant. Not since the dotcom era have we seen the exuberance that they express every single day. The past month is a great example that there is no threat that will dull their enthusiasm. Their sheer exuberance will work for them in the same way it did for those exuberant souls during the dotcom era. No doubt. Well, there you have it. Just some of the many, many reasons why I just love those ARM investors. And it's just as clear that Wall Street loves them too...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367954901244-222</Id><Title>Bounce near the end: means trend will continue tomorrow:25-26$</Title><Msg>==============================================================</Msg><Username>ngmike18</Username><Timestamp>1367954901244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:28:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367955073724-223</Id><Topic><Title>Going to all cash selling almost everything</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1367953999115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:13:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So why you still here?</Msg><Username>jj_the_homo</Username><Timestamp>1367955073724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:31:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367955161346-224</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesnt Intel have LTE implemented yet??</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367954657124</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:24:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read DigiTimes and shut up</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367955161346</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367955257775-225</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesnt Intel have LTE implemented yet??</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1367954657124</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:24:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am curious and don't want to go searching thru Digitimes. Is it legalities?</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367955257775</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367955349755-226</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny how that post, which takes some time to read, was thumbs upped just seconds after it was posted. There are some good posters on this board (Alexander, semi-equip, merlot, marsavian), and then there's you and the other bashers. Ever heard of being the bigger man? Ever heard of being a man at all? Your calls on ARM have been dreadful. We all make mistakes. Suck it up and move on. Come back later to laugh if it drops but stop the daily play by play which only shows how embarrassed you are about your dreadful calls on ARM stock price.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367955349755</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367955466479-227</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to have the emotional development of a 6-year-old. Why must you constantly pick fights with and taunt the ARMH investors? They just want to make money like you do. They're not bad people, or Boston bombers, or Gun-toting NRA Republicans, or anything. Fine to occasionally prod them, but it's all you ever do, and it has the effect of trashing this board. What perverse pleasure are you getting out of this? Is it something that happened in your youth to you, forever haunting you? The taunter is always the tauntee. The victim always the victimizer. KNOCK IT OFF!</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367955466479</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367955467094-228</Id><Topic><Title>Misinformation All Day Long</Title><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1367951705937</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:35:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>iOS applications are written in Objective-C and can be compiled for ARM or X86 NOW.</Msg><Username>intoodeep99</Username><Timestamp>1367955467094</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:37:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367955629613-229</Id><Title>Cliff note version in case you want to know about "WALLISWEAVER"</Title><Msg>ARM can't hold 25 ! ARM can't hold 26 ! ARM can't hold 27 ! ARM can't hold 28 ! ARM can't hold 29 ! ARM can't hold 30 ! ARM can't hold 31 ! ARM can't hold 32 ! ARM can't hold 33 ! ARM can't hold 34 ! ARM can't hold 35 ! ARM can't hold 36 ! ARM can't hold 37 ! ARM can't hold 38 ! ARM can't hold 39 ! ARM can't hold 40 ! ARM can't hold 41 ! ARM can't hold 42 ! ARM can't hold 43 ! ARM can't hold 44 ! ARM can't hold 45 ! ARM can't hold 46 ! ARM can't hold 47 ! ARM can't hold 48 ! ARM can't hold 49!</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367955629613</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:40:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367955758200-230</Id><Title>I'll never post here again if WALLISWEAVER stops acting like a cry baby</Title><Msg>Will never post again.</Msg><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367955758200</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:42:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367956012622-231</Id><Topic><Title>Cliff note version in case you want to know about "WALLISWEAVER"</Title><Username>wallisdreamweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367955629613</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you forgot the infamous INTC's good for 30, as it dropped to 19.00. that said intc and armh are both presently overbght, and a pullback would be beneficial to each as long as the technicals don't roll over in that process.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1367956012622</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:46:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367957364635-232</Id><Topic><Title>Misinformation All Day Long</Title><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1367951705937</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:35:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dewey_duhawk, It's good to know that I'm not the only one frustrated at this broad misconception.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367957364635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:09:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367957604673-233</Id><Title>Bunch of crazies on INTC board</Title><Msg>My god what is wrong with you lunatics?</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1367957604673</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:13:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367957672419-234</Id><Topic><Title>Why You Want Your Tablet To Run 64 bit Windows 8</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367947425911</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:23:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When they put an AMD APU inside the surface it will be worth it, versus the Intel kludge graphics.</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1367957672419</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:14:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367957682215-235</Id><Topic><Title>Misinformation All Day Long</Title><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1367951705937</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:35:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You guys are missing the forrest for the trees. It is not going to be Intel versus iPad tablets using ARM architecture. It is going to be iPad using Intel x86 processors in the future. I'd bet real money (and I have) that even now Intel and Apple are working on putting x86 processors in iPads for 2014. The MS Surface is a clunky prototype of what an x86 tablet could be. iPad with x86 processor will show what they should be. Thin, lightweight, long battery life, and NO COOLING FAN. By the way, I own INTC and AAPL. Pretty good dividends too.</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1367957682215</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:14:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367957765046-236</Id><Title>Why does anyone here care about ARM?</Title><Msg>Intel products are still weak versus AMD.</Msg><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1367957765046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:16:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367957818834-237</Id><Topic><Title>Why You Want Your Tablet To Run 64 bit Windows 8</Title><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367947425911</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:23:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your tablet is going to run 64-bit OS X. iPads will be using x86 processors. MS Surface Pro is a decent proof of concept, but Apple and Intel will work together to do an x86 processor in a tablet the right way.</Msg><Username>gulc94</Username><Timestamp>1367957818834</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:16:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367957831022-238</Id><Topic><Title>Why does anyone here care about ARM?</Title><Username>lostamericanpride</Username><Timestamp>1367957765046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:16:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why Intel's taking huge market share against AMD, right?</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367957831022</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:17:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367958053451-239</Id><Title>Is AMD still making 2nd rate junk for losers? I thought AMD was ROADKILL.</Title><Msg>Clearly this and clearly that said Hector as he ran AMD deep into a pile of sheeet. AMD fanboys wer in at 49 and a few of the idiots who were complete losers, like most AMD fanboys are, held it all the way down to wear it is today. Nothing so so dim and an AMD fanboy. AMD to 1.00</Msg><Username>amdroadkill2010</Username><Timestamp>1367958053451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:20:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367958975932-240</Id><Topic><Title>Weaver: Quit taunting these jerks</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367954032141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:13:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you guys ignoring the fact that Intel's future success has LOTS to do with how they compete with ARMH and their licensees? It is totally relevant to discuss ARMH on this board as the two companies are locked in an architecture war that will have huge impact on both concerns. I agree there's no need to taunt other investors, but get real please. If you don't think ARMH is a meaty topic line for this message board then you probably shouldn't be here, but more importantly you shouldn't be investing in either of the two companies (unless you enjoy roulette investing strategy)</Msg><Username>bhy11141</Username><Timestamp>1367958975932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:36:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367959368278-241</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why thank you for asking. It actually all started when the ARM fanbois started showing up, doing the Intel bashing 24/7. They started it. I'm going to finish it. Any other questions, grandpa? Otherwise I'd like to go outside and play now. Do you want me to get you another lemon to suck on before I go? As far as trashing this board, now that's a hoot. You got the Dana crowd (well just him actually and a fistful of IDs) posting 150 content-free messages a day and it's me who is trashing the board? Thanks for the laugh...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367959368278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:42:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367959505333-242</Id><Topic><Title>Weaver: Quit taunting these jerks</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367954032141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:13:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Droning on about ARM technicals and the stock over-valuation and hype is not a discussion of the technology issues. But it's too late. MOST of the posts on this board today are Hatfield's vs McCoy's.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367959505333</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367959687214-243</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not the least bit embarrassed by my ARM calls. I'm embarrassed for the mindless buying it at $48+. ARM has become a chain letter, ponzi scheme bubble. It no longer has anything to do with the company itself. It's become a vehicle for the manipulator momentum crowd. If you believe in that stock action then I have some Nigerian e-mail opportunities that you are gonna love. I have yet to find anyone willing to even argue for its current price based on anything real...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367959687214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:48:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367960623027-244</Id><Title>Mixed Signal / DSP</Title><Msg>A week ago I had that crazy idea an Intel/TI deal could be possible in the future? - read the SA blurb about Intel foundry business - read the one comment about TI. So far analysts only focused only on FPGA and ASIC but there is far more business Intel could grap. MSCC was kind of low profile news but it could have far more reaching implications than the ALTR announcement. "A mixed-signal integrated circuit is any integrated circuit that has both analog circuits and digital circuits on a single semiconductor die."[ "Definition of digital signal processing (DSP) : The process of converting analog transmissions into digital signals. The audio transmissions are processed in real-time .." Bohr said that when Intel had first announced it would be using tri-gate devices, other companies had argued that FinFET transistors would not aid analog design. “Well, they’re wrong,” declared Bohr. For analog designers, he asserted, an important transistor metric is trans-conductance by power out (GM x Rout). Bohr said that while this value had been steadily degrading over the past few generations, it had shot up again in 22-nm trigate SoCs, making it easier for analog circuit designers to use than Intel’s previous three generations of planar technology.</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367960623027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 17:03:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367960893446-245</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They started it. I'm going to finish it _________ How old are you again? thanks for clearly answering my question as to do you know what it's like to be the better man. That was an emphatic "NO." And thanks for having skin as thin as a 6 year old. As a result, the entire message board has to pay for it.</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367960893446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 17:08:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367961765512-246</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>14nm, If you don't like his posts, why not put him on ignore? Nothing's stopping you from doing that.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367961765512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 17:22:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367962250070-247</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about the 20 posts today calling him out on his dumb calls, and the 20 yesterday, the day before, the day before that, etc... What's the better solution? Me and every single other person having to constantly put people on ignore or Wallis using just a TINY bit of common sense and acting like an adult?</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367962250070</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 17:30:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367962471686-248</Id><Title>I'm 62 years old and all I can say is: They started it, I'm finising it</Title><Msg>Going outside to play hopscotch now. Anybody seen my liqourish stix?</Msg><Username>chump.weaver</Username><Timestamp>1367962471686</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 17:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367962608521-249</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am tired of having to put 90% of the posters on "ignore" because of Wallis' ego-maniacal issues.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367962608521</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 17:36:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367966831473-250</Id><Topic><Title>Weaver: Quit taunting these jerks</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367954032141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:13:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's not about ARMH, it's just en excuse to hassle the board and the main contributors</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367966831473</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 18:47:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367967224754-251</Id><Title>There are no ARMH investors on this board just some shills trying to distrupt the board !</Title><Msg>The shills envy wallis , ottelini and other contributors. ARMH is just an excuse!</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367967224754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 18:53:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367967617297-252</Id><Title>Intel's new Atom chip is 3 times faster than previous one.</Title><Msg>This should be huge for new design wins across the board. The new Atom chips from Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC), which have a new CPU architecture, will be almost three times speedier than the previous versions. These new upcoming chips, according to Intel, will be 5 times more efficient than the older ones and will oust the belief that ARM processors are more power efficient. The new architecture, which is called Silvermont as of now, will be integrated in the Smartphones, tablets, PC’s and servers from the current year. The atom chips being designed by Intel Corporation (NASDAQ:INTC) are codenamed Bay Trail, which will be mounted in the tablets this holiday season. The chip will be compatible with both Android and Microsoft Corporation (NASDAQ:MSFT) operating systems. Dadi Perlmutter, the chief product officer of Intel said that the new Silvermont chips will provide even better performance per watt, and there will be no difference between ARM processors and Atom chips any more. “We see that this kind of solution will be even better,” said Perlmutter, who is also the executive vice president and general manager of the Intel Architecture Group. The upcoming Atom chips based on Silvermont will be using 22 nanometer processes. Under this technology more transistors are allowed under 3D transistors. These chips will be smaller in size and will save more on power compared to the current Atom chips which is codenamed Clover Trail and is based on the 32-nm process. The Atom chips, before Bay Trail, were condemned for the lackluster performance compared to ARM chips, which is said to enhance the efficiency on chips. Now Intel says that its chip is as efficient as ARM since it launched the recent chip codenamed Medfield, which are being used in Smartphones. Other than tablets, Bay trail chip can also be integrated in hybrid laptops that are convertible, detachable and have folding screens.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367967617297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 19:00:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367967710188-253</Id><Topic><Title>There are no ARMH investors on this board just some shills trying to distrupt the board !</Title><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367967224754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 18:53:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thank you, passing.gas, for your astute observations.</Msg><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367967710188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 19:01:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367972021151-254</Id><Title>Barrons: Wells Fargo sees PC, Tablet Upside</Title><Msg>In addition to a note this morning from B. Riley &amp; Co.’s Craig Ellis cheering the appointment of COO Brian Krzanich as the company’s new CEO, and also cheering the formal unveiling of the company’s new “Silvermont” technology for mobile, the stock gets a thumbs up today from Daniel Berenbaum of MKM Partners, and from David Wong of Wells Fargo. Wong, who has an Outperform rating on the shares, and a $28 to $33 “valuation range,” reiterates a theme he explored a week ago, the prospect that the PC market is actually healthier than the Street is currently expecting. Wong likes the prospects for a doubling of the Atom line of mobile chips’ performance with Silvermont, relative to its predecessor, “Saltwell.” Wong sees a big increase in Intel tablet processor share in the coming two years:</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367972021151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 20:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367972083726-255</Id><Title>Barrons: MKM raises target on Intel to $28.</Title><Msg>MKM’s Berenbaum, who has a Buy rating, raises his price target to $28 from $24, writing that the “inclination to take profits after its recent run” is understandable — the stock is up 16% this year, outperforming the Nasdaq Composite’s 12% run — he thinks the stock can appreciate on multiple expansion alone. Berenbaum sees cheap valuation and the prospect of a greater progress with Intel’s “Haswell” processors for PCs adding fuel to the shares: First, macro factors are likely to continue to drive investors toward large-cap tech, where reasonable valuation and high dividend yields provide support. Second, new PC form factors (e.g., sub-$600 touch-enabled ultrabooks with all-day battery life) enabled by INTC’s new Haswell CPUs will likely help drive PC sales in 2H (against easy comps) – and, although this is far from a sure thing, we see a good chance that these new form factors will help short-circuit the bear argument that “the PC is dead.” Lastly, we maintain our view that, over the long term, INTC will be able to monetize its technology and manufacturing advantage through its own products in mobility, PCs, servers, and communications infrastructure, as well as through providing foundry services for non-competitors.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367972083726</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 20:14:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367972728604-256</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I am tired of having to put 90% of the posters on "ignore" because of Wallis' ego-maniacal issues." [You named yourself after a Roman emperor and I'm the ego-maniac???]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367972728604</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 20:25:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367972947764-257</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How old are you again? thanks for clearly answering my question as to do you know what it's like to be the better man. That was an emphatic "NO." And thanks for having skin as thin as a 6 year old. As a result, the entire message board has to pay for it." [I love how the people who complain about me talking smack jump in and start talking smack back. If only they weren't so lame at it. No style points on this post, butkus. You need to elevate your game...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367972947764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 20:29:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367973229716-258</Id><Topic><Title>Weaver: Quit taunting these jerks</Title><Username>aulus_vitellius_germanicus</Username><Timestamp>1367954032141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:13:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Droning on about ARM technicals and the stock over-valuation and hype is not a discussion of the technology issues. But it's too late. MOST of the posts on this board today are Hatfield's vs McCoy's." [Hey, it's not my fault if none of the ARM boys can mount a defense of their company based on fundamentals. I made the ole college try at getting them to talk about the problem with ARM's fabrication, roadmap, and fabless concept. There are none of them that can offer any explanation of ARM's price and P/E ratio. Of course, how can you defend an 81 P/E ratio? It's impossible...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367973229716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 20:33:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367975035763-259</Id><Title>Lenovo K900 Goes on Sale in China</Title><Msg>["Lenovo’s crown jewel has everything it takes to be a serious Galaxy S4, HTC One or LG Optimus G Pro contender. Besides the awesome design and the incredible 6.9 mm thickness, the K900 comes with a Full HD IPS screen, an explosive dual-core 2 GHz Atom CPU, Android 4.2 Jelly Bean, a 13 MP camera and 2 GB of RAM"] Well, look who’s getting serious about leaving a mark in the global smartphone world! It’s Lenovo, one of the world’s leading PC vendors, a company that until recently seemed like it couldn’t care less about mobile phones. By far Lenovo’s most exciting handheld for some time to come is going to be the IdeaPhone K900, first unveiled back in January and finally up for grabs in China starting today. The K900 is not just an extremely sexy slab of silicon, with a stunning metal chassis and uber-thin profile, but it’s also the zippiest Intel-powered phone to date, so there’s been a lot of media attention focused on it. Available in “The Middle Kingdom” for 3,299 Yuan ($530), the K900 is expected to roll out on a wider scale beginning next week. Rumor has it the 5.5-incher will look to take the whole Asian continent by storm, but unfortunately there’s no official word on a Western launch yet. Why unfortunately? Simple, because Lenovo’s crown jewel has everything it takes to be a serious Galaxy S4, HTC One or LG Optimus G Pro contender. Besides the awesome design and the incredible 6.9 mm thickness, the K900 comes with a Full HD IPS screen, an explosive dual-core 2 GHz Atom CPU, Android 4.2 Jelly Bean, a 13 MP camera and 2 GB of RAM. The 16 GB of on-board storage might not sound too hot, but there’s microSD support, so this thing still allows you more wiggle room than, say, the HTC One. And what can we say about that (Chinese) price other than it makes for an extremely lucrative all-around deal? thedroidguy</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367975035763</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:03:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367976692904-260</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can name a couple other stocks right now being manipulated to bubble valuations in the same way, 2 which I'm short (as a hedge) are RMBS and LNKD, in addition to ARMH of course. I think these stocks have the most to lose when the music stops and the market corrects. Anybody hating on this post, which gave me a LOL moment, is obviously in need of more fiber in their diet!</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1367976692904</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:31:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367977060841-261</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you were short ARMH since 38.. ouch How is that working for you. not to mention LNKD.</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367977060841</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:37:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367977289881-262</Id><Topic><Title>Barrons: MKM raises target on Intel to $28.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367972083726</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 20:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's a big one, he must see something ;). once it unflods many will join, i wonder who will be the first with above 30$ target..</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367977289881</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367977621835-263</Id><Title>Got ignore situated now, nice!</Title><Msg>Sometimes you have to press ignore a few times to actually get that person ignored. Got things nice and quiet now and I can quickly click on "show post" under those ignored to see if there's anything of value. For instance, I clicked on one and read about the Lenovo K900 and then refreshed the page and that person was back on ignore. Happy investing !</Msg><Username>fourteennanometer</Username><Timestamp>1367977621835</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367979236533-264</Id><Topic><Title>Barrons: Wells Fargo sees PC, Tablet Upside</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367972021151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 20:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Wong sees a big increase in Intel tablet processor share in the coming two years". ------------- Absolutely, Haswell and Bay Trail elevate tablet functionality and utility to a completely new level.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1367979236533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 22:13:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367979527772-265</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm a trader cloud, with the exception of high quality stocks I trade in and out of long and short positions regularly, and I even catch the occasional 10-20% gain on a dip such as with LNKD and RMBS lately, just as with a long position which is not going according to plan, I cut my losses and look for a better entry point. So, to answer your stupid question it is working out great, I'm up in total about 20% YTD and well prepared for any size correction, ok??</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1367979527772</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 22:18:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367981297966-266</Id><Topic><Title>$20.88 no way would I stay short this low</Title><Username>thirty_percent_factor</Username><Timestamp>1362097170427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 19:19:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go Intel. Congrats to all Longs.</Msg><Username>thirty_percent_factor</Username><Timestamp>1367981297966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 22:48:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367981351315-267</Id><Topic><Title>Barrons: MKM raises target on Intel to $28.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367972083726</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 20:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good news</Msg><Username>thirty_percent_factor</Username><Timestamp>1367981351315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 22:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367981431988-268</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I actually made money shorting ARMH from 44 to 40. I covered the 38 short for no loss/gain. I'm down on RMBS for the year, but up overall since I made a huge amount shorting it last year from 9 to 4.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1367981431988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 22:50:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367981721912-269</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm also way up on my LNKD short, dabbled with a small short position earlier this year but quickly covered when I saw that the trade was not going to be profitable. I didn't lose anything. More recently I covered my RMBS short on Thursday before LNKD reported earnings and went short at 202, and again at 185 last Friday. I covered today for a total gain of 8%. Since I didn't lose anything last time, that is a total of 8% up shorting that pig so far this year. I plan to short it again soon.</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1367981721912</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 22:55:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367982092362-270</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeh right. keep telling that to yourself... The fact is I saw your posts om ARMH and also your 24/7 posts on RMBS etc. but don't fret, 99% of any yahoo MB posters are buying at the bottom or shorting at the top, that's magic and you in part of it. lol</Msg><Username>passing.cloud7</Username><Timestamp>1367982092362</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367983537597-271</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Att4glte is that you?? Must be, you seem to have the same disdain for any ARMH trashing plus I haven't posted on the ARMH board in a very long time and I've never seen this alias before. Good to know some things never change!</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1367983537597</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:25:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367983793418-272</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's new Atom chip is 3 times faster than previous one.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367967617297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 19:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome! Now which will earn me the most as a result? My INTC long or ARMH short?</Msg><Username>gregory.lynn</Username><Timestamp>1367983793418</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:29:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367984065887-273</Id><Title>will ARM follow RMBS foot prints?</Title><Msg>maybe Rambus Expands Family of Revolutionary LED-Based Light Bulbs</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1367984065887</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:34:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367985471215-274</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's new Atom chip is 3 times faster than previous one.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1367967617297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 19:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably ARMH short in the long run. ARM isn't worth more than $20/share, so plenty of downside from here. At current prices you can sell inflated ARM currency for nearly $50/share.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367985471215</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:57:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367985517746-275</Id><Topic><Title>Wow, I Still Love Those ARM Investors!!!</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1367954876255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>att4glte is a psychopath.</Msg><Username>ashraf.eassa</Username><Timestamp>1367985517746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 23:58:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>