<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358576022855-1</Id><Topic><Title>Follow up on Intels $2billion capex increase for 450mm</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358569591494</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 23:26:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My take is the wall street weasels don't know jack when it comes to running a multibillion dollar Corp.</Msg><Username>sanjitkumar23</Username><Timestamp>1358576022855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 01:13:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358576576359-2</Id><Title>Wallis.... Re: Intel share repurchase of stock.</Title><Msg>As you know, Intel offerred $6 Billion in debt, most of which will be used for share repurchase. Being that Intel made a pretty good amount of profit for Q4, $3.2 Billion operating income, and that they only used $1 Billion for share repurchase, it looks like Intel has used very little if any of the debt for repurchase so far. So my guess is, Intel could be very aggressive in the current quarter to repurchase shares. Especially now that the stock has dropped over 6% because of negative investor sentiment. What do you think? Could be a good buying opportunity short term at least.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358576576359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 01:22:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358582439269-3</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis.... Re: Intel share repurchase of stock.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358576576359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 01:22:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't really have a good way to #$%$ the re-purchase program but I would assume Intel would be relatively aggressive given the hugely undervalued nature of the stock at this point. But here's what I was thinking. I was thinking about the value of the company verses a year ago. Intel has built this huge state-of-the-art manufacturing capability over the last year. And in spite of having this huge capability the company is actually valued at a much lower level. This is to conclude that all of that manufacturing capability is not just worthless but much less than worthless. Intel made billions in the last year. And invested them wisely. They invested in the future. Yet the market has concluded that those billions added nothing to the value of the company. Intel is so much stronger than they were a year ago. Their mobility roadmap is about to get a lot of traction. They have eliminated the power efficiency gap. And they continue to make huge investments in being even better prepared for the future. And yet the market has concluded that no value will ever come of any of it. Intel is about to become the most competitive they have been in their history. They are strong in every aspect of the processor business. In some areas they are about to open up technology leads that the competition will never regain. And yet the market has concluded that no value will ever come of any of it. Intel invested billions in R&amp;D and continues to do so. And yet the market believes that no value will result from any of the R&amp;D. The market is simply wrong. They are stuck on the "PC is dead" mantra and are unable to get their heads around the fact that Intel has totally re-designed its business for the post-PC era. All because it takes time to develop and put in place state-of-the-art technology. And now that almost all of the heavy lifting is done and Intel is starting to implement the new strategy along with 22 and 14nm production, the market is the most incorrect and the most wrongheaded they have ever been about Intel and its prospects. A blind man could see what is going to happen next. But a man in denial will never see. They have to be slapped upside the head. Repeatedly. But that's okay because Intel is going to slap all of them upside the head. Did they really think Otellini was blowing smoke when he said he thought Intel had already won? No, he simply has more facts at his disposal than the naysayers do. And he knows that the facts will speak for themselves shortly. Intel began the slapping during the earnings call when Paul and Stacy refused to let the ill prepared and wrong thinking analysts perpetuate their myths. 2013 will be the year that Intel's post-PC strategy begins to leave victims in its wake. 2013 may start slow but it will end with a bang that will leave Intel's competitors wondering why they ever thought Intel wasn't one of the most dedicated and competitive companies on the planet. Intel has prepared to resume it's role as the 500 lb gorilla of the technology world. I'd like to say that ARM had better quit running its mouth and get busy on fabrication. But it's too late. Intel has prepared to win. And now they will. ARM doesn't have enough time, money or technology to do anything about it...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358582439269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 03:00:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358582477287-4</Id><Topic><Title>Follow up on Intels $2billion capex increase for 450mm</Title><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358569591494</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 23:26:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the wall street weasels the weasels are drinking their own bath water</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358582477287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 03:01:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358582794418-5</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis.... Re: Intel share repurchase of stock.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358576576359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 01:22:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's hilarious. Yahoo thinks the word "a ess ess e s s" (as in "to evaluate") is a dirty word because it has "a ess ess" in it. Even Microsoft could have improved the message boards better...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358582794418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 03:06:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358585319957-6</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft doesn't rule out Intel-based Windows phones</Title><Username>intelonly_please</Username><Timestamp>1357786101250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 21:48:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>something to think about</Msg><Username>droxytolyn22</Username><Timestamp>1358585319957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 03:48:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358600046968-7</Id><Topic><Title>Alex- your thoughts?</Title><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1358567993508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:59:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shirley, you mean Q4...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1358600046968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:54:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358600182233-8</Id><Topic><Title>Alex- your thoughts?</Title><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1358567993508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:59:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Q1: MWC is the new big show for Intel. It will have an NFC flavor. Intel has acquired a lot of IP in the last two years and it should begin to come together on silicon. I have too much to learn in this area to be much help. The VIX has dropped to 12.46 which is very, very low. When the SEC made naked shorting illegal, even for market makers, I expected that the VIX would stay high since the market makers would have extra borrowing costs to hedge their positions. VIX is closely related to the premium on SPY options. When option premiums are low, you are better to be a buyer than a seller. If you are long options and the VIX goes up, the option premium goes up. Jan2015 $22 are out of the money and the price drop off will be non-linear with Intel share price drop. They are priced at $2.04/$2.08. The non-nickel pricing indicates that there is some activity pressing on both the buy and sell side. I would expec the pricing to be $2.05/$2.10. I don't know what happened to Romit Shah, Covello and all the other Intel negative analysts and their traditional downgrades. They will probably start their echos next week to maximize the damage. With the big drop and low VIX, I would probably take a partial position here (1/4 or 1/3 of your final goal) and another part if it breaches $20 and a final part when it gets to the $19.xx low area. If you have a concern about the analysts piling on, go a little lighter on the buy. The Jan $25 calls give you an idea of what would happen to the Jan$22 pricing if Intel dropped $3 to $19 tomorrow. The Jan 2015 $22 would probably priced like the Jan2015 $25 or $1.14/$1.18 area. This gives you an idea about your downside risk in a given share price range. You have to match the trade with your comfort level, risk tolerance, investment goals. The most important thing is to be able to sleep at night. Last week, I booked some Intel profits so it made Thursday AH and Friday much, much less painful. You might already know but I like to nag. Dividend impact on option pricing. The 2015 series is a place where you can see the pricing impact of the Intel dividend on puts and calls. Your Jan $22 is $2.04 bid and is 80 cents out of the money. The $20 put option is $1.20 out of the money (farther than the call) and is priced at $310. Notice the assymetric pricing. The extra $1 premium on the put option is long term pricing anomoly caused by the option market maker having to price the put higher for dividend arbitraging. Buying calls ties up the amount of cash for the calls. Selling puts ties up the amount of cash to cover the actual shares if they were "put" to you.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358600182233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:56:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358601606269-9</Id><Topic><Title>Intel on Track to Start Making 14nm “Broadwell” Chips in 2013</Title><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358564748944</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:05:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also hawell will be coming out in the first quarter of this year.with only 10 watts of comsumption. The quad core laptop and tablets wll last all day with out a recharge.</Msg><Username>kravcleve</Username><Timestamp>1358601606269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:20:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358601838362-10</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis.... Re: Intel share repurchase of stock.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358576576359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 01:22:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel Investor Relations replied to a question I asked about how they accomplished the Intel share repurchase. He indicated that they contract with a 3rd party and do not do the repurchasing themselves. What you are looking for is the rules limiting open market share repurchases or SEC Rule 10b-18 . "To come within the safe harbor the purchases must satisfy the Rule's manner, timing, price, and volume conditions. Failure to meet any one of the four conditions will disqualify the issuer's purchases from the safe harbor for the day." some of the restrictrions Rule restricts issuers from making repurchases that constitute the opening transaction in the security on a trading day, or that occur during the last 10 minutes before the scheduled close of trading. (10 minutes rather than 30 minute exclusion because Intel share float value is greater than $150mill and trades more than $1mill per day). The purchase price cannot exceed the higher of the highest independent bid or the last independent transaction price. The Rule limits the amount of securities an issuer may repurchase on the market on a single day to 25% of the four-week average daily trading volume in its shares (that is, the average daily trading volume during the four calendar weeks prior to the week in which the 10b-18 purchase is to be made). However, issuers are permitted to make one block purchase of its common stock per week outside of the volume restrictions.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358601838362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:23:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358602326160-11</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis.... Re: Intel share repurchase of stock.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358576576359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 01:22:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was gonna comment on that. It is yahoo that is "a ess ess i nine." You can't post the name of "Richard Bove" using the colloquial "Ddd eye c k " first name on the BAC board. Yahoo=idiots.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358602326160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:32:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358603101709-12</Id><Title>Where is the RAZR I smartphone for the US? #$%$????</Title><Msg>This is my biggest disappointment. FAILURE TO EXECUTE is a very very bad sign. Where oh where is the promised RAZR I??? Where is LTE?? FAILURE TO EXECUTE FAILURE TO EXECUTE FAILURE TO EXECUTE</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358603101709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:45:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358603159616-13</Id><Title>Bought around 21 six quarters ago</Title><Msg>I've cashed 6 Dividend checks and held onto the cash, which makes my average arouund 19.60. At the end of this year, I'll be at 18.60 or so. At the end of next year my average will be around 17.60. Why can't you crazies just do that math, buy as much as you can right here if you indeed love Intel and just turn the frigging perputer off? My guess is that nobody here has the patience or ability to buy here and allow Intel to pay you back your investment over time? Five years from now, my average buying price will be be around 15 or 16. Bet I'm happy at that time!</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1358603159616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:45:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358603528797-14</Id><Topic><Title>Bought around 21 six quarters ago</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1358603159616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:45:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most on here are greedy and broke and the reason they are broke is because they were greedy. lol</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358603528797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:52:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358604684056-15</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the RAZR I smartphone for the US? #$%$????</Title><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358603101709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:45:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is ready with the industry's first single chip 4G/LTE solution (after Qualcomm) and will be launching smartphones for the US market by combining this chip with its latest Atom offerings. Exact dates have not been disclosed but you can expect devices based on the new OOO 22nm Merrifield chip for the holiday season. Mots likely a Motorola follow on to the Razr I.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1358604684056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:11:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358604804284-16</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis.... Re: Intel share repurchase of stock.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358576576359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 01:22:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I take it that the purpose of the rules is to forbid manipulations of the pps for the day. I wonder if JPM, GS and such have similar restrictions .. or do have only their 'analysis' as a manipulation tool? meaning do you think that Intel negative analysts and their traditional downgrades in addition to their analysis have some 'other' entity shorting the stock at the same time they 'open their mouth' or is it suppose to be illegal?</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1358604804284</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:13:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358605460875-17</Id><Topic><Title>Alex- your thoughts?</Title><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1358567993508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:59:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Notice the assymetric pricing. The extra $1 premium on the put option is long term pricing anomoly caused by the option market maker having to price the put higher for dividend arbitraging. " ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- I realize that I don't fully understand the dividend arbitrage thing as my wrong thinking says the calls should have the higher premium since the calls-buyer can exercise them just before the ex-dividend day and profit from getting the divvy etc. But that aside it seems that buying puts have inherent disadvantage since the premium will always be higher due to this asymmetric pricing build into it. (that is regardless or what one thinks of the stock future direction)... am I missing something here?</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1358605460875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:24:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358605758394-18</Id><Topic><Title>Bought around 21 six quarters ago</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1358603159616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:45:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>inside, I think if you used the divvy to be reinvested (in INTC) you might do better. I think some have that feature automatic.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1358605758394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:29:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358606103561-19</Id><Topic><Title>Bought around 21 six quarters ago</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1358603159616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:45:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To much reading into the market will destroy U</Msg><Username>jsf34062</Username><Timestamp>1358606103561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:35:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358606983540-20</Id><Topic><Title>Bought around 21 six quarters ago</Title><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1358603159616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:45:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No need to reinvest. I like knowing my average will go down a dollar (or more) each year and be able to enjoy life at the same time with the money I get from the Dividend. Trips, etc.. .</Msg><Username>intc_inside</Username><Timestamp>1358606983540</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:49:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358607411785-21</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis.... Re: Intel share repurchase of stock.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358576576359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 01:22:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Manipulation as the goal in any form is illegal. 8-) If the goal of some action is to influence the price for profit, it is illegal. The problem is identifying the action and then being able to prove that the action was intended for that purpose. This is very vague generalization (my paraphrase). It is tough to prove and not all levels of manipulation is worth pursuing. It is tough to prove intent. There are some analysts that I believe are involved in overt manipulation. Romit Shah is one whose actions seem consistent with an attempt to maximize the negative impact. Each of the analyst companies that issue research has rules for disclosure on how they release the information and how they and their customers can trade. In July 2011, he lowered Intel to a SELL and target price of $18. Over the next year, he raised the Intel target to $25 in several steps but maintained his SELL rating. How can you raise the target price and keep a SELL rating? His predictable behavior in multiple reiterations with a final downgrade of the target price smelled very bad. BTW, I expect Romit maintain his SELL and lower the price target by $1 next week.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358607411785</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:56:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358608145100-22</Id><Title>A beautiful weekend for Teaparty johnny rebs. The Pres gets signed in for his 2nd term. Intel is fine.</Title><Msg>Intel is closer to the promised land than it was 12 months ago. (Massive growth) Unlike you teabagging rush limbutt listeners, Intel on a fast track to victory. Intel is not crying and predicting victory like your Hannity did. Intel is simply waiting for the good news announcements to come. Cap x spending up from 10 billion to 13 billion should be a good hint for those who are anal ists. yeah--Intel is investing for no reason right? Google Motorola phones Cisco DEAL Apple deal Likely all of them to come later this year and Intel will be looking back toward the 40 area where it flew by. WAHHH WAHHH I want my country back GOP nummmmbbbbskulls are now folding to Obummer on the debt ceiling. HAAA HAAA YEAH--we are drawing the line said they. We will hold on the fiscal cliff--NO On the debt ceiling--NO We will---NO Just shut the pluck up rightwing trashballs.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey7</Username><Timestamp>1358608145100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:09:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358608372813-23</Id><Title>Inturd Reduced from BELLWETHER to SMELLWETHER</Title><Msg>HI-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358608372813</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:12:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358608535928-24</Id><Title>Market viewing Intel Manufacturing as a liability not an asset</Title><Msg>Paul O. made a big PR mistake by saying at the call Manufacturing is Intel's biggest asset. The manufacturing economy is backwards thinking. We are in the digital, knowledge economy. As an Intel engineer/designer, I would be offended by his statement. Intel's business model is being trashed by the market. Paul O has failed to monetize Intel's Fabs. We better hope the new CEO gets it.</Msg><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1358608535928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:15:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358609290799-25</Id><Topic><Title>A beautiful weekend for Teaparty johnny rebs. The Pres gets signed in for his 2nd term. Intel is fine.</Title><Username>amdmonkey7</Username><Timestamp>1358608145100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:09:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Cisco and Apple deals will be huge but the Google-Motorola phone deal later this year which will bring Intel inside the best smart phone on the planet will become the opening for the promised land for Intel. Net profits exploding up will be a shock for the investment community but they will buy Intel and simply say that they always knew Intel would win. They are so full of it. I would trust Lance Armstrong denying drugs more than I trust Wall-street #$%$. By the way--we all knew it so what is the story? Another shocker--Baseball players like Sosa and Bonds used drugs to enhance there performance. Next thing we will be shocked to find that NFL players, not tested for those, are using them. HAAAA HAAA Yeah--we are surprised that football players smashing their heads for years end up brain dead? NO--people simply do not give a sheet. But Intel---Likely the profits this year will be 50% higher than projected and thus the stock explodes much higher. Yes--the republican party is in meltdown. If you think you got your rump kicked by Obummer, wait until a white Lib like Biden runs against you. He is an FDR dem and ready to put hurt on you unless Hillary runs in which case she will win 40 states and turn the GOP into a purely regional party non existent in the Midwest and the NE, and the West coast.</Msg><Username>hothectors</Username><Timestamp>1358609290799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:28:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358609942254-26</Id><Topic><Title>A beautiful weekend for Teaparty johnny rebs. The Pres gets signed in for his 2nd term. Intel is fine.</Title><Username>amdmonkey7</Username><Timestamp>1358608145100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:09:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My, aren't we angry today.</Msg><Username>bobhals</Username><Timestamp>1358609942254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:39:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610103918-27</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis.... Re: Intel share repurchase of stock.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358576576359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 01:22:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said: "No, he simply has more facts at his disposal than the naysayers do." And because of this, I have seen over the last 5 years, sell side analysts being very wrong many times over. It took a little time for Intel to take full advantage of its High K metal gate lead. But once they did, they reaped benefits that exceeded the expectations of the most positive analysts. So if Intel thinks it's important to invest $3 Billion more in capex for 2013 than what analysts expected, then I'm sure Intel knows enough to be doing the right thing. That there is a huge line of customers very eager to use their porducts. Especially in the smartphone area.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358610103918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:41:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358610171078-28</Id><Title>Next week's trade strategy</Title><Msg>Because Ex dividend date is on February 5th (someone please confirm), I think the analysts intentional exaggerated their reactions to the extra $2 billion in CAPex for 2013 and very old news about the PC business slowing due to IPads and other Tablets'. Obviously, the plan worked well on Friday and phase 2 will be as followed: They will scope up some oversold shares of INTC on Tuesday with monstrous catalysts provided by MSFT, APPL and other major companies that will push the whole market higher. With that said, I have no doubt that the S&amp;P will hit 1,500! As soon as they got their cheap shares and dividends, they will downgrade the stock on or after ex- dividend date. With that said, the buyng spree already started after hours on Friday and will continue to go up next week. In our current market environment: to make real money, it's not what you know, it's who you know. Good luck and feel free to leave your insights. Disclosure: I don't claim to be a licensed trader. Do your own DD and you will make money.</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1358610171078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:42:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610414700-29</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis.... Re: Intel share repurchase of stock.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358576576359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 01:22:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I noticed that too, how he raised his estimates and price target from $18 to $25 without changing his Sell rating at all. And not once did he state that his call was very wrong. The $18 price target is a 12 month price target. And for the stock to reach $25 within the next 12 months, obviously the Sell rating was a terrible call. He is obviously biased in that he wants the stock to drop.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358610414700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:46:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610777390-30</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis.... Re: Intel share repurchase of stock.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358576576359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 01:22:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I added to my shares as well. I actually leveraged some of my shares by selling them and buying 2015 calls. The premium seems to be pretty cheap for a 2 year period. So now I have some cash on hand to purchase more Intel shares, or even 2015 calls if the stock drops for stupid reasons like "they are spending too much on capex". I did buy some at the sudden 7% drop on Friday, and am looking to add more strategically. As for the calls, I chose 2015, because they will have a full year of LTE smartphone chip availability. In the meantime, they have a great innovative phone by Lenovo that uses their chip for China market. So in summary, given all the recent data, this seems to be a great buying opportunity for Intel stock.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358610777390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:52:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358611111307-31</Id><Topic><Title>Market viewing Intel Manufacturing as a liability not an asset</Title><Username>backbay_bstn</Username><Timestamp>1358608535928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:15:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm wondering if getting a CEO that has engineering background will help the perception on Intel by large investors. Even though Ottelini has done some great things with Intel, the investors have not raised the stock level above the $30 mark at all during his term as CEO. Maybe he knew this. Which is why he may have decided to allow a new CEO to take his place. I agree that it should be someone from within. Hopefully it's one with an engineering background since we already have a financial person in the CFO spot.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358611111307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:58:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358611296879-32</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis.... Re: Intel share repurchase of stock.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358576576359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 01:22:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good thoughts, money is cheap, even if inflation goes over 2% (which I believe in 2 or 3 years it will) a good investment now in a solid company with future growth (whether organic or otherwise) is wise. The old money families have always said buy when there is blood in the street and sell when they are paved in gold. The best thing you can do is bet against analysts, they mainly project for short time frames, and their jobs are to find garbage on companies, real or imagined. The are like professors at Universities who have to publish. They have to publish and for the most part most of it is #$%$, but they get paid to do it. If the world stops using chips (of any kind) tomorrow, I'd short Intel, I'm pretty sure that's not going to happen. Cheers, good investing!!</Msg><Username>albacornus</Username><Timestamp>1358611296879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:01:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358611703837-33</Id><Title>Not all asshhhhhoooles are Republicans, but all Republicans are asshhhhholes.</Title><Msg>simple truth</Msg><Username>amdsuckks</Username><Timestamp>1358611703837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:08:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358612964152-34</Id><Topic><Title>Alex- your thoughts?</Title><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1358567993508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:59:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you have it down accurately. For me, buying a call is similar to selling a put. In both cases the direction of the shares is toward me. Bullish: buy calls or sell puts Bearish: sell calls or buy puts.</Msg><Username>alexander.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1358612964152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:29:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358613781872-35</Id><Title>Intc</Title><Msg>Apparently the current Executives at INTC have not read the Harvard Business Professor's books on why large companies fail. Seems strange since the Professor was once a consultant at INTC. Per the Quarter Transcript these poor Executives are in total denial. Their world has changed before their very eyes, but they are still pursuing their compression strategy of the past 30 years--HELLO--Anybody Home? Gadgets have become throwaways--their economic life lasts as long as the next upgrade. The chip companies that are doing well only have to produce "just good enough" chips that are relatively low cost. The era of purchasing a computer for three or four years is history. Very few are looking for leading edge chips. Inexpensive and "good enough" is the new mantra. In the age of App Pages, the idea you spend huge amounts of R&amp;D and Capex on plants and equipment to run various versions of Windows is really out of touch with reality. The Current and former CEO have spent tens of billions over the past 12 years pursuing a dead end strategy. Hopefully a new CEO will be somebody with a "vision" that includes a understanding of why large companies fail and how to avoid that fate!</Msg><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358614610961-36</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pretty blog you wrote up there............but it's all trash. Intel isn't even in mobile yet and booked another 50 Billion + last year and 12 billion profit.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358614610961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:56:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358615438370-37</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh and ask AMD shareholders what they think about your blog or go ask all the technical people that spent countless hours getting ARM RT ready for market how they feel about "just good enough".</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358615438370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:10:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358615578949-38</Id><Title>If the "Death of the PC" is here...</Title><Msg>then why is it that we see alot more desktop and laptop offerrings that we do with tablets? Why is it that the success of laptop and desktop selling companies is more widespread than it is for tablets? For example, the only known success for tablets is the ipad. Nobody else seems to be successful in this area at this time. The reason could be that the tablet is such a simple form factor and so limitted in capabilities, that most consumers see the ipad as the only choice. And after purchasing one, they see that it is mostly useful as a complimentary computing device. Is the kindle successful? Maybe Amazon thinks so, but the sales of less than a million a quarter are only possible through a huge money losing discount. The facts are that over 80 million desktops/laptops/ultrabooks are still sold per quarter. That doesn't sound like the PC is dying to me. It only sounds like it is doing slightly worse than its huge selling year of 2011. Relative to 2011 it may look slightly weak but relative to the year when the ipad was first introduced, the PC sales are clearly higher today. And the lines between laptops and tablets are already starting to blur with the innovation of Intel and its partners.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358615578949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:12:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358616073226-39</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis.... Re: Intel share repurchase of stock.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358576576359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 01:22:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, we know that Goldman Sachs trading against customers is considered just another day at the office. It seems doubtful that the ethics of the other big firms are much different. We have extremely substantial proof that the big firms consistently deal in unethical behavior and far too often engage in illegal behavior. In other words, there just isn't much they won't do to make a buck. Since they are so powerful, they tend to just change the rules to encompass their manipulative activities. They don't want a level playing field. They want to be able to use their money, leverage and visibility to transfer wealth from the average investor into their pockets. In recent years they have shown an alarming preference for manipulation over simply making money the old-fashioned way by working for it. High speed trading is just one way they attempted to game the system...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358616073226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:21:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358616364629-40</Id><Topic><Title>If the "Death of the PC" is here...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358615578949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:12:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Millions and Millions of people will be hoping their current laptop dies as soon as we get 8-13+ hours of battery life.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358616364629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:26:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358616480692-41</Id><Topic><Title>A beautiful weekend for Teaparty johnny rebs. The Pres gets signed in for his 2nd term. Intel is fine.</Title><Username>amdmonkey7</Username><Timestamp>1358608145100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:09:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"NRA membership is exploding." [As are deaths from guns. The NRA is nuttier than a dozen fruitcakes. Only the NRA thinks cop-killing bullets should be readily available at all stores next to the gum. Just another case of extremists taking control and throwing out all common sense whatsoever. I expect the NRA to recommend next that 5-year olds should pack heat...]</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358616480692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:28:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358616523553-42</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gadgets have become throwaways--their economic life lasts as long as the next upgrade ___________________________ Thats why I'm so excited about Intel's future........People don't hold onto their phones for a long time, yet the demand for phones will NEVER go away which means Intel will eventually be sellling millions and millions of mobile chips every year as long as you and I are on this earth.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358616523553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:28:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358616574554-43</Id><Topic><Title>If the "Death of the PC" is here...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358615578949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:12:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have the seeds here of an interesting analysis. The tablets/smartphones ecoverse isn't a big enough or overlapping enough entity to be cannibalizing PC/desktops. Tablets are lightweight recreational devices. Smartphones are too small for the human fingers or eyeballs if your'e past age 50--mainly they're for teenies or the techni-challenged set. If you are a worker bee, or serious about anything, ie, a grownup, it's a PC or desktop for you. Just had this discussion at Panera...no one seriously writes/composes/computes/designs/photoshops/etc/etc on a Tablet. Kindle has a great "parchment" format, is really cheap, and font size adjustable for aging eyeballs... take mine everywhere....but so too the PC...try to download a book onto a Kindle in Japan...you have to go thru your PC in the hotel wifi and then USB it onto Kindle. Kindlefire is too much bucks for too little of anything, and the color is worse for the eyeballs than el-cheapo kindle. So, your point is---the PC and Desktop "recession" is really an indicator of the economy. Touche! Of course, none of the idiot-rotten-scoundrel-Vomit-Covello-ANALysts can figure that one out. To my mind much of it is just that, and last 6 months there was a real slowdown in China. And whenever our southern GOP terrorists start acting up, the US economy seizes up.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358616574554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:29:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358616968469-44</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ummmm...all I can say to that is ....duhhhhh. What on earth do you think the excess CAPEX spending is all about?? duhhhhhh. I'll spell it out: get the margins on mobile chips as BIG AS POSSIBLE by going to the unprecedented 450 mm wafer.... Does your Harvard Business Professor recommend NOT making margins go up? And #$%$ does this have to with your notion of fossil CEO's who aren't addressing the future? If I were you, I'd take your simpleton argument over to Taiwan Semi and ARMH and ask them if they've notived that 14nm and 10nm are about to arrive and, gee, maybe their world is about to change? And when you go, I hope the door slams your A ess ess so hard it bleeds.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358616968469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:36:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358617006759-45</Id><Topic><Title>Wallis.... Re: Intel share repurchase of stock.</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358576576359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 01:22:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those who build capacity during tough times look like geniuses later. This will clearly be the case with Intel. When they have six factories cranking out the 14nm product, no one is going to be able to question their wisdom and foresight. When they get to 450mm years before everyone else and their economics jump substantially ahead of the rest of the industry, no one is going to be able to question their wisdom and foresight. Bear Bryant once said, "It's not the will to win that's important. It's the will to prepare to win." Intel has the will to prepare to win. Intel's CapEx reflects this and it's just smart business. Intel has a totally revamped post-PC business plan and the will to prepare to win. In the meantime, ARM by its failure to maintain its competitiveness in fabrication has opened the door wide to failure...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358617006759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:36:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358617165729-46</Id><Topic><Title>Next week's trade strategy</Title><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1358610171078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:42:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree 100%. Just after ex date there will be some carefully crafted negative article about Intel planted somewhere high profile causing the stock to take a turn for the worse. Once it reaches down back into the 20's, analysts will upgrade, etc. People making a ton of money manipulating. SEC turns a blind eye (Nuff, your attempts have no effect. You're #$%$ in the wind. Even though you dream that you're some big time player).</Msg><Username>jerry.blown</Username><Timestamp>1358617165729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:39:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358617397842-47</Id><Topic><Title>If the "Death of the PC" is here...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358615578949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:12:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are over 500 million PC users now that have their units over 4 years old. Those have Core 2 duo processors with 45nm or 65nm chips. The batteries could be draining very fast. For one, the batteries have less capability of fully charging and maintaining the charge as a new one will. The life could be as little as 15 to 30 minutes. With the new ones offerring battery life of over 4 hours to 14 hours, many will upgrade with this fact alone as you stated. And this is not counting the emergin markets that could add to this number. As for the tablet, how will IDC or Gartner count the ultrabook hybrids as? This form factor will have a tablet built in. So with Intel offerring many chips that could easily be used in tablets and hybrids, the analysts have to group together the form factors of computing as non smartphone computing devices. Unless they decide to define a tablet as a consumption device that operates by apps alone. If that's the case, tablets sales will drop significantly as the all in one ultrabooks will have tablet capabilities built in for only a few hundred dollars more than a laptop yet very competitive in price to a quality or popular tablet such as the iPad.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358617397842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:43:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358617729379-48</Id><Title>What We Know Now</Title><Msg>1.) Intel has recognized that mobility is the major growth area and has total re-organized priorities to address this. They have changed the timetables for all mobile strategies and moved them to the top. It's amazing the so many Wall Street types think that Intel does not have a new post-PC business plan. Even more amazing that they think it's not working. There's plenty of evidence that it is. 2.) Intel will pass ARM in power efficiency in 2013. This is just some of the evidence that Intel's post-PC business plan is getting significant traction. 3.) The companies that went with Intel early on in smartphones and mobility will look like geniuses by the end of 2013. This early adoption is going to put them in the catbird seat for superior performance and power consumption efficiency that ARM will not be able to match. 4.) ARMs fabrication is substantially inferior. Two to three years til 20nm volume production. And then after that - nothing. They are looking at at least 4 years to develop 14nm. This will give Intel three years of having their way with the market with their 14nm production. And they will have a lot of it. 5.) In four years Intel will be doing volume production on 10nm and getting 7nm ready. No company that has to be on or even near the cutting edge of technology will be able to rely on ARMs fading fabrication. 6.) The ARM roadmap after 20nm is a looming void. They will likely have to do EUV and maybe even 450mm at the same time. It took TSCM a year to get 28nm yields just up to an acceptable level. Intel ramped 22nm smoothly and rapidly and will do the same with 14nm. They are already producing product. Expect all these things to prevent TSMC from reaching volume production on 14nm for years. It's so far out in the future with so many massively complex issues for them to solve that it's impossible to predict when it might happen. When it does, Intel will be at least 2 product cycles ahead. Intel is going to own mobility and that's because of its advanced fabrication and manufacturing. 7.) Otellini has commented on Intel coming in to a "golden age". He’s talking about Intel’s significant technology edge. He knows ARM can't keep up with Intel's fabrication cycles and that will determine how mobility will play out. 8.) It's not about talking smack as ARM CEO Warren East is fond of doing. He can talk all he wants. It won't do a thing to diminish Intel's rapidly growing advantage in fabrication. Intel's efforts have gone exactly where they needed to go. Years of preparation are coming to fruition. 9.) Intel will have huge 22nm capacity and then huge 14nm capacity. No one will want 28nm ARM processors, given a choice. As it becomes more and more obvious that Intel will stay on the cutting edge as ARMs fabrication fades, there will be much more of an incentive to switch. We are in the midst of that change where it is becoming obvious. 14nm will be available this year. That means discussions and planning are taking place right now for those who want to be on the cutting edge and then on a direct path to 14, then to 10, then to 7 and then to 5nm. 10.) It's possible that Intel will soon be the only major IDM (integrated device manufacturer) left in the world. As processors become more complex this is more and more important. The ARM fabless model is essentially broken because it doesn't have the tight integration of design and manufacturing that is required to have a successful experience with today's state-of-the-art processors and fabrication. 12.) Let us not forget the economics. Each new processor cycle brings improved economics. But this is only true for Intel and not for the ARM foundries. This is something that ARM would very much like to prevent becoming common knowledge. This is why Intel keeps telling us it is necessary for them to continue the every eight quarter pace. Those that can't keep up (the entire ARM world) will have lesser economics, worse margins and problems with cash flow. The trend in the area is clear and ARM is powerless to do anything about it. They don't have the time, money or technology to stay competitive in fabrication.</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358617729379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:48:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358618307000-49</Id><Topic><Title>If the "Death of the PC" is here...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358615578949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:12:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "death of the PC" is humorous. The creative types I know require graphics cards that are 10 inches long and require 1200 watt power supplies just to edit their videos. Some of the folks use two or three of these $500 graphics cards in the same desktop or workstation. This level of performance isn't available in a laptop and certainly not a tablet. Video has become an essential part of the web for businesses and consumers and the demand for more horsepower and larger capacity storage will only grow as more content is created and video resolutions increase across consumer and professional cameras. The desktop serves a specific role that will not be easily replaced by currently envisioned portable and mobile products.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1358618307000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:58:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358618394140-50</Id><Topic><Title>If the "Death of the PC" is here...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358615578949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:12:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 puts Intel fully into the tablet market. I'm really looking forward to being able to buy a fully capable Windows 8 tablet with PC-like performance. And I think a lot of other people are as well. I think a consistent OS across devices is a big pull. Certainly in the enterprise world it is...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358618394140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:59:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358618749803-51</Id><Topic><Title>If the "Death of the PC" is here...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358615578949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:12:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you want to watch BluRay quality video from the internet, which is becoming more and more common, you also need a pretty robust sound card in order to avoid audio degradation. You're not going to get that in any laptop or tablet either. Of course, there are those like khitchykook who are totally and completely satisfied with tinny sound and the ability to play solitaire and think everyone else should be as well. We just don't need performance anymore. Right, kook?</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358618749803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:05:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358618882819-52</Id><Title>Lenovo Chromebook - another great revenue stream for Intel</Title><Msg>Lenovo’s Latest Laptop Isn’t Running Windows 8 — It’s a Chromebook January 17, 2013 at 8:28 am PT In a tiny sidestep from its recent spate of Windows 8 convertible laptops, Chinese PC maker Lenovo has introduced a new Google Chromebook aimed at the education market. The ThinkPad X131e, which has already been sold to schools as a Windows-based laptop, is now running the Google Chrome OS, and supports Google Apps designed for education. X131e Chromebook Lenovo’s announcement is light on specifics. I’m willing to bet some K-12 kids know their processors in this day and age, but for now, Lenovo is simply stating that the 11.6-inch Chromebook has an “Intel processor,” along with an anti-glare LED screen, USB and HDMI ports. It weighs “under four pounds.” The $429 ThinkPad X131e isn’t being sold directly to consumers, but will be sold at volume pricing to K-12 education institutions. It will be available Feb. 26. Since the launch of Chromebooks, Google has extolled the benefits of the lightweight, low-cost laptops in classrooms. For Lenovo, which has a long-standing relationship with the Microsoft Windows OS, it’s an interesting move. It’s not a giant leap into the Chromebook market, by any means, but Lenovo is certainly dipping its toe into new territory with the Chromebook OS for the X131e shell.</Msg><Username>smokinghotblitch</Username><Timestamp>1358618882819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:08:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358619209357-53</Id><Topic><Title>If the "Death of the PC" is here...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358615578949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:12:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2: The Auzentech HTHD, ASUS HDAV 1.3, and Creative Titanium HD are all capable of streaming BD audio formats over HDMI, and should be capable of converting to multichannel analog without needing an outside program to handle the decoding.* Any soundcard can stream BD audio over analog if its decoded by another program [Windows Media Player, etc] first, and basic Dolby/DTS formats can always be sent over SPDIF connections. From Tom's Hardware forum. The information is a bit old. Prolly some new cards available now. I have an Auzentech in my home system. Good sound. Highly recommended if you have a home sound system to channel it into and a decent 1080 display...</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358619209357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:13:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358619268686-54</Id><Topic><Title>If the "Death of the PC" is here...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358615578949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:12:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More likely in the future (after first PAD burst cools down), tablet is just ONE of the computing devices, much less important than laptops/desktops, while some mixed and convertable models will come too. Intel, with its strong R&amp;D resources and budget will fill the gaps sooner than later. The dynamic impact due to PAD will stabalize in 1~2 years, the winners will be the one who have fundamental technologies an consistent investment. If this predictoin is true, current drop of INTC created good investment opportunties for long term investors, and believers.</Msg><Username>gli4213</Username><Timestamp>1358619268686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:14:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358619364361-55</Id><Topic><Title>If the "Death of the PC" is here...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358615578949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:12:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Longer battery life is just another reason for PC replacement, not neccsarily change to use PADs. It is good for Intel, not bad.</Msg><Username>gli4213</Username><Timestamp>1358619364361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:16:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358619642174-56</Id><Topic><Title>If the "Death of the PC" is here...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358615578949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:12:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You did not mention big screen TV in home users. Digital TV will interact with other devices, and this ill be a next big thing for computing technolgies. Even Apple may has to use Intel chips in their TV products.</Msg><Username>gli4213</Username><Timestamp>1358619642174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:20:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358619832500-57</Id><Topic><Title>If the "Death of the PC" is here...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358615578949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:12:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Auzen X-Fi HomeTheater HD outputs a bitstream of high-definition, multichannel audio from Blu-ray Discs with no downsampling, to take full advantage of lossless digital audio formats such as Dolby TrueHD and DTS-HD Master Audio when combined with Cyberlink PowerDVD (available separately). Developed in partnership with Creative, Cyberlink and Silicon Image, the X-Fi HomeTheater HD has broad support for the latest audio technologies in the marketplace. *** ASUS Xonar HDAV1.3 Slim 24-bit 192KHz PCI Interface Audio Card with True Blu-ray Audio Designed to Fit All Home Theater PCs</Msg><Username>wallisweaver</Username><Timestamp>1358619832500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:23:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358620622665-58</Id><Topic><Title>Next week's trade strategy</Title><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1358610171078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:42:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why do you think AAPL,MSFT will push market higher? their market performance suggest otherwise imo</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1358620622665</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:37:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358621368693-59</Id><Topic><Title>Next week's trade strategy</Title><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1358610171078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:42:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$23 calls for .04 where a steal easy 4 bagger .20-.30 next week as $22.50's are hit..... Dividend date will help.</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1358621368693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:49:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358623266061-60</Id><Topic><Title>A beautiful weekend for Teaparty johnny rebs. The Pres gets signed in for his 2nd term. Intel is fine.</Title><Username>amdmonkey7</Username><Timestamp>1358608145100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:09:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since when did you on the right care about education? You voted for Bush. If Obummer is so stupid, why is it he just made the GOP in the House fold two times now. They folded on the fiscal cliff and now they are folding on the Debt ceiling. After that they will fold on the cuts. Surrender monkeys and you vote for them.</Msg><Username>amdmonkey7</Username><Timestamp>1358623266061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:21:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358623551274-61</Id><Topic><Title>A beautiful weekend for Teaparty johnny rebs. The Pres gets signed in for his 2nd term. Intel is fine.</Title><Username>amdmonkey7</Username><Timestamp>1358608145100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:09:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's angry every single day. He's the poster boy for all Liberals: Full of arrogance, false pride, hate, etc...I think it's because he's so gay and emotional.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358623551274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:25:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358623755114-62</Id><Topic><Title>A beautiful weekend for Teaparty johnny rebs. The Pres gets signed in for his 2nd term. Intel is fine.</Title><Username>amdmonkey7</Username><Timestamp>1358608145100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:09:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he's not a sane guy like your good buddy, Alex Jones.... Are all your friends to the right of Adolph himself?</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358623755114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:29:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358624030530-63</Id><Title>17 Trillion in debt and Lady Gaga set to sing for Obama and Michelle tomorrow</Title><Msg>ONLY in America would you see such a freek show. The rest of the world is shaking their heads at how we've ruined such a beautiful country.</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358624030530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:33:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358624429736-64</Id><Title>Same song, tenth verse?</Title><Msg>During Thursday's CC, the first question was by the Deutsche Bank analyst who asked when, after all the cap-ex over the past several years, can we expect returns to shareholders on those investments to be coming? Otellini talked about "line of sight", completely dodged the question, and the analyst did not follow up. I have the same question. Management has talked a good game for at least the past ten years, but the fact remains that you could have bought Intel shares at anytime over the past ten years for the price it is selling at today. I am a long-term holder and enjoy the dividend, but also wonder when these company investments will begin to pay off in terms of share price. Even on this message board, the longs with anything substantive to say talk about all of the great things Intel is doing, and how they are (or will be) killing the competition, but also seem to have taken on the "wait till next year" attitude. Has Intel become nothing more than a trading vehicle? Is its future one of just hanging in there with a good dividend and share buy-back program to keep the stock price afloat?</Msg><Username>jceandthegirls</Username><Timestamp>1358624429736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:40:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358624699116-65</Id><Topic><Title>A beautiful weekend for Teaparty johnny rebs. The Pres gets signed in for his 2nd term. Intel is fine.</Title><Username>amdmonkey7</Username><Timestamp>1358608145100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:09:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"NRA membership is exploding." That would be GREAT!!! All NRA members hold hands and ..... 3, 2, 1 ....... pull the PINS ..... boom!!!!!! Membership fact source is the ..... NRA .... repeated by the conservative entertainment complex. Must be true. TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYY</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1358624699116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:44:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358624839665-66</Id><Title>Intel's Fabrication is KILLING ARM...........</Title><Msg>yet ARM has doubled in price in just the past year while Intel has gone nowhere in 10 years and still doesn't have a phone? Laughable! Has Wally "fleeced" YOU?</Msg><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1358624839665</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:47:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358624904097-67</Id><Title>INTEEN COMING TO A COMPUTER SCREEN NEAR YOU SOON!</Title><Msg>LOOK OUT BELOW! IT'S TEEN TIME AGAIN! HI-HO WEAVERINO!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358624904097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:48:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358625069688-68</Id><Topic><Title>17 Trillion in debt and Lady Gaga set to sing for Obama and Michelle tomorrow</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358624030530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:33:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The real freak show happens in Boehner's House of Pan Flakes. 4 years and they are still looking for a way to blame someone else for the disaster that Bush and Boehner's House of Pan Flakes inflicted upon the USA. Terminal denial ... TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYY</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1358625069688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:51:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358625177255-69</Id><Topic><Title>INTEEN COMING TO A COMPUTER SCREEN NEAR YOU SOON!</Title><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358624904097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:48:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BYE, BYE ..... hope your parachute opens. TOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYYY is TOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYYY is TOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYYY is TOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYYY is TOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYYY is TOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYYY is ....</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1358625177255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:52:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358625330075-70</Id><Topic><Title>Intel's Fabrication is KILLING ARM...........</Title><Username>ghostupinhere</Username><Timestamp>1358624839665</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:47:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC profits UP in latest quarter. TSMC revenues FLAT ARM will be the last domino to fall. Their customers still have to pay them something even if they ship no product.... TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYYY</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1358625330075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:55:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358625446457-71</Id><Topic><Title>17 Trillion in debt and Lady Gaga set to sing for Obama and Michelle tomorrow</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358624030530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:33:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The real freak show is on this message board where Wallis cheerleads and talks to his aliases 24x7 in an lame effort to resuscitate a dead stock . HI-HO WEAVERINO!!!</Msg><Username>tooofunnny</Username><Timestamp>1358625446457</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:57:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358625879320-72</Id><Topic><Title>intc don't care about the stock price</Title><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1358556679001</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 19:51:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Longs who held over earnings gave up over a years worth of dividends in one fell swoop, Poor Waldo, too dumb to sell INTC when, once again, it hit overbght, 6.20 below the height of bubble 29.20 top.</Msg><Username>wdblawgrow</Username><Timestamp>1358625879320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:04:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358627910866-73</Id><Topic><Title>intc don't care about the stock price</Title><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1358556679001</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 19:51:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC is a good buy at $19.00 or lower, it's just not a buy for me here with the markets so high and talk of a 20% correction. The Fiscal Cliff it in the winds again - too much negativity. Even the guys on Fast Money are mostly in cash here. I can wait.</Msg><Username>iroc88joe1234</Username><Timestamp>1358627910866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:38:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358628345549-74</Id><Topic><Title>A beautiful weekend for Teaparty johnny rebs. The Pres gets signed in for his 2nd term. Intel is fine.</Title><Username>amdmonkey7</Username><Timestamp>1358608145100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:09:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know, if Goldman Sachs isn't bad enough, Net'n'yahoo really makes your people look bad. Just back from Miami where a 30-something bejewelled j-princess on the beach was #$%$ so loud about her drink, the service, her Hilton accomodations, this and that, she's lucky the collective will of the people didn't run her out to shark bait, or worse, back to Queens. GFYS</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358628345549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:45:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358629214405-75</Id><Topic><Title>17 Trillion in debt and Lady Gaga set to sing for Obama and Michelle tomorrow</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358624030530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:33:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've ruined America, what are you a Bushie?</Msg><Username>tfhddg</Username><Timestamp>1358629214405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:00:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358629270772-76</Id><Topic><Title>17 Trillion in debt and Lady Gaga set to sing for Obama and Michelle tomorrow</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358624030530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:33:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He said he ruined America so that means he must be a Bushie.</Msg><Username>tfhddg</Username><Timestamp>1358629270772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:01:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358629386365-77</Id><Topic><Title>17 Trillion in debt and Lady Gaga set to sing for Obama and Michelle tomorrow</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358624030530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:33:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Meantime, America is sitting on top of $240 trillion in oil, coal and nat. gas....all owned by the Koch Brothers. GFYS</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358629386365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:03:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358629753635-78</Id><Title>Intel Demonstrates Industry’s First Fully Patterned 450mm Wafer: Photos</Title><Msg>tinyurlDOTcom/9wvrpz5 450mm Fab details ... tinyurlDOTcom/adu92kv</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358629753635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:09:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358630089531-79</Id><Topic><Title>Haswell to be Released on June 2, 2013</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1356706673533</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 09:57:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tinyurlDOTcom/brdgvej Intel Corp. has decided to delay the official introduction of its next-generation code-named Haswell chips from April to late May – early June, new documents by the chip giant that emerged on the web reveal. While Core i-family 4000-series central processing units will become available later than expected, the company will introduce a broader range of chips for different mobile market segments. The world’s largest manufacturer of microprocessors will introduce Core i 4000 “Haswell” products for desktop and mobile applications between May 27 and June 7, 2013, according to excerpts from documents (which presumably originate from Intel) that were published by VR-Zone web-site on Friday. The exact introduction date is still to be determined, but Intel strongly advices its partners not to sell, ship or advertise the new products until June 2, 2013. While the launch of highly-expected code-named Haswell products will occur later than originally expected, the amount of chips for notebooks that will be made available will be higher. Originally, Intel planned to launch only three premium mobile products powered by Haswell architecture; according to the new plan, that number grows to seven, thanks to models Core i7-4702MQ, Core i7-4702HQ, Core i7-4700MQ and Core i7-4700HQ. The desktop lineup will be as broad as expected earlier this month. The actual reasons for the delay are unclear, but sources with knowledge of the talks between Intel and its partners among computer makers indicate that the latter had asked the former to postpone the roll-out of Haswell by several weeks to let them sell current-generation Core i 3000 “Ivy Bridge” chips. Another reason why Intel might be interested in the delay of formal launch of Haswell is that Computex Taipei 2013 trade-show takes place in early June and at that exhibition numerous designs with new chips will be shown to the public. The launch aligned with actual PC makers is going to allow Intel to demonstrate not only performance, but also form-factor, usability, design, feature-set and other benefits that Haswell has to offer in a short period of time, something that will likely attract attention of typical end-users to Haswell and products on its base.</Msg><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358630089531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:14:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358630836591-80</Id><Topic><Title>intc don't care about the stock price</Title><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1358556679001</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 19:51:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>exactly. that's what intel did a few months ago</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1358630836591</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:27:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358631374070-81</Id><Topic><Title>Same song, tenth verse?</Title><Username>jceandthegirls</Username><Timestamp>1358624429736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:40:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fundamentals on INTC are much better than they were a decade ago. Stock price? Ask the (people) who control and manipulate this market and the drunks at the SEC. When you're real big it's hard to grow. It's also easy to fall down. All this yak about mobile, and if INTC owned all of it , it would only amount to 10% of their current revenue. The question is, what are the possible overall growth catalysts open to INTC? The server industry is supposed to quadruple in 10 years. At 25% of INTC revenue that would imply a naive double in revenue, but I'm not so sure I see how the margins will be there to double earnings. Overall internet of everything will grow, tablets will grow, smartphones will grow, and INTC will grow into these markets. So too, PC's and Desktops will find a way to grow, in blended form factor mode. So, I would bet on a firm factor of 43 or more in revenues and factor of 2 or more in earnings growth over the next decade. Conservatively. That means divvy will double (which is consistent with current rate). Stock price? Ask the people who control and manipulate this market and the drunks at the SEC.</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358631374070</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:36:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358631433723-82</Id><Topic><Title>Same song, tenth verse?</Title><Username>jceandthegirls</Username><Timestamp>1358624429736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:40:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>typo: So, I would bet on a firm factor of 3 or more in revenues</Msg><Username>galba_imperator</Username><Timestamp>1358631433723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:37:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358632596160-83</Id><Topic><Title>Same song, tenth verse?</Title><Username>jceandthegirls</Username><Timestamp>1358624429736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:40:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bought more yesterday, and will keep buying on the dips</Msg><Username>gotburned26</Username><Timestamp>1358632596160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:56:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358632612376-84</Id><Topic><Title>17 Trillion in debt and Lady Gaga set to sing for Obama and Michelle tomorrow</Title><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1358624030530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:33:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The real freak show is on this message board where Lucy makes noise and talks to his aliases 24x7 in an lame effort to stick his nose in Wallis's "business". Whew!!! Talk about 130db of noise!!! Ear pain for all!!! thats ..... TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYYY FI-FO FUNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNYYYREENO</Msg><Username>aholewad</Username><Timestamp>1358632612376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:56:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358636334396-85</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel sees the changing landscape, but there is little they can do about it in the near term. They are a chip company, and semiconductors are becoming commodities. The move to 450nm will help, but its gonna take a while.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358636334396</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:58:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358638853794-86</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel had 12 Billion in profits and CEO is being replaced by new blood who contributed a lot to Intel's bottom line. His only misjudgment, imo, is buying MacCafee, yet profitable, instead of buying ARMH.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1358638853794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:40:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358640156679-87</Id><Title>semiaccurate gaming on intel's atom z2670</Title><Msg>google: semiaccurate gaming on intel's atom z2670</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358640156679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:02:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358640322151-88</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel is taking a risk in building additional high end chip fabrication capacity in anticipation of demand for its chips in tablets and smartphones. As of today, this demand is zero, and as you correctly point out, Intel faces cut-throat competition in this space from well established players. Therefore, its unclear whether demand for Intel chips in tablets and smartphones will ever become significant. If it doesn't, their fabs will idle. I think this is the scenario the street fears most.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1358640322151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:05:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358640653886-89</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the additional high end chip fabrication capacity is for current and future demand. Your assumptions don't hold water nor would have any idea what the street 'fears' or nor. you just pull things our of your b@@</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1358640653886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:10:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358644083790-90</Id><Topic><Title>semiaccurate gaming on intel's atom z2670</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358640156679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:02:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is pathetic. I wonder if INTC will ever deliver quality gaming graphics drivers? But on the flipside, is there even a tablet out there that you can play Crysis on? I feel sorry for the masses getting sucked into the tablet craze. On second thought, I don't.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1358644083790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:08:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358644317156-91</Id><Topic><Title>Alex- your thoughts?</Title><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1358567993508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:59:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would never buy OTM/ATM calls, even Leaps, to go long. Far better to go with deep ITM calls say 18 or even safer 15 stike.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1358644317156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:11:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358644624312-92</Id><Title>If Intel's growth was more evenly distributed...</Title><Msg>their current numbers would have looked very healthy regarding PC growth. Going back to the 3rd quarter of 2009, when Intel's revenues were a solid $9.4 Billion for that time. Much higher than any of the expectations by analysts. If Intel grew seasonly from that point forward, such as minus 5% for Q1 sequentially, flat for Q2, 7% for Q3 and another very healthy 7% for Q4 sequentially, that would be a steady 8.5% or more growth annually. Expectations for Q1 of 2013 should be about $12.2 Billion. Yet Intel's guidance was about $12.7 Billion. The only reason growth is looking so weak is due to a very strong, much better than expected 2010 and 2011 sales. Especially 2011. PC client group revenue for Q3 of 2009 was $7.06 Billion. For 2012, it was $8.633 Billion. That does not sound like the PC is dying to me. It sounds more like it had a huge growth cycle in 2010 and 2011, and the new hybrid versions will help propell growth once again by Q3 of 2013.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358644624312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:17:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358645472087-93</Id><Topic><Title>If Intel's growth was more evenly distributed...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358644624312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:17:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So did tablets, or more precisely, iPads cannibalized PC sales? While Intel sold $7.06 Billion in Q3 of 2009, a very strong quarter for Intel, there were no iPads yet available. A year later, Intel sold $8.055 Billion for the PC client group when Apple sold 4.19 million units of iPads during its second quarter of release. Another year later, the iPad sales exploded to 11.12 million units for the coinciding quarter against Intel's Q3 2011 sales. So did they cannibalize PC sales then? No.... Intel sold a whopping $9.42 Billion in PC client group. Even if Intel sold a mere $8.055 Billion that quarter, that would mean that iPad sales are not cannibalizing PC sales. So for the quarter that coincides with Intel Q3 2012 season, Apple sold 14 million iPad units. Intel still sold about $8.633 Billion in PC client group. Relative to when the iPad was not available, that is still 22% higher than the Q3 of 2009, when iPads were not available. As Intel stated very recently, even if PC sales remain a constant, they have many other areas of growth, including the smartphones which will be huge starting in 2014 due to LTE introduction, they will show good steady growth in general. Making the current PE of 10 seem extremely cheap and a great bargain for those that invest for the future. With a 5 year fabrication lead and huge innovative product roadmap in the pipeline using Intel chips, it looks like the future belongs to Intel.</Msg><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358645472087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:31:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358648504308-94</Id><Topic><Title>semiaccurate gaming on intel's atom z2670</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358640156679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:02:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I wonder if INTC will ever deliver quality gaming graphics drivers?" Been asking the same for yrs... but hey, INtel has Renee James... "is there even a tablet out there that you can play Crysis on? " does this count ?? youtubeDOTcom/watch?v=ZteW1tMPZeY</Msg><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358648504308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:21:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358648973340-95</Id><Topic><Title>If Intel's growth was more evenly distributed...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358644624312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:17:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to have data handy Can you fill in the blank? I think that would shed more light into the matter. --------------------------------- PC client group sales / Apple Units Q3 2009 $7.06 Billion / Apple 0 million iPad units Q3 2010 $8.055 Billion / Apple 4.19 million iPad units Q3 2011 $9.42 Billion / Apple 11.12 million iPad units Q3 2012 $8.633 Billion / Apple ??? million iPad units</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1358648973340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:29:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358649229642-96</Id><Topic><Title>semiaccurate gaming on intel's atom z2670</Title><Username>getanid61</Username><Timestamp>1358640156679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:02:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don;t know... it looks pretty lame too, but at least it runs</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1358649229642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:33:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358649973671-97</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Demonstrates Industry’s First Fully Patterned 450mm Wafer: Photos</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358629753635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:09:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imprint lithography firm Molecular Imprints Inc. said Thursday (Jan. 17) that one of its machines is being used by an unnamed semiconductor company to support the development of chip production on 450-mm diameter wafers. The company claimed that the availability of the machine would shorten the semiconductor industry's transition to 450-mm wafers by at least two years. Remember the "surprise" $2 billion capex SPECIFICALLY for 450mm - a good analyst would have followed up asking what portion of $2 billion is equipment. Non asked for a breakdown of $2 billion. The amount is just right for building/equiping a pilot line - I think Intel is pulling in the schedule for 450mm wafers. Everybody KLAC, LRCX, NVLS, AMAT is onboard - ASML was reluctant but Intel "addressed" ASML concerns EUV / double patterning is only applied to the critical layers - so Molecular Imprints might be on something</Msg><Username>semi_equip_junkie</Username><Timestamp>1358649973671</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:46:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358650836684-98</Id><Topic><Title>If Intel's growth was more evenly distributed...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358644624312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:17:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good stats. Thanks for the numbers. The main issue with intel stock - people/analysts see stellar growth in ipads and feel that Intel should have been a part of this growth. Not being in that space - intel stock is punished.</Msg><Username>vinebills</Username><Timestamp>1358650836684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 22:00:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358651827190-99</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the long term the market will consilidate to 2 semi companies. Intel and one other (Samsung maybe).. No one else can afford to play the game. Heard anything about TSMC's 20nm lately.</Msg><Username>will_amd_yu</Username><Timestamp>1358651827190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 22:17:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358652255204-100</Id><Topic><Title>If Intel's growth was more evenly distributed...</Title><Username>paul.ottelini</Username><Timestamp>1358644624312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:17:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The large ipad is being cannabalized by the small ipad which is nothing but a toy. You should educate yourself on Intel's thrust into tablets. I suggest you educate yourself by reviewing Intel's presentation at the CES. This is availiable at the Intel Investor Relation site After watching the presentation, I believe you will appreciate the difference between toys and tablets for work.</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1358652255204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 22:24:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358652784868-101</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Khitchdee believes that humans will never need a device that has more performance that the iphone5. He along with CEO Warren East believe that the human race has reached its technological peak.</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1358652784868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 22:33:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358654285336-102</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Demonstrates Industry’s First Fully Patterned 450mm Wafer: Photos</Title><Username>marsavian</Username><Timestamp>1358629753635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:09:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSMC and Samsung have agreed to fund ASML 1B each. Has TSMC already paid it or will they have to add it to their 9B capex? Has Samsung accounted for their payment?</Msg><Username>justfine790</Username><Timestamp>1358654285336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 22:58:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358655645411-103</Id><Topic><Title>Intc</Title><Username>shmemony</Username><Timestamp>1358613781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much performance users will get on their smartphones and tablets will be determined by the frontrunners in this space, Apple and Samsung, both of which have in house ARM chip development. If Intel comes out with a chip with far better performance than what Apple or Samsung offer, the added value of that performance will get downplayed because there isn't a marquee device that is showcasing it. Based on past trends, its unlikely Intel chip will have higher performance in any case. Building volumes from third place (at best) to fill up extra fabs is a tall order even for a company as efficient as Intel.</Msg><Username>khitchdee</Username><Timestamp>1358655645411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 23:20:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>