<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-09"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349764830551-1</Id><Title>How to Make an Objectivist's Head Spin p1</Title><Msg>Counterpunch Weekend Edition October 5-7, 2012 Contradictory Justifications The Free Market: Means or End? by JASON BERNARD CLAXTON Free market advocates sometimes champion the free market as a means to an end, sometimes as an end in itself. Sometimes the free market is better at achieving certain goals than any alternative, sometimes there is no alternative. Sometimes the free market is the best way of achieving prosperity, security, and a good life for a people, sometimes the free market is “the only moral system.” If it were clear at any given moment which justification were being offered, a lot of confusion might be avoided. But free market advocates often take both positions within the same argument – a strategy that is rhetorically effective, but logically dubious. When an owner’s right to dispose of property exactly as that owner desires is considered morally ultimate, then the free market becomes an end in itself. And if individual property rights are so sacred that no state of affairs that market intervention could possibly bring about would justify the rights violations that market intervention implies, then it simply wouldn’t matter whether more market regulated economies are more productive than free market economies. It wouldn’t matter whether more “socialistic” economies have, say, lower infant mortality and poverty rates, or higher literacy, job satisfaction, and social mobility rates than more free market oriented economies. All that matters is that individual property rights, which are supreme, are not violated. As long as this condition is met, the consequences of the free market system don’t matter at all. If, on the other hand, individual property rights represent not a supreme concern, not an utterly inviolable set of rights, but rather one set of concerns among many, all of which must be weighed against each other and delicately balanced, then consequences do matter. And if consequences matter, then the comparative claim that freer markets necessarily equal greater prosperity would have to be tested. And the claim can be tested: All we need to do is define those benchmarks that free markets are supposed to deliver with so much more efficiency than any alternative. Then we can compare the performance of economies with more market intervention to economies with less market intervention. One type of economy will meet the benchmarks better than the other. If, with enough ingenuity, we can isolate all the relevant factors, then we will be able to answer the comparative question, one way or another.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1349764830551</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 02:40:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349764871576-2</Id><Topic><Title>How to Make an Objectivist's Head Spin p1</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1349764830551</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 02:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The distinction between free markets as a means and free markets as an end may seem subtle at first, but it yields an important consequence. The distinction helps us realize that one justification (“the market is the only moral system”) rests on moral grounds, and the other (“markets function better than any alternative”) rests on empirical grounds. This clarifies the point being argued. It makes it possible to determine what kind of evidence needs to be presented, and what kind of argument will prove the case. It is infinitely more difficult to chose an end than it is to determine whether a given means will achieve that end. It will be incredibly difficult, if not impossible, for people who believe that individual property rights are ultimate and supreme to convince those that disagree that they are wrong, and vice versa. But when a claim is empirically testable – such as the claim that free markets are necessarily better at delivering certain results than any available alternative – then the claim can be objectively evaluated. One economic system will or won’t out-perform the other – and the difference won’t depend on our moral evaluation or opinion. But then, of course, we will have to debate the value of the goals one or the other system is supposed to achieve. When free market advocates stealthily alternate between justifications, they only end up evading either argument. When intervention is on the table, they argue “That’s socialism, and socialism just doesn’t work.” That is, markets are better for prosperity than redistributive market intervention. In the face of evidence that certain interventions might actually yield desirable results, or at least prevent certain harms, they argue “Sure, but do you really want the government telling you what to do?” The implied argument, then, must be that having “the government tell you what to do” is worse than the poverty and insecurity that a stronger social safety net could avoid. If the free market is an end, its purpose is achieved as soon as it is instituted. It is not good for any further purpose. It meets its goal immediately and perpetually. Its value is inherent. As a means, the free market’s value is not inherent, but instrumental. It is subservient to the values it is supposed to promote. Its value lies in its ability to deliver certain results, and its own value is always relative to the value of those results. The free market can’t be both end and means. Arguing both is logically inconsistent. But since logical consistency isn’t a requirement for persuasive marketing, free market advocates will surely continue to sacrifice one for the other. Jason Bernard Claxton is an attorney in New York.</Msg><Username>barking_dogmas</Username><Timestamp>1349764871576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 02:41:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349782259173-3</Id><Title>Pay No Attention to IMF, Look at Companies</Title><Msg>Noted investor and the publisher of The Gartman Letter, Dennis Gartman dismissed the latest warning on global economic weakness to come from the International Monetary Fund (IMF), saying he “paid no attention [to it] whatsoever.” “I give very little credence to what the IMF says. I give far more credence to what FedEx says, what the railroad companies say, and the earnings outlook and expectations of the auto companies rather than the IMF,” Gartman told CNBC Tuesday. FedEx [FDX 86.37 -0.10 (-0.12%) ] and other multinationals including Hewlett-Packard [HPQ 14.46 -0.27 (-1.83%) ] have warned in recent weeks that the worsening global economic outlook has hampered their bottom lines. The IMF said on Monday that it expected global growth to remain sluggish and lowered its growth forecasts blaming the looming U.S. fiscal cliff and the on-going euro zone debt crisis. (Read More: IMF Slashes Forecasts for Global Economic Growth.) It added that the fate of the global economy lay in the hands of U.S. and European policymakers. As earnings season gets under way, Gartman also downplayed the importance being given to earnings, claiming most downward risk had already been factored in to the markets. “I am amused at how often and how much we pay attention to earnings. Wall Street has ramped down its expectations, I don’t think anyone is going to be very surprised,” he said. Gartman rejected the impact of earnings from bellwether Alcoa [AA 9.12 0.03 (+0.33%) ] — the world’s largest aluminium producer — which reports later on Tuesday. Financials will be watched closely Friday when heavyweights JPMorgan Chase [JPM 41.66 -0.05 (-0.12%) ] and Wells Fargo [WFC 35.80 -0.04 (-0.11%) ] report, however, Gartman said trading would be “demonstrably less important” to banking than it has been in the past. “The value of banking going forward is that we’ll see a return to old style banking rather than the banking of the last few years, where it was predicated on trading. More about loans, who we’re lending money to, and my bet is that banks’ earnings will get better quarter-on-quarter,” he said. Gartman, a veteran commodities trader, added that he was shorting oil due to a drop in demand for gasoline consumption. “Demand is down everywhere, we’re simply driving less and less, and new automobiles are much better than the old ones and we’re finding crude oil everywhere,” he said. He described the situation as “crude bidding for storage,” which he said was the marker for a commodity in excess supply.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1349782259173</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 07:30:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349793207527-4</Id><Title>Obama Threw Away hie Re-election Change in the Debate Last Week!</Title><Msg>Did Obama Just Throw The Entire Election Away? The Pew poll is devastating, just devastating. Before the debate, Obama had a 51 - 43 lead; now, Romney has a 49 - 45 lead. That's a simply unprecedented reversal for a candidate in October. Before Obama had leads on every policy issue and personal characteristic; now Romney leads in almost all of them. Obama's performance gave Romney a 12 point swing! I repeat: a 12 point swing. Romney's favorables are above Obama's now. Yes, you read that right. Romney's favorables are higher than Obama's right now. That gender gap that was Obama's firewall? Over in one night: Currently, women are evenly divided (47% Obama, 47% Romney). Last month, Obama led Romney by 18 points (56% to 38%) among women likely voters. Seriously: has that kind of swing ever happened this late in a campaign? Has any candidate lost 18 points among women voters in one night ever? And we are told that when Obama left the stage that night, he was feeling good. That's terrifying. On every single issue, Obama has instantly plummeted into near-oblivion. He still has some personal advantages over Romney - even though they are all much diminished. Obama still has an edge on Medicare, scores much higher on relating to ordinary people, is ahead on foreign policy, and on being moderate, consistent and honest (only 14 percent of swing voters believe Romney is honest). But on the core issues of the economy and the deficit, Romney is now kicking the president's #$%$: By a 37% to 24% margin, more swing voters say Romney would improve the job situation. Swing voters favor Romney on the deficit by a two-to-one (41% vs. 20%) margin.... Romney has gained ground on several of these measures since earlier in the campaign. Most notably, Obama and Romney now run even (44% each) in terms of which candidate is the stronger leader. Obama held a 13-point advantage on this a month ago. And Obama’s 14-point edge as the more honest and truthful candidate has narrowed to just five points. In June, Obama held a 17-point lead as the candidate voters thought was more willing to work with leaders from the other party. Today, the candidates run about even on this (45% say Obama, 42% Romney). Lies work when they are unrebutted live on stage. And momentum counts at this point in the election.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349793207527</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:33:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349793569639-5</Id><Title>More Bad News for Obama from the Washington Times/ Zogby Poll</Title><Msg>Round of polls  shows tight race  after Obama-Romney debate Independents favor challenger By Stephen Dinan-The Washington Times Monday, October 8, 2012 Powered by his widely-acclaimed debate performance last week, Mitt Romney has closed a 9 percentage-point gap and is once again tied with President Obama in the latest The Washington Times/Zogby Poll conducted by Zogby Analytics, released Monday. Likely voters who watched Wednesday’s debate overwhelmingly scored it a win for Mr. Romney, 65 percent to 14 percent for Mr. Obama, and among independents it was even worse for the president — only 8 percent said he triumphed. The poll showed Mr. Romney turning the gender gap in his favor, recapturing an overall lead among independent voters and taking the lead when voters were asked who they thought would do a better at handling jobs and the economy. “Don’t ever ask again if debates matter,” said John Zogby, the pollster who conducted the survey. The poll was taken Friday through Sunday, meaning voters also had time to digest Friday’s monthly jobs report, which signaled the unemployment rate has dropped below 8 percent for the first time since Mr. Obama took office. Mr. Romney led in the poll 45.1 percent to 44.5 percent when he was stacked up against Mr. Obama alone. Adding in third-party candidates such as Libertarian nominee Gary E. Johnson gave Mr. Obama a slight edge, 45.5 percent to 45 percent. Both numbers, though, represent a major change from a week earlier, before the debate, when Mr. Obama was flirting with 50 percent — a 9 percentage-point lead over Mr. Romney. “Obama lost as many points as Romney gained. And Romney has now pulled ahead among independents and consolidated a few of his own groups,” Mr. Zogby said. Read more: Round of polls shows tight race after Obama-Romney debate - Washington Times http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/oct/8/round-polls-show-tight-race-obama-romney-debate/#ixzz28oRsbE7w Follow us: @washtimes on Twitter</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349793569639</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:39:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349793908139-6</Id><Title>Scott Brown Leads the Fake PowWow Warren by 3 Points in the Blue State of Massachusetts</Title><Msg>Poll: Scott Brown leads by 3 points A different poll released earlier this week found Brown trailing, 50 percent to 45 percent. By KEVIN ROBILLARD | 10/9/12 7:53 AM EDT Updated: 10/9/12 10:35 AM EDT Sen. Scott Brown has a 3-point edge over Democratic challenger Elizabeth Warren in a poll released Tuesday. Brown leads Warren, 48 percent to 45 percent, in the WBUR poll. A Western New England University poll released earlier this week found Brown trailing, 50 percent to 45 percent. In the WBUR poll, Brown maintains a big favorability advantage: 54 percent of Bay Staters have a favorable image of him, compared with 31 percent who view him negatively. For Warren, those numbers are 47 percent and 38 percent. There are bright spots for Warren. When asked about what they are considering when casting their vote, 62 percent said which political party will control the Senate after the election is very important to them, giving Warren a leg up in a Democratic state. Only 50 percent said which candidate would compromise more was very important to them, and only 26 percent said which candidate was more likable was very important.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349793908139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349794487784-7</Id><Topic><Title>When will Romney discuss his tax plan and his taxes?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1349742587424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:29:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sammy, While advice is being handed out. Make sure that the "silver cords are (NOT) loosed" or the "golden bowl is (NOT) broken" before you make things right for eternity. (Ecclesiastes 12) BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1349794487784</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349794569089-8</Id><Title>Women Now Abandoning Obama in Droves... Romney Erases a 8 Point Lead, Pulls Even.</Title><Msg>The Romney's Mo Un-Precidented... Chicago Smells Smoldering Peanuts.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349794569089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:56:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349794927046-9</Id><Title>Wow! Romney leads in 11 Swing States, PA in Play! Dik's Blue Wall Crumbled and Blew Away.</Title><Msg>Daily Swing State Tracking Poll Swing State Tracking: Romney 49%, Obama 47% Tuesday, October 09, 2012 The full Swing State tracking update offers Rasmussen Reader subscribers a combined view of the results from 11 key states won by President Obama in 2008 and thought to be competitive in 2012. The states collectively hold 146 Electoral College votes and include Colorado, Florida, Iowa, Michigan, Nevada, New Hampshire, North Carolina, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Virginia and Wisconsin. If you do not already have a Rasmussen Reader account, subscribe now. In the 11 swing states, Mitt Romney earns 49% support to Obama’s 47%. One percent (1%) likes another candidate, and three percent (3%) are undecided. This is the first time Romney has led the daily Swing State Survey since September 19. Until today, the president had led for 17 of the previous 19 days, and the candidates had been tied twice. This survey is based on findings from the previous seven days, with most of the responses now coming since Romney’s debate win last Wednesday night.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349794927046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:02:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349795150719-10</Id><Title>The Liberal NYTimes having Labor Problems..Do as I Say, Not What I Write, eh?</Title><Msg>New York Times staffers stage walkout Unionized workers at the Gray Lady coordinate a brief protest over contract negotiations BY NATASHA LENNARD New York Times building (Wikimedia) Unionized New York Times staffers plan a short walkout on Monday afternoon, reported Katherine Fung at the Huffington Post. The staffers, members of the Newspaper Guild of New York, will meet up and collectively walk outside of the new but iconic New York Times building in Manhattan to protest management’s position on contract negotiations. Fung reports that “the walkout won’t be the first protest that Times’ staffers have staged over proposed contract terms. Earlier this year, employees held a silent protest outside a meeting of top editors, and demonstrated outside the company’s annual shareholders meeting. Angry staffers also made their demands heard in a series of videos.”....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349795150719</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:05:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349795230281-11</Id><Topic><Title>Women Now Abandoning Obama in Droves... Romney Erases a 8 Point Lead, Pulls Even.</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349794569089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:56:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Women get it that killing women and children with drone strikes is not cool</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1349795230281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:07:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349795561858-12</Id><Title>The Republicans New Reality</Title><Msg>“The Republican Party is on a mission not just to win elections, but to build a New Reality, a Republican Universe. By running for office, each Republican candidate has an opportunity to add to the New Reality every time one speaks. “The New Reality is the reality to which each and every Republican is entitled. It is a land unbound from any kind of restraint, whether it be government regulations, the laws of arithmetic, the laws of nature, or even the limits of common sense. It is the land you, as a member of the Grand Old Party, want it to be, and nothing less.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349795561858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349795626710-13</Id><Topic><Title>The Republicans New Reality</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349795561858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:12:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Following are speaking guidelines, not just for winning an election, but for building the New Reality, one GOPsmacker at a Time” the working document says. The 10 guidelines include: 1) Make it up. And when you do, stick to your guns. Remember, the only tarnish on the New Reality is when we admit that the words we utter are less than golden. When you stick to your message, you are building the New Reality, one claim at a time. 2) Invoke rape whenever you can. The pundits think it’s red meat that’s the stimulus that jump starts a Republican heart. It’s not. It’s rape. 3) Keep in mind at all times who fits through the portal to the New Reality and who does not. This is a pure reality that we are creating and not to be tinged by those who do not belong, including (but not limited to): feminists, racial minorities who do not know their place in the New Reality, immigrants who cling to their native tongue and culture, and union members (unless they’re NFL refs). 4) Smile. Always smile. If you’re smiling when you say it, you can say anything. 5) Think before you say it. Ask yourself: How would this sound in high school? 6) Tie it back to constitutional rights, if it’s a law or regulation that is restraining the desire of an individual. Tie it back to the Declaration of Independence if the objectionable is restraining individual happiness. 7) Tie your opponent to socialism, always socialism. Candidates are sometimes tempted to tie their opponents to Hitler. But we mustn’t lose sight of the fact that it’s social, communal, and group realities that are the enemy of the New Reality. 8) Invoke Marx, Lenin, Stalin, and Ho Chi Minh in the same sentence when mentioning your opponents name. (see #7) 9) Remember, the GOP is God’s instrument and the New Reality is His. Therefore, anything other than the New Reality is unGodly. 10) Glossary and philosophy guidelines. Using the right words will not only keep you on message, but also will influence the audience’s thinking. It’s what the New Reality is all about. Master the New Reality’s vocabularly: belief, not reason getting America back, not moving forward prosperity, not social good individual, not society enterprise, not intercourse bomb, not negotiate man, not woman wife, not partner.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349795626710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349795693183-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Threw Away hie Re-election Change in the Debate Last Week!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349793207527</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:33:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Historically, the guy who wins the first debate tends to lose the election.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1349795693183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:14:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349796486649-15</Id><Topic><Title>When will Romney discuss his tax plan and his taxes?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1349742587424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:29:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would like to see a budget and how much of it includes Moochelle's vacation costs if the Obummer is reelected.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1349796486649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:28:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349796717254-16</Id><Title>Turning Medicare into a Voucher Program</Title><Msg>Romney and Ryan plan to repeal the Affordable Care Act and transform Medicare into a voucher system, and it's clear that such a plan will cost seniors money.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349796717254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349796930559-17</Id><Title>17 of 24 Romney foreign policy advisors are Bush neo-cons</Title><Msg>I can’t figure out Mitt Romney, though I think I’m hardly alone in that sentiment. When he’s not trashing the president (his only clear-cut campaign initiative) he spends the rest of the time dallying around issues that deserve serious consideration. He’s inscrutable and you don't need to look any further than the list of names on his sizeable foreign policy team as evidence. One wonders then who on this list has Romney’s ear? Between his hawkish stance toward Russia or his belligerence toward Iran it would seem that there’s little room for moderates at the Romney foreign policy table. It is because 17 of the 24 Romney foreign policy advisors are Bush neo-cons. It is further evidence that the inner circle is populated by old, right wing, Cold War warriors, which is as frightening as having no particular foreign policy experience or stance at all. Romney’s foreign policy “agenda” remains nebulous and thoroughly perplexing. There is just enough evidence, however, that when this agenda does in fact take shape, it will be alarmingly outdated.</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349796930559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:35:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349797133242-18</Id><Topic><Title>Turning Medicare into a Voucher Program</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349796717254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seniors will have the choice of taking the voucher or staying in medicare -- stick to topics in your area of expertise, like Big Bird</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1349797133242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:38:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349797385672-19</Id><Topic><Title>Turning Medicare into a Voucher Program</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349796717254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jet: Liberals hate Facts!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349797385672</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:43:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349797660338-20</Id><Topic><Title>Turning Medicare into a Voucher Program</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349796717254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you know that's a fact?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1349797660338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:47:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349797976832-21</Id><Topic><Title>17 of 24 Romney foreign policy advisors are Bush neo-cons</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349796930559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:35:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lawrence Wilkerson, the former chief of staff to Secretary of State Colin Powell, skewered Mitt Romney’s foreign policy team on Monday, saying their policies make his stomach turn. Wilkerson took particular aim at John Bolton, former President George W. Bush’s ambassador to the United Nations—and now an adviser to Romney. “The man scares me to death,” Wilkerson, a retired U.S. Army colonel told MSNBC’s Ed Schultz. “He would defeat all the enemies in America and the world—and believe me they’re plentiful—and he’d do it with everyone else’s blood. John is like Dick Cheney, never served a day in his life and wouldn't serve a day in his life … These people make me sick.” Wilkerson’s harsh rhetoric comes on the heels of Romney’s foreign policy speech earlier in the day, in which the former Massachusetts governor laid out a hawkish approach. Without offering much in the way of specifics, Romney vowed to prevent Iran from acquiring a nuclear weapon, go after terrorists who attacked the U.S. consulate in Libya, and work to ensure Syrian rebels obtain arms to defeat Bashar al-Assad’s regime. -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- "Utterly unbelievable, Wilkerson said, blasting Romney as “operating on a Cold War music sheet.” Asked about former Defense Secretary Donald Rumsfeld’s endorsement of Romney’s speech, Wilkerson declared that Rumsfeld, one of the key architects of the Iraq War “has zero credibility with me and he’ll never regain it again.”</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349797976832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:52:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349798168950-22</Id><Title>Big Bird Gives Obama the Middle Feather... Sesame Street Says Remove Obama's Political Add</Title><Msg>Shameful Obama Can't Seem to Get Anything Right these Days, eh? Sesame Workshop Response to Campaign Ads Sesame Workshop is a nonpartisan, nonprofit organization and we do not endorse candidates or participate in political campaigns. We have approved no campaign ads, and as is our general practice, have requested that the ad be taken down.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349798168950</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:56:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349798183947-23</Id><Title>POLL: Obama loses lead on key voter issues: Economy, national security...</Title><Msg>Voters now give Mitt Romney the nod when it comes to handling national security, and he has recaptured a lead over President Obama when voters are asked who will do a better job on the economy — findings that spell bad news for the incumbent. Little more than a week ago, heading into the first debate of the campaign season, Mr. Obama led on the economy and national security, as well as handling of energy, immigration and foreign affairs. In each of those categories he either topped or was just below the magic number of 50 percent support. But that changed in the latest The Washington Times/Zogby Poll conducted by Zogby Analytics, released Monday, which gave Mr. Romney a 48 percent to 45 percent advantage on national security and a 50 percent to 44 percent advantage on jobs and the economy. Read more: Obama loses  lead on key  voter issues: economy, national security - Washington Times http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/oct/8/obama-loses-lead-key-voter-issues/#ixzz28opfsVQ3 Follow us: @washtimes on Twitter</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349798183947</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:56:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349798344042-24</Id><Topic><Title>Turning Medicare into a Voucher Program</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349796717254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can Read. Can you?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349798344042</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:59:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349799280828-25</Id><Title>Romney Now Leads in Ohio... Obama is Crumbling... Jimmy Carter All Over Again!</Title><Msg>American Research Group, Inc</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349799280828</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349799769683-26</Id><Title>Obama Campaign in Utter Chaos... Now the Finger Pointing Begins!</Title><Msg>Was it Axelrod? Was it Obama? Or was 2008 Just a Mirage that Can't be Repeated? Anger and Frustration in Chicago will Blow Up in Obama's Face! They are Desperate and Desperate People Do Desperate Things. Americans Like Winners... They are Hitching their Wagons to Mitt and Paul in Droves.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349799769683</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:22:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349800091442-27</Id><Title>Is Romney still using the KKK slogan</Title><Msg>Political commenters have reported that GOP presidential candidate Mitt Romney has used a catchphrase in his stump speeches that the Ku Klux Klan favored in the 1920s. When the white supremacist group used “Keep America American,” it was to rally people against blacks American, gay people, Catholics...etc. Long before the KKK picked up the slogan, it was used in the 1850s by members of the “Know Nothing Party,”an anti-immigrant, anti-Catholic nativist party....etc. hmmm...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349800091442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:28:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349800092393-28</Id><Topic><Title>Turning Medicare into a Voucher Program</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349796717254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For Medicare, the CBO report reveals that the Ryan plan would raise the age at which people become eligible from 65 to 67, even as it repeals the health reform law's coverage provisions. This means 65- and 66-year-olds would have neither Medicare nor access to health insurance exchanges in which they could buy coverage at an affordable price and receive subsidies to help them purchase coverage if their incomes are low. This change, which is not mentioned in the 73-page booklet on his plan that Chairman Ryan released,[4] would put many more 65- and 66-year-olds who don't have employer coverage and can't afford insurance into the individual insurance market — where the premiums charged to people in this age group tend to be very high — leaving them uninsured. People of limited means, such as those who are trying to get by on incomes as low as $12,000 a year in today's dollars, would be affected most harshly because they wouldn't be able to afford private coverage.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349800092393</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:28:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349800216840-29</Id><Topic><Title>Is Romney still using the KKK slogan</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349800091442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The people that are "falling for this crap" are bigots. Proof republicans are using white supremacy/WASP to gain votes. Romney is lying because bigots know that is the only strategy that may work. The more Romney lies the more the bigots like it.</Msg><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1349800216840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:30:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349800387180-30</Id><Topic><Title>Is Romney still using the KKK slogan</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349800091442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep Trying as Obama Continues to Sink in the Polls... Americans See Through Your Desperation, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349800387180</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349800655920-31</Id><Title>Where are the video clips........</Title><Msg>......there are hundreds of video clips of Obama lying saying increasing the deficit is is immoral and unpatriotic, he would cut the deficits in half, close Gitmo, you could keep your doctor, he wouldn't raise taxes on the middles class, yada, yada, yada. You would think with all the lies they are telling us Romney has told, they could come up with at least one video clip to substantiate their claims but nada, zilch, zero are presented.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349800655920</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:37:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349800829367-32</Id><Topic><Title>Turning Medicare into a Voucher Program</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349796717254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder which Ryan will show-up to the VP debate the Sen. Joe Biden. -the lyin' Ryan ala the two-faced Romney liar - the Ryan who doesn't man-up to all that he has proposed as policy, who refuses to answer questions/challenges ala Palin in 2008, who says that Mittens will be the boss so ask him -or the real person...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349800829367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:40:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349800925542-33</Id><Title>Vegas Now Predicts a Romney Landslide Victory in November</Title><Msg>Romney wins in a landslide -- Las Vegas oddsmaker doubles down on prediction By Wayne Allyn Root Published October 09, 2012 Oct. 8, 2012: Mitt Romney delivers a foreign policy speech at Virginia Military Institute (VMI) in Lexington, Va. (AP) Yes, you read that headline correctly. I am a Las Vegas oddsmaker (and former Libertarian vice presidential candidate) and here's why I am so boldly predicting a Romney landslide. In November of 2004, only days before the presidential election, I went on CNBC and predicted a Bush victory by 3 points and 30 electoral votes. Every poll at the time showed Kerry in the lead. Bush won by 3 and 35. Newsmax magazine called it the most accurate prediction of 2004. In October of 2006, I went on Fox News to predict the GOP would get slaughtered in the midterm election and lose Congress. They did. In December 2011, before the GOP primary, I predicted Mitt Romney would win the GOP presidential nomination and go on to win the presidency. For the next few months, Romney trailed by a wide margin to a range of contenders -- Donald Trump, Rick Perry, Herman Cain, Michele Bachmann, Newt Gingrich, Rick Santorum. It seemed no one wanted Mitt for president. It seemed no one believed in Mitt. No one, that is, except this Las Vegas oddsmaker and capitalist evangelist. Fast forward to Spring 2012 after Romney clinched the GOP nomination, but trailed in every poll to President Obama. I boldly predicted a Mitt Romney landslide on Election Day, November 6. Fast forward to June 2012, when experts predicted a defeat for Wisconsin Governor Scott Walker in his recall election. Unions were pouring unheard of sums into the race in a longtime Democratic state that welcomes union rights. I boldly predicted a Walker landslide victory of 7 to 10 points. He won by exactly 7 (despite reported Democratic voter irregularities). For the past month, as Mitt Romney trailed badly in almost every poll, especially in the all-important battleground states, I continued to predict a big Romney victory. Today I’m making it official: I’m doubling down. Mitt Romney will win the presidency, and it won’t be close. I’m predicting a 5 to 7 point popular vote victory. Electorally it won’t even be that close. Romney will win many states that went to Obama in 2008. I’m predicting Romney victories in Ohio, Florida, Colorado, Virginia, Iowa, Wisconsin, New Hampshire, North Carolina, and Indiana. I predict a Romney victory by 100 to 120 electoral votes. In the days before the first presidential debate, polls showed Romney trailing badly in most of those states. But, as I’ve argued from day one, the polls are wrong. They are badly skewed towards Democrats. Quite simply they are over-polling Democratic voters and assuming a turnout that looks like 2008, when record numbers of Democrats came out for Obama. After Romney’s overwhelming victory in the first debate he now leads, or is dead even in battleground states where, only days before, he was supposedly way behind. My contention is a 1 point Romney lead in those Democrat-skewed polls is really a comfortable 5 to 7 point Romney lead on election day....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349800925542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349801125615-34</Id><Topic><Title>Is Romney still using the KKK slogan</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349800091442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you admit Obama was ahead in the polls 47/9 to 43/4 given the margin of error of polls Desperation, fabrications, hate, anger, fear are what the Republicans of today stand for...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349801125615</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:45:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349801304151-35</Id><Topic><Title>Is Romney still using the KKK slogan</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349800091442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No........but it is quite evident that you want to promulgate racism.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1349801304151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:48:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349801459918-36</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the video clips........</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349800655920</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are Available and Plentiful... Just Waiting for the Best Time to Expose Obama Again as the Hypocrite He Truly is! The "Intellect" of an Affirmative Queen is Starting to Show. Timing is Everything. No Wonder Obama was Looking at His Shoes Last Wednesday, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349801459918</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:50:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349801473408-37</Id><Title>imaccom/x6xxx234/payforityourself</Title><Msg>+30 post 0 rated approx 3 replies = desperation via the RWNJ 5-cent per koch-sucker poster lol</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349801473408</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:51:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349801579370-38</Id><Topic><Title>imaccom/x6xxx234/payforityourself</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349801473408</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:51:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I Know... Liberals are Morning Obama's Upcoming Landslide Defeat!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349801579370</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:52:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349801839650-39</Id><Title>market goes up BA goes down, market goes down BA goes up</Title><Msg>wat's up wit dat</Msg><Username>xwamaparoo</Username><Timestamp>1349801839650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:57:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349801925026-40</Id><Title>Our Ambassador Died abd Obama Lied and The GM Volt battery died too.......</Title><Msg>.....and GM still owes us 25 Billion dollars.......or as Obama would say when he's down south 25 biliaawn Daahlas.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349801925026</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:58:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349802030693-41</Id><Title>Obama's Pathetic Use of Big Bird to Attack Romney Backfires Big Time... Middle Feather!</Title><Msg>Obama is Looking More and More Desperate as he Continues to Slip in the Polls!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349802030693</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:00:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349802117307-42</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the video clips........</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349800655920</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has been filling in the hole left by the neo-cons/Boosh. Repugs want to give Rmoney the shovel to dig the hole deeper. You were warned about Boosh in 2000, but failed to heed the warnings same as Boosh failed to heed the warnings about 9/11. Will you fail to heed the warning about the rotten Rmoney too, and why?</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349802117307</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349802187514-43</Id><Topic><Title>Our Ambassador Died abd Obama Lied and The GM Volt battery died too.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349801925026</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's company that makes the Volt Battery declares bankruptcy!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1349802187514</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:03:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349802236964-44</Id><Topic><Title>imaccom/x6xxx234/payforityourself</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349801473408</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:51:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need t read that one back to yourself... two negatives = a positive, Obama by a landslide!</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349802236964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349802476642-45</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the video clips........</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349800655920</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still Running Against W Four Years Later... Pathetic. When Will Obama Accept Responsibilities for His Own Failures? The American People See Obama Shirking Responsibilities and Blaming Someone Else... American See Weakness in Obama.... Romney is Waiting for Obama to Lead with His Chin on that Subject in the Next Debate. Romney will Knock Obama Back to Chicago with One response.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349802476642</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:07:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349802545426-46</Id><Topic><Title>imaccom/x6xxx234/payforityourself</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349801473408</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:51:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Government Schooled, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349802545426</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:09:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349802698096-47</Id><Topic><Title>Vegas Now Predicts a Romney Landslide Victory in November</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349800925542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:42:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The hope was delusional and the change was all fore the worse......now time to face reality and change presidents.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349802698096</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:11:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349803242958-48</Id><Title>Black Christians Abandoning Democrats</Title><Msg>For the first time since the black community’s political realignment with the Democrat Party in the 1960′s, a nationally prominent black Pastor has called on the black church community to leave the Democrat Party in a movement dubbed “EXODUS NOW!” Bishop E.W. Jackson’s call to “come out from among them” is apparently being heeded by many black Pastors and Christians across America and creating a stir in many churches. There is concern at the highest levels of the Democrat Party. The impetus for EXODUS NOW, and what has given it credibility in the black community is the Democrat Party’s increasingly secular stand, particularly making “same-sex marriage” an official part of the Party Platform. This came on the heels of a number of other actions which many Christians found objectionable: President Obama’s support for same-sex marriage; regulations ordering Catholic and other Christian institutions providing healthcare to distribute free contraceptives and abortion drugs; Convention speakers support for unrestricted abortion up to the moment before delivery; and taking God out of the party platform and no longer recognizing Jerusalem as the capital of Israel. Across the country, as black Christians debate the call to EXODUS NOW, Democrats are shaken. They desperately need the votes of black church goers. Democrats are responding by attacking Jackson personally on left wing blogs. “They can say anything they want about me,” says Jackson, “but I do not intend to leave Christians in bondage to a party that is hostile to everything Christians hold dear. Either we worship and rely on God or we worship and rely on a political party. We are supposed to rely on Almighty God, not the government or any party. When a party disdains God and His word, as the Democrat Party clearly does, it is time to leave that party.” Says the Bishop, “This movement is not about Party, but principle; not about race, but righteousness. This is not about winning an election, but saving a generation.”</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349803242958</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:20:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349803430908-49</Id><Topic><Title>imaccom/x6xxx234/payforityourself</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349801473408</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:51:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Landslide defeat is not two negatives.........but I perfer the word "shellacking" like Obama used after the 2010 congressional races in which the Democrats suffered a landslide defeat (landslide victory for the Republicans) and which I expect Obama will experience come November. You'll be mo(u)rning t(o) read about it.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1349803430908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:23:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349803594116-50</Id><Title>Pennsylvania, Wisconsin and Michigan All in Play... A Landslide in the Making for Romney</Title><Msg>Washington Times.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349803594116</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:26:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349804258930-51</Id><Title>Obama Ship Listing Badly: Sends out SOS</Title><Msg>The Pew poll is devastating, just devastating. Before the debate, Obama had a 51 - 43 lead; now, Romney has a 49 - 45 lead. That's a simply unprecedented reversal for a candidate in October. Before Obama had leads on every policy issue and personal characteristic; now Romney leads in almost all of them. Obama's performance gave Romney a 12 point swing! I repeat: a 12 point swing. Romney's favorables are above Obama's now. Yes, you read that right. Romney's favorables are higher than Obama's right now. That gender gap that was Obama's firewall? Over in one night: Currently, women are evenly divided (47% Obama, 47% Romney). Last month, Obama led Romney by 18 points (56% to 38%) among women likely voters. Seriously: has that kind of swing ever happened this late in a campaign? Has any candidate lost 18 points among women voters in one night ever? And we are told that when Obama left the stage that night, he was feeling good. That's terrifying. On every single issue, Obama has instantly plummeted into near-oblivion. He still has some personal advantages over Romney - even though they are all much diminished. Obama still has an edge on Medicare, scores much higher on relating to ordinary people, is ahead on foreign policy, and on being moderate, consistent and honest (only 14 percent of swing voters believe Romney is honest). But on the core issues of the economy and the deficit, Romney is now kicking the president's #$%$: By a 37% to 24% margin, more swing voters say Romney would improve the job situation. Swing voters favor Romney on the deficit by a two-to-one (41% vs. 20%) margin.... Romney has gained ground on several of these measures since earlier in the campaign. Most notably, Obama and Romney now run even (44% each) in terms of which candidate is the stronger leader. Obama held a 13-point advantage on this a month ago. And Obama’s 14-point edge as the more honest and truthful candidate has narrowed to just five points. In June, Obama held a 17-point lead as the candidate voters thought was more willing to work with leaders from the other party. Today, the candidates run about even on this (45% say Obama, 42% Romney). Lies work when they are unrebutted live on stage. And momentum counts at this point in the election.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349804258930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:37:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349804319983-52</Id><Title>Ryans Path To Prosperity</Title><Msg>Ryan's Path To Prosperity; line his pockets with Americas money...!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349804319983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:38:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349804664531-53</Id><Topic><Title>imaccom/x6xxx234/payforityourself</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349801473408</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:51:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah yes.....Obama's campaign is getting worse mourning, knew'n and knight.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349804664531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:44:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349804711469-54</Id><Topic><Title>Ryans Path To Prosperity</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349804319983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's obvious that both the R's and the D's serve the 1%.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1349804711469</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:45:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349804917250-55</Id><Topic><Title>Is Romney still using the KKK slogan</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349800091442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Before you call other people bigots, ask yourself this. Would you tolerate the reckless bombing of civilians in other countries if it was a white president doing it?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1349804917250</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349804946415-56</Id><Topic><Title>Is Romney still using the KKK slogan</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349800091442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would you tolerate it if the civilians were Europeans?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1349804946415</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:49:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349805085644-57</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the video clips........</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349800655920</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's been digging the hole deeper. The military budget continues to expand. The DoD employs 3 million people accomplishing not a whole hell of a lot.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1349805085644</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:51:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349805783251-58</Id><Title>Ohio GOP Appealing Every VoterCounts To Supreme Court</Title><Msg>why, when the GOP has been caught in more than a few states registering ineligible voters ?</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349805783251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:03:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349806911166-59</Id><Topic><Title>Ryans Path To Prosperity</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349804319983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the difference is that the R's are purposely destroying America</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349806911166</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:21:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349807824906-60</Id><Topic><Title>Stop the Prgress of Progressivism</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1349805566342</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:59:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>regressivism is just another word for the republicon fascists/nazi anti-american myth Rmonery/lyin' Ryan's isn't it lol</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349807824906</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:37:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349808051279-61</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. top earners pay larger share of taxes than any other industrialized nation...</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1349806148466</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:09:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>apparently all except mittens rmoney and lyin' ryan when compared to joe biden and barack obama/the average american including the rev., al sharpton who is blacker and sharper than your rwnj pinhead</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349808051279</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349808320688-62</Id><Topic><Title>When will Romney discuss his tax plan and his taxes?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1349742587424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:29:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wutangbk2...wouldn't we all the more I listen to Mittens Rmoney...the more I wanna puke, and the less I know truly shallow/empty RWNJ souls including the mittens rmoney sons/chickenhawks</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349808320688</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:45:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349808428637-63</Id><Topic><Title>When will Romney discuss his tax plan and his taxes?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1349742587424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:29:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bulky_blob has turned into nothing but a hit and run RWNJ driver for jesus</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349808428637</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:47:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349808488577-64</Id><Topic><Title>Huge run on Xanax.....prices soar</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1349805142336</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:52:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey buttlicker... get your facts straight... liberals can't afford xanax...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349808488577</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:48:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349809132903-65</Id><Title>Extreme Panic Sets in for Obama Supporters... Defacing Romney Signs... Violent Libs Scared!</Title><Msg>Romney signs defaced with excrement in Virginia By David Sherfinski - The Washington TimesOctober 9, 2012, 01:12PM Romney signs defaced with excrement in Virginia Poll: Romney surges in Pennsylvania McCain mocks Obama's Big Bird attack ad Voters say Ryan will stomp Biden A conservative radio host based in central Virginia, has posted a video on his website of a GOP office with its window smashed in, expletive-laced rants presumably delivered at Republicans, and Mitt Romney/Paul Ryan signs torn down, defaced and smeared with what appears to be human excrement. The clip (prefaced with a warning of "extremely graphic content") on the "Schilling Show" blog, written by radio host Rob Schilling, begins with President Obama on the campaign trail telling attendees to "argue with them and get in their face," a phrase he used in 2008 to encourage his supporters to talk to friends and neighbors about voting and accurately delivering his message, whether they were Republican or independent. The clip then shifts to an expletive-laced rant labeled "Actual phone call received at Albemarle County, Virginia GOP Headquarters — September 11, 2012." It goes on to show a man tearing down yard signs at an Americans For Prosperity event in Charlottesville while screaming obscenities, then a montage of Republican political signs that have been defaced — in one case with excrement — and Nazi imagery plastered onto an AFP sign. The video ends with the words "Don't let Democrats, vandals, thieves, oppressors, intimidators, and tyrants silence you … Remember, NOVEMBER IS COMING." Virginia is a critical battleground state, with the Charlottesville and Albemarle area — where the video was filmed — essentially the only Democratic stronghold in the state's expansive southside 5th Congressional district. Sign wars are a traditional part of campaigning, and operatives use all sorts of tactics to try to put up as many signs as they can, and to protect their signs from vandalism by angry opponents.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349809132903</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:58:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349809210317-66</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. top earners pay larger share of taxes than any other industrialized nation...</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1349806148466</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:09:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals are too Dumb to Understand Your Post!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349809210317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:00:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349809721461-67</Id><Title>Romney Hits Obama on Big Bird as Big Bird Gives Obama the Middle Feather!</Title><Msg>Romney hits Obama on Big Bird focus Mitt Romney, speaking to a crowd of about 1,200 on a farm here in Van Meter, Iowa, criticized President Obama's recent focus on Big Bird on the campaign trail. "You have to scratch your head when the president spends the last week talking about saving Big Bird," he said. "I actually think we need to have a president who talks about saving the American people and saving good jobs." Romney's not the only one, as my colleague Dylan Byers notes, criticizing the Obama campaign for focusing on a "small" issue like Big Bird.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349809721461</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:08:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349810180100-68</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. top earners pay larger share of taxes than any other industrialized nation...</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1349806148466</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:09:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As an 80-98%'er The best I can do is beat the Series I savings bonds and create few jobs now what is the myth rmoney/lyin' ryan plan ?</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349810180100</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:16:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349810241591-69</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Ship Listing Badly: Sends out SOS</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349804258930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:37:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finger Pointing in Chicago to Go Along with the Heavy Drinking as They See the Election Slip Sliding Away from Obama! Obama's Campaign Staff Starting to Eat Themselves!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349810241591</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349810487530-70</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. top earners pay larger share of taxes than any other industrialized nation...</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1349806148466</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:09:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>believe me treated 100,000's for the U.S. military days, nights, weekends, 24/7 for many years @ $4/pt. visit including taking rides on good aerolanes/heliocopters into hot LZ';s, etc. and rmoney/lyin' ryan wanna call me a 47%'er when IAM only 12% fully-abled according to the rules of the game</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349810487530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:21:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349810571940-71</Id><Title>Obama is Naked... Nothing to Run On... His Failed Policies Attacked by Everyone....</Title><Msg>In Fighting in Chicago Says it All... Major Changes Coming in Obama's Campaign... Not a Positive Sign for Hussein, eh? They Know They are Losing.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349810571940</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:22:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349810689375-72</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. top earners pay larger share of taxes than any other industrialized nation...</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1349806148466</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:09:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You Must be an Un-Educated Fool, eh? Life is Not Fair....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349810689375</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:24:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349811066016-73</Id><Topic><Title>When will Romney discuss his tax plan and his taxes?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1349742587424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:29:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"bulky_blob has turned into nothing but a hit and run RWNJ driver for jesus" I will count as a compliment that you associate me with Jesus. And how would you characterize your associations? I am unmoved, unaffected, and unimpressed with the personal commentary, otherwise. Get right and get ready, it is going to be a bumpy ride.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1349811066016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:31:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349811436866-74</Id><Title>When Will Obama Release His College Transcripts? Affirmative Action Queen Showing</Title><Msg>The American People Know he is an Affirmative Action Queen, we Just Want to See the Proof... What Obama is Hiding and Embarrassed of, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349811436866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:37:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349812264116-75</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Confused: Ask Why are they using Facts against us?</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1349811695164</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:41:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals Hate Facts... Ever Wonder why When a Socialist or Communist Takes Power, the First Order of Business is to Silence the Press? They Can Only Survive on Lies. The Once "Main Stream Press" no Longer Controls the Narrative... And they Hate That!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349812264116</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:51:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349812347277-76</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. top earners pay larger share of taxes than any other industrialized nation...</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1349806148466</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:09:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That smarmy Bas5ard would say that - of course that's his prescription for everything when he's on TV which seems all the time - more tax cuts for the rich. MAYBE THE REASON WE GET MORE TAX MONEY FROM THE RICH COMPARED TO OTHER COUNTRIES IS THE GIGANTIC AND GROWING DISPARITY IN INCOMES/WEALTH IN AMERICA!! His smile gives me the creeps!</Msg><Username>windyhorn</Username><Timestamp>1349812347277</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349812418253-77</Id><Topic><Title>When will Romney discuss his tax plan and his taxes?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1349742587424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:29:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jefferson aerpplane 1966-67 it don't mean #$%$ to a tree in front of jesus</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349812418253</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:53:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349812942528-78</Id><Title>It's 4:oo on Wall Street - Do You Know Where You're Money Is Going...</Title><Msg>down the tubes with Myth Rmoney and Lyin' Ryan... fire Big Bird!</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349812942528</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:02:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349813131583-79</Id><Topic><Title>It's 4:oo on Wall Street - Do You Know Where You're Money Is Going...</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349812942528</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:02:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a Stupid Post. Did You Get Past 8th Grade in Your Government Run School?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349813131583</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:05:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349813238135-80</Id><Topic><Title>Huge run on Xanax.....prices soar</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1349805142336</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:52:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IAM still wondering which drug "Mormon" Mittens was on...during the debate when he was foaming at the mouth about slashing PBS and Big Bird 5-hour Energy Methylphenidate/Ritalin - for AD/ADD or Coke it wasn't jack daniels and high-fructose corn syrupy cola drink for breakfast plus what he have harvested or approved by the Mormon Church!</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349813238135</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:07:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349813432961-81</Id><Title>Intrade says Barry is at 60%...</Title><Msg>down a whole 20% from the day before the debate. Barry is going down faster than a cheap hooker on a paying customer -- or Monica on Bill. If Mitt can trash Barry this badly in an hour and a half, you dumbocrats need to wait til you see what Mitt does to him after another three hours on stage!!</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349813432961</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:10:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349813546750-82</Id><Topic><Title>Intrade says Barry is at 60%...</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349813432961</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:10:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vegas Already Says Romney Wins... Hussein is Toast!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349813546750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:12:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349813722870-83</Id><Topic><Title>Huge run on Xanax.....prices soar</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1349805142336</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:52:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Four, You Make a Fool of Yourself Every Time you Post! What Did Your Union Boss Tell you to Do Today?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349813722870</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:15:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349814135847-84</Id><Title>Face it, Obama will raise taxes on you people in the mediocre class</Title><Msg>He is only using you fools. All his friends and big donors are rich people like myself only I don't invest in buying politicians like they do.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349814135847</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:22:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349814353871-85</Id><Topic><Title>It's 4:oo on Wall Street - Do You Know Where You're Money Is Going...</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349812942528</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:02:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have already told you 80-98% percentile (tied twice for first place in esoteric and diverse subjects across this vast nation)... and still 12% fully-bodied able according to military-VA injustice system or about the average IQ of a red-sate RWNJ in other words according to the black knight in Monty Pytrhon;s In Search of the Holy Grail: I'd bite you from your ankles up to your knees and nose and ears off you slimey RWNJ coward/chickenhawk, get back here... if you were a real man...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349814353871</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349814646893-86</Id><Topic><Title>Huge run on Xanax.....prices soar</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1349805142336</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:52:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>la di dah di de la di dah de dah the drums keep pounding rythyms to the brain and 'Mormom' Mittens will not be 'elected' by The People nothing against most Mormon people... and the beat goes on all, imho...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349814646893</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:30:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349814709313-87</Id><Topic><Title>Face it, Obama will raise taxes on you people in the mediocre class</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349814135847</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As Stalin Said, Communist/Liberals Need Useful Fools Like Dik, Paul, Black, etc....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349814709313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:31:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349814826966-88</Id><Topic><Title>Vegas Now Predicts a Romney Landslide Victory in November</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349800925542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:42:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't get whole article in cut top part, but here it is. Romney wins in a landslide -- Las Vegas oddsmaker doubles down on prediction By Wayne Allyn Root Published October 09, 2012</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349814826966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:33:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349816258248-89</Id><Title>Why Does the Mediocre Class Spend so much Time and Energy being Jealous and Envious?</Title><Msg>Is it because high achievers remind them they aren't willing to do what it takes to be a high achievers? Or is it the same mentality robbers use to try and get the rewards without achieving? Whatever......the Democrat politicians have been feeding off this foolish mentality for over a hundred years.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349816258248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:57:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349816833424-90</Id><Topic><Title>Why Does the Mediocre Class Spend so much Time and Energy being Jealous and Envious?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349816258248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 16:57:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But What Else Can Dik and His Multiple Aliases Do?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349816833424</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:07:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349817052266-91</Id><Title>Why is Obama Hiding From the Press... We Know!</Title><Msg>No White House Press Briefing in Last 15 Days 4:05 PM, OCT 9, 2012 • BY DANIEL HALPER The White House has not held a press briefing in the last 15 days, according to records on the White House's website. The last one was held on September 24, 2012, by White House press secretary Jay Carney. However, in that 15 day time period, and including today, there have been 11 press gaggles. Nine have been conducted by Carney, while 2 have been held by principal deputy press secretary Josh Earnest. Campaign surrogates David Axelrod and traveling press secretary Jen Psaki have participated in the gaggles.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349817052266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:10:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349817698378-92</Id><Title>Did You know Jealousy and Envy Causes some Losers to Hallucinate?</Title><Msg>It's true! If they can't get a date, they get a blow-up doll and let their hallucinations run wild. I know one #$%$ transvestite that actually has a blow-up doll that looks like Sir Paul. Some times he even dresses up as Sir Paul himself and goes out looking for one legged women. I don't know why since he's a #$%$ but no matter how much he shakes, kicks or dances he still can't get on of those one legged women to hop his way.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349817698378</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349818043750-93</Id><Topic><Title>Turning Medicare into a Voucher Program</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349796717254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryan is a punk... just like his new boss</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349818043750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:27:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349818516542-94</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Obama Hiding From the Press... We Know!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349817052266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:10:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is the White House teleprompter in the repair shop?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349818516542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:35:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349818620515-95</Id><Topic><Title>Vegas Now Predicts a Romney Landslide Victory in November</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349800925542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:42:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since it's a cakewalk - you Romney voters can save your energy and stay home from the polls on election day and just watch Fox News all day and wait for it to be official</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1349818620515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:37:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349818626857-96</Id><Topic><Title>Turning Medicare into a Voucher Program</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349796717254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean like the 90 year old Boosh41or the 65 year old Mittens 3-1 boosh 41</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349818626857</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:37:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349818972813-97</Id><Title>Anyone heard from the Kent Raven since Obama Bombed?</Title><Msg>He's probably in a deep deep depression since the disaster-N-chief has been exposed.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349818972813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:42:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349819018403-98</Id><Title>Mommy, Why's Grandma Holding "Toothless BJ 4 Food" By The Road?</Title><Msg>Because, dear, the Republicans put all the money in the hands of the rich through corporate welfare, tax cuts and Social Security/Medicare cuts. Mommy, that's nasty. Almost as bad as Rumsfeld sending us that robo-signed letter about daddy dying in Iraq. Did they ever find WMDs that were going to kill me? No, dear, the Republicans lied about the WMDs I'm so sad, can I watch Big Bird to feel better? The Republicans put Big Bird to sleep. Instead of TV let me tell you about better days when I was little. About the five pounds of free cheese Reagan gave us and school lunches with real ketchup as the vegetable. Checking out "Green Eggs And Ham" from the library without it being reported to Homeland Security. And for a bedtime story can Grandma tell me about Watergate and Reagan promising a balanced budget but forgetting because he had Alzheimer's? And my favorite, Dan Quayle and the potato! Yes, dear, but I don't want Grandma kissing you good-night.</Msg><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1349819018403</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:43:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349819232767-99</Id><Topic><Title>Did You know Jealousy and Envy Causes some Losers to Hallucinate?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349817698378</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:21:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dik.....all you friends.....that means both of them, know at least one #$%$ transvestite.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349819232767</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:47:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349819892660-100</Id><Title>The Most Serious Conversation Yet from the Disaster-N-chief</Title><Msg>"Obama campaign's frivolous Big Bird ad, which has gotten them laughed at and slapped with a cease and desist request from Sesame Street. When I first saw the new spot, I really thought it was a spoof produced for Conan or Colbert. No sir; it was an official OFA ad, approved by the president himself. Oh, good. We've got 23 million Americans out of work, a national debt charging toward $17 trillion, poverty rates and food stamp usage at all-time highs, and a dangerous conflagration in the Middle East -- yet this president is trying to score cheap points with sub-moronic arguments about Muppets. Watch our Commander-in-Chief try to convince himself that this Elmo joke is chuckle-worthy." KP</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349819892660</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:58:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349821051243-101</Id><Topic><Title>Turning Medicare into a Voucher Program</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349796717254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trying to elicit a serious discussion with a RWNJ is like trying to bate a jellyfish/lyin' ryan so joe biden is bringing a staple gun to the vp debate... and... shhhh....</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349821051243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:17:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349822069746-102</Id><Topic><Title>Turning Medicare into a Voucher Program</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349796717254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"seniors will have the choice of taking the voucher or staying in medicare" not even close to 'the plan" as espoused by Mittens Romney/lyin' Ryan that is for the pre-senior/pre-55 year old plan outdated RWNJ plan take your voucher and shove it up your gramma's butt it'll shave you hundreds of dollars when she feels constipated if you can find that wamparoos's butt -Luke Skywalker, using the Yoda mind-control</Msg><Username>xwamaparoo</Username><Timestamp>1349822069746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:34:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349822715524-103</Id><Topic><Title>brilliant Joe Biden</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1349817172879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:12:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>joe might not know how to make millions ripping off folks but I'm sure he can make romney look like a first grader when it comes to politics</Msg><Username>eddiew37</Username><Timestamp>1349822715524</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349822733513-104</Id><Topic><Title>Turning Medicare into a Voucher Program</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349796717254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you know what a loser boosh41 was compared to a mittens and a detriment to America for Americans</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349822733513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349823102126-105</Id><Topic><Title>brilliant Joe Biden</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1349817172879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:12:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Give a man a fish and he will eat for a day. Teach a man to fish and he will feed himself for a lifetime. Don;t feed fish or the women"... one con-fused lyin; Ryan that dot looks a piece of dust re: the use of drone aeroplanes ?</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349823102126</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:51:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349823749739-106</Id><Topic><Title>brilliant Joe Biden</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1349817172879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:12:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You know that is not true" as for economic and foreign policy Besides filling in the Boosh hole and making the world a safer place...believe me when we say that the 'Libyans' who killed our ambassador there will pay a higher price than what Moammar Khadaiify did under 40 years of Raygun and Boosh...is true... debating a hariydoke is like debating a rwnj pinhead no offence to independent pinheads</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349823749739</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:02:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349823937989-107</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone heard from the Kent Raven since Obama Bombed?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349818972813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, you talk to yourself on a regular basis?</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1349823937989</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:05:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349824705804-108</Id><Title>Romney LEADS Obama in most polls</Title><Msg>now that the American people can see Obama without a teleprompter and realize that he's just not that smart. Romney is an accomplished and capable leader.</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1349824705804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:18:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349824822446-109</Id><Title>Is it safe ?</Title><Msg>der weiss angel do not break knuckles with refrigerator door hinges Is it safe?</Msg><Username>xwamaparoo</Username><Timestamp>1349824822446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349825045600-110</Id><Topic><Title>Turning Medicare into a Voucher Program</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349796717254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Koch's agenda is for the Vulture to #$%$ out of your Social Security and the Voucher to #$%$ out of your Medicare. The Vulture /Voucher ticket.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1349825045600</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349825920552-111</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone heard from the Kent Raven since Obama Bombed?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349818972813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't pay attention, do you? But then you're a resident of the right-fringe.</Msg><Username>bronx_bomber_fan2009</Username><Timestamp>1349825920552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349826864737-112</Id><Title>Reject Right Wing Obama !</Title><Msg>Obama is almost as right wing as Ryan-Romey! Call Obama right wing lite! Obama does not push to have "Everyone pay FICA tax on all incomes" Obama is allowing almost unregulated fracking plus the keystone pollution pipe. He appointed Monsanto executives to the FDA. He caves way too easily to tea potty Koch brother positions! ~~~ Vote instead for Jill Stein of the Green Party! She will really help 99% of us the most! She is on the ballot in all 50 States! ~~~ Do not be afraid to waste a vote because voting for any one of the right wingers is more than a wasted vote!</Msg><Username>jaked.canine</Username><Timestamp>1349826864737</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:54:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349829438590-113</Id><Title>Fortunately BA does not rely on AA as much</Title><Msg>The company reported a net loss of $143 million, or 13 cents per share, compared with a profit of $172 million, or 15 cents per share, in the same quarter last year. Excluding charges from the settlement of a civil lawsuit and environmental remediation of a New York state river, earnings were 3 cents per share, down from 15 cents a share in the year-earlier period. Revenue decreased 9 percent to $5.83 billion from $6.42 billion a year ago.</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1349829438590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:37:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349831522999-114</Id><Topic><Title>Fortunately BA does not rely on AA as much</Title><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1349829438590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We bettter cut taxes on the rich.... in order for them to collect the aluminum cans and then arresting them for littering... -Alice;s restaurant</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349831522999</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 21:12:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349832137621-115</Id><Topic><Title>Fortunately BA does not rely on AA as much</Title><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1349829438590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Dark Ages were better than the Nixon\Raygun/Boosh era vive la renaqissance the giants live to see another day tweet</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349832137621</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 21:22:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349834035977-116</Id><Topic><Title>How to Make an Objectivist's Head Spin p1</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1349764830551</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 02:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1349834035977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 21:53:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349834131120-117</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Ship Listing Badly: Sends out SOS</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349804258930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:37:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd give Obama one of my life preservers but I need both to stay afloat in this economy.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1349834131120</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 21:55:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349834659916-118</Id><Title>This Kid Tells Everyone At Show and Tell He's A Horse</Title><Msg>After the kids finished laughing the teacher gently asked him why fearing she was uncovering a serious mental problem in front of a class of children too young to understand. The little boy replied between his priest and Sandusky he was mounted every day so he had to be a horse.</Msg><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1349834659916</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:04:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349836756533-119</Id><Topic><Title>Lowest Unemployment number in 44 months.</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1349825096592</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:24:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the economy isn't so fragile as it was when compared to now 50% more clams it's a lobster either way give mittens a shovel and the boosh hole will be deeper</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349836756533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:39:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349837111217-120</Id><Topic><Title>Lowest Unemployment number in 44 months.</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1349825096592</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:24:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cummins, Inc. just announced it is lowering expectations and will be laying off another 1,500 workers by the end of the year because of continuing weak economies and downturns in sales/orders both here and abroad.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1349837111217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 22:45:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349839375466-121</Id><Title>Thew best stories of 1962 imho...the Gemini missions</Title><Msg>the Cuban missile/cigar crisis and three busting outta Alcatraz never to be seen again... with a tablesopon in the bay with your new id</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349839375466</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:22:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>