<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356325599871-1</Id><Topic><Title>V-22 dumps crew member</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1356207937882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 15:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How does CG and Gerbil answer the fact that Boeing and it V-22 are significantly responsible for the deaths of the ambassador and CIA support at Benghazi. Oh their are others, Penetta, Hillary, BO, and some others. The reason they couldn't send any help, they say was because they didn't know what was going on. Translated, you can't send the V-22 into a hot zone, period. So they all lied like the snakes in the grass that they are. And some Americans perished. A really sad sorry tale.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1356325599871</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 00:06:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356326663534-2</Id><Topic><Title>How Walmart Helped Make the Newtown Shooter's AR-15 the Most Popular Assault Weapon in America</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356280882964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 11:41:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's true there are a lot of law abiding gun owners, but more and more a lot of people handling guns, whether they own them, borrowed them, or stole them, are not law abiding citizens. Some are not citizens at all. And it's true that gun sales took off at a feverish pitch when it became clear that Obama was going to be President. A lot of people had an irrational fear that Government was going to be coming down on them. And the NRA really capitalized on that. People must have thought that somebody was going to be resentful of something, and that they would need to protect themselves. For a lot of people, it's not a tyrannical government they are worried about.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1356326663534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 00:24:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356327908026-3</Id><Topic><Title>Do States Have the Right to Secede?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356108413857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:46:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any state contrary enough to secede would soon be rattling sabres with a foreign entity and expecting the US to protect it. Can't think of many states that would actually think there were more pros than cons to independence. Say Tennessee, just for the sake of discussion, wanted and got independence. Just the logistics alone of exporting goods to any country other than the US would be a nightmare. All we have to do is tariff them to death. Lots of the lower 48 are landlocked. That hurts other countries around the world and it would hurt one of ours.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1356327908026</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 00:45:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356331169473-4</Id><Topic><Title>Message to All the Anti-religon and Anti - NRA Nutjobs</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356293703121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 15:15:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It doesn't matter what other countries do. THIS country pretends to rise above the level of other countries. THIS country DOES grant religious freedom. Right-fringers who want to lower THIS country to the same level as other counties are NOT Patriots. They are fraidy cats.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356331169473</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 01:39:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356331246754-5</Id><Topic><Title>V-22 dumps crew member</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1356207937882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 15:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take a pill.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356331246754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 01:40:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356331936664-6</Id><Topic><Title>V-22 dumps crew member</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1356207937882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 15:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No CG I wouldn't let you habits become one on mine. Left wing nuts can't answer the hard questions.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1356331936664</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 01:52:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356335407183-7</Id><Topic><Title>V-22 dumps crew member</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1356207937882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 15:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad Yahoo! won't allow links to be posted, because I Googled CH-47 interior and V-22 Osprey interior and found photos of the interior of both (The Osprey was on flikr). I couldn't see a whole lot of difference in headroom based on comparing the cabin roof height to the seats. Straighten me out. Give me the headroom for both aircraft in inches. Once verified, that should make it obvious how dangerour the Osprey is in the height thingie.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356335407183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 02:50:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356348412738-8</Id><Topic><Title>Message to All the Anti-religon and Anti - NRA Nutjobs</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356293703121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 15:15:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you having another one of your non-lucid dreams about your lucid dream again?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1356348412738</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 06:26:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356357570493-9</Id><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Msg>The petition to deport Piers Morgan over his repeated attacks against the second amendment has surpassed the number of signatures required to mandate a White House response.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356357761495-10</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What did you think of it ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357761495</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:02:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356358282617-11</Id><Topic><Title>Message to All the Anti-religon and Anti - NRA Nutjobs</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356293703121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 15:15:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow...Frank Capra pr Norman Rockwell could not capture the simple passionate truth of this man in the face of a corrupt Congress. "The villain was not the club he used. Neither was it the NCA, the National Club Association. The true killer was Cain, and the reason for the murder could only be found in Cain's heart. "In the days that followed the Columbine tragedy, I was amazed at how quickly fingers began to be pointed at groups such as the NRA"</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356358282617</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:11:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356358450388-12</Id><Topic><Title>A Message to the NRA's Wayne LaPierre</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356106766814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/mbview/threadview/?&amp;bn=7d8d92d6-c287-340e-8126-be6d06b3eecf&amp;tid=1356293703121-fd8c5fad-ce33-4cd9-99c8-2f60df74f35a&amp;tls=la%2Cd%2C0</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356358450388</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:14:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356358943963-13</Id><Title>Setting the Record Straight</Title><Msg>Its the Republican party that is to blame should the economy fall over the fiscal cliff. The Republcan Tea Party members want to go over the cliff because it will cut the national deficit These recalcitrants would not compromise even with the Boehner proposal. Republicans plain don't care if the US goes over the cliff because the Rich strive in a depression. Obama does not want to go over the fiscal cliff because the people he cares most about the middle class and the lower class end up as the victims in a depression.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1356358943963</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:22:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356359759066-14</Id><Title>Homicide Offenders by race</Title><Msg>The rate of homicide offenders is 757% higher for black Americans than white Americans. FBI Bureau of Justice Statistics numbers on gun homicides per 100,000 population by race, show that the rate for white Americans are the same as rates for European countries 3.5/100,000 but that the rate for black Americans is 26.5/100,000 Other facts from the FBI's Homicide Trends in the USA: Murder rates in the US are rapidly declining. The majority of murders are committed by blacks using illegal guns in states which voted heavily for Obama. Many Democrats intentionally blur facts to try to give the impression that white Repuplicans are gut nut jobs and that a culture of guns is a problem that is increasing in ALL parts of the USA. But the statistics prove that this is not the case. In order to get a better understanding and avoid confusion as to where the real problem is, you need to separate the black from the white murder rates, separate the red state from the blue state murder rates and separate the legal and illegal gun murder rates. When you do this, you see that the real problem lies in the extreme misbehavior of Obama’s Democrat constituency in blue state cities like Chicago, Detroit, NY, etc. So instead of being honest and admitting that Democrats have a problem controlling their gun crime problem in their blue states and blue cities, Democrats mobilize their crazy progressive anti-gun fanatics who want to take guns away from everyone. This is why you see these nuts playing to people's emotions rather than discussing statistics and reality of where the real problem lies. So it isn't that America has a gun problem but rather blue/Democrat America has a gun problem. Blue/Democrats need to stop blaming others like little brainless children and start being honest with themselves in taking ownership of their own problems, and most of they need to stop their war against law abiding people by trying to strip them of their constitutional rights.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1356359759066</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:35:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356360734150-15</Id><Topic><Title>Homicide Offenders by race</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1356359759066</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:35:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The big contribtor over the decades basically starting with JBJ's Great Society, and his welfare state is liberals destroying the very fabric/foundation of America. They've intentionally taken GOD out of the publics view, attacked Christians as right wing zellots, They've destroyed the inner citties with their liberal policies removing any ownership in America Blacks could have achieved replacing that with generations of welfare brolken homes feeding at the trough on the govt plantation knowing they would vote democrat to keep the freebies coming...tax payer funded abortion, and on, and on. Take a tour through a city like Chicago, or Detroit, and see hwo they've done. And now we have no more money, deep in debt, and Obama wants to increase taxes on the rich to keep socialism afloat.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356360734150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:52:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356360744287-16</Id><Topic><Title>Over the cliff layoffs have started, The best thing is to go over the cliff , we get spending cuts and higher taxes its the best thing for the USA in the long run, but it will hurt and we will get over it just like 1937</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356315789347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 21:23:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get ready for the market drop, Protect your 401k's first half of the year is going to be real bad</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356360744287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:52:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356361062731-17</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is what gets attacked..ANYONE, ANY GROUP that speaks against big, centralized govt socialistm. If you do not want taxes raised to pay for it, if you want waste reduced in govt., if you speak out against the rising cost that we can no longer pay for...you GET ATTACKED!...from the Tea Party folks, to all GOP conservatives! Right now the socialists wanting more, and more funding for bigger centralized govt, and more massive debt, are attacking Marko Rubio ALREADY!! They see him as the theat to their ideology in 2016. Best wise up America.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356361062731</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:57:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356361166394-18</Id><Title>Good Place to Short</Title><Msg>Rangebound stocks are good to fade at support/resistance until that barrier breaks. BA is right at multi-year resistance. Good short here until it's not.</Msg><Username>xtgeminiman</Username><Timestamp>1356361166394</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:59:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356361471924-19</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If we had fair ...Non Diabold elections Ron Paul would have been the GOP candidate...never has it been more obvious how our election cycles are controlled then this one...Google "black box.org" by Bev Harris to show how courrupt the voting was...so folks talking about Rubio this or Romney that ...does not matter....The older I get the more we have to go after ROOT causes.....Our voting systems should go back to paper ballots...and the Federal Reserve needs to be disbanded with Congress controlling the issuance of the money supply as mandated by the Constitution...(not private bankers)...there is no other hope now.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356361471924</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 10:04:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356362744279-20</Id><Topic><Title>BA is too superior to skip right now. Explore why!</Title><Username>raylal56</Username><Timestamp>1356353678873</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 07:54:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i love them</Msg><Username>davisjames686</Username><Timestamp>1356362744279</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 10:25:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356363651181-21</Id><Topic><Title>BA is too superior to skip right now. Explore why!</Title><Username>raylal56</Username><Timestamp>1356353678873</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 07:54:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks good</Msg><Username>larryschuler501</Username><Timestamp>1356363651181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 10:40:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356364235218-22</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How typically UN-AMERICAN of you. Defend the second amendment by disposing of the first. Typical Spartaloon anti-logic. What a despicable Anti-American creep you are.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1356364235218</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 10:50:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356365053869-23</Id><Topic><Title>Setting the Record Straight</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1356358943963</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:22:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you insane enough not to want to cut the national? You set the record straight alright. You're a generational thief and belong to a party of thieves that are now stealing from future generations.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356365053869</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:04:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356365489651-24</Id><Topic><Title>Setting the Record Straight</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1356358943963</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:22:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There can only be one conclusion...the left want to take down the country. When we hit rock bottom, and more murders have been created, more poverty created, more debt created that we can not recover from, the left then considers it victory, and now a communist style fed govt takes over total control. There is little difference between Progressivism, and communism...matter of what term the left likes to use.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356365489651</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:11:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356365755843-25</Id><Title>The Government Takes in More Money Than it's Competent to Manage</Title><Msg>That's a fact proven by $16.5 trillion of debt. It's insane to give them more. DO NOT raise the debt limit for these numbskulls. Oh sure, they'll scream we can't pay SS benefits, Veteran's benefits and we'll default on out debt while waste money on a thousand socialized programs and donor pay-offs. Not raising the debt limit is the only sure way to force them to balance the budget.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356365755843</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:15:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356366137192-26</Id><Title>If Democrats Were Serious about Reducing the Debt.......</Title><Msg>.....they wouldn't have refused to produce a budget for the past 3 going om 4 years while they were running up $ trillion + deficits each year.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356366137192</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:22:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356366567986-27</Id><Topic><Title>If Democrats Were Serious about Reducing the Debt.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356366137192</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The feds own, Obama's own CBO, his congressional Budget Office reported that it would be EASY to reduce 1.6 trillion dollars from fed. govt spending by eliminating duplications, policies/programs we've paid for for years that we don't need, govt waste that is easy to identify.....Obama said "stick it in your ear". Obama is more ideologically driven to establish socialism getting a grip on more, and more sectors of the economy, and destroying those GOP bad guys that want to stop it.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356366567986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:29:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356368932769-28</Id><Title>Banker run Publication calls for repeal of Second Amendment...Right on Cue!</Title><Msg>The Economist has called for “drastic gun control” in the wake of the Sandy Hook tragedy, saying that the Constitution should be amended to ban all guns on a national scale. In a brazen editorial published on its website this past weekend, the Bilderberg endorsed outlet notes “If America is ever to confront its obsession with guns, that time is now.” The piece compares Adam Lanza’s rampage in Newtown to an incident in China, where a deranged maniac recently attacked a classroom of children with a knife. Because firearms are banned in the Communist state, none of the children were killed. ” Every country has its madmen” argues the editorial, intimating that living under a tyrannical government regime is preferable because your children are safer. The article also compares US murder rates to those of Britain and Germany, contending that more guns equates to more homicides. ” America’s murder rate is four times higher than Britain’s” the editorial suggests, without noting that the population of the US is approximately six times larger than that of Britain, and that when firearms were banned in the UK, gun crime exploded. The piece then calls for the reinstatement of the assault rifle ban and an end to “gun-show exemption” from background checks, before outright calling for the repeal of the Second Amendment. “If you want to be safer, change the constitution” the editorial suggests, in a remark that would have Benjamin Franklin spinning. “The great bulk of America’s murders are committed with ‘ordinary’ handguns,” the piece adds, arguing that gun control legislation needs to become all encompassing. “Handgun bans, such as those that operated in Chicago and Washington, DC, before the Supreme Court struck them down, would be needed on a national scale.” the piece continues. “Gun licences, obtainable only after extensive police and medical review as in most other civilised countries, would be needed for hunting and sporting weapons.” the editorial adds, outlining a plan for full scale disarmament of the American people. “Tough police action, coupled with an extensive “buy-back” programme, would be needed to mop up the hundreds of millions of guns that are already held.” the piece adds, ridiculously comparing taking guns away from Americans to sweeping some sort of unsightly mess under the rug. “If, as seems probable, this is held to conflict with the constitution, then the constitution needs to be amended.” the piece states in a final audacious and tawdry conclusion. The editors admit that “None of this is likely to happen soon”; too right, not before a full scale civil war breaks out. Of course, one would fully expect this kind of offering from a British based “newspaper” that is for the most part owned by the Rothschild banking family and a group of shareholders intrinsically tied to the world’s megabanks. The piece represents the latest knee jerk and unconsidered offering from the corporate media, calling for completely disarming and re-educating the populace. A week ago Reuters argued that “Obama should treat gun control like LBJ did civil rights”, outlining a plan for gun-control education programs to be initiated in schools. A horde of Hollywood celebrities have also jumped on the gun control bandwagon, without hesitation and without consideration that the disengaged unreality of mass culture many of them ceaselessly promote could be more of a major factor in such rare and tragic acts of wanton violence.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356368932769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:08:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356369319777-29</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In a response to Morgan’s complaint, when he tweeted, “Ironic U.S. gun rights campaign to deport me for ‘attacking 2nd Amendment rights’ – is my opinion not protected under 1st Amendment rights?,” Wall Street Journal columnist James Taranto responded, “Your opinion is protected, your presence in the U.S. is not. See Kleindienst v. Mandel (1972).” LOL...I SHOOT I SCORE !!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356369319777</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:15:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356369656185-30</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know you're a looney toon when you have to give yourself your own kudos. Loon.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356369656185</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:20:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356369779262-31</Id><Topic><Title>If Democrats Were Serious about Reducing the Debt.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356366137192</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What part of the word "Congressional" in front of "Budget Office" leads you to believe it is Obama's?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356369779262</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:22:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356370296274-32</Id><Topic><Title>Message to All the Anti-religon and Anti - NRA Nutjobs</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356293703121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 15:15:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you have any idea what you are talking about, please try again to put it in words. You sound like you are going for the Harry Caul award for posting vacuous questions.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356370296274</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:31:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356370520269-33</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing you "scored" was another piece of proof that you are an Un-American POS. Your reference does not apply (I am sure you are too looney to get that). "Kleindienst v. Mandel, 408 U.S. 753 (1972), was a decision by the United States Supreme Court, which held that the United States Attorney General has the right to refuse somebody's entry to the United States, " Piers is already here, and has violated no law. What is ironic and amusing is that if the accident of your birth did not occur in the US, this would apply to you. You would think your discharge from the air force due to mental illness would sink in, but then you are a whack job.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1356370520269</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:35:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356370709561-34</Id><Topic><Title>BA is too superior to skip right now. Explore why!</Title><Username>raylal56</Username><Timestamp>1356353678873</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 07:54:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>biggest winners around</Msg><Username>rickyanthony361</Username><Timestamp>1356370709561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:38:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356371035408-35</Id><Topic><Title>Over the cliff layoffs have started, The best thing is to go over the cliff , we get spending cuts and higher taxes its the best thing for the USA in the long run, but it will hurt and we will get over it just like 1937</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1356315789347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 21:23:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Balanced is better than cuts only or tax hikes only, but......</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1356371035408</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:43:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356371046038-36</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deporting a foreigner, (who is not a US citizen in any case) does not violate their first amendment rights...Sorry norividiot..I will take Justice Stevens and Blackmun from the supreme courts words over yours every singel day and twice on Sundays. (I shoot I score again) Taranto linked to transcripts from a 1972 U.S. Supreme Court ruling that the U.S. Attorney General’s refusal to allow a foreign journalist into the United States did not violate the First Amendment. The case resulted from Nixon administration attorney general Richard Kleindienst’s refusal to grant a temporary nonimmigrant visa to Marxist Belgian journalist Ernest Mandel. Taranto’s tweet was praised by Twitter users who would like to send Morgan back to his native land.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356371046038</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:44:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356371158339-37</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you think if both the Chinese and Russians want us to do something, that it raises a red flag?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1356371158339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:45:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356372866431-38</Id><Topic><Title>BA is too superior to skip right now. Explore why!</Title><Username>raylal56</Username><Timestamp>1356353678873</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 07:54:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yup cash in</Msg><Username>traviswillie228</Username><Timestamp>1356372866431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 13:14:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356373200336-39</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You miss the point, Sparty. The point is that you support sending people away simply because you disagree with what they say. That means it is not Piers who is unAmerican and un-Constitution and un-individual rights -- It's YOU. Patriot my hairy cheek.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356373200336</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 13:20:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356375511010-40</Id><Topic><Title>48 planes delivered so far.in DEcember</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1356117754578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:22:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>total as of Saturday is now 52. Added 1 each 737, 747, 777, 787.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1356375511010</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 13:58:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356375861743-41</Id><Topic><Title>BA is too superior to skip right now. Explore why!</Title><Username>raylal56</Username><Timestamp>1356353678873</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 07:54:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>read the report</Msg><Username>rdavid543</Username><Timestamp>1356375861743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:04:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356376772277-42</Id><Title>A 4500 dollar class to get a job at Boeing??</Title><Msg>i worked at A-3730 at Plant 2 from 66-70 and it was a great job. They hired almost everyone that came from North Dakota. A dollar an hour job to 3.50 an hour, plus 95 bucks to work the weekend was a great incentive. A nice one bedroom apartment was 100 bucks a month, so a weekend of work would pay your rent for the month. i had a graveyard desk job getting blueprints and rept's and chasing down tools that the expediters couldn't find. The new 737 tool orders were coming in by the bucket load. i was crazy enough to work one stretch of 70 nights. They used to have their own employment office and if you knew someone on the inside, most likely you had a job. A friend who trained me in the garage door business and who's brother owned the business, later saw the business fold and tried to get on at Boeing. Even though he had worked for many years putting in garage doors, framing and building his own house, including the wiring and plumbing, the lady at the employment office told him he didn't have enough mechanical experience and didn't hire him. A week earlier i did a spring change for a Boeing supervisor who lived in Kirkland. i gave him a call and he told me to bring Rod over the next night. A week later Rod was driving a fork-lift at Boeing Everett. He worked a few months and then moved into Maintenance. A did a spring change the other day for a Boeing worker who paid out the 4500 bucks and was given a job. There are so many young people around here who don't have 450 bucks, much less 4500 and they can't get past the computer. THEY WANT TO WORK. A computer might have a mechanical brain, but it doesn't have a Heart.....</Msg><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1356376772277</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:19:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356376843211-43</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "I shoot I score" is simply a parody of you logging in under different ID's to say "He shoots he scores" to do that VERY thing. You've never fooled anyone...but if immitation is the sincererst form of flattery you can be flatered if you so choose.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356376843211</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:20:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356376901155-44</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well thats the latest joke...what do the Russians the Chinese and Obama ALL ahve in common...the disarming of our citizens</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356376901155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:21:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356377581034-45</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps he will NOT be deported but 6 supreme court justices disagreed with your principle. For example.. the Supreme Court casein question, Kleindienst v. Mandel was regarding a Man who advocated Communism in the United states, similar to what is happenning with Morgan...Now Dik...bear in mind you ALSO advocate communism and other anti America values, but I NEVER advocated deporting you ..you are an American citizen and entitled to your Objectional views.......Piers Morgan is NOT!!!!!. (I tried to dumb down the concepts as much as I could for you to understand)</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356377581034</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:33:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356378021256-46</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry Sparty, Your case does not apply. Morgan is ALREADY HERE and has legal residency. The case you quote is for denying entry to somebody that is overseas and not here yet. You shoot and don't even get it on the paper. TIme to re-zero your brain.</Msg><Username>gerbilfood4me</Username><Timestamp>1356378021256</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:40:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356378251873-47</Id><Topic><Title>America Must Stop Codling the Mediocre Class</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356102848431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're wasting your time trying to educate anyone on this board. If my only choices were a job at Boeing or retirement, it's time to quit. I wouldn't last a day in this environment. How do any of the professionals do it?</Msg><Username>lmquaalude</Username><Timestamp>1356378251873</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:44:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356378862683-48</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry Gerbil (Genna in disguise...its obvious so dont deny it)..its YOU that are missing the point and Multiple Supreme Court Judges disagree with you. and I quote "First, it argues that exclusion of Mandel involves no restriction on First Amendment rights at all since what is restricted is "only action -- the action of the alien in coming into this country." The Government also suggests that the First Amendment is inapplicable because appellees have free access to Mandel's ideas through his books and speeches, and because "technological developments," such as tapes or telephone hook-ups, readily supplant his physical presence. This isnt about restrciting Free Speech, he can STILL make his claims heard in Great Britain or ANY OTHER state he so chooses, and ANYONE who wants to hear his rants such as yourself can do so... but he has no AUTOMATIC right to stay in America....just as in the case previously stated.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356378862683</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:54:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356378986084-49</Id><Topic><Title>Merry Christmas, Piers Morgan</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356378273842</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:44:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps you can start a petition to see how many people want Piers Morgan to STAY. I shoot I score !</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356378986084</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:56:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356379554514-50</Id><Topic><Title>Merry Christmas, Piers Morgan</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356378273842</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:44:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got a link for the 300,000,000 that all feverishly want Morgan to stay ? Facts dont seem to faze you dik..but Hypocracy IS your friend..you know like saying anyone who objects to Obamas endless Wars is a racist while he kills Thousands of Brown women and Children on the other side of the world.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356379554514</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 15:05:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356381409536-51</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd say his brain is already at zero ... Oh, you mean ... sorry! Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356381409536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 15:36:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356381473625-52</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope the White House response is, "Kiss it."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356381473625</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 15:37:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356381550384-53</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got it Loon. The fact that you are ALWAYS wrong about other posters being me only makes it more hilarious.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356381550384</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 15:39:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356381804556-54</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Genna/Nowarrantneeded/Gerbil .. I could care less how many IDs you relog in as and could care less if you think I'm a loon. Speaking of Loon No sane person could possibly believe that that drugged-out little punk who murdered all those children in Connecticut would have even contemplated, let alone succeded, in doing what he did if there were two armed security guards at the entrance of that elementary school. All of the “mainstream media,” from Joe Scarborough and his fellow liberal cackling hens and crowing roosters on MSNBC, to the neocons at the New York Post, are either crazy or insidious liars and propagandists whose objective is to disarm the law-abiding civilian population. Totalitarian control is only possible in a disarmed society, as the Nazis and communists demonstrated in the twentieth century. If believing this makes me a loon then sign me up in spades.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356381804556</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 15:43:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356382167155-55</Id><Topic><Title>If Democrats Were Serious about Reducing the Debt.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356366137192</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not one dime of anyone's new budget goes to reducing the debt!!!</Msg><Username>sparrowgt</Username><Timestamp>1356382167155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 15:49:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356382376197-56</Id><Topic><Title>Good Place to Short</Title><Username>xtgeminiman</Username><Timestamp>1356361166394</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 09:59:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fine! It's a good place to take profits! Either way, this is a sell up here.</Msg><Username>xtgeminiman</Username><Timestamp>1356382376197</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 15:52:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356382604180-57</Id><Topic><Title>V-22 dumps crew member</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1356207937882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 15:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The V-22 has about 5 1/2 feet center. That's enhanced as all of the V-22 spec's are. You would likely have to find C-47 blue prints to get a figure, however passengers walking upright was a design requirement. I have been in them, a tall person has room. Its a part of the design that steered future aircraft design.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1356382604180</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 15:56:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356382866561-58</Id><Title>POTUS wants to go over the cliff</Title><Msg>And blame it on the GOP. its about raising everyone's taxes,down sizing the military, going after 401k's, etc. etc. then the welfare state. You left wingers will bellyache, and blame it on the GOP.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1356382866561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 16:01:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356383041501-59</Id><Topic><Title>V-22 dumps crew member</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1356207937882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 15:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw a source that said 5.5 feet, and I agree that's short. But I saw another that said 6 feet and that's just 2" short of a CH-47, which I'm sure was taller than a CH-46. Every aircraft has problems that flight crews have to train around -- the Huey was too loud (and a little thin-skinned) to my taste. So we'll have to agree to disagree that a low overhead makes the V-22 a POS. I would not like to fly it because it has to capability to autorotate in the event ot total power loss. But I cannot see how losing an passenger can be considered a design flaw. Seems like Darwin to me. You know what they say: "Life's a beetch, then you die." Merry Christmas!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356383041501</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 16:04:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356383128926-60</Id><Topic><Title>Merry Christmas, Piers Morgan</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356378273842</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:44:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Piers Morgan has a net worth of $20 million and was born with a silver spoon in his mouth in an upper cl#$%$ family yet this dishonest journalist Tim Molloy tries to make it look like Piers is some poor Eastern European that came here with nothing more than the shirt on his back and worked his #$%$ off to be successful. Tim Molloy is a #$%$ artist selling fantasy and false equivalence that only #$%$ could swallow. Chew slowly Hooz. ROTFLOL</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1356383128926</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 16:05:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356383168810-61</Id><Topic><Title>V-22 dumps crew member</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1356207937882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 15:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: the V-22 "... has NO capability to autorotate ..." sorry for the typo.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356383168810</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 16:06:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356383667084-62</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Having such confidence in two armed guards does not make you a loon, Sparty. Almost everything else about you makes you a loon -- the paranoia that makes you think every poster you dislike is me, your oath-keeping super-patriotism, the way you want everyone to worship your 25 years sitting one your butt in uniform, but belittle the service of anyone who disagrees with you politically, your totally whacked out understanding of MOST history, and the viciousness of your ad hominem attacks on everyone you accuse of ad hominem attacks. Oh, and did I mention all the rights of others you are perfectly willing to trample as you wrap yourself in the flag and spank your monket while you skim the Constitution without grasping any of it? Oh, and let's not forget the wild-eyed speculations -- none of which has ever proven true -- that you call "The PROPHECIES of Spartacus." THAT's what makes you a Looney Toon.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356383667084</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 16:14:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356386366170-63</Id><Title>Idiots are born every minute!</Title><Msg>The last time Boeing stock went to the next level was back in 1970. Things are a changing at Boeing and Boeing is going to be a 100 dollar stock. Don't believe, wait and see!</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1356386366170</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 16:59:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356387646660-64</Id><Topic><Title>Idiots are born every minute!</Title><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1356386366170</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 16:59:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO, not in this economic depressing climate. No one knows if Obama will come in, and steal stocks from shareholders.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356387646660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 17:20:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356389207674-65</Id><Topic><Title>Merry Christmas, Piers Morgan</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356378273842</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 14:44:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly...and Piers Morgan is SURROUNDED by security with guns....yet we have idiots who claim we cant protect ourselves breeding an atmosphere of victimhood.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356389207674</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 17:46:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356391437212-66</Id><Topic><Title>POTUS wants to go over the cliff</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1356382866561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 16:01:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a dumb post - you hitting the Christmas sauce already? LOL</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1356391437212</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 18:23:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356392456788-67</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THe Kent Raven : "I hope the White House response is, "Kiss it." Maybe the Whitehouse should LEAD BY EXAMPLE and have all the Secret Service disarm...</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356392456788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 18:40:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356392688576-68</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356392688576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 18:44:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356395203007-69</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one is asking you to disarm, Loon -- or expecting you too. It's another one of your straw-man reductio ad absurdumb-dumbs.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356395203007</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:26:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356395901268-70</Id><Title>God Bless President Obama !</Title><Msg>And God bless the USA</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356395901268</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:38:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356396494287-71</Id><Title>OJ SIMPSON DIDN'T HAVE A GUN</Title><Msg>when his wife was killed.......</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356396494287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:48:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356396733807-72</Id><Title>Regarding Gold....Alan Greenspan says</Title><Msg>"We know that by studying the Weimar Republic...in Extremis...only GOLD has real value"</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356396733807</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:52:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356397722109-73</Id><Topic><Title>OJ SIMPSON DIDN'T HAVE A GUN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356396494287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:48:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"OJ SIMPSON DIDN'T HAVE A GUN" Have you ever considered that's probably why he killed 93% less than the Newtown gunman?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1356397722109</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:08:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356398035059-74</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. Go get some help. 2. Go get a life.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1356398035059</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:13:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356398285116-75</Id><Title>Charlie Sheen To Be Crapo In "Driving Like Crapo"</Title><Msg>Nothing funnier in comedy than real life Republicans. Republicans are well, just too dumb to realize their stupid. Potatoe, Mission Accomplished, I'm not a #$%$, ketchup is a vegetable, media is killing people not guns, Rush is a Oxycontin addict, the comedy doesn't end.</Msg><Username>waynelepierre</Username><Timestamp>1356398285116</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:18:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356398297302-76</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are all going to needs Gods help in the dark times ahead</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356398297302</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:18:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356398523998-77</Id><Topic><Title>OJ SIMPSON DIDN'T HAVE A GUN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356396494287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:48:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shoudln't we ban knives too ? ...and the guy who killed with chainsaw...lets remove them from Home Depot...keep going you're making a lot of sense</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356398523998</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:22:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356398959637-78</Id><Topic><Title>OJ SIMPSON DIDN'T HAVE A GUN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356396494287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:48:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess the rest of the world always seems to miss the *REAL* story.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1356398959637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:29:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356399096768-79</Id><Topic><Title>A Christmas Eve Present</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356392062509</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 18:34:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump it !!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1356399096768</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:31:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356399262661-80</Id><Topic><Title>OJ SIMPSON DIDN'T HAVE A GUN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356396494287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:48:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YEAH...like when Barry Hussein Obama Frank Marshall Davis said he would never sign the NDAA last New Years Eve...then went ahead and signed it anyway..after head faking numerous senators.....and with the stroke of a pen signed away Due Process and Habeuw Corpus...so I ask you honestly...SHOULD WE TRUST A GUY WHO SIGNED AWAY YOUR MOST SACRED RIGHT TO A QUICK AND SPEEDY TRIAL TO DECIDE IF AMERICANS SHOULD BE ARMED OR DISARMED ?? THINK ABOUT IT ..DO YOU REALLY TRUST THIS GUY ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356399262661</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:34:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356399333725-81</Id><Topic><Title>Regarding Gold....Alan Greenspan says</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356396733807</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 19:52:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356399333725</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:35:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356399359805-82</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump it !!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356399359805</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:35:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356399397844-83</Id><Topic><Title>Banker run Publication calls for repeal of Second Amendment...Right on Cue!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356368932769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 12:08:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump it !!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356399397844</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:36:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356399447939-84</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Global Elite need to Disarm us before the inevitable collapse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355749618478</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 08:06:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump !!!!!!!...!!!!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356399447939</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 20:37:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356400872705-85</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Crying for the Kids Killed by False Flag "Fast and Furious" ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355969329825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 21:08:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356400872705</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:01:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356400916178-86</Id><Topic><Title>Man who ALMOSt went on shooting spree STOPPED by a man with a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355976779166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 23:12:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots he scores</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356400916178</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:01:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356401776263-87</Id><Topic><Title>Man who ALMOSt went on shooting spree STOPPED by a man with a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355976779166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 23:12:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Off duty deputy........not some death wish 3 sucker</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1356401776263</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:16:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356401947593-88</Id><Title>Finally, A 9/11 Truther Movie Starring Martin Sheen And Woody Harrelson</Title><Msg>Finally, A 9/11 Truther Movie Starring Martin Sheen And Woody Harrelson You've watched Martin Sheen play a beloved president, and you've watched Woody Harrelson play a high-powered political strategist (and beloved pornographer)—so why not watch them take on roles in a 9/11 Truther movie? The pair has reportedly signed on to star in "September Morn," a look at what really happened on September 11, 2001. The movie's website boasts a cast that also includes Ed Asner, Daniel Sunjata and Judd Nelson and the statement, "We the people demand that the government revisit and initiates a thorough and independent investigation to the tragic events of 911. In the vein of "Twelve Angry Men" this dramatic piece is set with a stellar and award winning cast and filmmakers." Truthers question how the World Trade Center Building 7 was destroyed: While the official line is that debris from WTC Tower 1 and fires caused it to collapse, truthers suggest it was the result of a controlled demolition by the government. Mayor and President of all things 9/11, Rudy Giuliani, deemed someone who asked about WTC 7 a "conspiracy nut" which is either an insult or a badge of honor—Giuliani did have his Office of Emergency Management there! Martin Sheen said in 2007, "I did not want to believe that my government could possibly be involved in such a thing, I could not live in a country that I thought could do that—that would be the ultimate betrayal. However, there have been so many revelations that now I have my doubts, and chief among them is Building 7 - how did they rig that building so that it came down on the evening of the day?” At a 9/11 Truther conference last year, panelists emphasized that events like the "October Surprise" and Watergate set precedent for a massive government conspiracy, therefore, it's totally feasible WTC 7 was blown up by the government. Deadline had reported that details about the film were expected to be revealed at the American Film Market next week, but now that Deadline article link is dead (here's the cached page). Will the conspiracy never end?!?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356401947593</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:19:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356402101374-89</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It means "HOW AND WHEN TO LIE" ... Somthing you have become very proficient at De-Genna-rette!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356402101374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:21:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356402646725-90</Id><Title>MICHAEL MOORE HAS "ARMED" BODYGUARD....as he critizises schools having Bodyguards !</Title><Msg>On Friday, filmmaker Michael Moore used his Twitter account to criticize the National Rifle Association's "National School Safety Shield" program. While Moore has a problem with an armed guard protecting every school, he doesn't seem to have a problem with an armed guard protecting him. The filmmaker, who rose to prominence with documentaries like the anti-gun Bowling for Columbine, often travels with a bodyguard, which is reasonable, considering his level of celebrity. That decision, however, led to an awkward situation in 2005 when his bodyguard was detained at JFK Airport in New York - for carrying a gun. The story has again resurfaced as the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting in Newtown, Connecticut has made gun control an issue again. Moore himself stepped into the fray by posting various anti-gun messages on Twitter. "Armed guards in schools? Hmmmm... Oh! That's why the 2 armed guards that were at Columbine HS that day were able to prevent the 15 deaths?" he tweeted Friday. On Tuesday, Moore tweeted the following statement: "Guns are for hunters...and cowards." There have been those who claim the 2005 story is untrue, but they are only partially correct. Initial reports that the bodyguard was arrested were not correct. The bodyguard was not arrested, and did declare to a screener that he had an unloaded handgun, which he had a permit for. However, he refused to check it into luggage, and insisted he be allowed to carry it with him on the plane. After being briefly detained to argue his case, the bodyguard was reportedly not allowed to carry it on his person. The fact that he does carry a gun to protect Moore is still true. It isn't the first time an anti-gun liberal has been caught being a hypocrite. California Senator Diane Feinstein has been critical of those advocating for increased concealed handgun access, but she admitted to having a concealed handgun permit in 1995. After saying the National Rifle Association doesn't care about children killed by guns, but only for "white, Republican life," it was revealed that Rosie O'Donnell's bodyguard carries a gun. She angrily blamed gun rights supporters for spreading the truth only to shame her.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356402646725</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:30:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356402941763-91</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think about BARRY's absolutley FRIGHTENING NAZI AGENDA...He has Signed teh NDAA (after he said he would not), which allows indefinite dtention of American citizens, no judge-no jury...then is in charge of "Fast and Furious" ...which was meant to demonize the second amendment.....and NOW wants to enforce a GLOBALIST-United Nations Treatey to disarm Americans.....Coincidently Communist China is calling for that very thing...NOW I ASK YOU...As a REAL AMERICAN ...After all this can you REALLY trust a guy who wants to disarm Americans ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356402941763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 21:35:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356404453983-92</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Crying for the Kids Killed by False Flag "Fast and Furious" ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355969329825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 21:08:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good point</Msg><Username>sparrowgt</Username><Timestamp>1356404453983</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 22:00:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356408911436-93</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Crying for the Kids Killed by False Flag "Fast and Furious" ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355969329825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 21:08:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats, Socialists/communists don't cry for innocent people....only for those that mightrovide some kind of political advantage. Same thing as in the USSR.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356408911436</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:15:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356409136835-94</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Global Elite need to Disarm us before the inevitable collapse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355749618478</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 08:06:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on Sparty! The global economic meltdown is close at hand and guns will be a necessity. DObama wants us defenseless.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356409136835</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:18:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356409518164-95</Id><Topic><Title>If Democrats Were Serious about Reducing the Debt.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356366137192</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 11:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama can't seem to produce a budget anyone will vote for. Genna could never find a job he could keep. No wonder he likes Obama.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356409518164</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:25:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356409520210-96</Id><Topic><Title>Petition to Deport Piers Morgan surpasses number of Signatures required to mandate a White House Response</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356357570493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 08:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then why were the two armed guards at Columbine so ineffective? There were literally hundreds of armed personnel at Fort Hood, why didn't that stop the mass killings there? The facts do not support your position, but then they never do.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1356409520210</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:25:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356409556937-97</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Global Elite need to Disarm us before the inevitable collapse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355749618478</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 08:06:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All the Fascist laws are in place. NDAA, Patriot Act, Surveillance on a mass scale, TSA gone wild...Get ready</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356409556937</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:25:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356410009487-98</Id><Title>Some Knucklehead just stated that Armed Guards are useless !!</Title><Msg>"On another thread...Some Knucklehead just stated that Armed Guards are useless...using Columbine as an example !!" If that is so, shouldn't Michael Moore get rid of his body guards ? Shouldn't Piers Morgan ? All of them hypocrytically complaining that Armed Guards at Schools would do no good...yet are surrounded by Guards and Guns....using this logic shouldn't Obama get rid of the secret service ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356410009487</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:33:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356410184296-99</Id><Topic><Title>Some Knucklehead just stated that Armed Guards are useless !!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356410009487</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:33:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Regardoing the Guards at Columbine...they kept the carnage less thaen it might have been: ----------------------------- Yes, the critics respond, and there was an armed security guard at Columbine High School in 1999. Yet, 12 students and a teacher were killed by two armed intruders, as if that disqualified the solution of placing armed guards, possibly unemployed army veterans, at each of our nation's 100,000-plus schools. Yes, there was, and it was the guard's presence and the resistance he and others offered that kept the carnage less than it might have been. On April 20, 1999, Neil Gardner, an armed sheriff's deputy who had been policing the school for almost two years, was eating lunch when Eric Harris and Dylan Klebold arrived at Columbine with their deadly arsenal and deadlier intentions. Gardner said he got a call from a custodian that he was needed in the school's back parking lot. A few minutes later, he encountered Harris, and the two exchanged gunfire. The exchange with Harris lasted for an extended period of time, during which Harris' gun jammed.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356410184296</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-24 23:36:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>