<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-31"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346387314000-1</Id><Title>The American Dream?</Title><Msg>http://reason.com/blog/2012/08/28/lundy-khoy-barely-escaped-pol-pots-purge</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1346387314000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 00:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346389080403-2</Id><Topic><Title>God Bless President Obama..!!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346358654838</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:30:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wu - you are still kicking. I figured you had a taste for a Slurpee and left Nannie Nervana-land NY for a red state, where you can still get them, and maybe kicked the lib kool-aid jones in your travels. Sadly it looks like I was wrong. But hey, Stickman 007 is a lot more dangerous sounding handle; I hear Joe Biden is Stickman 006.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1346389080403</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 00:58:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346391130800-3</Id><Topic><Title>God Bless President Obama..!!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346358654838</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:30:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. May the Lord bless former President Obama as he pursues a new career as a private citizen come the 20th of January 2013.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1346391130800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 01:32:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346391382215-4</Id><Topic><Title>No Bounce From The Convention, Obama Will Win Easily!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346355816477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:43:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, Get used to having your toes in the water as you contemplate an new career. The days of beating the drum for Obama are almost over. That was an incredible line-up of speeches at the RNC convention! Let's see, the Democrats plan to invite the condom queen, Fluke, to speak on behalf of what immoral point that so enamors the Dems? BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1346391382215</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 01:36:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346415083208-5</Id><Topic><Title>God Bless President Obama..!!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346358654838</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:30:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's very difficult to get a good job when all you have is a forged birth cert, a fake Social Security number, no college transcripts and a work history of total failure. Maybe he can get by with just some crazy jive talk. He should give it a try, because it has worked before.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1346415083208</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 08:11:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346417646000-6</Id><Title>The REPUBLIWHOPPERPALOOZA</Title><Msg>It was hard to count all the lies in Lyin Ryan's speech. There was the lie about when the GM plant in Kenosha closed, and why. There was the lie about Obamacare raiding Medicare. There was the lie about the "need" to cut Medicare, Medicaid and Social Security. But anyone who thought that Ryan was going to win the liar's contest at the convention wasn't counting on Wafflin Willard The Repub nominee trumped his running-mate with one line Thursday night. Willard, who started campaigning for president in 2007 and never stopped said: "I wish President Obama had succeeded."</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346417646000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 08:54:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346419069897-7</Id><Title>Reagan and Obama: A Tale of Two Recoveries</Title><Msg>How these two presidents responded to a deep recession reveals polar extremes in policy. And in results. Just Google the Title</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1346419069897</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346419578670-8</Id><Title>With out a change of Presidents.....</Title><Msg>.....why would you expect the next 4 years to be any different than the last for years?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1346419578670</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:26:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346419832628-9</Id><Title>Half of Democrats think that "the rich" don't benefit the economy</Title><Msg>I’d like to see them get a job from a poor person! Oops....wait a minute Democrats don't want jobs.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1346419832628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:30:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346420200816-10</Id><Title>Voters, are you bluffing?</Title><Msg>Now begins the final phase of this cognitive dissonance campaign. America’s 57th presidential election is the first devoted to calling the nation’s bluff. When Mitt Romney selected Paul Ryan, Republicans undertook the perilous but commendable project of forcing voters to face the fact that they fervently hold flatly incompatible beliefs. Twice as many Americans identify themselves as conservative as opposed to liberal. On Nov. 6 we will know if they mean it. If they are ideologically conservative but operationally liberal. If they talk like Jeffersonians but want to be governed by Hamiltonians. If their commitment to limited government is rhetorical or actual. If it is, as Daniel Patrick Moynihan suspected, a “civic religion, avowed but not constraining.” This is the problem for uneasy Republicans. The Democrats’ problem is worse because they are not uneasy about their dissonance, being blissfully unaware of it. In “Spoiled Rotten: How the Politics of Patronage Corrupted the Once Noble Democratic Party and Now Threatens the American Republic” — a book more measured and scholarly than its overwrought title — Jay Cost of the Weekly Standard says that the party has succumbed to “clientelism,” the process of purchasing cohorts of voters with federal favors. This has turned the party into the servant of the strong. Before Franklin Roosevelt, “liberal” described policies emphasizing liberty and individual rights. He, however, pioneered the politics of collective rights — of group entitlements. And his liberalism systematically developed policies not just to buy the allegiance of existing groups but to create groups that henceforth would be dependent on government. Under FDR, liberalism became the politics of creating an electoral majority from a mosaic of client groups. Labor unions got special legal standing, farmers got crop supports, business people got tariff protection and other subsidies, the elderly got pensions, and so on and on. Government no longer existed to protect natural rights but to confer special rights on favored cohorts. As Irving Kristol said, the New Deal preached not equal rights for all but equal privileges for all — for all, that is, who banded together to become wards of the government.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1346420200816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:36:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346420694660-11</Id><Title>U.S. Corporate Taxes Driving Businesses Abroad</Title><Msg>The Wall Street Journal reports that America’s uncompetitive corporate tax code is driving U.S. businesses to relocate their headquarters to other countries. One of the major reasons these businesses are fleeing our shores is taxes. Each of the countries the article cites as places where U.S. businesses have moved their headquarters—the United Kingdom and Ireland, for example—is a nation with a lower corporate tax rate than the United States. This is wholly unsurprising, since the U.S. now has the highest corporate tax rate in the developed world. No matter where a U.S. business relocates its headquarters, it would face a lower rate.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1346420694660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:44:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346420860000-12</Id><Topic><Title>The REPUBLIWHOPPERPALOOZA</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346417646000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 08:54:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>..." There was the lie about when the GM plant in Kenosha closed, and why." SOURCE - FACTS ?? .... There was the lie about Obamacare raiding Medicare... NOPE -ALREADY DONE - 7 PLUS BILLION REDUCTION IN MEDICARE THRU SO CALLED SAVINGS OVER A DECADE</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1346420860000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:47:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346421437276-13</Id><Title>737 competitor</Title><Msg>Bombardier Commercial Aircraft is considering a high-density version of its largest CSeries, the CS300, to meet growing demand from airlines for an aircraft with 160 seats. The Canadian airframer is hoping to make a decision “in the next few months,” Rob Dewar, VP and general manager for the CSeries program, tells Aviation Week. Dewar says the manufacturer has received requests from airlines for an aircraft that would offer cabin capacity for up to 160 seats. Such an aircraft would be particularly attractive to low-fare carriers, but it also places Bombardier in direct competition with Airbus and Boeing. If Bombardier proceeds with a high-density CS300, it may have to introduce double overwing exits to allow for quick disembarkation in an emergency. Dewar says Bombardier is discussing the issue with authorities and has not made a decision on how to proceed. If another overwing exit would have to be added on each side, the aircraft would incur a weight penalty over the baseline variant. According to Dewar, Bombardier is considering the double exit as an option, so customers of the baseline aircraft are not affected by the increased weight. Other changes to the CS300 likely include a reduction in the number of lavatories. Bombardier also has presented its customers slim seats that will allow for a 28-inch seat pitch. AirAsia CEO Tony Fernandes recently expressed interest in a 160-seat CS300 and has indicated that the airline has a need for about 100 such aircraft. However, the carrier also is negotiating a large follow-on order with Airbus that could be announced next month at the Berlin Air Show. Dewar says a decision about the high-density variant needs to be made “as soon as possible,” as the CS300 is nearing its detailed design phase. The CS300 is scheduled to enter service at the end of 2014, one year after the baseline CS100. According to Dewar, all fuselage parts for the CS100 static test aircraft have now arrived in Montreal, and the wings for the static aircraft are expected in September. The wings for the first flight-test CS100 are due in early October</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346421437276</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:57:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346421594819-14</Id><Topic><Title>737 competitor</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346421437276</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:57:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now it is clear why Boeing dallied so long before making up their mind to only build the up engined NG- they can still do an all composite replacement for the 737- it should be an off the shelf aircraft considering all of Boeings experience with the 787</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346421594819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:59:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346421776973-15</Id><Title>The article on the new C series aircraft was from the Wichita Business Journal.</Title><Msg>The URL somehow couldnt be disguised</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346421776973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346422152421-16</Id><Topic><Title>Half of Democrats think that "the rich" don't benefit the economy</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1346419832628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:30:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds good however the facts don't support your argument. 90% of all wealth in this country is inherited wealth. "Trust fund babies". They don't take risks with their money and they don't invest their money to create jobs. They buy T-bills for income and undeveloped land for long term, tax deferred, capital growth. And with their extra cash, they buy Congressmen to preserve their wealth. The inherited wealth in this country make decisions in this country because they feel they own the country. Its been like this since the days of the Roman empire.</Msg><Username>gpd8252</Username><Timestamp>1346422152421</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346422159504-17</Id><Title>Rmoney wants to abolish Soc. Sec. and Medicare</Title><Msg>same as Boosh, and privatize it all via the Wall St. bankers and vulture capitalists like himself...and we all know how honest they are all the while lowering taxes the most on the upper classes and paying for it by slashing benefits and raising fees on the most needy that is not going forward, but backwards to the days of the robber barons, company towns, and 18 hr. workdays for slave wages Never pull the lever for Willard</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346422159504</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:09:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346422313492-18</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney wants to abolish Soc. Sec. and Medicare</Title><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346422159504</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:09:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>....and repeal the Affordable Care Act (Obamacare) Is there anything more evil than a republican or bagger?</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346422313492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:11:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346422579112-19</Id><Title>Raygun had a recession and ran the debt to 4 trillion</Title><Msg>from a half trillion and that was 30 years ago when 400 billion was a lot of money but then we gotta give a handsome cowboy acter who always wears a white hat a pass right?</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346422579112</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346423206910-20</Id><Topic><Title>Raygun had a recession and ran the debt to 4 trillion</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346422579112</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the bedtime for bonzo pretzeldent bought us 100 MX missiles, gave millions upon millions in armamements to iran illegally and funeled the proceeds to the contras in nicaraugua, and to iraq, and to afghanistan before finally abandonning the freedom fighters in afghanistan, all with our taxpayer monies... what a great guy</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346423206910</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:26:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346423328824-21</Id><Topic><Title>Half of Democrats think that "the rich" don't benefit the economy</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1346419832628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:30:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you don't get is the "rich" benefit the economy significantly less than they think they do. The capital gains tax rate was implemented to spur savings (and investment), in reality most of it is used (legally) by people like Romney to shelter their income from the tax code. Any capital gains over 100K should be treated as straight income. Arrogance rarely meets reality.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1346423328824</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346423604433-22</Id><Topic><Title>Half of Democrats think that "the rich" don't benefit the economy</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1346419832628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:30:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so, you are just a coporate ho-ho who wants to squash the real job creators, the middle class and 'the poor' put every dollar back into the economy, even paying the proprty taxes of their landlords, while the middle-class struggles to pay more in taxes than the ultra-rich like Rmoney, who has not created a single job in the past eight years make my day just like the senile old geezer, clint, who wouldn't spend $20k to build a wheelchair ramp to comply with the ADA at his Carmel Mission Ranch Inn, but would spend three to five times that much in court costs before fianlly losing...</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346423604433</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:33:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346423916382-23</Id><Title>Rmoney and lyin' Ryan want to ban all abortions</Title><Msg>except those for those wealthy enough to have their private ob/gyn do a D&amp;C at the posh private office Repugs need more poor, unwanted babies to exploit for cheap labor and troops for their imperialistic wars</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346423916382</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346424185141-24</Id><Topic><Title>one more day</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346356712918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We need at least 6 deliveries today. Odds are against it but it could happen.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346424185141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:43:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346424270154-25</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney wants to abolish Soc. Sec. and Medicare</Title><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346422159504</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:09:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>get off the faux news channel crack-pipe you are sounding like the senile 82 year old clint someone needs to eiger sanction his grand torino and all the RWNJ lies</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346424270154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:44:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346424584566-26</Id><Topic><Title>Raygun had a recession and ran the debt to 4 trillion</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346422579112</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boosh43 had six years with a republicon congress, and still manged to double the national debt and bring on the Great Recession Facts! Exactly what Obama wants to do, but the republicon lyin' Ryan and 'bagger do-nothing congress would rather have America fail than Obama to succeed, Facts!</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346424584566</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346424839130-27</Id><Topic><Title>Raygun had a recession and ran the debt to 4 trillion</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346422579112</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey even tho it was Rayguns watch ole farry #$%$ gotta blame the Dems- hey go fairy go</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346424839130</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:53:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346424937996-28</Id><Topic><Title>Are BA employees over paid hillbillies?</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1346355964521</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:46:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you as dumb as you seem?</Msg><Username>duffymagoo</Username><Timestamp>1346424937996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:55:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346425177685-29</Id><Title>Lying Media "Fact Checkers" and Gullible Liberals</Title><Msg>The Media's 'Fact Check' Smokescreen Posted 08/30/2012 06:58 PM ET Journalism: If media "fact checkers" are just impartial guardians of the truth, how come they got their own facts wrong about Paul Ryan's speech, and did so in a way that helped President Obama's re-election effort? Case in point was the rush of "fact check" stories claiming Ryan misled when he talked about a shuttered auto plant in his home state. Washington Post fact-checker Glenn Kessler posted a piece — "Ryan misleads on GM plant closing in hometown" — saying Ryan "appeared to suggest" that Obama was responsible for the closure of a GM plant in Janesville, Wis. "That's not true," Kessler said. "The plant was closed in December 2008, before Obama was sworn in." What's not true are Kessler's "facts." Ryan didn't suggest Obama was responsible for shuttering the plant. Instead, he correctly noted that Obama promised during the campaign that the troubled plant "will be here for another hundred years" if his policies were enacted. Also, the plant didn't close in December 2008. It was still producing cars until April 2009. An AP "fact check" also claimed that "the plant halted production in December 2008" even though the AP itself reported in April 2009 that the plant was only then "closing for good." CNN's John King made the same claim about that plant closure. But when CNN looked more carefully at the evidence, it — to its credit — concluded that what Ryan said was "true." Subscribe to the IBD Editorials Podcast Media fact-checkers also complained about Ryan's charge that Obama is cutting $716 billion from Medicare to fund ObamaCare. Not true, they said. Medicare's growth is just being slowed. But Obama achieves that slower growth by making real cuts in provider payments. And in any case, the media always and everywhere call a reduction in the rate of federal spending growth a "cut." So why suddenly charge Ryan with being misleading for using that same term? In any case, Obama himself admitted that he's doing what Ryan says. In a November 2009 interview with ABC News, reporter Jake Tapper said to Obama that "one-third of the funding comes from cuts to Medicare," to which Obama's response was: "Right." The rest of Ryan's alleged factual errors aren't errors at all; it's just that the media didn't like how he said it. But since when is it a fact-checker's job to decide how a politician should construct his arguments? This isn't to say that journalists shouldn't check facts. Of course they should. The problem is that the mainstream press is now abusing the "fact check" label, using it to more aggressively push a liberal agenda without feeling the need to provide any balance whatsoever. And, as the reaction to the Ryan speech shows, they are now blatantly using it to provide air support for Obama. Is it any wonder that soon after Ryan's speech ended, the Obama campaign rushed out an ad using the media's "fact check" stories as its source?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346425177685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:59:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346425182323-30</Id><Title>Sports and politics...</Title><Msg>If politics is sport all the politicians wii be fighting at wwe raw instead at the UFC.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1346425182323</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:59:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346425434193-31</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney and lyin' Ryan want to ban all abortions</Title><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346423916382</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where's the Evidence to support your Liberal Lying nonsense? You are a fool... prog101 It's the Economy, Stupid, err, prog!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346425434193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:03:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346425522911-32</Id><Title>Republicans sound like a broken record!!</Title><Msg>.... singing the same ole hate messages !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346425522911</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:05:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346425663589-33</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney wants to abolish Soc. Sec. and Medicare</Title><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346422159504</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:09:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again, prog, where is your evidence to support your Lying Liberal nonsense? Don't have any, eh? Thought so. It is Obama that stole $700 plus Billion from MediCare to pay for ObamaCare... that's pathetic and the Seniors are mad as 'ell at Obama... Florida is lost for Obama!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346425663589</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:07:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346425739118-34</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney wants to abolish Soc. Sec. and Medicare</Title><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346422159504</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:09:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where's the RWNJ plan? Everyting was far worse under Boosh, and Rmoney/lyin' Ryan offer nothing excpet more failed Boosh RWNJ policies! We don't need an etch-a-sketch windsock for a president!</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346425739118</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:08:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346425760533-35</Id><Topic><Title>God Bless President Obama..!!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346358654838</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:30:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Definitely!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346425760533</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:09:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346425895421-36</Id><Title>Is History gonna repeat?</Title><Msg>Cheaney Bush and his weapons of mass destruction cost plus Iraq War "Were at War so worry about the Debt later and blame the Democrats to boot!" Ryan Romney and his much more costly centrifuges cost plus War with Iran "Were at War so let the next administration worry about the debt and we can blame them Democrats and their entitlements for it again anyway!"</Msg><Username>lostcityundead</Username><Timestamp>1346425895421</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346425910473-37</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans sound like a broken record!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346425522911</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:05:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the Unemployment Rate hovering above 8% for three years plus is a broken record... you should ask the Hurting Americans out of a job what they think They want real Change this Election Cycle and not what Obama "Hopes" for...</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346425910473</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:11:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346426050737-38</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Media "Fact Checkers" and Gullible Liberals</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346425177685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:59:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fox News called Ryan a blatant liar, world record sized. And the RWNJ dittoheads believe that Obama removed a bust of Churchill from the \ Oval Office and sent it back to England. Face it, when Mittens spoke at the RNC you creamed your panties and hairydope licked it up.</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346426050737</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:14:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346426074567-39</Id><Topic><Title>Is History gonna repeat?</Title><Username>lostcityundead</Username><Timestamp>1346425895421</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lost, did you get past 8th grade?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346426074567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346426150553-40</Id><Title>Ryan selection and the RNC = No bounce in the polls</Title><Msg>Willard is doomed in November HaHaHaHa</Msg><Username>annegsirhc</Username><Timestamp>1346426150553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:15:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346426321988-41</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans sound like a broken record!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346425522911</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:05:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everything is still getting better since the Boosh Great Recession. Real Americans do not want a return of the failed RWNJ policies. Forward, not backwards!</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1346426321988</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346426335435-42</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan selection and the RNC = No bounce in the polls</Title><Username>annegsirhc</Username><Timestamp>1346426150553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, Dummy, Romney just spoke last night... Polls will take a day or two catch up and report. Are you really that dumb?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346426335435</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:18:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346426480416-43</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans sound like a broken record!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346425522911</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:05:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Things are NOT getting better under Obama... Unemployment is Higher under Obama than anytime under W... Google and check for yourself.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346426480416</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:21:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346426797913-44</Id><Title>The REPUBLIWHOPPERPALOOZAS</Title><Msg>The repubs have created universe of Orwellian dimension – where anything can be asserted, where paid pollsters and propagandists are free to create whatever concoction of lies will help elect their clients, and where “fact-checkers” are as irrelevant and intrusive as is the truth.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346426797913</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:26:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346426889388-45</Id><Title>Labor Day is Not a Socialist Holiday</Title><Msg>its a tribute for the contributions and achievements of American workers - Not for the contributions of greedy Corprate America....</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346426889388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:28:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427096907-46</Id><Topic><Title>Is History gonna repeat?</Title><Username>lostcityundead</Username><Timestamp>1346425895421</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There have been a troubling suggestions of war coming out of Republicans at the RNC in Tampa. Mitt Romney reiterated this on Thursday, when he accepted his party's 2012 nomination for president of the United States. Romney criticized President Obama for not using force against Iran to stop their nuclear program, saying that he "has failed to slow Iran's nuclear threat." But he also made comments about the relationship between the United States and Russia that implied a willingness to ignite another Cold War. Romney said that President Obama was "eager to give Russia's president Putin the flexibility he desires after the election." Add those comments to Romney's economic plan, which adds another $1 trillion to the defense budget, and Americans have serious cause for concern. Talk of war at a political convention by a candidate with absolutely no foreign policy experience should send up a warning flag to a war-weary nation. Sen. John McCain (R-AZ) also made remarks on Wednesday that suggested another war was the answer to America's foreign policy issues. "We are now being tested by an array of threats that are more complex, more numerous, and just as deeply and deadly as I can recall in my lifetime," McCain said. "We can't afford to give governments in Russia and China a veto over how we defend our interests and the progress of our values in the world. I believe we cannot afford to substitute a political timetable to a military strategy," he added. McCain then made his own plea to expand the deficit with more defense spending for more wars, and mentioned troubled spots in the Middle East including, Syria and Iran. He also mentioned Russia. Both Romney and McCain readily used the words "freedom," and "strength" and "justice," as if they came with no price tag. While war-mongering and more defense spending may not have been a detail many people took away from the RNC, it should have been. This is dangerous talk from Romney, whose first visit abroad as a candidate, resulted in little more than a diplomatic disaster and embarrassment for the United States.</Msg><Username>lostcityundead</Username><Timestamp>1346427096907</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:31:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427245121-47</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Media "Fact Checkers" and Gullible Liberals</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346425177685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:59:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got any evidence on the Ryan lie? Didn't think so. Also, the story on returning the Bust of Churchill Story was/is True... The Obama Adm issued an Apology for getting caught in another lie. Want me to post the WH Apology for you? For Libs like you, WH stands for White House... where Obama lives for only a few more months. Geez, you Libs are Dumb!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346427245121</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427306864-48</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan selection and the RNC = No bounce in the polls</Title><Username>annegsirhc</Username><Timestamp>1346426150553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you that dumb imadumb?</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1346427306864</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:35:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427715491-49</Id><Topic><Title>Is History gonna repeat?</Title><Username>lostcityundead</Username><Timestamp>1346425895421</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course, Freedom, Strength , Justice and Peace Does come with a price tag.... Are you willing to pay for your's? Or, are you just a freeloader? PS. Obama embarrasses America abroad everyday... No wonder Hillary is staying very Far away from Charlotte next week! It's the Economy, Stupid!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346427715491</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:41:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427726220-50</Id><Topic><Title>Is History gonna repeat?</Title><Username>lostcityundead</Username><Timestamp>1346425895421</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rep. Paul Ryan (R-WI) isn’t exactly the most sophisticated observer of international politics. As such, he was treated to a crash course in foreign policy by the Romney campaign prior to his selection as the GOP Vice Presidential nominee. Now, one of Ryan’s key advisers during that briefing period is calling for congressional authorization for war with Iran. Elliott Abrams, a former Bush Administration official who focuses on the Middle East, took to the pages of the Weekly Standard to argue that neither Iranians nor Israelis think the Obama administration is “serious” about attacking Iran, and that the only real way to convince them is having Congress vote for war:</Msg><Username>lostcityundead</Username><Timestamp>1346427726220</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427737563-51</Id><Topic><Title>The REPUBLIWHOPPERPALOOZAS</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346426797913</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Facts still matter. The next step in the repub propaganda media driven, cash juiced process of the SugarDaddyBillionaires' (SDB's) is to convince as many baggers as possible that facts do not matter t. But they are wrong. Facts are ALL that matters. Without facts, there is no debate. Without debate, there are no new ideas. Without new ideas, we will regress to the old ideas. With old ideas in a new world the middle class will be lost. Just where the SDB's want you. But just do not lose your way to the voting booth. There is where democracy lives. The voting booth is the place most despised and feared by repubs and their SDBs.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346427737563</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:42:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346427875459-52</Id><Title>Half of Americans Don't Pay their Fair Share</Title><Msg>That's why they don't work and usually vote Democrat.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1346427875459</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427912295-53</Id><Topic><Title>The REPUBLIWHOPPERPALOOZAS</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346426797913</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What? No mention of Obama's SDBs? What a Hypocrite!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346427912295</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427915953-54</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan selection and the RNC = No bounce in the polls</Title><Username>annegsirhc</Username><Timestamp>1346426150553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Catch up to what, that the RNC chose to air a senile 82 year old, multi-millionaire who resembles Smithers on The Simpsons, out of touch with mainstream and even the repugs. Or that Mittens side-stepped the issues of Social Security. Medicare. Iraq. Afghanistan. Undocumented immigration, etc. Glued to his telepromptor, Mittens could not do his canned campaign-stop, blame-obama speech with his weird lawn-sprinkle motions. Lyin' Ryan was selected when?</Msg><Username>annegsirhc</Username><Timestamp>1346427915953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346428063665-55</Id><Title>BA competitor boosting profits by cutting benefits</Title><Msg>Word on the street is one of BA's competitors is boosting profits by under funding the pension and significantly raising health care premiums. I also heard they are demanding unpaid overtime from its employees.</Msg><Username>ballistic_trajectory_impact</Username><Timestamp>1346428063665</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:47:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346428139813-56</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Media "Fact Checkers" and Gullible Liberals</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346425177685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:59:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like the liberal media, most so-called "fact checkers" have lost all credibility.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1346428139813</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:48:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346428219270-57</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Media "Fact Checkers" and Gullible Liberals</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346425177685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:59:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which Ryan lie are you referring to, there are so many? Simple enough for even a RWNJ #$%$ to google.</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346428219270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:50:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346428252112-58</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Media "Fact Checkers" and Gullible Liberals</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346425177685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:59:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bingo... it will take the Libs years to realize the obvious!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346428252112</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:50:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346428329476-59</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Media "Fact Checkers" and Gullible Liberals</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346425177685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:59:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden gonna chew lyin' Ryan up and spit him out in the debates. Lyin' Ryan is about as good a 'debaitor' as the average RWNJ #$%$dittohead.</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346428329476</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:52:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346428391331-60</Id><Topic><Title>BA competitor boosting profits by cutting benefits</Title><Username>ballistic_trajectory_impact</Username><Timestamp>1346428063665</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:47:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which Competitors are speaking of? Got a link/proof? Do you know that for a fact or did your Union Steward tell you that?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346428391331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:53:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346428793321-61</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney and lyin' Ryan want to ban all abortions</Title><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346423916382</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I may be a fool, but you have been fooled enough times by the republicons to qualify you as a complete IDIOT. The economy is chugging along. Even Mittens says big business is doing fine. Could it be better...Yes, but it would take bi-partisanship on the part of the republicon baggers in congress. Could it be worse...it was under Boosh and the republicons, and would be with Mittens!</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1346428793321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:59:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346428858425-62</Id><Title>Leftist Media Turns on Clint Eastwood over Fact Filled Speech... For Criticizing Obama!</Title><Msg>The Liberal Media is in Full Panic Mode... they know full well Obama is in Deep Kimche in November! MEDIA STRIKES BACK AFTER DIRTY HARRY DARES TO MOCK OBAMA by JOHN NOLTE 30 Aug 2012 805 POST A COMMENT Newsflash: Obama can't take a joke. But we already knew that. For four long years we've waited, hoped and prayed that some young comic would break free of the politically correct demands of The State and mock Obama the way all presidents and all people in power should be mocked. But for four long years (with a few exceptions) all we've seen instead are cowardly toadies of The State: Bill Maher, Jon Stewart, David Letterman, Chris Rock, the cast of "Saturday Night Live"… Since Obama won the presidency, comedy has pretty much gone straight to hell as our Entertainment Overlords morphed into pathetic lapdogs to The State; begging for scraps of attention and affection from Obama, and in the process becoming stale, lazy, dull, predictable, painfully unfunny, and like a needy poodle -- more than a little annoying. Who would've ever thought that one of the men who would display enough backbone and "edge" to finally take it to Obama with wicked mockery on about 30 million live television screens would be 82 year-old Clint Eastwood? Once we learned Eastwood was the night's mystery guest, no one knew what to expect. And anyone who took a guess most certainly didn’t guess that the Oscar-winning American icon would use his opportunity to relentlessly and hilariously mock Barack Obama in front of the entire free world. You can watch the highlights here: It was glorious! And everyone I've talked to who was in the hall absolutely loved it. Eastwood hit Obama in every sweet spot we've been waiting for him to get hit on: The incompetence; the lies; the empty, pretentious rhetoric; the inexperience; and that roaring blowhard of a #$%$ Obama chose to be a heartbeat away. Oh, and the empty chair. Other than an empty suit, there is no sharper metaphor. Eastwood also made one of the very best points of the night: WE own this country, and when someone doesn't do the job "we have to let them go." The media, naturally, is furious. They don’t like to see Their Precious One mocked and they also understand the power of mockery -- which is why they keep Stewart and Colbert on such a tight leash. This is why the media has already written 25 stories (5 from Politico) mocking Eastwood. Had Eastwood said the things the media likes to hear with the same nervousness and hesitation, they would've called him wizened and seasoned. But because he mocked Their Precious One, suddenly he's some kind of embarrassment. And now Politico, Ben Smith and CNN are all talking about how they intend to use Eastwood as way to overwhelm Mitt Romney's speech in the coming days. Like they wouldn't have found another reason. All I can say in response is: Go to hell you Obama-shilling crybabies. Eastwood showed more grit and honestly in those few minutes than you water carriers have during your entire propaganda-for-the-collective careers. What Eastwood did tonight was funnier, fresher, edgier, and braver than anything those comedy cowards Chris Rock, Jon Stewart or Stephen Colbert have done in 15 years. 82 years-old, and Dirty Harry is still #$%$ all the right people off. My hero.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346428858425</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346428906150-63</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Media "Fact Checkers" and Gullible Liberals</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346425177685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:59:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you open your eyes, look at the facts from what Romney and Ryan put forth in their speeches, as George W. Bush would have said, the "math is very fussy"! Romney brought up Steve Jobs. It use to be that in the United States not only did US companies designed their products here, but also build them here. Today Apple builts most if not all of their products in Asia, mostly in China. Steve Jobs at a dinner a couple years ago and other executives told President Obama that those manufacturing jobs are never coming back! This all happen by-the-way on President George W. Bush's watch, not President Obama's watch. Same with the GM plant closing in Wisconsin, decided and done while George W. Bush was president. You can't increase employment as long as companies remain greedy and only answer to share holder instead of employees who made companies strong in the first place. When people loose their jobs to foreign lands, they no longer are a revenue stream for taxes, they become a burden, that is a fact. If you know so much, tell me how Romney will bring 12 million jobs, and please don;t bring up the five points from his speech, because it didn't tells us anything!</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1346428906150</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:01:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346429076690-64</Id><Topic><Title>The REPUBLIWHOPPERPALOOZAS</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346426797913</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hokeydokeycom, while Wafflin Willard still refuses to disclose his big money bundlers -- even though the Obama campaign has -- USA TODAY managed to ferret out a list. It turns out that fully 25 percent of these bag men come from the financial sector, which the American public rates as the second worst in the country, barely edging out the oil and gas industry, which BTW are virtually unanimous in opening their wallets to repubs.. To make matters worse, this summer was so packed with banking scandals that the independent investigative journalists at ProPublica put out a scorecard to keep track of the perpetrators (Barclays, JPMorgan Chase, Citigroup, UBS, Deutsche Bank and more), crimes, victims, and investigations. No wonder Willard wants to keep his relationships to these crooks under wraps.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346429076690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:04:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346429457778-65</Id><Topic><Title>The REPUBLIWHOPPERPALOOZAS</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346426797913</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, hokeydokeycom, but Lyin Ryan and Wafflin Willard's lies were so blatan tthey were on the news tonight for #$%$ lying. I'm guessing you missed it because you don't watch the "lamestream liberal news," right? I bet you get all your news from a criminal, Australian billionaire and a Saudi sheikh, because they're real Americans.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346429457778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:10:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346429515667-66</Id><Topic><Title>BA competitor boosting profits by cutting benefits</Title><Username>ballistic_trajectory_impact</Username><Timestamp>1346428063665</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:47:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>underfunding of pension plan doesnt impact profits...where did you go to school?</Msg><Username>makboe</Username><Timestamp>1346429515667</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:11:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346429869398-67</Id><Topic><Title>The Vulture/Voucher Ticket</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346169827875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 12:03:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Birther/Girther 2016 already acting like they are undermining the Vulture/Voucher 2012</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346429869398</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346431268268-68</Id><Topic><Title>Leftist Media Turns on Clint Eastwood over Fact Filled Speech... For Criticizing Obama!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346428858425</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:00:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clint is a wannabee and has always been one. He portrays a tough guy and soldier in many movies but unlike Charles Bronson,Jack Palance and lee Marvin he never served a day in the military. His type of fake macho is perfect for the Repubes now running their party. Days when Bob Dole and GHW Bush were the representatives and voice of the real Republican party are sadly gone.</Msg><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1346431268268</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:41:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346431737000-69</Id><Title>Top US General: I sraelis are FRIGGEN Nuts</Title><Msg>http://antiwar.com/ BLOCKED</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346431737000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346431745578-70</Id><Title>Barack Obama’s top 10 most outrageous Big Labor paybacks</Title><Msg>In his book “The Audacity of Hope,” then-presidential candidate Barack Obama wrote: “I owe those unions. When their leaders call, I do my best to call them back right away. I don’t consider this corrupting in any way.” After Big Labor spent nearly $1 billion to get President Obama and his forced-unionism allies elected in 2008, Obama did not disappoint. Here is a breakdown of the top 10 most outrageous Big Labor paybacks of the Obama administration: 1. Hiding union boss expenditures. Obama started his term strong. Shortly after getting elected, Obama appointed forced-unionism partisan Hilda Solis to run the Department of Labor. Solis, in combination with numerous Obama executive orders, promptly rolled back any (albeit modest) progress in union boss transparency and disclosure that had been made the prior eight years. Now it is even more difficult for workers to know where their forced dues dollars are being spent. 2. Neutering the watchdog. Obama’s first budget slashed funding for the Office of Labor and Management Standards (OLMS), the federal agency that enforces union disclosure laws. It’s one of the few areas of the budget that Obama has proposed cutting. 3. Fox guarding the henhouse. Obama appointed union lawyer Craig Becker to the National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), the federal agency that administers and enforces federal labor law. Becker was never confirmed by the U.S. Senate because of bipartisan opposition to his nomination. Obama appointed him to the NLRB via recess appointment. 4. Throwing away election ballots. Becker was a key vote in striking down any protections workers had against card-check union organizing drives, despite the fact that he previously participated as a union lawyer in the very case that established those worker protections. These limited protections allowed workers to petition the NLRB for a secret ballot election within 45 days of a coercive card-check union organizing campaign. Ballots from any pending elections to remove a union after a card check were chucked into the trash. This decision directly affected thousands of workers such as Barbara Ivey, a Kaiser IT department employee in Washington State who is now stuck under Service Employees International Union (SEIU) boss control for at least two years. 5. Ambushing workers. The Obama NLRB pushed new rules to make union organizing campaigns as one-sided as possible by ambushing workers into union membership and dues payments. The new rules dramatically shortened the time frame individual workers have to share truthful information with their coworkers about the adverse effects of unionization and to hear their employers’ views on the subject. 6. Compelling employers to promote unionism. The Obama NLRB pushed new rules requiring job providers to post pro-union notices in their facilities. Tellingly, no new requirement was made for unions to post notices informing workers of their right to refrain from union activities or throw out an unwanted union. 7. Persecuting job providers. Obama-appointed NLRB Acting General Counsel Lafe Solomon used the federal agency to punish Boeing for locating production of its 787 Dreamliner jets in right-to-work South Carolina over non-right-to-work Washington State. The frivolous persecution of Boeing eventually fizzled, but only after the company guaranteed future jobs would go to Washington State, where union bosses get to collect forced dues as a condition of employment. 8. Constitution out on “recess.” Earlier this year, Obama subverted the U.S. Constitution and installed two pro-forced unionism lackeys onto the NLRB as “recess” appointments even though the U.S. Senate was not in recess. Not surprisingly, the NLRB continues to churn out lopsided decisions in favor of union bosses. 9. Runaway (unionism) train. Obama’s appointments to the National Mediation Board (NMB), the federal agency that administers labor law in the railway and airline industries, changed the election procedures of unions organizing under the Railway Labor Act (RLA). The two Obama-appointed NMB members who approved the new rule, Harry Hoglander and Linda Puchala, are former union officials with the Air Line Pilots Association (ALPA) and Association of Flight Attendants (AFA) unions, respectively. Both unions are a major part of an American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) union-led coalition that urged the three-member board to discard its election policy of 75 years. The new procedure stacks the deck in favor of unionization by granting a union monopoly bargaining power over railway or airline industry workers if the union acquires support from just a bare majority of eligible workers in an election, no matter how few actually vote. This means that a small bloc of workers could force union boss “representation” on the whole group rather than having a true majority of all workers deciding for themselves. 10. Obamacare(s) for union bosses. The effects of Obama’s pro-forced unionism agenda will be felt long after his stay in the White House ends. Obamacare is full of sweetheart deals aimed at placating union bosses. For example, nonunion medical facilities are basically ineligible to participate in Obamacare’s professional-development grant program for healthcare workers. The funds in this program must be administered jointly with a labor organization — much like the Department of Labor’s grants for construction apprenticeship programs, which have turned into a cash cow for construction industry union officials on the order of hundreds of millions of dollars each year. Obamacare is full of these sorts of provisions — provisions that further unionize the healthcare industry. Mark Mix</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1346431745578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:49:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346431941000-71</Id><Topic><Title>Top US General: I sraelis are FRIGGEN Nuts</Title><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346431737000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:48:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>General Dempsey, Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff to Netanyahu: You are a warmongering fool!</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346431941000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:52:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346432017234-72</Id><Title>Airbus A320neo tops Boeing 737 Max</Title><Msg>Notice how the friends,brothers and In-Laws favorable to Boeing do not discuss anything important like Boeing stock price has gone down 5% for the year or 3.6% for the last 10 days , whil companies like apple 's stock price has gone up over 60% for the year and day trade stocks like BONT has gone up 60% in just 10 trade days. A stock investor could go broke in Boeing as a friend,brother or in-law of the few users here who point to airplane orders and heckle the users who prefer to make money the real way on stock price appreciation. the real story is the 787 is 4 years late, 34 billion in debt, the 747 is 2 billion in debt and 2 years late , the 777X is on hold due to Boeing has no money, the competition is more than a duopoly now and the "customer whil wait " comment by the Boeing CEO still is killing the Boeing stock price look at what just happened the Airbus is getting huge airplane orders and the FBI ers are celebrating a handful of flying boeing planes late and overcost flying around Seattle being tested der !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1346432017234</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346432091000-73</Id><Title>Gen. Dempsey Warns on Supporting Terrorists in Syria</Title><Msg>http://news.antiwar.com/2012/08/30/dempsey-backs-away-from-obamas-threat-to-intervene-in-syria/</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346432091000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:54:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346432133112-74</Id><Title>Left-wing Lunatic collectivist are going Berserk</Title><Msg>They're praying to Karl Marx and asking for more guidance.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1346432133112</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:55:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346432581066-75</Id><Topic><Title>Half of Americans Don't Pay their Fair Share</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1346427875459</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A big proportion of "Half of Americans" are children, ya friggin idiot.</Msg><Username>iheartmyjob2</Username><Timestamp>1346432581066</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346432642326-76</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus A320neo tops Boeing 737 Max</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1346432017234</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:53:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hi fred !!! how many different nicks do you have?</Msg><Username>makboe</Username><Timestamp>1346432642326</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:04:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346432992873-77</Id><Title>attack the fact checkers</Title><Msg>screw facts, #$%$ you lie , liberal media!! we make our own facts and you suck! Got to love the GOP these days. if they disagree with you about anything you are instantly a liberal on welfare in their little pee brains.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346432992873</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:09:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346433029193-78</Id><Topic><Title>Left-wing Lunatic collectivist are going Berserk</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1346432133112</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:55:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Should any political party attempt to abolish social security, unemployment insurance, and eliminate labor laws and farm programs, you would not hear of that party again in our political history. There is a tiny splinter group, of course, that believes that you can do these things. Among them are a few Texas oil millionaires, and an occasional politician or businessman from other areas. Their number is negligible and they are stupid." President Dwight D. Eisenhower, l952-----</Msg><Username>lostcityundead</Username><Timestamp>1346433029193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:10:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346434613758-79</Id><Topic><Title>attack the fact checkers</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346432992873</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:09:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one is attacking the so called "fact checkers"' just holding them accountable Liberals hate facts.....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346434613758</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:36:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346434995559-80</Id><Topic><Title>attack the fact checkers</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346432992873</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:09:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry imaccon, you`re one of the worse fact deniers there is out there, you have all the gop talking points down too, just keep repeating them as many times a day as you can and they will still be lies , #$%$ and misinformation. GOP is counting on the stupid vote to win this thing , and they will say and do anything to get it . good thing though that most the stupid voters have already been convinced of the big lie and all that can happen now is Romenys numbers will continue to drop</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346434995559</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:43:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346435375000-81</Id><Topic><Title>Gen. Dempsey Warns on Supporting Terrorists in Syria</Title><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346432091000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:54:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would we support the Assad regime?</Msg><Username>ichbinienmachoman</Username><Timestamp>1346435375000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346435470391-82</Id><Topic><Title>attack the fact checkers</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346432992873</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:09:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, the "Stupid" vote will come from the Liberals... The Liberal so called "Fact Checkers" got caught lying.... Pure and Simple... Facts don't lie.... Unemployment over 8% for more than three years... Pathetic! Romney will clean Obama's clock in November.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346435470391</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:51:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346435660501-83</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Media "Fact Checkers" and Gullible Liberals</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346425177685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:59:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Care to tell the board when Apple started outsourcing their products overseas... Ummm, well before W's time in office... Get your facts correct before post such Liberal nonsense. Nitwit !</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346435660501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:54:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346436004347-84</Id><Topic><Title>attack the fact checkers</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346432992873</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:09:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romeny wont do anything but create bigger problems that somebody else will Inherit, that`s how Republicans always work. more wealth will be transferred to the already wealthy people, wages will go down for most Americans, good chance we will in involved in another war. and to top it all off Romeny has not once said how he will accomplish a thing, just a trust me ! yeah right . Romeny has no specifics about anything all he can do is attack Obama and then stand their and play like he is some kind of victim when somebody wants to know a little about him. The GOP is a hypocritical pathetic Party of wimps, liars and thieves!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346436004347</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:00:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346436140604-85</Id><Topic><Title>Half of Americans Don't Pay their Fair Share</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1346427875459</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, nitwit, almost half of the tax filers don't pay any Federal Income Taxes... and they are not children as you seem to be. That is why the Stupid Liberals don't understand why the aforementioned filers do not get tax cuts when tax cuts are enacted. Only tax payers can get a tax cut... understand... probably not! Geez, liberals....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346436140604</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346436296084-86</Id><Topic><Title>Half of Americans Don't Pay their Fair Share</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1346427875459</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The statistics are half of all income earners.....doesn't include children you stupid collectivist.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1346436296084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346436478250-87</Id><Topic><Title>Half of Americans Don't Pay their Fair Share</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1346427875459</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said, but the Stupid Liberals don't understand that... they were educated in Govt schools!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346436478250</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:07:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346436555274-88</Id><Title>Liberals Just Don't Get it.</Title><Msg>You can't have employees without employers. Karl Marx forgot to mention that and liberals can't figure it out on their own. Of course why should they try.....they don't want jobs anyway....they want hand outs.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1346436555274</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:09:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346436788806-89</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Media "Fact Checkers" and Gullible Liberals</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346425177685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:59:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is estimated that 8 million U.S. manufacturing jobs were eliminated between June 1979 and December 2009. One report describes the grim process of deindustrialization: “Long before the banking collapse of 2008, such important U.S. industries as machine tools, consumer electronics, auto parts, appliances, furniture, telecommunications equipment, and many others that had once dominated the global marketplace suffered their own economic collapse. Manufacturing employment dropped to 11.7 million in October 2009, a loss of 5.5 million or 32 percent of all manufacturing jobs since October 2000. The last time fewer than 12 million people worked in the manufacturing sector was in 1941. In October 2009, more people were officially unemployed (15.7 million) than were working in manufacturing.”</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346436788806</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:13:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346436906206-90</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals Just Don't Get it.</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1346436555274</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:09:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you can`t have employees turning an economy around if you only hire in India and China.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346436906206</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:15:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346437005771-91</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans sound like a broken record!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346425522911</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:05:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and they're Desperate!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346437005771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:16:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346437382788-92</Id><Title>Romney has Obama on the Defensive... Playing Catch Up to Romney!</Title><Msg>Obama bounced into announcing visit to storm-ravaged Louisiana after Romney shows him up with surprise visit By TOBY HARNDEN IN TAMPA, FLORIDA PUBLISHED: 10:21 EST, 31 August 2012 | UPDATED: 12:36 EST, 31 August 2012 President Barack Obama was today forced to announce he will fly to storm-hit Louisiana on Monday – hours after Mitt Romney beat him to the punch by deciding to head there this afternoon. After it emerged that Obama was still taking time to fit in a campaign stop in Cleveland, Ohio before checking out how clean-up operations are proceeding in the Bayou state, the Obama campaign abruptly cancelled that event. 'In light of the President’s travel to Louisiana to meet with local officials and view ongoing response and recovery efforts to Hurricane Isaac, President Obama will no longer travel to Cleveland, Ohio on Monday, September 3,' the campaign said in a terse statement. Romney had changed his schedule to head to an affected town outside New Orleans while Obama, who has yet to visit the Tropical Storm Isaac zone, headed off to Texas to campaign. Concern: Mitt Romney, pictured at the American Legion National Convention in Indianapolis, has changed his campaign trail plans and will visit a storm-hit area of Louisiana on Friday Seven years ago, President George W. Bush was lambasted for inaction and incompetence in dealing with Hurricane Katrina, which devastated New Orleans and much of the Mississippi and Louisiana gulf coast. Romney’s last-minute trip to New Orleans came as his wife Ann told CNN that swing women voters in particular had told her that 'it's time for the grown-up to come, the man that's going to take this very seriously and the future of our children very, very seriously'. He opted out of a joint campaign appearance in Richmond, Virginia with Paul Ryan, his vice-presidential running mate, to head to Louisiana. The first day of the Republican convention in Tampa was cancelled as Isaac bore down on Florida and the Gulf of Mexico area. More... 'It's time to turn the page': Romney accepts GOP nomination... as Clint Eastwood delivers bizarre comedy routine mocking Obama 'Obama's not a bad guy - he's a bad President!' Marco Rubio wows GOP convention as he introduces Romney</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346437382788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:23:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346437465473-93</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 332, Romney 206</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346278217273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:10:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346437465473</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:24:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346438033915-94</Id><Title>Clint Eastwood on the phone with Obama!!</Title><Msg>"It all went according to plan,sir."</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346438033915</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346438123731-95</Id><Title>GOP more Gender and Racially Diverse than Democrats...</Title><Msg>Listen to the Pathetic response from the Liberal Mayor of LA respond to a simple question from a MSNBC host about Party Diversity... and this guy io going to speak at Obama's Convention next week! Liberals have a hard time looking in the mirror! Chuck Todd: Why Do Republicans Have More Women and Hispanic Governors? 2:02 PM, AUG 31, 2012 • BY DANIEL HALPERSingle PagePrintLarger TextSmaller TextAlerts MSNBC host Chuck Todd asked the co-chair of the Democratic party's convention, L.A. mayor Antonio Villaraigosa, why there are more Republican women and Hispanic governors: "Let me ask you though, this one question, why is it that the Republicans have elected more women governors and have two Hispanic governors and the Democrats don’t?," asked Todd. "Don’t have as many women governors and don’t have Hispanic governors, why do you think that is?" "Well we have a lot more legislators and mayors and Congress members that are women, that are Latino, that are Asian, that are African American. We have a much broader tent, a much broader representation of every walk of life, people from, you know, every ethnicity and race and sex," said Villaraigosa. "It’s true, they may have more governors but we have a much broader field when you look at all of the elected officials."</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346438123731</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:35:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346438384949-96</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood Pokes Obama in the Eye</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346379252079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:14:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who's embarrassed...... ha ha ha ha ha ha !!!! ____________________________________ TAMPA, Fla. – Appearing on a couple of morning network television shows Friday, potential First Lady Ann Romney sounded like she wanted her 12 minutes back. That would be the 12 minutes of prime television time the night before that her husband’s handlers handed to movie icon Clint Eastwood just before the climax of the Republican National Convention. Eastwood, 82, turned the 720 precious seconds into a meandering walkabout through his (not entirely cogent) political beliefs. And Romney, in return, damned him with faint praise.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346438384949</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:39:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346438430427-97</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood on the phone with Obama!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346438033915</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't think so by watching the Liberal Media go into contortions about Clint's speech! Their reactions say everything! Obama is very worried and for good reason.... he looks and is acting like the Peanut, Jimmy Carter.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346438430427</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:40:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346438563138-98</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood Pokes Obama in the Eye</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346379252079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:14:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are confused. Clint embarrassed himself, he looked semi-senile and confused. Keep drinking the cool aid, it eliminate you having to do any thinking. As if you could.....</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1346438563138</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:42:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346438626613-99</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood on the phone with Obama!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346438033915</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey buttlicker - ask Anne Romney how it went!!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346438626613</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346438762009-100</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood Pokes Obama in the Eye</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346379252079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:14:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah, Clint was Great and that is why only the Panicked Liberal Media is attacking him! They know full well the impact Clint Eastwood made on the American people's perception of Obama... Heavy drinking in Chicago again tonight.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346438762009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346439001181-101</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood on the phone with Obama!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346438033915</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now, now, one can tell when Liberals are beaten and out of ideas... they start ugly name calling Ask the American voters what they think of Clint's speech, stick.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346439001181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346439189627-102</Id><Title>Ann Romney throws Eastwood under the Bus!!</Title><Msg>TAMPA, Fla. – Appearing on a couple of morning network television shows Friday, potential First Lady Ann Romney sounded like she wanted her 12 minutes back. That would be the 12 minutes of prime television time the night before that her husband’s handlers handed to movie icon Clint Eastwood just before the climax of the Republican National Convention. Eastwood, 82, turned the 720 precious seconds into a meandering walkabout through his (not entirely cogent) political beliefs. And Romney, in return, damned him with faint praise. Asked on ABC’s “Good Morning America” about Eastwood’s rambling, unscripted speech, the wife of the Republican presidential nominee allowed that she was “grateful for his support,” but quickly heaped much more effusive praise on Olympic athletes and fellow Mormons "that knew Mitt so well" who also spoke on behalf of her husband Thursday night. Those testimonials did not reach the vast majority of viewers because they were delivered before 10 p.m EDT, when the networks opened their live coverage. Eastwood's 'Invisible Obama' skit amuses some, confuses others Eastwood's 'Invisible Obama' skit amuses some, confuses others On CBS on Friday morning, Romney again quickly segued away from Eastwood’s performance. “You can never take away from the fact that this country is in trouble,” she said, “and people are looking for real leadership and that I know that Mitt is the man for this moment.” That chilly reception—combined with the desire to not mire their campaign for another day in peripheral issues—explains why Romney advisors had very little to say about the Eastwood bit, in which the entertainer addressed an empty chair, where he imagined President Obama was sitting.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346439189627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:53:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346439358108-103</Id><Title>The Liberal Media</Title><Msg>Always get a kick out of people posting about the liberal media , what do you think happens if You watch nothing but Fox news and get no other opinions or views? (this should be good)</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346439358108</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:55:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346439437308-104</Id><Title>Thanks, Obama... Most New Jobs are Low Paying</Title><Msg>And this article is from the NYTs Majority of New Jobs Pay Low Wages, Study Finds Brian Blanco for The New York Times A waitress at Arco Iris Restaurant in Tampa, Fla., last week. The food industry has added 300,000 low-paying jobs in the recovery. By CATHERINE RAMPELL Published: August 30, 2012 While a majority of jobs lost during the downturn were in the middle range of wages, a majority of those added during the recovery have been low paying, according to a new report from the National Employment Law Project. The disappearance of midwage, midskill jobs is part of a longer-term trend that some refer to as a hollowing out of the work force, though it has probably been accelerated by government layoffs. “The overarching message here is we don’t just have a jobs deficit; we have a ‘good jobs’ deficit,” said Annette Bernhardt, the report’s author and a policy co-director at the National Employment Law Project, a liberal research and advocacy group. The report looked at 366 occupations tracked by the Labor Department and clumped them into three equal groups by wage, with each representing a third of American employment in 2008. The middle third — occupations in fields like construction, manufacturing and information, with median hourly wages of $13.84 to $21.13 — accounted for 60 percent of job losses from the beginning of 2008 to early 2010. The job market has turned around since then, but those fields have represented only 22 percent of total job growth. Higher-wage occupations — those with a median wage of $21.14 to $54.55 — represented 19 percent of job losses when employment was falling, and 20 percent of job gains when employment began growing again. Lower-wage occupations, with median hourly wages of $7.69 to $13.83, accounted for 21 percent of job losses during the retraction. Since employment started expanding, they have accounted for 58 percent of all job growth. The occupations with the fastest growth were retail sales (at a median wage of $10.97 an hour) and food preparation workers ($9.04 an hour). Each category has grown by more than 300,000 workers since June 2009. Some of these new, lower-paying jobs are being taken by people just entering the labor force, like recent high school and college graduates. Many, though, are being filled by older workers who lost more lucrative jobs in the recession and were forced to take something to scrape by. “I think I’ve been very resilient and resistant and optimistic, up until very recently,” said Ellen Pinney, 56, who was dismissed from a $75,000-a-year job in which she managed procurement and supply for an electronics company in March 2008. Since then, she has cobbled together a series of temporary jobs in retail and home health care and worked as a part-time receptionist for a beauty salon. She is now working as an unpaid intern for a construction company, putting together bids and business plans for green energy projects, and has moved in with her 86-year-old father in Forked River, N.J. “I really can’t bear it anymore,” she said, noting that her applications to places like PetSmart and Target had gone unanswered. “From every standpoint — my independence, my sense of purposefulness, my self-esteem, my life planning — this is just not what I was planning.” As Ms. Pinney’s experience shows, low-wage jobs have not been growing especially quickly in this recovery; they account for such a big share of job growth mostly because midwage job growth has been so slow. Over the last few decades, the number of midwage, midskill jobs has stagnated or declined as employers chose to automate routine tasks or to move them offshore. Job growth has been concentrated in positions that tend to fall into two categories: manual work that must be done in person, like styling hair or serving food, which usually pays relatively little; and more creative, design-oriented work like engineering or surgery, which often pays quite well. Since 2001, employment has grown 8.7 percent in lower-wage occupations and 6.6 percent in high-wage ones. Over that period, midwage occupation employment has fallen by 7.3 percent. This “polarization” of skills and wages has been documented meticulously by David H. Autor, an economics professor at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. A recent study found that this polarization accelerated in the last three recessions, particularly the last one, as financial pressures forced companies to reorganize more quickly. “This is not just a nice, smooth process,” said Henry E. Siu, an economics professor at the University of British Columbia, who helped write the recent study about polarization and the business cycle. “A lot of these jobs were suddenly wiped out during recession and are not coming back.” On top of private sector revamps, state and local governments have been shedding workers in recent years. Those jobs lost in the public sector have been primarily in mid and higher-wage positions, according to Ms. Bernhardt’s analysis. “Whenever you look at data like these, there is this tendency to get overwhelmed, that there are these inevitable, big macro forces causing this polarization and we can’t do anything about them. In fact, we can,” Ms. Bernhardt said. She called for more funds for states to stem losses in the public sector and federal infrastructure projects to employ idled construction workers. Both proposals have faced resistance from Republicans in Congress.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346439437308</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:57:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346439438684-105</Id><Title>Obama and Democrats Devastating to Middle Class Workers</Title><Msg>It isn't the rich guy they put out of work.......it's 23 million middles class workers.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1346439438684</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346439749453-106</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Democrats Devastating to Middle Class Workers</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1346439438684</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:57:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Obama and his Jobs Council that hasn't met in six (6) Months doesn't seem to care about the Hurting American People... Obama would rather Play Golf instead! Sad, really sad. "You may be a Good Man, but you are a BAD President!'</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346439749453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:02:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346439976326-107</Id><Title>Role model...</Title><Msg>Who is president obama's role model ?</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1346439976326</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:06:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346440067942-108</Id><Topic><Title>The Liberal Media</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346439358108</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:55:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, the Liberal Media is starting to Eat itself over support for Obama... They must sense the change in the Direction of the Wind. They are very biased, not all are Stupid! They like winners... hitch changers are in High Demand.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346440067942</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:07:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346440402184-109</Id><Topic><Title>Role model...</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1346439976326</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:06:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The America Hating and Racist Rev Wright is Obama's Role Model, why of course! If the Dems/Socialists want to play Religion about Mitt's Mormonism... it will backfire badly as Rev Wright is radioactive to the American People! Obama will lose handily in that debate if he chooses to go there.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346440402184</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346440487331-110</Id><Topic><Title>The Liberal Media</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346439358108</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:55:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another trick the Right has it`s Propaganda Repeaters do is just say a bunch of bazzarro stuff that makes no sense to anyone, use a few fancy words, call liberals a few names and the stupid people will follow us to the polls, BELIEVE IN AMERICA, just bank and invest overseas!!!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346440487331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:14:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346440735043-111</Id><Topic><Title>Role model...</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1346439976326</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:06:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that should be simple enough to Google. I have heard that Lincoln and Regan are a few of his role models so is spider man and Chuck Norris</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346440735043</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:18:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346440810692-112</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Democrats Devastating to Middle Class Workers</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1346439438684</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:57:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>next you`ll be telling us your an informed voter LMAO</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346440810692</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:20:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346444949983-113</Id><Title>LAN Air 787 delivered</Title><Msg>EVERETT, Wash., Aug. 31, 2012 /PRNewswire/ -- Boeing (NYSE: BA) and LAN Airlines, one of Latin America's leading passenger and cargo carriers, celebrated the delivery of the first 787 Dreamliner to LAN making it the first airline in the Americas to receive the new airplane. LAN is only the fourth customer in the world to include the Boeing 787 in its fleet with 32 of this new aircraft on order and lease.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346444949983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:29:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346445622345-114</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood on the phone with Obama!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346438033915</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clint is a good man... and im so glad he spoke at the RNC...!!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346445622345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:40:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346445988759-115</Id><Title>Republicans are not Out of Touch and Ignorant..!!!</Title><Msg>... are they.? or do they really believe the #$%$ they keep repeating...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346445988759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:46:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346446176170-116</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood Pokes Obama in the Eye</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346379252079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:14:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought Clint Eastwood had the audience applauding and on their feet throughout his humorous presentation. He was terrific with his one liners blasting Obama and Biden. He told the public not to reelect Obama because he many be a nice guy and that we should hold Obama accountable for his record. Clint Eastman is a consummate actor, what some consider his rambling was a brilliant performance. He held my attention and he made perfect sense. His speech besides Romney's won the evening.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1346446176170</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346446685994-117</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are not Out of Touch and Ignorant..!!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346445988759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:46:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... that answers the question!!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346446685994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:58:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346448431229-118</Id><Title>Lying Obama Administration Can't Keep Lies Straight!</Title><Msg>Romney has the Initiative... Obama Chasing Romney and he Knows it... say it all ! Obama has become a 'me too, me too" fool trying so hard to keep up with Mitt. Change in plans: Obama will visit La. Monday By DONOVAN SLACK | 8/31/12 11:47 AM EDT President Obama will visit Louisiana after all. Obama campaign spokeswoman Jennifer Psaki told POLITICO earlier Friday that the president had no plans yet to visit the Gulf state and review damage from Hurricane Isaac, even though Mitt Romney announced plans to visit Friday. (Also on POLITICO: Romney heads to storm-ravaged Louisiana) But the White House announced a few hours later that he is now planning to go there. "On Monday, September 3rd, President Obama will travel to Louisiana to meet with local officials and view ongoing response and recovery efforts to Hurricane Isaac," the White House said in a release. The president was en route Friday to Fort Bliss, Texas, where he planned to meet with military service members and their families on the two-year anniverary of his visit there to mark the end of the war in Iraq.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346448431229</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346449404106-119</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346449086085</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:38:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or, better, Obama has Given America an Unemployment Rate Above 8% for More than Three Years.... The American people are Hurting and Want Jobs... Something Mitt will Deliver on and Something Obama Failed to Deliver On! Take a Hike, Barak!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346449404106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:43:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346449850314-120</Id><Title>Ah, Poor Liberal Protesters Crying about Lack of Turn Out</Title><Msg>What a Bunch of Losers... Liberal Losers! Occupy RNC ends in tears, frustration TAMPA, Fla. — Republican National Convention protesters sobbed in each other’s arms as their weeklong series of protests came to an abrupt and unremarkable end. As Mitt Romney delivered his remarks at the RNC on Thursday night, marking the end of planned events, demonstrators living in the “Romneyville” protest camp led a final march through the streets of Tampa. Following a fragmented march against the GOP, TheDC’s photo team spoke to several protesters who said they were disappointed by low turnout at protests and the lack of open discussion between protesters and Republican leadership. Referencing the large number of bicycle-based police officers, a protester named Lash told TheDC, “we can see liberty crumbling on bikes.”......</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346449850314</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:50:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346450044552-121</Id><Topic><Title>The Liberal Media</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346439358108</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:55:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Viewers are actually leaving the Liberal Media in record numbers. Fox viewer numbers just keep on growing. Even liberals are tired of being lead around by the nose. The LameStream Media give them that. Don't think. They'll tell you what to think. Fox gives you fair and balanced reporting so you can make a better decision. Just ask Liberal Correspondant Juan Williams of Fox News. You remember Juan Williams,don't you? He was that Liberal Radio Correspondant that was fired the very same day by NPR for making counter statements that weren't agreed to by NPR staff. So much for the First Amendment at Liberal NPR.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1346450044552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:54:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346450230714-122</Id><Topic><Title>The REPUBLIWHOPPERPALOOZAS</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346426797913</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clint stole the show last night with his impersonation of a goofy old geezer.. He came off looking very well compared to Willard's impersonation of a lying treacly high school .junior. BTW someone at the coronation should have tipped off "Dirty Harry" it looked like he combed his hair with firecrackers.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346450230714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:57:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346450290603-123</Id><Title>Even the Fed Reserve admits Obama Policies are Failing!</Title><Msg>The Fed Chief said the Economy was far from Satisfactory.... It's the Economy, Stupid, err, Obama" Bernanke confirms bias towards easing By Robin Harding in Jackson Hole ©AP Ben Bernanke took another step on the US Federal Reserve's march towards more monetary easing with a speech that said the economic situation was “far from satisfactory”. Speaking at the Fed's annual gathering in Jackson Hole, Wyoming, Mr Bernanke offered no direct promise of further easing. But he spelt out the feeble state of the economy, the Fed’s intention to be forceful, and that it has effective policy tools available. “Taking due account of the uncertainties and limits of its policy tools, the Federal Reserve will provide additional policy accommodation as needed to promote a stronger economic recovery and sustained improvement in labour market conditions,” said the Fed chairman. The clearest hint that Mr Bernanke is ready to do more came from his disappointment with the economy's progress. He noted some recovery over the past few years but said that improvement in the labour market had been “painfully slow”. Growth in recent quarters had been “tepid”, he said, and “unless the economy begins to grow more quickly than it has recently, the unemployment rate is likely to remain far above levels consistent with maximum employment for some time”.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346450290603</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:58:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346450789926-124</Id><Topic><Title>The REPUBLIWHOPPERPALOOZAS</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346426797913</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah, now the fellow Seniors in the State of Florida will not take kindly to your Discrimination toward the Elderly!!!! Why are Liberals so Racist and Discriminatory? You ignorant Libs were set up and you didn't even realize it! Took the Bait Hook, Line and Sinker!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346450789926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:06:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346450819963-125</Id><Topic><Title>The Liberal Media</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346439358108</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 14:55:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...what do you think happens if You watch nothing but Fox news and get no other opinions or views? (this should be good)." ======= What do you think happens if You watch ANYTHING but Fox News AND GET ONLY MOSTLY BIASED OPINIONS (LITTLE, IF ANY, TRULY BALANCED NEWS)? (this should be even better).</Msg><Username>dm60010</Username><Timestamp>1346450819963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:06:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346451562076-126</Id><Title>Veep Debates... Ryan vs the Buffoon Biden... Not a Fair Fight</Title><Msg>Ryan will crush the Buffoon Biden in the Upcoming Debate with his Superior Intellect and Poise. Obama's Campaign Dreads this Veep debate almost as much as they dread Obama debating Mitt.... Obama will be totally on the Defensive... Nothing Positive to Run On! Hopelessness and Hate is Not Selling. Mitt will also crush Obama!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346451562076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346453934195-127</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Retains Lead Through Dismal Puke Convention</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346449686988</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:48:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO - have you always been this stupid or is it just since you began residing in Chicago? (Actually, you are sooo far off, I believe you may have been born and brainwashed, er, raised there).</Msg><Username>unions_suk</Username><Timestamp>1346453934195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:58:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346454063187-128</Id><Topic><Title>Role model...</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1346439976326</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:06:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Strange that no immediate family mentioned, not even one.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1346454063187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346454971999-129</Id><Topic><Title>They Love the Lies Paul Ryan Tells</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346453274782</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:47:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But, why did Obama take $700 plus Billion from MediCare to pay for the very unpopular ObamaCare? Why is he killing MediCare? Unemployment has been over 8% for more than three years... Worse than any of Bush's Terms.... Take a Hike, Barak!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346454971999</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:16:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346455731629-130</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm Dick Hertz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346455560622</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:26:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares... You must be one attention deficient Liberal... we all feel sorry for you... Get some s Help. Pathetic!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346455731629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:28:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346455811964-131</Id><Topic><Title>Role model...</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1346439976326</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:06:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well I`m gonna bet the Cable Guy is not on his list.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346455811964</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:30:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346455987253-132</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm Dick Hertz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346455560622</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:26:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So huge it will make you`re Dick hertz!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346455987253</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346457202111-133</Id><Topic><Title>Ryans Speech "attempt to set record for greatest number of blatant lies"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346456826975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Snore... Just repeating Discredited Left Wing Propaganda... Hard to believe Dik believes such garbage! What is Not Propaganda is the Unemployment Rate Above 8% for more than Three Years!!! Mitt will create Jobs that Obama Failed to Do! Hit the Road, Barak!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346457202111</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:53:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346459008118-134</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan's Diet of Whoppers</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346458585592</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Obama has the Buffoon, Biden as his VP... Romney has an Intelligent VP.... Seems the Liberals are very afraid of Paul... He scare the crap out of them. Biden has a diet of Stupidity! He is an embarrassment to Obama, America and himself! Unemployment over 8% for over three years! Pathetic!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346459008118</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346461233739-135</Id><Topic><Title>The Definition of Insanity</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346459450872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:30:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rmoney and lyin' Ryan - about the most dishonest/deceitful campaign with no substance in history. They don't stand a chance, and it is driving imacon and other RWNJ's insane.</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346461233739</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 21:00:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346461609655-136</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm Dick Hertz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346455560622</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:26:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do the other 100 polls say. kaah, kaah, kaah parrot-headed rwnj's are so dumb they think they are supposed to est the food stamps</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346461609655</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 21:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346461617596-137</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm Dick Hertz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346455560622</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:26:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rassmussen calls the same people everyday kah kah kah the parrothead rwnj's go</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346461617596</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 21:06:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346462178958-138</Id><Topic><Title>The Definition of Insanity</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346459450872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:30:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your definition of insanity is correct... So why does Obama keep enacting the same policies over and over again and creating the same Unemployment Rate over 8% for more than three years? Hard to say this, but Obama needs to listen to you! Obama is the epitomy of Insanity. You exemplify a Boomerang.... Dik.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346462178958</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 21:16:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346462455828-139</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm Dick Hertz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346455560622</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:26:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hood, if you were able to get yourself to study recent polls other than those conducted by the not so fair minded MSNBC's of this world, you may be surprised to learn that Roimney is surging. Even a poll just conductrd by liberal darling James Carville reluctantly shows Romney passing "O" with the most important voter demographic -- the undecideds. Do you think there will be a "Bubba Surprise" next week? Say what you?</Msg><Username>dm60010</Username><Timestamp>1346462455828</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 21:20:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346462878347-140</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm Dick Hertz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346455560622</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:26:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Liberal Media are very worried that their "Dear Leader" will go down in ashes in November.... They say nothing Positive about Obama's "achievements" only attack adds/commentaries against Mitt... and that speaks volumes! They are afraid, very afraid.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346462878347</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 21:27:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346464151003-141</Id><Title>"Romney fails to make the sale" - Kudlow</Title><Msg>It concerns me that in the economic zone, he didn't make the sale to the independents, so-called Reagan Democrats, or to Clinton Democrats. I didn't hear anything new. I didn't hear anything specific, and it troubles me. I do think he helped himself enormously with his biographical narrative. Again, on the economic front I don't think he made the sale; I don't think he convinced the independent voters and I don't think he's going in the right direction in tax policy. He talked about a jobs tour. I frankly have no idea what a "jobs tour" is. I do know that 23 million Americans need jobs. I don't know that they need a president on a jobs tour to inspect them. I think he needs to be more specific. It's not about big business, it's really about small business. And guess what? Small businesses pay the personal tax rate -- the LLCs and the S-corps. - In other words, Rmoney has no plan, only fluff and blame Obama for an economy that is much better than when the Boosh repubes were shut down.</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346464151003</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 21:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346465435215-142</Id><Title>Todd Akin Angered By Karl Rove</Title><Msg>JEFFERSON CITY, Mo. — Republican strategist Karl Rove has apologized to Congressman Todd Akin about the Missouri Senate candidate being murdered! Akin campaign adviser Rick Tyler told The Associated Press that Akin accepted Rove's apology during a phone call Friday. A Rove spokesman didn't return messages Friday. Bloomberg Businessweek's website had quoted Rove as telling GOP donors in Florida: "We should sink Todd Akin. If he's found mysteriously murdered, don't look for my whereabouts!" Rove and other top Republicans have urged Akin to drop his challenge to Sen. McCaskill.</Msg><Username>lostcityundead</Username><Timestamp>1346465435215</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 22:10:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346468156887-143</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Retains Lead Through Dismal Puke Convention</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346449686988</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:48:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This recent poll showed Mitt Romney trailing way behind President Obama even as Romney accepted the Republican Party's presidential nomination last night. While some may assume that Romney benefited from the Republican National Convention, the two polls taken after the RNC began actually show Romney losing much ground over that short time.The record breaking Pinocchio's awarded the Republican Party's speakers did not help Romney.A RNC spokesman speaking “on condition of anonymity” said it was a disaster. Of course, many expect Romney to receive a small boost in the polls after they watched his nomination speech last night. Random Poll of 55,025 registered voters Obama 57% Romney 21% Neither 22%</Msg><Username>lostcityundead</Username><Timestamp>1346468156887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 22:55:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346468374812-144</Id><Title>Feds close criminal investigation on Ariz. sheriff</Title><Msg>Feds say forget it Joe. We were just funning you. No problem. Just forget it. See Yahoo news.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1346468374812</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 22:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>