<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345782213000-1</Id><Topic><Title>"2016" The Movie</Title><Username>lanczagato2</Username><Timestamp>1345725584000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 08:39:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing more than masturbation material for right wing morons.</Msg><Username>ichbinienmachoman</Username><Timestamp>1345782213000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 00:23:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345787659678-2</Id><Topic><Title>"2016" The Movie</Title><Username>lanczagato2</Username><Timestamp>1345725584000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 08:39:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should have called it Birth in Some Nation, now if they make a movie about Biden it could be called Gone With the Wind or maybe Jaws</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1345787659678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 01:54:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345790284525-3</Id><Title>Rmoney Says Big Business 'Doing Fine' After Criticizing Obama for Similar Remarks</Title><Msg>Romney then added that the reason that big businesses are "doing fine in many places" is because they are able to invest their money in "tax havens." "They know how to find ways to get through the tax code, save money by putting various things in the places where there are low tax havens around the world for their businesses," said Romney. Additionally, while Romney said tax havens were helping businesses succeed during his remarks, the candidate's own personal finances are under scrutiny after it was revealed that many of his investments were placed in offshore accounts in the Cayman Islands. URL's are not allowed under yahootys new mega sucky messageboard.</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1345790284525</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 02:38:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345797427000-4</Id><Topic><Title>"2016" The Movie</Title><Username>lanczagato2</Username><Timestamp>1345725584000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 08:39:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perfectly summarized.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1345797427000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 04:37:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345797690000-5</Id><Topic><Title>"2016" The Movie</Title><Username>lanczagato2</Username><Timestamp>1345725584000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 08:39:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lanczagato2 is possibly the most deluded (and stupid) RWNJ in this forum.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1345797690000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 04:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345799351000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Is A Horse Of A Different Color</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1345745866000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 14:17:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How anyone can vote for this creep after knowing all this... is way beyond me.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1345799351000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 05:09:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345803392114-7</Id><Title>Carriers get paid to cancle delayed plane orders.</Title><Msg>Boeing has so many planes on back order the carriers get paid to cancel their orders. There are 30 percent of existing orders will be lost when as air travel is too expensive of a broke world is going broke. Back to the Gray Hound bus.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1345803392114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 06:16:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345810592304-8</Id><Title>euro and china recession</Title><Msg>TIP OF THE ICEBERG.....ORDERS CANCELLED......GLOBAL ISSUE. HEDGE BIG......</Msg><Username>slimjim2005007</Username><Timestamp>1345810592304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 08:16:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345810691909-9</Id><Title>EUROPE AND CHINA GLOBAL RECESSION</Title><Msg>CANCELLED ORDERS JUST TIP OF THE ICEBERG......</Msg><Username>slimjim2005007</Username><Timestamp>1345810691909</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 08:18:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345814352836-10</Id><Title>Quansas just the begining of dropping orders.</Title><Msg>The carriers ordered the planes when gas was $2.50 a gallon. Now it is $4 dollars. Carriers are going to use the delay as an easy way out of contracts. Boeing is going to get hosed.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1345814352836</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 09:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345815266567-11</Id><Title>ana 787 delivery flight last nite</Title><Msg>Left Paine field at about 945 PDT.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1345815266567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 09:34:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345816422208-12</Id><Title>Boeing lost 8 billion dollar 787 order , more to come , jet fuel</Title><Msg>Boeing . got roughed up Thursday after Qantas Airways Ltd. said it can’t afford to buy all the new 787 Dreamliners it had initially ordered. The news sent Boeing BAshares 2.5% lower, making the company the second-biggest decliner on the Dow Jones Industrial Average DJIA. The biggest Dreamliner cancellation to date raises concerns the U.S. aerospace giant can’t simply brush off. Qantas QAN, facing what many in the industry call a unique set of challenges, canceled orders for 35 of Boeing’s new 787-9s a move it claims will save about $8.5 billion. The announcement accompanied the Australian national airlines full-year report. Having posted an annual loss for the first time in 17 years, it makes perfect sense for Qantas to take steps to stop the bleeding. Fuel costs are a major cause of Qantas’s financial problems. Jet-fuel prices are high and headed higher. Since June, spot jet-fuel prices have surged nearly 24%. That’s not hitting just Qantas; its hitting all the airlines. . In some ways, that makes it the canary in the Boeing order book, as jet fuel prices go up airplane orders get cancelled and airlines cut back, thin profits mean no airplane deliveries. There are other concerns. Qantas Chief Executive Alan Joyce, summing up the past years results, said the airline also faces lower growth requirements in this uncertain global context Just about any airline executive could say that with equal conviction. Europe’s economy has stumbled badly, China’s growth engine has slowed and currency markets are in turmoil. All this makes the future very murky. Add rising fuel prices to the mix, and it’s easy to see some investors saw the situation as a</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1345816422208</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 09:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345816722761-13</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney Says Big Business 'Doing Fine' After Criticizing Obama for Similar Remarks</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1345790284525</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 02:38:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As a lifelong 1%'er, a vulture-capitalist, a tax-haven seeker, and a person who doesn't practice what he preaches - Willard wants the RWNJ sheeple to believe that he is for the 'little people' and wants to help them. By completing the outsourcing of the middle-class!!!</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1345816722761</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 09:58:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345817122743-14</Id><Title>US Durable Goods Surge in July on Boeing Orders</Title><Msg>New orders for long-lasting U.S. manufactured goods surged in July, but a second straight month of declines in a gauge of planned business spending pointed to a slowing growth trend in the factory sector. George Frey | Bloomberg | Getty Images -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- The Commerce Department said on Friday durable goods orders jumped 4.2 percent on strong demand for civilian aircraft after an upwardly revised 1.6 percent increase in June. Last month's increase was the largest since December. Economists polled by Reuters had forecast orders for durable goods, items from toasters to aircraft that are meant to last at least three years, rising 2.4 percent after a previously reported 1.3 percent increase in June. Orders excluding transportation fell 0.4 percent, dropping for a second month in the a row. Nondefense capital goods orders excluding aircraft, a closely watched proxy for business spending plans, declined 3.4 percent after falling 2.7 percent in June. Economists had expected this category to rise 0.7 percent after a previously reported 1.7 percent decline in June. Shipments of nondefense capital goods orders excluding aircraft, used to calculate equipment and software spending in the gross domestic product report, were flat after rising 1.5 percent in June. The mixed report hinted at a cooling in the growth pace in manufacturing, a sector that has shouldered the economy's recovery from the 2007-09 recession (learn more). It could favor additional monetary easing by the Federal Reserve (learn more) next month, even though other data on jobs, consumer spending and the housing sector suggested an improvement in the economy early in the third quarter after growth slowed in the April-June period. (Read More: ‘A Lot of Reason’ for More Easing: Fed Presidemt Evans.) Overall orders last month were buoyed by a 14.1 percent jump in transportation equipment as demand for civilian aircraft surged 53.9 percent. Boeing [BA 70.27 -0.09 (-0.13%) ] received orders for 260 aircraft, up from 24 planes in June, according to information posted on the plane maker's website. United Airlines placed an order of 150 planes last month. The aircraft surge was complemented by a 12.8 percent increase in motor vehicle orders, the largest increase since July last year. Away from transportation, details of the report were mixed with gains in new orders for primary metals, computers and electronic product. There were declines in new orders for fabricated metal products, electrical equipment and appliances and machinery.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1345817122743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 10:05:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345820541000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Is A Horse Of A Different Color</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1345745866000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 14:17:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mascot uniform back You shouldn't be taking the Clown costume home with you. Moron</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1345820541000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 11:02:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345820639000-16</Id><Topic><Title>"2016" The Movie</Title><Username>lanczagato2</Username><Timestamp>1345725584000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 08:39:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>masturbation material for the far right is pictures of little boys or Caribou Barbie.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1345820639000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 11:03:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345821076000-17</Id><Topic><Title>1 Spectacular list, 50 stocks, immense opportunity. Find out how?</Title><Username>kuyxchijxzn</Username><Timestamp>1345725781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 08:43:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>much better, a revolutionary improvement</Msg><Username>kirbymolina998</Username><Timestamp>1345821076000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 11:11:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345822414000-18</Id><Title>What's this?</Title><Msg>Didn't a lot of other names disappear from the board when imaccom did?</Msg><Username>vaclav_havel_fan</Username><Timestamp>1345822414000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 11:33:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345822560812-19</Id><Topic><Title>US Durable Goods Surge in July on Boeing Orders</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1345817122743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 10:05:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All middling to GOOD.</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1345822560812</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 11:36:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345823587311-20</Id><Title>Boeing 777X airplane on hold failure</Title><Msg>Boeing has no development money so the 777X is on hold, another of the “customer’s will wait thinking of Boeing’s CEO, no doubt. How is that outsourcing working for you now Jim McNearney, CEO of Boeing? So the 32 billion hole caused by outsourcing failure on the 787, is going to mean you cannot develop and compete with Airbus. By 2015, China will start selling their 737 replacement plane. . Remember those poor Boeing CEO decision words about the improvement plans being on hold for the 737, , he said” the customer will wait,” on his decision to improve the 737. The result was a huge Boeing market share decline for the 737 market section, and the Airbus neo took away over 1000 plane orders away from Boeing .. This only stopped when the Boeing CEO changed his mind on dissing the 737 customers. The indecision and vacillation resulted in a loss of Boeing market share and some previous all Boeing 737 customers went to Airbus. One thing about failure you can’t teach stupid, now get ready for the 777 repeat of the 737, another no learning experience for the Boeing shareholders who pay the Boeing CEO more than they pay for all the Boeing company taxes Major Boeing customers say the jet maker has tapped the brakes on its plan to develop a new version of its star wide body jet, the 777, a The slowdown in the schedule for the so-called 777X has raised suspicion within the industry that despite a competitive threat from rival Airbus, Boeing's management in Chicago is unwilling to commit the money because of the risk attached to doing several major new jet programs at once. "If Boeing doesn't do anything, the A350 will kill the 777. Period. Everybody knows that," said one major Middle Eastern airline executive who is a top 777 customer, speaking on condition of anonymity. Aerospace analyst Richard Aboulafia, of the Teal Group, said in a letter to clients this week that Boeing's reluctance to move ahead is reminiscent of the six years before the 2004 launch of the 787 when company management slashed research and development spending, hoarded its cash and repeatedly declined to commit to new airplanes. "A parsimonious, risk-averse (and by some estimations greedy) management culture made launching a new jet a near-impossibility," Aboulafia wrote. He added that "backpedaling on promising efforts such as the 777-X ... would presage a return to Boeing's dismal pre-787 days of shortchanging the engineering department." Boeing has no development money so the 777X is on hold, another of the “customer’s will wait thinking of Boeing’s CEO, no doubt. By 2015, China will start selling their 737 replacement plane. .</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1345823587311</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 11:53:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345825462391-21</Id><Title>8-23 midday status</Title><Msg>787: A total of 17 have been delivered so far in the 787 program. 3 are ready for delivery. 6 are in pre delivery flight test. 9 are in pre delivery flight test prep. 10 are in change incorporation and rework. 8 are in final assembly. Other: there are two planes in the air at 12:21 EDT. One emirates 777. One turkish military AWAC 737.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1345825462391</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 12:24:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345826094000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Did the I sraelis try to Assassinate General Dempsey?</Title><Username>skeptically98</Username><Timestamp>1345683282000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-22 20:54:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're the poster by for ignorance and stupidity.</Msg><Username>ichbinienmachoman</Username><Timestamp>1345826094000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 12:34:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345826808059-23</Id><Title>SPEEA files Unfair labor practice against Boeing</Title><Msg>SPEEA files labor complaint against Boeing SPEEA claims Boeing broke federal labor law, telling employees they couldn't make negative comments about the company or display union materials at work. SPEEA represents 23,000 engineers and technical workers, mostly in the Puget Sound region. As the second largest union at Boeing, SPEEA has staged only two labor strikes in its history, the last one was : a 40-day strike in 2000 This is the Boeing Management way , since the IAM is not in contract negotiations , the Boeing Company needs an excuse to cry that the Boeing worker is the scapegoat for the late, or postponed, or over budget 787, 777X and 737MAX and the 767 tanker program’s. Instead of actually looking at poor management decisions We are beginning to witness the effects of 15 years of catastrophic strategic decisions made by the McDonnell clan subsequent to the merger with Boeing and the management coup that lead to the ascension of Stonecipher/ Sears to the strategic leadership positions of Boeing. Stonecipher still controls the strategic decisions of Boeing and the Board by virtue of voting both his shares, and the shares of John McDonnell, making Stonecipher the largest individual voting block on the BOD. Boeing no longer has the internal resources and talent to bring new technology products to market (witness the 787) and we will see a continuing decline of the Boeing company as it loses market share to Airbus and new, emerging competitors in Japan and China. The root cause of this unfolding debacle: Phil Condit.</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1345826808059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 12:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345826821141-24</Id><Title>At 55 and 53, couple split by Rmoney/Lyin' Ryan Medicare plan</Title><Msg>CHICAGO (AP) — Mike O'Malley is 55; wife Sharon is 53. So what? So they're on opposite sides of the age cutoff in Mitt Romney's Medicare plan, and that could create a bumpy transition for the suburban Chicago couple and others like them. It would be the difference between being in the traditional program for the elderly and a less certain future. As the issue rises in importance in the presidential campaign, it's leading to inevitable comparisons for couples and siblings who are just a few years apart — and sometimes perhaps a touch of envy. -\ AFTER SO MANY YEARS SUPPORTING THOSE BEFORE ME, I DON'T WANT NO STINKING VOUCHERS AGE 53!!!</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1345826821141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 12:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345828282894-25</Id><Title>Obama's Budget to Add $4.4 Trillion to Debt in Next Four Years</Title><Msg>Obama's Budget to Add $4.4 Trillion to Debt in Next Four Years On track to $20 trillion in debt in 2016. Unemployment in America IS about to GO Double Digit Again in 2013!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Second Page but Posted this Morning!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! WSJ Boeing 787 Profit Plan Strained by Order Cuts READ the BLOG America!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! The REAL News Matters</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1345828282894</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 13:11:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345828633891-26</Id><Title>Obama, the Fake President!</Title><Msg>Obama has millions of fake Twitter followers Comments By David Jackson, USA TODAY Updated 1h 32m ago CAPTIONAP photos President Obama's Twitter account has 18.8 million followers -- but more than half of them really don't exist, according to reports. A new Web tool has determined that 70% of Obama's crowd includes "fake followers," The New York Times reports in a story about how Twitter followers can be purchased. "The practice has become so widespread that StatusPeople, a social media management company in London, released a Web tool last month called the Fake Follower Check that it says can ascertain how many fake followers you and your friends have," the Times reports. "Fake accounts tend to follow a lot of people but have few followers," said Rob Waller, a founder of StatusPeople. "We then combine that with a few other metrics to confirm the account is fake." Notes the Times: If accurate, the number of fake followers out there is surprising. According to the StatusPeople tool, 71 percent of Lady Gaga's nearly 29 million followers are "fake" or "inactive." So are 70 percent of President Obama's nearly 19 million followers. Republican opponent Mitt Romney has far fewer Twitter followers -- not quite 900,000 -- but it's a good bet that some of them are fake as well. Both campaigns have denied buying Twitter followers.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1345828633891</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 13:17:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345828909095-27</Id><Title>Obama's 2012 Slogan... Hopelessness and Hate</Title><Msg>Low blows, lower turnouts and low expectations: Four years after he was swept to victory, how Obama's election campaign is a joyless slog By TOBY HARNDEN PUBLISHED: 15:21 EST, 23 August 2012 | UPDATED: 22:03 EST, 23 August 2012 Comments (75) Share Barack Obama was swept to the White House in 2008 by a wave of idealism and inspirational campaigning in which he encapsulated the mood of the nation with his slogans of ‘Hope’, ‘Change’ and ‘Yes we can’. Then, his message was a fundamentally positive one. Americans wanted an end to the Bush era but that almost went without saying. Obama pointed to his own vision of the country; a post-partisan, post-racial America in which gridlock in Washington was ended and common-sense centrist solutions were adopted. What a difference four years makes. Obama is campaigning ferociously for a second term – and he is a candidate who would have probably have been disdained by the Obama of 2008. Four more years? President Obama, pictured left in March 2008, and right, at an event in Las Vegas earlier this week; the Commander-in-Chief is waging a relentlessly negative campaign for the White House Drawing crowds: While many came to hear Obama speak Wednesday at Canyon Springs High School in Las Vegas, it's nowhere near the numbers he was reaching in 2008 Obama is waging a relentlessly negative campaign of changing the subject from the one that, overwhelmingly, most Americans care about – the economy. Every week there is a new issue his campaign seizes on, preferring to talk about something, anything other than jobs and 8.3 per cent unemploymemt</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1345828909095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 13:21:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345830907635-28</Id><Title>Medicare SS and other Entitlements you already paid for</Title><Msg>If Ryan Akin and puppet Romney win these entitlements that the right wing now calls "assistance" will be stolen and used to pay for the Ryan Iran War !</Msg><Username>natsu4fun</Username><Timestamp>1345830907635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 13:55:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345831038477-29</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid's Lie about Romney paying Zero Taxes...</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1345414393000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 18:13:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I missed where it says that releasing tax returns is a qualification for the Orifice of President. Having a valid birth certificate IS.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1345831038477</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 13:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345832113385-30</Id><Topic><Title>At 55 and 53, couple split by Rmoney/Lyin' Ryan Medicare plan</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1345826821141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 12:47:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing says lots of things.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1345832113385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 14:15:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345833764673-31</Id><Topic><Title>At 55 and 53, couple split by Rmoney/Lyin' Ryan Medicare plan</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1345826821141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 12:47:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wah, wah, wah double-dipper when one size fits all, +/- nice dig at Chicago, but then where is Willard from leatlone where is he going, not practicing what he preaches aside, say $10,000.00 and it's not good!!!</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1345833764673</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 14:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345833785614-32</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's 2012 Slogan... Hopelessness and Hate</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1345828909095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 13:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans have done nothing but be constant negative since the day Obama took office , not once have one single republican worked with or complimented the President on anything , they have had one mission since the day the President took office and that was to promote failure at all costs, party over country, I find these pukes rather treasonous and pathetic. Republicans will constantly tell bold face lies in the hopes they get more mis informed / low information voters to vote for them all while they will tell you Obama lied when they filibustered or have been 100% against just about everything Obama has put forth.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1345833785614</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 14:43:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345834175351-33</Id><Topic><Title>8-23 midday status</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1345825462391</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 12:24:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump...</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1345834175351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 14:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345834288859-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's 2012 Slogan... Hopelessness and Hate</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1345828909095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 13:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tropical Storm Issac gonna dump on the Rmoney/lyin' Ryan parade according to God's will, not a forcible catgory hurricane unless we really pray hard</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1345834288859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 14:51:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345835117943-35</Id><Title>Boeing unlikely to be profitable Wall Street Journal</Title><Msg>Boeing Co. (NYSE:BA) has seen the cancellation of orders for 35 of its 787 Dreamliners by Qantas Airways. This blow makes it more unlikely that Boeing can make profitable go of its flagship jet programs, says the Wall Street Journal.As listed today next to BA yahoo finance, news !</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1345835117943</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 15:05:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345836226072-36</Id><Title>Boeing has already been profitable today</Title><Msg>71.0920.73(+1.04%)3:18 PMEDT</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1345836226072</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 15:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345838087350-37</Id><Title>Blacks (Charlie Rangle) Turn on Obama/Biden!</Title><Msg>Rangel on Biden’s ‘Chains’ Comment: ‘You Bet Your Life It Was Stupid’ By Colin Campbell 11:04am Twitter240 Facebook399 Reddit Email Print (Photo: Getty) After Vice President Joe Biden infamously told an audience that Mitt Romney is “going to unchain Wall Street,” and concluded they are “going to put y’all back in chains,” Mr. Romney’s campaign cried foul. This was an obvious and unfair allusion to slavery, Mr. Romney’s surrogates argued. Well, count veteran Congressman Charlie Rangel among Mr. Biden’s critics on the Democratic side of the aisle. “The Vice President said he’s going to put “y’all in chains,” Mr. Rangel told The Perez Notes in a recent free-wheeling interview. “Was he talking about slavery? You bet your #$%$ he was. Was he using the vernacular? Yes, he was. Did he think it was cute? Yes, he did. Was it something stupid to say? You bet your life it was stupid.” “It was something that if a black had said it, we would have been laughing, because we would know deep down, they may be beating the hell out of us but they ain’t thinking about putting us into any chains,” he added. Republicans have called on Mr. Biden to apologize, but that doesn’t seem likely to happen anytime soon. “Let’s look at what the vice president said: Speaker Boehner and even Paul Ryan have been traveling this country talking about the need to unshackle the private sector, to unshackle the financial industry,” Mr. Obama’s deputy campaign manager, Stephanie Cutter, argued earlier this week. “And the vice president was just taking that metaphor a step further and talking about wanting to put other people in shackles. And the word that he used, chains, is a distraction from the larger argument.”</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1345838087350</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 15:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345838223358-38</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price down 2.4% on airplane orders !</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1345733374000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 10:49:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus9991, indeed hum- read the Yahoo definition for historical quotes, then go to October 2,2007. Boeing did not close above $100 . Any time a historical price is given you must look at the adjusted close as that chart is historical , and contains several factors. BA did spike to 107.15 , on October 2, 2007 however for that day the adjusted close was less than 100 dollara , it was actually $92.88Boeing closed the day at only $92.88, you need to get your facts straight spartacus99991. Spartacus9991 learn how to read a historical Yahoo finance stock price chart, learn what the adjusted close for Boeing is for that day, and the few other days around that date, go to yahoo, adjusted close. then read the definition of historical adjusted stock price. Spartacus99991, your all wrong BA has never hit and closed at 100 let alone 107, never BA did have a real close below 100. In conclusion at no time has Boeing been a great stock at 92 or 107 you miss the point all together are you a spammer or do you have a personality defect? Hummmmmmmmmmmmm for you and good for the original user comment, you must be a basher for Boeing</Msg><Username>tammyanderson600</Username><Timestamp>1345838223358</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 15:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345838312746-39</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price down 2.4% on airplane orders !</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1345733374000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 10:49:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>adjusted close is the nistorical final price andBoeing has never been a 100 dollar stock more like 92 so the original comment stands look up adjusted close</Msg><Username>tammyanderson600</Username><Timestamp>1345838312746</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 15:58:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345840031093-40</Id><Topic><Title>Medicare SS and other Entitlements you already paid for</Title><Username>natsu4fun</Username><Timestamp>1345830907635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 13:55:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hmmm... Iran, hostages, 1980 election... one candi-date said he will not negotiate with 'terrorists' but then he did along with #$%$ chieney and donald rummy, and funded the monies into Ncarauga...and to ollie north and faux nes dittoheads These are the facts!!!~!</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1345840031093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 16:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345840338806-41</Id><Topic><Title>Medicare SS and other Entitlements you already paid for</Title><Username>natsu4fun</Username><Timestamp>1345830907635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 13:55:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WQhat war are your referring to... the most kind and beneficial Isreali strike against the sum of all fears or IS Isreali still a verboten word on the new and improved YaHooty messageboads even though I supported the notion of the state of israel and the league of nations f0rcefully in my papers as a child does not mean my opines have changed much</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1345840338806</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 16:32:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345841925778-42</Id><Topic><Title>test</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1345762537408</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 18:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>test test</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1345841925778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 16:58:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345842024340-43</Id><Topic><Title>Carriers get paid to cancle delayed plane orders.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1345803392114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 06:16:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>test test</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1345842024340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 17:00:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345846706523-44</Id><Topic><Title>WE NEED HELP</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345567841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney hit a home run in new mexico. the oil people in hobbs and two other liked his statement about opening production of oil and gas on federal lands. owe-bamba has closed this all down....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345846706523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 18:18:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345846834145-45</Id><Title>And throw the RWNJ/bagger Congress out too</Title><Msg>if by their lyin' Ryan record: a. renamed a post-office b. chnaged the tax code on arrows</Msg><Username>republicanfascists</Username><Timestamp>1345846834145</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 18:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345847128280-46</Id><Title>reply to Boeing has already made a gain today!</Title><Msg>By black_mariah777.2 hours 49 minutes ago, you said BA has already made a gain today? IF you must be a Boeing supporter, at least take your blinders off, Boeing was a 75 dollar stock a few days ago and is a 71 dollar stock today. A YTD view on BA Boeing - on the first trade day of 2012 Boeing was a $72.92 stock, now a $71.09 dollar stock down 2.51% for the YTD Compare this to apple AAPL for the start of the year aapl was a 409 dollar stock , today it is a 622 dollar stock and has gained more in the last 20 days than Boeing has historically been worth, so you just missed a 100 dollar gain. The highest adjusted close stock price for Boeing was October 2,2007 at $92.88 so while you look at the wrong statistics black-mariah777, apple shareholders have made over 61% gain since january of this year on apple while you made nothing long or short term on . or try HD or aapl , both stocks have beat BA allt he way from a 5 day to a month to 3 months to 1-2-05 and max use the Yahoo finance comparison stock chart , any Boeing shareholder is a loser compared to apple or HD. get it now !</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1345847128280</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 18:25:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345856041877-47</Id><Title>August week three delivery totals</Title><Msg>A total of 34 planes were delivered so far in August. twenty six 737's. One 747. One 767. Four 777's. Two 787's. There were many test flight planes in the air today. But it does not look like BA will hit 50 deliveries for the month unless they open the delivery floodgates for the next 7 days.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1345856041877</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 20:54:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345866115000-48</Id><Title>Paul Ryan: Galt, Gold and God pt1</Title><Msg>Paul Ryan: Galt, Gold and God Published on Friday, August 24, 2012 by the New York Times by Paul Krugman So far, most of the discussion of Paul Ryan, the presumptive Republican nominee for vice president, has focused on his budget proposals. But Mr. Ryan is a man of many ideas, which would ordinarily be a good thing. In his case, however, most of those ideas appear to come from works of fiction, specifically Ayn Rand’s novel “Atlas Shrugged.” Illustration: Drew FriedmanFor those who somehow missed it when growing up, “Atlas Shrugged” is a fantasy in which the world’s productive people — the “job creators,” if you like — withdraw their services from an ungrateful society. The novel’s centerpiece is a 64-page speech by John Galt, the angry elite’s ringleader; even Friedrich Hayek admitted that he never made it through that part. Yet the book is a perennial favorite among adolescent boys. Most boys eventually outgrow it. Some, however, remain devotees for life. And Mr. Ryan is one of those devotees. True, in recent years, he has tried to downplay his Randism, calling it an “urban legend.” It’s not hard to see why: Rand’s fervent atheism — not to mention her declaration that “abortion is a moral right” — isn’t what the G.O.P. base wants to hear. But Mr. Ryan is being disingenuous. In 2005, he told the Atlas Society, which is devoted to promoting Rand’s ideas, that she inspired his political career: “If I had to credit one thinker, one person, it would be Ayn Rand.” He also declared that Rand’s work was required reading for his staff and interns. And the Ryan fiscal program clearly reflects Randian notions. As I documented in my last column, Mr. Ryan’s reputation for being serious about the budget deficit is completely undeserved; his policies would actually increase the deficit. But he is deadly serious about cutting taxes on the rich and slashing aid to the poor, very much in line with Rand’s worship of the successful and contempt for “moochers.” This last point is important. In pushing for draconian cuts in Medicaid, food stamps and other programs that aid the needy, Mr. Ryan isn’t just looking for ways to save money. He’s also, quite explicitly, trying to make life harder for the poor — for their own good. In March, explaining his cuts in aid for the unfortunate, he declared, “We don’t want to turn the safety net into a hammock that lulls able-bodied people into lives of dependency and complacency, that drains them of their will and their incentive to make the most of their lives.”</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1345866115000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 23:41:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345866165000-49</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan: Galt, Gold and God pt1</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1345866115000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 23:41:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somehow, I doubt that Americans forced to rely on unemployment benefits and food stamps in a depressed economy feel that they’re living in a comfortable hammock. But wait, there’s more: “Atlas Shrugged” apparently shaped Mr. Ryan’s views on monetary policy, views that he clings to despite having been repeatedly, completely wrong in his predictions. In early 2011, Mr. Ryan, newly installed as the chairman of the House Budget Committee, gave Ben Bernanke, the Federal Reserve chairman, a hard time over his expansionary policies. Rising commodity prices and long-term interest rates, he asserted, were harbingers of high inflation to come; “There is nothing more insidious that a country can do to its citizens,” he intoned, “than debase its currency.” Since then, inflation has remained quiescent while long-term rates have plunged — and the U.S. economy would surely be in much worse shape than it is if Mr. Bernanke had allowed himself to be bullied into monetary tightening. But Mr. Ryan seems undaunted in his monetary views. Why? Well, it’s right there in that 2005 speech to the Atlas Society, in which he declared that he always goes back to “Francisco d’Anconia’s speech on money” when thinking about monetary policy. Who? Never mind. That speech (which clocks in at a mere 23 paragraphs) is a case of hard-money obsession gone ballistic. Not only does the character in question, a Galt sidekick, call for a return to the gold standard, he denounces the notion of paper money and demands a return to gold coins. For the record, the U.S. currency supply has consisted overwhelmingly of paper money, not gold and silver coins, since the early 1800s. So if Mr. Ryan really thinks that Francisco d’Anconia had it right, he wants to turn the clock back not one but two centuries. Does any of this matter? Well, if the Republican ticket wins, Mr. Ryan will surely be an influential force in the next administration — and bear in mind, too, that he would, as the cliché goes, be a heartbeat away from the presidency. So it should worry us that Mr. Ryan holds monetary views that would, if put into practice, go a long way toward recreating the Great Depression. And, beyond that, consider the fact that Mr. Ryan is considered the modern G.O.P.’s big thinker. What does it say about the party when its intellectual leader evidently gets his ideas largely from deeply unrealistic fantasy novels?</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1345866165000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 23:42:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>