<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-11"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344663342000-1</Id><Title>Democrats - A Complete Disaster for the Market</Title><Msg>January 3rd, 2007 was the day the Democrats took over the Senate and the Congress. At the time: The DOW Jones closed at 12,621.77 The GDP for the previous quarter was 3.5% The Unemployment rate was 4.6% Remember the day... January 3rd, 2007 was the day that Barney Frank took over the House Financial Services Committee and Chris Dodd took over the Senate Banking Committee. The economic meltdown that happened 15 months later was in what part of the economy? BANKING AND FINANCIAL SERVICES! Unemployment... to this CRISIS by (among MANY other things) dumping 5-6 TRILLION Dollars of toxic loans on the economy from YOUR Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac FIASCOES! And who took the THIRD highest pay-off from Fannie Mae AND Freddie Mac? OBAMA And who fought against reform of Fannie and Freddie? OBAMA and the Democrat Congress</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1344663342000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 01:35:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344693937000-2</Id><Title>Worst VP In History</Title><Msg>Come on libs -- be intellectually honest for once -- you know he's an idiot -- makes Sarah Palin look like Einstein "Look, John's last-minute economic plan does nothing to tackle the number-one job facing the middle class, and it happens to be, as Barack says, a three-letter word: jobs. J-O-B-S, jobs." --Joe Biden "When the stock market crashed, Franklin D. Roosevelt got on the television and didn't just talk about the, you know, the princes of greed. He said, 'Look, here's what happened." -Joe Biden, apparently unaware that FDR wasn't president when the stock market crashed in 1929 and that only experimental TV sets were in use at that time "Hillary Clinton is as qualified or more qualified than I am to be vice president of the United States of America. Quite frankly, it might have been a better pick than me." --Joe Biden, speaking at a town hall meeting in Nashua, New Hampshire "Stand up, Chuck, let 'em see ya." --Joe Biden, to Missouri state Sen. Chuck Graham, who is in a wheelchair, Columbia, Missouri, Sept. 12, 2008</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1344693937000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:05:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344694669000-3</Id><Title>Breaking News: Ryan is NOT Rmoney's VP pick.</Title><Msg>Candidate Rmoney has just announced his VP pick and it's NOT Paul Ryan contrary to what he had announced earlier. He angrily denied he had made the earlier announcement himself and blamed it on White House dirty tricks that he made that announcement. "Why would I want to arouse the ire of the senior citizens, the middle-class, moderates, and independents by picking someone so opposed to their well being?"</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1344694669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344695427000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Worst VP In History</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1344693937000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:05:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1 Dickless Cheney 2 Danforth Quayle 3 Spiro (I completely undertand every one of Biden's staements.)</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1344695427000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:30:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344695910000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking News: Ryan is NOT Rmoney's VP pick.</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1344694669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zero chance the RWNJ crowd will get it.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1344695910000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:38:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344696012000-6</Id><Title>Since Everyone Wants Their Medicare and SS Cut Ryan Is</Title><Msg>the best choice.</Msg><Username>yupitsmedex2004</Username><Timestamp>1344696012000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:40:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344697584000-7</Id><Topic><Title>The Newest and Hottest Stock Site on the Web</Title><Username>norrisroberts659</Username><Timestamp>1344603781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>buy lots of share and earn lots of profit............</Msg><Username>bryancain763</Username><Timestamp>1344697584000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:06:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344698370000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking News: Ryan is NOT Rmoney's VP pick.</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1344694669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That nice, but why not talk about Boeing instead! There is a nice article of Romney picking Ryan in Yahoo news that you can post to instead of the Boeing message board, OK!</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1344698370000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:19:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344698668000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking News: Ryan is NOT Rmoney's VP pick.</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1344694669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because, the impending Fiscal Cliff due to the political gridlock in part caused by Ryan has a bigger potential impact on BA than anything on the Boeing docket other than an all out world war, another potential R/R republicon disaster in waiting.</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1344698668000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:24:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344698751000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking News: Ryan is NOT Rmoney's VP pick.</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1344694669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now your talking Boeing, keep going!</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1344698751000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:25:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344698813000-11</Id><Topic><Title>The Newest and Hottest Stock Site on the Web</Title><Username>norrisroberts659</Username><Timestamp>1344603781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except this the Boeing message board, go away!</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1344698813000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344699032000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Since Everyone Wants Their Medicare and SS Cut Ryan Is</Title><Username>yupitsmedex2004</Username><Timestamp>1344696012000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vote for Boein instead!</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1344699032000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:30:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344699137000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Worst VP In History</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1344693937000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:05:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats nice, pick Boeing instead</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1344699137000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:32:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344699405000-14</Id><Topic><Title>News came out for The Boeing Company</Title><Username>analisacarta</Username><Timestamp>1344691117000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same message on every board, right. Everyone should put you on ignore!</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1344699405000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:36:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344703131000-15</Id><Topic><Title>The Newest and Hottest Stock Site on the Web</Title><Username>norrisroberts659</Username><Timestamp>1344603781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the high time for buying the stock........</Msg><Username>underwoodbryan248</Username><Timestamp>1344703131000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:38:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344703864000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking News: Ryan is NOT Rmoney's VP pick.</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1344694669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Foremo.. You need to lay off the weed dude. It is messing with your mind.. The RR ticket would benefit BA greatly. And the rest of the nation as well.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1344703864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:51:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344704849000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Imperative Momentum Stepping In</Title><Username>charlette_hallie87</Username><Timestamp>1344701023000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:03:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just joined your site.</Msg><Username>aurea_coleen32</Username><Timestamp>1344704849000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 13:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344704999000-18</Id><Title>Elimate the Government Debt- Bernard Madoff</Title><Msg>I bet he knows how to make the dept disappear without you seeing it come out of you paycheck and not raise any taxes.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1344704999000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 13:09:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344706154000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Choosing Ryan</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1344704407000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 13:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wouldn't matter who he chose as a vp, you would have had negative comments regardless of who it was. It is, and will always be about the economy, NO WORK, NO MONEY for the average American. A crappy record for the community organizer, can't change that no matter what you throw in the trash.</Msg><Username>hope4usa2</Username><Timestamp>1344706154000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 13:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344709933000-20</Id><Title>WMD in Syria ? whoda thought ?</Title><Msg>Syria admitted they have WMD, chemicals, gas, etc Syria borders Iraq Wonder if S Hussain simply drove his WMD stuff over the border for safekeeping and later use? Nawwwwwww! raqi-Syrian relations have been marked by their long shared border as well as cultural links. The two countries lie in what was once ancient Mesopotamia. Political relations between Iraq and Syria have in the past been hostile. However new diplomatic relations were established in November 2006, which they heralded as the beginning of an era of close cooperation between Iraq and Syria.[1] Saddam was hung in dec 2006 . . . . BTW- If one reads American sniper by Chris Kyle- he makes it clear that WMD and precursors WERE found in Iraq. . .</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344709933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344710483000-21</Id><Topic><Title>WMD in Syria ? whoda thought ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344709933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris Kyle is a liar. He told a story about a fight with Jesse Ventura and then he couldn't back it up.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1344710483000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:41:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344710660000-22</Id><Topic><Title>WMD in Syria ? whoda thought ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344709933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can Saddam use it later when he's dead?</Msg><Username>right_outfield2010</Username><Timestamp>1344710660000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:44:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344716039000-23</Id><Topic><Title>WMD in Syria ? whoda thought ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344709933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong- the court case brought by ventura has yet to be heard. Ventura has been uhnable to date to back up HIS view/claims CASE 0:12-cv-00472-RHK-AJB Document 2 Filed 02/24/12 Governor Jesse Ventura, a/k/a James G. Janos, an individual, Plaintiff, vs. Chris Kyle, an individual,Defendant ...(Defendant upon information and belief understands that Plaintiff has moved to Baja California, Mexico and that Plaintiff on or about November 4, 2011, announced to news media outside the Warren E. Burger Federal Building in St. Paul, Minnesota, that he would be applying for Mexican citizenship), and therefore denies that allegation. ...11. Upon information and belief, Defendant admits that Plaintiff served in the Naval Special Forces Underwater Demolition/SEAL Teams. Defendant states that he is without information or knowledge sufficient to form a belief as to the truth of the remaining allegations contained in Paragraph 11 of the Complaint (except Defendant further states that Plaintiff has made statements in his presence that appear to be inconsistent with the allegations contained in Paragraph 11 of the Complaint), and therefore denies them. .. ..18. Defendant states that the contents of the book speak for themselves. 19. Defendant denies the allegations and argument contained in Paragraph 19 of the Complaint. 20. Defendant admits and alleges that in national-media interviews connected with the sale of American Sniper, he has responded to questioning about the identity of “Scruff Face” by confirming that the account in the book refers to an incident involving Jesse Ventura. Defendant denies that he intended that readers of the book would understand that Jesse Ventura was “Scruff Face” and accordingly denies that he “has confirmed that the quoted references in his book were intended to and do refer to Governor Ventura” (emphasis added)... .26. Upon information and belief, Defendant admits that the FOX Television Network and HarperCollins are owned by News Corporation. Defendant lacks direct knowledge of how FOX Television Network, HarperCollins, and/or News Corporation view any individual or joint economic interests that they might have. Defendant states that he wants American Sniper to be well-received but that he is deriving no personal profit from any sales of the book. Any and all proceeds that Defendant personally may obtain from the book are being given to charities and to the families of Marc Lee and Ryan Job, his fellow SEALs who died as a result of injuries sustained in combat, in honor of their service to their country. ...Upon information and belief, Defendant alleges that Plaintiff is not a citizen or resident of the State of Texas.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344716039000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344716156000-24</Id><Topic><Title>WMD in Syria ? whoda thought ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344709933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he didn't plan on being dead !! HE WAS GOD in his own mind . . .</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344716156000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344717739000-25</Id><Topic><Title>WMD in Syria ? whoda thought ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344709933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris Kyle said on Fox News that he knocked Jesse Ventura down. He could not back up his story. If he could back up his story, do you think he'd be defending a lawsuit? Fox News issued a retraction on the story. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f4P2fzR9dcA</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1344717739000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:42:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344718311000-26</Id><Topic><Title>WMD in Syria ? whoda thought ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344709933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What shred of evidence do you have that Syria's WMD were once Iraq's? Other than wishing it?</Msg><Username>mister_aero_nut</Username><Timestamp>1344718311000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344718555000-27</Id><Topic><Title>WMD in Syria ? whoda thought ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344709933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as usaual totally wrong on YOUR extract Jesse Ventura demanded a retraction from Fox news for the story they ran on his big mouth getting punched by the most awesome human ever; Chris Kyle. Here is the retraction Fox gave him. with the following headliner on youtube Fox Retracts the Chris Kyle Punches Jesse Ventura story! OK, not really. Its up to Ventura to prove HIS allegation- Jesse is the Plaintiff- and making the allegation that Kyle Lied see my previous post of Kyles response to the court . .</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344718555000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:55:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344718752000-28</Id><Topic><Title>WMD in Syria ? whoda thought ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344709933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no evidence - but I tend to believe Kyle over Ventura- since Kyle was there- and wrote about it. Of course Ventura credibilty is not exactly on the high quality- he also believes 911 was a bush conspiracy, etc.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344718752000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:59:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344720453000-29</Id><Topic><Title>WMD in Syria ? whoda thought ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344709933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No they didn't.</Msg><Username>green.onions23</Username><Timestamp>1344720453000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:27:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344720583000-30</Id><Topic><Title>WMD in Syria ? whoda thought ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344709933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don W. Shuper actually has many of the precursors to the same WMD's under his kithcen and batroom sinks, as well as on his breath. I have heard that there are newborn puppies which can alert to such disease.</Msg><Username>green.onions23</Username><Timestamp>1344720583000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:29:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344720693000-31</Id><Topic><Title>WMD in Syria ? whoda thought ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1344709933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And your Clinton sent our good troops ointo Somali to relieve a rebel of his U.S. armamaments bought on the open and free-market!</Msg><Username>green.onions23</Username><Timestamp>1344720693000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:31:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344720978000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Choosing Ryan</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1344704407000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 13:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney picked a vain narcasistic a-hole who worships a dead vain narcassitic a hole.</Msg><Username>ichbinienmachoman</Username><Timestamp>1344720978000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344722103000-33</Id><Title>On this board WHAT THE F DOES PAUL RYAN HAVE TO DO WITH BA?</Title><Msg>??????????????????????????????????</Msg><Username>bay_8931</Username><Timestamp>1344722103000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:55:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344723681000-34</Id><Topic><Title>On this board WHAT THE F DOES PAUL RYAN HAVE TO DO WITH BA?</Title><Username>bay_8931</Username><Timestamp>1344722103000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;We are on the brink of BK as a country Right. That's why we need to immediately cut the defense budget by 80%. They've had ten years to beat a bunch of farmers armed with AK-47s and ammonium nitrate, and they can't beat them any more than they could beat the farmers armed with AK-47s in Vietnam.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1344723681000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 18:21:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344723962000-35</Id><Topic><Title>On this board WHAT THE F DOES PAUL RYAN HAVE TO DO WITH BA?</Title><Username>bay_8931</Username><Timestamp>1344722103000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Create jobs wihtout trumped-up wars and/or yellow journalism. Have you ever heard of Soylent Green. Taste just like cow.</Msg><Username>green.onions23</Username><Timestamp>1344723962000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 18:26:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344724740000-36</Id><Title>Fox news: Ryna will balance the budget by 2040</Title><Msg>for the hearing IMPAIRED</Msg><Username>green.onions23</Username><Timestamp>1344724740000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 18:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344726770000-37</Id><Topic><Title>On this board WHAT THE F DOES PAUL RYAN HAVE TO DO WITH BA?</Title><Username>bay_8931</Username><Timestamp>1344722103000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, nothing. But a lot of people who have no sane outlet for their political rants seem to flock to stock message boards. Sad, but they have no lives of their own.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1344726770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 19:12:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344727787000-38</Id><Topic><Title>Fox news: Ryna will balance the budget by 2040</Title><Username>green.onions23</Username><Timestamp>1344724740000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 18:39:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hillary will balance it by 2020</Msg><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1344727787000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 19:29:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344729465000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Fox news: Ryna will balance the budget by 2040</Title><Username>green.onions23</Username><Timestamp>1344724740000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 18:39:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>of course was ready to put the shields into the UP postion on the USS Space Enterprise the way RWNJ's were hurling insults, hate, and anger \again today instead of going ??? E-Reconcilliation over the budget proposals.</Msg><Username>green.onions23</Username><Timestamp>1344729465000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 19:57:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344730512000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Choosing Ryan</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1344704407000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 13:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the voice of reason...</Msg><Username>green.onions23</Username><Timestamp>1344730512000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 20:15:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344732948000-41</Id><Topic><Title>8-10 summary</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1344637982000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 18:33:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No deliveries reported by the websites Saturday. The puget sound test flight site has no reports for today. And when I go there I get a malware blocked flag from my Avast anti virus so make sure you have antivirus software activated if you go there. KPAE website has no entries since Thurday. There was a 787 in the air Saturday per the NYC787 site and flightaware tracking. Hope we see something tomorrow...</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1344732948000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 20:55:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344741728000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Putin Seeks 600 Military Jets</Title><Username>phantomtown</Username><Timestamp>1344739554000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 22:45:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>accordingly typed gently putin me, kamchatka peninsula, train ticket can we we count the R-R ticket in.... the future Let us just say for the cats sake the answer remains the same... the black caT IN THE 400 IS ALL MINE</Msg><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1344741728000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 23:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344742054000-43</Id><Topic><Title>The Newest and Hottest Stock Site on the Web</Title><Username>norrisroberts659</Username><Timestamp>1344603781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you...I will buy more...</Msg><Username>romanroman79</Username><Timestamp>1344742054000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 23:27:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>