<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355986432976-1</Id><Topic><Title>Man who ALMOSt went on shooting spree STOPPED by a man with a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355976779166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 23:12:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Guns save lives." You are truly a very sick unit.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1355986432976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 01:53:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355986560354-2</Id><Topic><Title>More Americans Want School Officials Armed Than Assault Weapons Banned</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355959863322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 18:31:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"bump!!!!!! bump it hard" Sounds like you have an erotic fixation on guns. I'm not surprised.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1355986560354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 01:56:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355986724808-3</Id><Topic><Title>The Founding Fathers</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355961996574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 19:06:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"are you in favor of that kind of end run around Congress ?" In this case, YES. Because much if not most of Congress doesn't have the courage to meet the NRA head on. NRA = Nat'l Rampage Association.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1355986724808</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 01:58:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355987749892-4</Id><Topic><Title>Same losers stiil posting on BA board</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1355958005385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 18:00:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You confuse Cause and Effect. Were you a fan of Timothy McVeigh?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1355987749892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 02:15:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355987759463-5</Id><Title>Boehner Plan B</Title><Msg>The Boehner plan B would leave intact government spending cuts, including those related to defense, which are required under a budget deal reached last year to raise the federal debt ceiling. The threat of cuts was intended to motivate Congress to reach a deal.</Msg><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1355987759463</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 02:15:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355988277772-6</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner Plan B</Title><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1355987759463</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 02:15:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boehner announced Tuesday morning a “back-up bill” that would increase taxes on those who earn over $1 million but would preserve Bush-era rates for those making under it. The back-up bill pointedly does not deal with the sequestration, the automatic spending cuts due to be triggered by the end of the year.</Msg><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1355988277772</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 02:24:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355988725608-7</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner Plan B</Title><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1355987759463</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 02:15:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans said they had concerns about the defense cuts that would take place if the bill becomes law.</Msg><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1355988725608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 02:32:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355995985834-8</Id><Topic><Title>More Americans Want School Officials Armed Than Assault Weapons Banned</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355959863322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 18:31:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You alone? Or were there 4-5 SANE people on board who could restrain you when you started talking about your bodily essence?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1355995985834</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 04:33:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355996041601-9</Id><Topic><Title>More Americans Want School Officials Armed Than Assault Weapons Banned</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355959863322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 18:31:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When assault rifles are outlawed, Sparty will have one.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1355996041601</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 04:34:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355996293130-10</Id><Topic><Title>NBCNews: Barack Obama named 2012 TIME Magazine Person of the Year.</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355921383607</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 07:49:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1355996293130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 04:38:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355996539896-11</Id><Topic><Title>Society</Title><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355961736000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 19:02:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please tell me you are NOT urging Sparty to get back into the business of making phony "prophesies." He got spanked so bad on the one about Obama being out of the running by Sept. 1, he hasn't been able to sit down since.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1355996539896</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 04:42:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355997368952-12</Id><Title>Genius Boeing corporate raiders !</Title><Msg>Genius. This is the new America Boeing grants Bonuses and stock options for the top brass, pink slips and blame for the working class. This trend is from the right-wing think tanks and pundits who demonize union members as freeloaders and thugs. It has been a decades-long project, and it’s been incredibly successful. Of course, union scolds never pause to ask why Boeing executives, love to underfund pension funds — that is, to fail to live up to the contracts the with employees in the first place. In this way, private equity operators of Boeing are stuffing companies with debt, squeezing fees and profits into the right executive pockets, and shafting patsies like Boeing shareholder’s, wage employees. When Condit purchased MD , he did not know he purchased a corporate raider company, the few who post here all the time in Boeing Executive defense don’t get it, the Boeing company is being raided. First the massive amount of Boeing held land was sold, . , then the work was outsourced, or moved to a right to work state, and the goal is to bleed Boeing dry then move on.. Boeing will be sucked dry for bankruptcy, which is another technique to pass on Boeing worker pensions to the taxpayer . . All this corporate insider raiding is convered with , . all the bluster about Union’s as characterized as the moochers off society, one group is habitually ignored the executive moochers.. This is the new America:. The reality is not quite so simple — from the Wall Street Journal, no less — consider all the hype surrounding the Hostess company union had crippled and forced Hostess out of business. The truth is that Hostess executives, after their workforce had already taken pay cutbacks or pay freezes,while the Hostess executives had diverted employee retirement funding payments, so payments it was supposed to make to the employee pension fund went into other accounts! The American taxpayer will fund the hostess blue collar workers pensions and the executives move on to retirement or to work for another company to corporate raid it into bankruptcy. The days of the corporate raider have shifted from the Icahn’s and skipped this middle man and gone directly to the Boeing BOD, as worked by the CEO of Boeing company. This is the game plan from Chicago for Boeing , it's the business plan per MD bankruptcy experts, they learned on their own company first, and now are applying this to Boeing, it is so simple to . Condit is very happy with his slice and retired.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355997368952</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 04:56:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356002306395-13</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Crying for the Kids Killed by False Flag "Fast and Furious" ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355969329825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 21:08:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same two party dictatorship...both parties have had their false flags.....But Obama and Holder were in on it too...and the only thing "racist" about it was little Mexican kids being killed.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356002306395</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 06:18:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356002459188-14</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Crying for the Kids Killed by False Flag "Fast and Furious" ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355969329825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 21:08:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All part of a plan to DEMONIZE THE SECOND AMENDMENT...let that sink in for a moment. If our OWN executive branch/justice dept gets caught giving guns to Mexican drug lords to turn around and demonize the second amendment (and this is no longer even debated) then they are capable of ANYTHING</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356002459188</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 06:20:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356002687487-15</Id><Topic><Title>NBCNews: Barack Obama named 2012 TIME Magazine Person of the Year.</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355921383607</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 07:49:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dik: "wouldn't you want a nice guy?" Hamlet: "A Man may Smile and Smile and be a villain" Shakespeare</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356002687487</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 06:24:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356003254216-16</Id><Topic><Title>More Americans Want School Officials Armed Than Assault Weapons Banned</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355959863322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 18:31:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a fixation on the original American principles of freedom and Liberty and the Constition of the United States...even if I have to give my life in the process</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356003254216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 06:34:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356003983703-17</Id><Topic><Title>Society</Title><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355961736000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 19:02:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Although Ive been more right then wrong on the "prophecies" You got me on that one CG. Obama being out of office prediction was made when it looked like America still had a spine. Lots of people got "Breitbarted", brillant politically motivated False flag with OBL a week after Barry released a forged Birth Certificate and the state run media succesfully diverted attention from the Kenyans Birth country....one of the greatest Hoaxes of all time....got to give the Devil his due........What is left of America is in deep deep trouble "I watched with glee While your kings and queens Fought for ten decades For the gods they made I shouted out, Who killed the kennedys? When after all It was you and me Let me please introduce myself I'm a man of wealth and taste And I laid traps for troubadours Who get killed before they reached bombay Pleased to meet you Hope you guessed my name" Sympathy for the Devil</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356003983703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 06:46:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356007372736-18</Id><Topic><Title>Show some respect for the babies that got murdered, gunslingers.</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1355958158419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 18:02:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump it..bump it hard....bump it till it hurts BUMP IT !!!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356007372736</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 07:42:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356007547228-19</Id><Topic><Title>Right-wing author, the "Daily Show" host has helped "drive [God] out of our society"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355963975117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 19:39:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We are witnessing a gruesome crime wave unprecedented in American history" Have you tried looking at economic policies that have bankrupted America as the leading cause of crime ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356007547228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 07:45:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356008705259-20</Id><Topic><Title>Show some respect for the babies that got murdered, gunslingers.</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1355958158419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 18:02:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartakook humping and bumping like a #$%$ DOG.</Msg><Username>shameless_commie</Username><Timestamp>1356008705259</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:05:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356008829160-21</Id><Topic><Title>Genius Boeing corporate raiders !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355997368952</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 04:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and the beat goes on. Next up is to crush SPEEA (that evil union) that will be followed by an IAM bashing (next contract). At the top they set the example for what they care about ($$) and the unions just follow their example. Its amazing that Boeing executives have been traveling to Japan to study the "Toyota way" for years (over 20). Did they learn anything? No, the execs actually think that the "Toyota way" is a smorgasbord of pick and choose. That is why they are still going to school trying "to get it". They never will get it because the "Toyota way" requires them to change their way of being with their employees. Look for articles describing the problems Toyota had with their "sticking" accelerator and the Japan earthquake. Times were tough at Toyota and what did the executives there do? They took a cut in pay before asking their employees to freeze their wages. Do you get it? It is called "walking the talk". What do the Boeing executives (and many other US companies) do? They ask for everyone to cut back on wages in benefits, while their own pay and benefits increase at ludicrous rates. They hire PR firms (with company $$) to bash the unions and glorify executives value and the rank and file are written about as if they were a scourge on the face of the earth and the cause of all problems. Their PR machine is so good that many people believe that the US Executives are justified in their excesses and have earned every penny of their compensation. Since when does a political science major with and MBA know anything about engineering. Well, that is who running the Boeing company. Recent studies have shown that outsiders with no knowledge of how a company operates from the inside out usual fail at running the company (read about HP/CPQ etc). James McN is going to add to this study and he is performing (way beyond expectations) at a high level to achieve failure, but he and his family are guaranteed several life times of income each and every year for the hard work he has put in to destroy the Boeing company. Of course the BOD approves this process. The beat goes on....</Msg><Username>zevach</Username><Timestamp>1356008829160</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:07:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356009316112-22</Id><Topic><Title>Jamie Foxx "I kill all the white people" echos</Title><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1355891900610</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 23:38:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is called institutional racism.</Msg><Username>zevach</Username><Timestamp>1356009316112</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:15:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356009456932-23</Id><Topic><Title>BA is too beneficial to miss right now. Discover why!</Title><Username>gurneyjason392</Username><Timestamp>1356008665846</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:04:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looking good</Msg><Username>juanronald501</Username><Timestamp>1356009456932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:17:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356017328427-24</Id><Topic><Title>BA is too beneficial to miss right now. Discover why!</Title><Username>gurneyjason392</Username><Timestamp>1356008665846</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 08:04:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i signed up</Msg><Username>johnmcneilly36</Username><Timestamp>1356017328427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 10:28:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356017494173-25</Id><Topic><Title>Genius Boeing corporate raiders !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355997368952</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 04:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I worked at two companies that decimated their unions. Convair, owned by General Dynamics and Rohr Industries. Both got union concessions such as split wage rates that lowered entry level wages for new employees and lower retiree benefits. The company claimed they needed these concessions to stay in business. Rohr offloaded work or started shifting work to right to work states. Now, because of their decision they are both out of business. They closed the doors. What happened is they could not attract quality workers and those they did get were quickly disenchanted by working next to employees that made more than they ever would. It became an extremely hostile work environment. It was not the unions that busted these companies. It was short sighted management that did them under.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1356017494173</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 10:31:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356019812737-26</Id><Topic><Title>Right-wing author, the "Daily Show" host has helped "drive [God] out of our society"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355963975117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 19:39:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two things: 1. Hooz, I am surprised that you would post an article about driving God out of our society. I would simply refer you back to the 2012 Democrat Convention - the "booing of God", the unfettered abortions, and same-sex marriage; 2. Gin, While the teachings of the Taliban may be different from strict Islam, as they are "radicalized", the Koran and Islam are nevertheless the antithesis of the Bible and Christianity. They are polar opposites. The Koran explicitly declares that Jesus is NOT the Son of God (he was ONLY a lesser "prophet"), that Jesus was not Deity, that there is no Trinity, that Jesus was NOT crucified (hence, no resurrection), and that it is OK to lie and deceive in order to promote the cause of Islam (Taqiyya). And some people think that the God of the Bible is the same as Allah. It is impossible for both to be true.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1356019812737</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 11:10:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356020627304-27</Id><Topic><Title>Genius Boeing corporate raiders !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355997368952</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 04:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rohr was acquired by Goodrich</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1356020627304</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 11:23:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356020716803-28</Id><Topic><Title>Would you give up your right to buy a assault rifle</Title><Username>gin.haruko</Username><Timestamp>1355965872018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 20:11:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you take a assault rifle bowling? does it help your score?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1356020716803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 11:25:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356021544726-29</Id><Topic><Title>Society</Title><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355961736000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 19:02:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty gets his prophesies from ME. I get my $ from donors like Sparty. A nice circle. s/ Orly</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1356021544726</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 11:39:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356023144734-30</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC the Ed Show interview revealed Obama is attacking the Middle Class but Ed cut him right off at the knees</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1355978262018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 23:37:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He and the rest of us have heard enough from the spin doctors from Fox News......that's why he cut him off</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1356023144734</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 12:05:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356023551979-31</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC the Ed Show interview revealed Obama is attacking the Middle Class but Ed cut him right off at the knees</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1355978262018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 23:37:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama was attacking the Middle Class, and he poor when he took the campaign strategy of "taxing the upper 2% only, and protecting the middle class from having their taxes raised" That is a blatant lie, but as James Carville said, "easy to lead stupid folks like democrats to the polls."</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356023551979</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 12:12:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356024033851-32</Id><Topic><Title>Genius Boeing corporate raiders !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355997368952</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 04:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing talks a good story about cutting costs, increasing stakeholder value, blah-blah-blah. All those things come at the expense of the productive workforce. When it comes to Management, however, they circle the wagons and protect their own. Its always been that way.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1356024033851</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 12:20:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356024597276-33</Id><Topic><Title>Society</Title><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355961736000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 19:02:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a prime example of the people who should never be allowed to own firearms of any kind.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1356024597276</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 12:29:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356025555398-34</Id><Topic><Title>Society</Title><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355961736000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 19:02:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? I don't recall a single one of your "prophesies" that have come true. Your record is SO BAD that I was beginning to think you were spoofing yourself even to call them "prophesies." You know, like someone who today would call the Titanic unsinkable..</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356025555398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 12:45:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356028192446-35</Id><Topic><Title>Jamie Foxx "I kill all the white people" echos</Title><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1355891900610</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 23:38:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the tards that can't tell fantasy from reality, it's CALLED A MOVIE!</Msg><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1356028192446</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:29:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356028453436-36</Id><Title>Why Are All Obama Haters On This Board Such Tards?</Title><Msg>I know it's not 'just me' that notices this. And in fact go to any political news story and read the comments. Without fail, the anti Obama posters sound like they are either working with sub 50 IQ points or they are deranged. Without fail!</Msg><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1356028453436</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:34:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356028575362-37</Id><Title>How Much Will Cliff Plunge Cost You</Title><Msg>The Bush tax cuts added $2.6 trillion to public debt from 2001 - 2010. Locate where you are in the data below to determine what it will cost you when the tax cuts expire, as they will because of repub pigheadedness: Below $10,000. Average tax cut is $52. $10 - $20,000. Average tax cut is $387. $20 - $30,000. Average tax cut is $769. $30 - $40,000. Average tax cut is $894. $40 - $50,000. Average tax cut is $909. $50 - $75,000. Average tax cut is $1119 $75K- $100,000. Average tax cut is $1871. $100K - $200,000. Average tax cut is $3690. $200K - $500,000. Average tax cut is $7152. $500K - $1,000,000. Average tax cut is $17,467. $1,000,000+. Average tax cut is $103,835. Note that the wealthy made out like bandits (excuse the redundancy).</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356028575362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:36:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356028579415-38</Id><Title>How Much Will Cliff Plunge Cost You</Title><Msg>The Bush tax cuts added $2.6 trillion to public debt from 2001 - 2010. Locate where you are in the data below to determine what it will cost you when the tax cuts expire, as they will because of repub pigheadedness: Below $10,000. Average tax cut is $52. $10 - $20,000. Average tax cut is $387. $20 - $30,000. Average tax cut is $769. $30 - $40,000. Average tax cut is $894. $40 - $50,000. Average tax cut is $909. $50 - $75,000. Average tax cut is $1119 $75K- $100,000. Average tax cut is $1871. $100K - $200,000. Average tax cut is $3690. $200K - $500,000. Average tax cut is $7152. $500K - $1,000,000. Average tax cut is $17,467. $1,000,000+. Average tax cut is $103,835. Note that the wealthy made out like bandits (excuse the redundancy).</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356028579415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:36:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356030035678-39</Id><Topic><Title>Let's Bulletproof the Kids</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355960444452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 18:40:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give those little kids some handguns! At least they will be able to shoot back. Body armour and semi automatic weapons, now that's the answer. Maybe an easily defendable safe room in ever school too. Sounds like a plan!</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1356030035678</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 14:00:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356030832158-40</Id><Topic><Title>Man who ALMOSt went on shooting spree STOPPED by a man with a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355976779166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 23:12:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The OFF DUTY COP JUST PROVED IT - Guns DO save lives</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1356030832158</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 14:13:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356032051540-41</Id><Topic><Title>Let's Bulletproof the Kids</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355960444452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 18:40:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like a bleeding heart socialist</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1356032051540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 14:34:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356032376384-42</Id><Topic><Title>Let's Bulletproof the Kids</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355960444452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 18:40:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like someone who doesn't know what "socialism" means. There sure are a lot of you idiots.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1356032376384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 14:39:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356033025079-43</Id><Topic><Title>Let's Bulletproof the Kids</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355960444452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 18:40:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spot on! No need for assault weapons. If ye must have them, join the army! It's that simple! Druid</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1356033025079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 14:50:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356034520890-44</Id><Topic><Title>Let's Bulletproof the Kids</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355960444452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 18:40:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are very few "assault weapons" in private hands. An assault weapon/rifle is a selective fire item capable of full auto fire. Please get your facts straight before pontificating on something you are obviously ignorant of.</Msg><Username>exeter1954</Username><Timestamp>1356034520890</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:15:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356034596646-45</Id><Topic><Title>Let's Bulletproof the Kids</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355960444452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 18:40:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yerp they will wear them all day in the class room and they do not cover the head or front of the body. Time to arm the teachers and the kids at the age of 12. Most states allowed to hunt then</Msg><Username>jamesw34677</Username><Timestamp>1356034596646</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:16:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356035046281-46</Id><Title>A New Election Is being Held</Title><Msg>Rich guys like myself are voting with our feet. We always win these elections.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356035046281</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:24:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356035139616-47</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Will Cliff Plunge Cost You</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356028579415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:36:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not true....the lack of spending cuts added to the debt</Msg><Username>makboe</Username><Timestamp>1356035139616</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:25:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356035402120-48</Id><Topic><Title>Genius Boeing corporate raiders !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355997368952</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 04:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>interesting rant.....but it falls apart given the company keeps launching new aircaft and aircraft derivitves....nice try.</Msg><Username>wredde</Username><Timestamp>1356035402120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:30:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356035819957-49</Id><Title>is there any common sense on assault weapons</Title><Msg>I am tired seeing our children killed with automtic weapons. Aren't you?</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1356035819957</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:36:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356035896080-50</Id><Title>we are almost as good as Israel</Title><Msg>guns with no freedom</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1356035896080</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:38:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356036233509-51</Id><Topic><Title>Man who ALMOSt went on shooting spree STOPPED by a man with a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355976779166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 23:12:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guns don't save lives -- PEOPLE save lives. Idiot.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1356036233509</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:43:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356036340746-52</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Will Cliff Plunge Cost You</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356028579415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:36:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rich people like myself should be able to keep more of the money we earned because we have proven that we are able to manage our money, produce more jobs and create more wealth than politicians. People that accumulate $ 16 trillion of debt obviously are incompetent and shouldn't be trusted with other people's money. If you live in this country and find the best you can do at 40 years of age is flip hamburgers or twist wrenches on an airplane assembly line, then you deserve to pay higher taxes for being part of the mediocre class.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356036340746</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:45:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356036369247-53</Id><Topic><Title>A New Election Is being Held</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356035046281</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:24:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for self-deporting. Nothing could possibly make us happier. Don't let the door hit you in the #$%$ on the way out.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1356036369247</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:46:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356036807826-54</Id><Title>Global Warming is a Hoax - Russia's Coldest winter in 70 years</Title><Msg>Russia is enduring its harshest winter in over 70 years, with temperatures plunging as low as -50 degrees Celsius. Dozens of people have already died, and almost 150 have been hospitalized. ­The country has not witnessed such a long cold spell since 1938, meteorologists said, with temperatures 10 to 15 degrees lower than the seasonal norm all over Russia. Across the country, 45 people have died due to the cold, and 266 have been taken to hospitals. In total, 542 people were injured due to the freezing temperatures, RIA Novosti reported. The Moscow region saw temperatures of -17 to -18 degrees Celsius on Wednesday, and the record cold temperatures are expected to linger for at least three more days. Thermometers in Siberia touched -50 degrees Celsius, which is also abnormal for December. For you victims of socialized government education -50 degrees Celsius is equal to - 50 degrees Fahrenheit. IOWs it's cold but I know you've been brainwashed to believe it's cold because of global warming.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356036807826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:53:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356037905863-55</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming is a Hoax - Russia's Coldest winter in 70 years</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356036807826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>= For you victims of socialized government education -50 degrees Celsius is equal to - 50 degrees Fahrenheit. = This well-educated individual, schooled in public schools of the S.F. (East) Bay Area, CA, in the 60s and 70s, learned how to _perform_ this basic conversion at a very young age, and never forgot: In fact, Celsius and Fahrenheit are equal at -42, and not a degree warmer or colder. So what is your problem? Never learned elementary math in your fancy private school? Who's the brainwashed idiot now?</Msg><Username>wonderdoc</Username><Timestamp>1356037905863</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 16:11:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356038020061-56</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming is a Hoax - Russia's Coldest winter in 70 years</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356036807826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- 50 C = - 58 F</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1356038020061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 16:13:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356039159710-57</Id><Topic><Title>A New Election Is being Held</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356035046281</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:24:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO.....we don't have to leave.....just go on a nice vacation and open a bank account and deposit some money that will create lots of jobs elsewhere. We can always come back and just for entertainment watch all the sacred mediocre class crash and burn while they keep shooting themselves in the foot over and over again.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356039159710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 16:32:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356039450843-58</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming is a Hoax - Russia's Coldest winter in 70 years</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356036807826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be the president of the flat earth club</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1356039450843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 16:37:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356039803824-59</Id><Topic><Title>is there any common sense on assault weapons</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1356035819957</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:36:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"is there any common sense on assault weapons" Not since you started posting.</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1356039803824</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 16:43:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356039938912-60</Id><Topic><Title>Man who ALMOSt went on shooting spree STOPPED by a man with a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355976779166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 23:12:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well if people save lives then people kill as well ..in your example guns neither kill nor save, therefore all this talk about banning guns is stupid</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1356039938912</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 16:45:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356040058847-61</Id><Topic><Title>Genius Boeing corporate raiders !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355997368952</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 04:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... and who do you think launches the new aircraft - Management? LOL - nice try to you, too!</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1356040058847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 16:47:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356040085362-62</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Will Cliff Plunge Cost You</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356028579415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:36:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>snugor rim, so which are you? A burger flipper or a rivit bucker? Apparently they are only occupations you are familiar with. Nothing to be ashamed of. Many people work hard for a living. Pretending to be rich or fantasizing you will become rich someday is a characteristic of the typical bagger.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356040085362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 16:48:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356040197376-63</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Will Cliff Plunge Cost You</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356028579415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:36:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>makboeing, what is you want to cut most? Boeing defense contracts?</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356040197376</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 16:49:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356040206186-64</Id><Topic><Title>Genius Boeing corporate raiders !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355997368952</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 04:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Launching new programs is NOT the same as getting certified new models into the sky.</Msg><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1356040206186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 16:50:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356040485344-65</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Will Cliff Plunge Cost You</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356028579415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:36:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Willard might have to cough up over two million more next year. Pity!</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356040485344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 16:54:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356040774326-66</Id><Title>How to Balance the No-Budget and Eliminate our National Debt</Title><Msg>Get a copy of the U.S. Constitution. Look up Article 1, Section 8 and read the 18 things the Federal government is authorized to do. Eliminate all expenditures for anything not listed. Eliminate all government agencies not listed. Make the Democrat led Senate grow a pair and produce a budget like the constitution requires.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356040774326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 16:59:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356040815168-67</Id><Topic><Title>A New Election Is being Held</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356035046281</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:24:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People like you don't create jobs. Demand, mostly from people who work for a living and contribute something of value to society, creates jobs. You're just a leech, whose self-esteem is so low you have to waste time on an Internet message board telling total strangers how important and wealthy you are in an effort to prop it up. You're a joke dude, but your delusions are wonderful. Please tell us more. BWAA! HA! HA! HA! HA! HA! HA! BWAA! HA! HA! HA! HA! HA! HA!</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1356040815168</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 17:00:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356041304265-68</Id><Topic><Title>Genius Boeing corporate raiders !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355997368952</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 04:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wredde, As I pointed out some of your language to other posters is vulgar and I hope you put me on ignore, your attitude of "nice try" pretends to make you some expert, your not. You have , most likely no opinion backed up by facts. So Wredde, the only new plane since the 777 is the 787, the 747 is 2 years late and 2 billion over expected budget and not selling as planned. The 737 , no reason to think Boeing contractor will bring the engine in on time or working as planned reference the 787. So Wredde, Your obvious support of Boeing clearly clouds your vision and inhibits your ability to accept facts in evidence, each 787 delivered is at a loss for the shareholder, the Boeing company stock price has been flat or gone down over 1% year to date and these plane deliveries are nothing more than a planted news story with no substance related to how the new and derivitave planes are delivered late and overbudget</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1356041304265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 17:08:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356041569988-69</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Will Cliff Plunge Cost You</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356028579415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:36:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mir rogoons delusions of grandeur are the manifestation of a psychopathological condition in which a person has fantasies of wealth. These people often also have an inflated sense of self-importance, and may hold an obsession with grandiose or extravagant ravings. Even when presented with evidence contradicting their delusions, they will still cling to their erroneous beliefs. .</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356041569988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 17:12:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356041831888-70</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming is a Hoax - Russia's Coldest winter in 70 years</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356036807826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "designers" of man induced global warming know it is a hoax. Scientists who are not govt. scientists whose salaries are not in jeapardy say it is a hoax. Just a way to steal money from the private sector, and finance socialism. Just like Obama is doing with his economic proposals right now that will push us over the cliff...no cuts, he needs more revenue to keep socialism funded.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356041831888</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 17:17:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356041844673-71</Id><Topic><Title>NBCNews: Barack Obama named 2012 TIME Magazine Person of the Year.</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355921383607</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 07:49:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Third place goes to Lyin Ryan at the Tampa republiwhopperpalooza.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356041844673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 17:17:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356043026002-72</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Will Cliff Plunge Cost You</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356028579415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:36:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Newtie says he woulda done better than Willard on election day. So says the master of Moonbase Alpha. These repubs are faaantastic!.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356043026002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 17:37:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356045025687-73</Id><Title>BRRRRRRR!: EARTH'S GLACIERS ARE GROWING, NOT SHRINKING!</Title><Msg>CFP: Contrary to Gore's assertions, almost all of the ice-covered regions of the Earth are growing, not melting --and the seas are not rising “Almost all of the ice-covered regions of the Earth are melting — and seas are rising,” said Al Gore -in an op-ed piece in the New York Times on February 27. Both parts of Gore’s statement are false. Never mind that Mr. Gore makes only passing reference to the IPCC’s fraudulent claims that the Himalayan glaciers will all melt by 2035. (“A flawed overestimate,” he explains.) Never mind that Mr. Gore dismisses the IPCC’s fraudulent claims that the oceans are rising precipitously. (“Partly inaccurate,” he huffs.) Never mind that Mr. Gore completely ignores the admission by the CRU’s disgraced former director Phil Jones that global temperatures have essentially remained unchanged for the past 15 years. I’ll let someone else dissect Gore’s lawyering comments, and concentrate on just the one sentence about melting ice, because neither part of that sentence is true. Contrary to Gore’s assertions, almost all of the ice-covered regions of the Earth are growing, not melting—and the seas are not rising. Let’s look at the facts. If you click on the words “are melting” in Gore’s article, you’re taken to a paper by Michael Zemp at the University of Zurich. Mr. Zemp begins his paper by warning that “glaciers around the globe continue to melt at high rates.” However, if you bother to actually read the paper, you learn that Zemp’s conclusion is based on measurements of “more than 80 glaciers.” Considering that the Himalayas boast more than 15,000 glaciers, a study of “more than 80 glaciers” hardly seems sufficient to warrant such a catastrophic pronouncement. Especially when you learn that of those 80 glaciers, several are growing. Growing. Not melting. “In Norway, many maritime glaciers were able to gain mass,” Zemp concedes. (“Able to gain mass” means growing.) In North America, Zemp also concedes, “some positive values were reported from the North Cascade Mountains and the Juneau Ice Field.” (“Displaying positive values” means growing.) Remember, we’re still coming out of the last ice age. Ice is supposed to melt as we come out of an ice age. The ice has been melting for 11,000 years. Why should today be any different? I’m guessing that most Canadians and Northern Europeans are very happy that the ice has been melting. Unfortunately, that millenniums-long melting trend now appears to be changing. No matter how assiduously Mr. Gore tries to ignore it, almost all of the ice-covered regions of the Earth are now gaining mass. (Or, displaying positive values, if you will.)</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356045025687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:10:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356045856067-74</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming is a Hoax - Russia's Coldest winter in 70 years</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356036807826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Globally, five countries this year set heat records, but none set cold records. 2012 is on track to be the warmest year on record in the United States. Worldwide, the average through November suggests it will be the eighth warmest since global record-keeping began in 1880.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1356045856067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:24:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356045962914-75</Id><Topic><Title>Adolf Hitler: TIME Magazine Man of the Year, 1938</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356045403007</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:16:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time gets some right &amp; some wrong.....Sarah Palin was picked in 2008.....was that a right or wrong pick</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1356045962914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:26:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356046089778-76</Id><Topic><Title>BRRRRRRR!: EARTH'S GLACIERS ARE GROWING, NOT SHRINKING!</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356045025687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:10:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you pay a higher air conditioning bill this summer due to more usage or because the utility company jacked up their fees</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1356046089778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:28:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356046331596-77</Id><Topic><Title>Adolf Hitler: TIME Magazine Man of the Year, 1938</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356045403007</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:16:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think "right" and "wrong" are terms too relative (and too subjective) for Time's selection process. (That would also explain why Spartacus, our very own canary in our outrage coal mine, go so upset about Hitler and Stalin. :-) I think Time wants its person of the year to be someone who had a huge effect on people, or on a huge number of people; someone who was "in the news" a lot. That's why this year, Obama was named -- though Romney was probably a close second with his chat about the 47%</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356046331596</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:32:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356046421719-78</Id><Topic><Title>Adolf Hitler: TIME Magazine Man of the Year, 1938</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356045403007</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:16:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably; but it also explains YOUR problem.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356046421719</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:33:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356046626643-79</Id><Title>Boeing and Potato Heads</Title><Msg>Boeing uses potatoes to simulate humans in test of Wi-Fi signals Boeing, the Chicago-based company that has built some of the world's most sophisticated aircraft, has turned to a very basic food staple to test airplane Wi-Fi: potatoes. About 20,000 pounds of potatoes were used as stand-ins for passengers during tests at the company's laboratories to ensure onboard Wi-Fi signals are consistent through the cabin without interrupting the navigation and communication systems, the company said Wednesday. The sacks of potatoes replicate the way human passengers reflect and absorb electronic signals, said Boeing spokesman Adam Tischler. goes on Guess the Boeing Board of Directionless was not available to be used as human dummies What is the difference between Boeing BOD and a sack of Potatoes ? The potatoes have eyes, and will spoil unless kept in the dark. ? The BOD cannot see- and grow if kept in the dark . ? The sack of potatoes has a useful function ? and probably a composite IQ above that of the BOD</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1356046626643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:37:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356046708282-80</Id><Topic><Title>Why Every REAL AMERICAN Should Own Multiple Firearms</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356035383693</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:29:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have very few REAL AMERICANS left......thanks to socialized government education most are too dumb and ignorant to live in freedom.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356046708282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:38:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356046755980-81</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Will Cliff Plunge Cost You</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356028579415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:36:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But I slept in a Holiday Inn last night.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356046755980</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:39:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356047039758-82</Id><Topic><Title>Adolf Hitler: TIME Magazine Man of the Year, 1938</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356045403007</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:16:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A little bitter are we? Pity.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1356047039758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:43:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356047162059-83</Id><Topic><Title>Antarctic ice growing, not shrinking</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356041772104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 17:16:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Global warming is a hoax to let fat cats like weird Al Gore get fatter by preying on the ignorance of victims of socialized government education. Al probably laughs every night at how stupid people are to believe his nonsense.....then laughs again next morning as he takes their money to the bank.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356047162059</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:46:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356047423003-84</Id><Topic><Title>So another Obama lie, tax the millionaires and billionaires is actually tax the Middle Class</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1356046613613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:36:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The GOP exposed it but nobody was listening</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356047423003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:50:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356047755556-85</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing and Potato Heads</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1356046626643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:37:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you sure those were potatoes and not union members? I once asked A Boeing engineer how many people worked at Boeing. He said about 30% and the rest were union members.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356047755556</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:55:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356047922397-86</Id><Topic><Title>Why I'm for the Brady Bill</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356047652186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:54:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brady's a good Quarterback but he's not a Bill......Plays for New England.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356047922397</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:58:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356048029723-87</Id><Topic><Title>22 Schoolchildren Stabbed in China on Same Day As Sandy Hook</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356035776579</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:36:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does it matter how long it took him?</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356048029723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:00:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356048148388-88</Id><Topic><Title>22 Schoolchildren Stabbed in China on Same Day As Sandy Hook</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356035776579</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:36:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Responding to a troll like Mir only encourages him.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1356048148388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:02:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356048165438-89</Id><Title>Why Won't Democrats Produce a Budget for a Vote?</Title><Msg>Why won't they grow a pair and let you know how they want to spend your money?</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356048165438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:02:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356048222108-90</Id><Topic><Title>Adolf Hitler: TIME Magazine Man of the Year, 1938</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356045403007</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:16:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I KNEW EXACTLY what criteria Time uses pea brain. As you might recall, it was the DIK who made the initial post with the insinuation that the critera was NOT so much "who had the greatest impact on humaity" but who was the BEST PERSON....otehrwise Time would not have had Osama Bin Ladin as runner up one year...and Hitler and Stalin other years....correcting your drivel is a full time job.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356048222108</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:03:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356048318785-91</Id><Title>Why Did Obama Want a Communist in His Administration?</Title><Msg>.....more importantly why didn't liberals care if he wanted a communist in his administration?</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356048318785</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:05:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356048469349-92</Id><Topic><Title>Why Every REAL AMERICAN Should Own Multiple Firearms</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356035383693</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:29:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Mir....couldn't have said it better myself. The collectivists are pushing hard to take guns. If they get them, they will have their way with us.....FEMA Camps, reeducation centers, robbing blind anyone left with any money even if you DO comply....and those who dont well be branded as terrorists by a complicit media and swat teams will be standing by. Basically we are headed into the worst parts of the Orwellian distopic future.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356048469349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:07:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356048684962-93</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Crying for the Kids Killed by False Flag "Fast and Furious" ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355969329825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 21:08:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356048684962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:11:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356048823370-94</Id><Title>What do Stalin, Mao, Castro and Obama have in Common?</Title><Msg>Besides being Communist Dictators they were all Time magazine's Person of the Year.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356048823370</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:13:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356048838756-95</Id><Topic><Title>In Wake of School Massacre, Tea Party Holds 'Great Gun Giveaway'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356045929775</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:25:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Switzerland has a Great Gun giveaway for all able bodied Men (which leaves you out Dik..sorry)..but I wonder..why do they ahave the lowest crime rate and why have they never been invaded ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356048838756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:13:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356048910128-96</Id><Topic><Title>Life is Dangerous.....Ban Everything !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355886479309</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 22:07:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Our main agenda is to have all guns banned. We must use whatever means possible. It doesn't matter if you have to distort the facts or even lie. Our task of creating a socialist America can only succeed when those who would resist us have been totally disarmed." Sara Brady Chairman, Handgun Control Inc, to Senator Howard Metzenbaum The National Educator, January 1994, Page 3.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356048910128</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:15:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356049037509-97</Id><Title>Why Are Democrats so Concerned About 20 School Children being killed</Title><Msg>.....when they make it possible for 6 million innocent babies to be killed every year?</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356049037509</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:17:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356049056606-98</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Will Cliff Plunge Cost You</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356028579415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:36:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A perfect description of mIR's wealth fantasy. Sort of like a welfare recipient with a net worth of $100 who subscribes to Forbes magazine.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1356049056606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:17:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356049124338-99</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Will Cliff Plunge Cost You</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356028579415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:36:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mir wouldn't last 20 minutes trying to buck rivets on the 747 wing line.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1356049124338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:18:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356049251554-100</Id><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Msg>If you liberal Nimrods drinking the Koolaide are so worried about the proliferation of Guns and school shootings ......then why does our own Chief Executive give guns to Mexcan Drug Lords...and EVEN ALQAEDA in Syria...(ALL VERIFIABLE ..so dont say its not happenning) ? For those of you who think Operation Fast and Furious is a conspiracy theory, you'll be more inclined to believe it when you read that the President of the United States of America is supplying weapons to AL QAEDA IN SYRIA. Makes that whole giving-guns-to-Mexican-drug-cartels look like child's play, huh? Though the New York Times has not seen fit to report the scandal about the cover up of the assassination of our Ambassador in Libya on the front page, it has managed to conjure a bit of space to this gobsmacking report: WASHINGTON — Most of the arms shipped at the behest of Saudi Arabia and Qatar to supply Syrian rebel groups fighting the government of Bashar al-Assad are going to hard-line Islamic jihadists, and not the more secular opposition groups that the West wants to bolster, according to American officials and Middle Eastern diplomats. “The opposition groups that are receiving the most of the lethal aid are exactly the ones we don’t want to have it,” said one American official familiar with the outlines of those findings, commenting on an operation that in American eyes has increasingly gone awry.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356049370978-101</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming is a Hoax - Russia's Coldest winter in 70 years</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356036807826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Attention Mirdoofus глупый: Please return to your private school and demand tuition refund from all after about 4th grade.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1356049370978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:22:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356049715194-102</Id><Topic><Title>Why Every REAL AMERICAN Should Own Multiple Firearms</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356035383693</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:29:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FEMA Camps? Aren't you a little late on this one? Why didn't you tell everybody BEFORE the election? This way everybody could have voted for Huh Kyung-young (with the 430 I.Q.). At least we would have good dope so we could enjoy our FEMA camp.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1356049715194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:28:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356049998329-103</Id><Topic><Title>Why Every REAL AMERICAN Should Own Multiple Firearms</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356035383693</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:29:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah...As the board buffoon you're too much fun</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049998329</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:33:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356050057016-104</Id><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Msg>We have a congress with 11% approval, a supreme court with 18% approval a president with under 50% approval most of the time. We are not being governed by consent of the governed, Even the majority isn't approved by 50% of REAL AMERICANS. Remember the American Revolution was fought by a minority of the residents. The Declaration of Independence said it is our duty to over throw the government when it becomes abusive. A government that takes by force the property of a person who earned it and gives it to a person who didn't earn it is abusive.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356050141164-105</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are Democrats so Concerned About 20 School Children being killed</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356049037509</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:17:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>....the truth never gets old......only the people who ignore it.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050141164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:35:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356050808711-106</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you were a sitting President and it was discovered that you were openly supporting al-Qaeda—openly supplying them with weapons—what would you do? Since al-Qaeda is the sworn enemy of the United States, since al-Qaeda has murdered countless Americans, and therefore supporting al-Qaeda would be treason in every sense of the word, of course you would resign or brace for impeachment. But we’re not talking about a normal President who operates within the confines of reason. We’re talking about Barack Hussein Obama, who operates in a strange Twilight Zone type of reality broadcast to the masses via his compliant mainstream media. The Syrian “rebels” have openly identified themselves with al-Qaeda. They have openly said, “When We Finish With Assad, We Will Fight the U.S.”, so it’s no secret they are the enemy. And Barack Obama has been arming them. And this isn’t the first time. When Obama was basking in the light of his “democratic moment” in arming the Libyan “rebels” to topple Gadaffi, here again he was arming al-Qaeda. The dirty little secret of course is that the weapons that Barack Obama was lavishing on the “democratic” rebels found their way into the hands of their sister group, Ansar al-Sharia. Have you heard of them? They are the group that murdered the four Americas at the Benghazi consulate and CIA annex—more than likely with weapons Barack Obama supplied. That’s the other dirty little secret of why Obama refused to go into Benghazi to rescue Americans in need: he was afraid his fingerprints would be found on the weapons that were left behind when Tyrone Woods and Glen Doherty had to fight off the attack themselves. So with Obama admitting that he is supplying arms to the Syrian al-Qaeda “Freedom Fighters”, what does he do? Yesterday, he officially recognized the rebels as the “true” government of Syria. Maybe I’m wrong. Maybe I haven’t watched enough Twilight Zone episodes, but isn’t Obama kind of guilty of that little thing called “treason?” “Treason against the United States, shall consist only in levying War against them, or in adhering to their Enemies, giving them Aid and Comfort.” U.S. Constitution, Article 3, Section 3.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356050808711</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:46:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356050900474-107</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Crying for the Kids Killed by False Flag "Fast and Furious" ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355969329825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 21:08:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356050900474</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:48:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356051425937-108</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are Democrats so Concerned About 20 School Children being killed</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356049037509</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:17:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good Post Couldn't have said it better myself...oh wait...I DID say that myself</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356051425937</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:57:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356052062561-109</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are Democrats so Concerned About 20 School Children being killed</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356049037509</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:17:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Proof that you need help RIGHT NOW. You are amusing most of the time but sometimes scary. Psychosis indicated.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1356052062561</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 20:07:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356052648723-110</Id><Topic><Title>God Bless Barack Obama...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356052101413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 20:08:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"right puts on a display"...That would make you wrong</Msg><Username>spartacus778899</Username><Timestamp>1356052648723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 20:17:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356053213269-111</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Washington times thinks Benghazigate was DUE to Obama supplying guns to Islamic Jihadists. The evidence suggests that the Obama administration has not simply been engaging, legitimating, enriching and emboldening Islamists who have taken over or are ascendant in much of the Middle East. Starting in March 2011, when American diplomat J. Christopher Stevens was designated the liaison to the “opposition” in Libya, the Obama administration has been arming them, including jihadists like Abdelhakim Belhadj, leader of the al Qaeda franchise known as the Libyan Islamic Fighting Group. Once Moammar Gadhafi was overthrown, Stevens was appointed ambassador to the new Libya run by Mr. Belhadj and his friends. Not surprisingly, one of the most important priorities for someone in that position would be to try to find and secure the immense amount of armaments that had been cached by the dictator around the country and systematically looted during and after the revolution. One of the places in Libya most awash with such weapons in the most dangerous of hands is Benghazi. It now appears that Stevens was there — on a particularly risky day, with no security to speak of and despite now copiously documented concerns about his own safety and that of his subordinates — for another priority mission: sending arms recovered from the former regime’s stocks to the “opposition” in Syria. As in Libya, the insurgents are known to include al Qaeda and other Shariah-supremacist groups, including none other than Abdelhakim Belhadj. Fox News has chronicled how the Al Entisar, a Libyan-flagged vessel carrying 400 tons of cargo, docked on Sept. 6 in the Turkish port of Iskenderun. It reportedly supplied both humanitarian assistance and arms — including deadly SA-7 man-portable surface-to-air missiles — apparently destined for Islamists, again including al Qaeda elements, in Syria. What cries out for further investigation — and debate in the remaining days of this presidential election — is whether this shipment was part of a larger covert Obama effort to transfer weapons to our enemies that could make the Iran-Contra scandal, to say nothing of Operation Fast and Furious, pale by comparison.</Msg><Username>spartacus778899</Username><Timestamp>1356053213269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 20:26:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356053951728-112</Id><Topic><Title>Why I'm for the Brady Bill</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356047652186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:54:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Before banning our guns, are you in favor of recovering the ones your BATF sent to Mexico ?</Msg><Username>spartacus778899</Username><Timestamp>1356053951728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 20:39:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356054735546-113</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing and Potato Heads</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1356046626643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:37:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without the potatoes, Tischler said Boeing would have to employ dozens of people to sit in a grounded plane for hours while Wi-Fi signals are measured and adjusted. So why not just have the BA managers do the testing ! after all sitting around for hours, doing nothing but playing with wi fi and not moving fits their everyday job description</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1356054735546</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 20:52:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356056269557-114</Id><Title>Republicans Taking America Over Fiscal Cliff</Title><Msg>There is no question in my mind that the Republicans intend to take America over the fiscal cliff. They will not compromise with the President. They are thinking to hell with the US and world economy. Mind you it is not fact, the following opinions as reasons why why the Republicans are considering throwing America over the cliff, namely: 1. They care more for the wealthy than the middle class. 2. Their priority to cut the 16 trillion dollar deficit outweighs concern the nation will head into a depression. The wealthy will be able to ride it out. 3. It is vendetta time for the Republicans to get even with Obama for getting re-elected. 4. Boehner wants to see Obama have a failed administration. 5. Boehner, Ryan and others hate President Obama. 6. I am going to throw in the race card. Some Republicans can't stand a successful black President.</Msg><Username>mbfield50</Username><Timestamp>1356056269557</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 21:17:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356057193650-115</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Over my dead body! I have sworn to protect and defend the Constitution of the United States and its implementation. The way to make change is by way of the ballot.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1356057193650</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 21:33:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356057541663-116</Id><Topic><Title>God Bless Barack Obama...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356052101413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 20:08:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're actually talking about the God Allah,right? I don't believe Obama believes in the Christian Judeo version of God. Anyone have any idea where the President keeps his Koran? Somewhere in the dark recesses of the White House your President keeps one. Maybe it's in Michelle's chester drawers along with her panties.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1356057541663</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 21:39:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356057545133-117</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Taking America Over Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>mbfield50</Username><Timestamp>1356056269557</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 21:17:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The primary job for the republicans is to keep taxes low for the wealthy. Plain and simple. Everything else is a distant, next galaxy distant, second.</Msg><Username>flyininmytaxi</Username><Timestamp>1356057545133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 21:39:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356058112729-118</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Taking America Over Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>mbfield50</Username><Timestamp>1356056269557</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 21:17:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I made a mistake. I didn't want to use the nick mbfield50.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1356058112729</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 21:48:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356058424458-119</Id><Topic><Title>God Bless Barack Obama...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356052101413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 20:08:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank God for voter fraud in America otherwise we'd be talking about what President Obama is going to do with his life after the inauguration of the new president in 2013.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1356058424458</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 21:53:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356058901644-120</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Taking America Over Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>mbfield50</Username><Timestamp>1356056269557</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 21:17:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is Obama that is the President. He is the one who was pushing to do the "cliff" thing all along. This is what he wants, don't fool yourself otherwise. His version of "the buck stops with me" is "the buck stops with my predecessor". Please do not cite the monumental "51%" - the so-called "landslide" - that Obama got of the popular vote. The Republicans took 52% of Congress (Senate + House). That would mean that the Republicans had a "super-landslide". When Obama decides to treat the people's representatives as other than doormats, then something will happen - or he can, and probably will, simply issue an executive order, not unlike his Pharaoesque "Brother" Morsi of Egypt. In the mean time, pay up!</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1356058901644</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 22:01:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356059009874-121</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparatcus, It is called "Taqiyya". BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1356059009874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 22:03:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356062277758-122</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have a ballot box problem. One Party insists on maintaining the right to cheat in our elections and an Attorney General who refuses to bring abusers to justice. . Politicians are bought by lobbyists and special interests. All congressmen swear to protect and defend the constitution then carry on doing neither. Most of what congress does is unconstitutional but supreme court that is not elected refuses to hold them accountable. Even if elections were fair and mob rule prevails that lets 51% of the population plunder the other 49% democracy loses its value. If politicians obeyed the constitution we would have the problems we have but they don't, If the electorate only voted for politicians who obeyed the constitution we would have the problems we have but they don't.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356062277758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 22:57:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356062472927-123</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama also did that. Who enforces it on him?? Dems got 156%of the vote in some counties.....who fixes that???</Msg><Username>sparrowgt</Username><Timestamp>1356062472927</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 23:01:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356062636636-124</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't Democrats Produce a Budget for a Vote?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356048165438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:02:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By law Oboma must produce a buget eveery year. So far he has let 3 yr. go by w/o a budget. Who enforces that??</Msg><Username>sparrowgt</Username><Timestamp>1356062636636</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 23:03:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356062970070-125</Id><Topic><Title>Why Every REAL AMERICAN Should Own Multiple Firearms</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356035383693</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:29:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there comes a time when people get frustrated w/ corruption &amp; begin to act on their own. People try to do whats "right" then they give up . Self survival trumps what's 'right'.</Msg><Username>sparrowgt</Username><Timestamp>1356062970070</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 23:09:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356063746209-126</Id><Title>Constitutional Corruption</Title><Msg>Let's ponder these questions: why did Congress amend the Constitution in 1916 giving it the power to collect taxes on any source? Why was the 17th Amendment enacted in 1913 to select Senators by popular vote rather than, as originally designed, selected by state legislatures? Finally, why did Congress pass the 18th Amendment in 1919 outlawing alcohol sales? To really get into these questions and gain an appreciation for today's rogue Congress and Supreme Court, let's not get bogged down on the merits of these amendments. Let's simply look at the Constitution's restrictions. In Article I, Section 8, of the Constitution the Framers enumerated 18 functions of the federal government. Nowhere among those functions was Congress given the power to prohibit alcohol sales. Article I, Section 2 of the Constitution expressly states "direct taxes shall be apportioned among the several states" and forbids direct taxes on individuals. Then there's Article I, Section 3, that requires state legislatures to appoint Senators. During earlier periods, Congress and the Supreme Court had far greater respect for the Constitution. They understood that if the federal government was to have a power not delegated, or expressly forbidden, by the Constitution they had to use the provisions of Article V to gain that power by amendment. They knew, for example, Congress had not delegated power to prohibit alcohol sales. They couldn't find that power by manipulating the "commerce clause" or going penumbra hunting. Today, it's an entirely different story. Congress, the White House and the Supreme Court have abiding contempt for the Constitution and we Americans are left with a constitutional carcass. Take just a tiny comparison of today with yesteryear. Yesteryear there were alcohol prohibitionists; today we have tobacco prohibitionists. No matter what we think about the alcohol prohibitionists, we can have a bit of admiration for them because they used the constitutional route to get their agenda across. Tobacco prohibitionists employ constitutional stealth: taxes, majority votes and the totalitarian tactics of the EPA, and FDA. In 1787, the Constitution would have never been ratified without both the Ninth and Tenth Amendments. "The enumeration in the Constitution, of certain rights, shall not be construed to deny or disparage others retained by the people.", is the Ninth Amendment and, "Powers not delegated to the United States by the Constitution, nor prohibited by it to the states, are reserved to the states respectively, or the people.", is the Tenth. The Framers justifiably feared concentration, of power in Washington. Today, the Ninth and Tenth Amendments have been completely trashed and Congress is well on the way to finally trashing the Second and Fifth Amendments. When and how we developed today's constitutional contempt is debatable. The federally-caused Great Depression played a role but the education establishment has played a greater role through the dumbing down of Americans. The resulting ignorance has allowed us to let charlatans and quacks in the legal profession tell us what the Constitution means. The Constitution was not written for intellectual elites; it was understandable to a nation of mostly farmers at the time it was written. So where do we go and what do we do? Each of us is duty-bound to read and understand our Constitution. If we do that we'll realize Washington has little or no moral authority. Its authority rests mostly on intimidation and force of arms. And like the Founders, we should adopt the attitude that "There is one thing in the world more wicked than the desire to command, and that is the will to obey." Walter E. Williams</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356063746209</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 23:22:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356063912107-127</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you see where in Ohio and Pensylvania Obama got 99 percent of the vote in huge numbers of counties ? It doesnt matter......there was no real Democracy in this country for 20 years.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356063912107</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 23:25:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356064196953-128</Id><Title>Swearing to uphold and defend the U.S. Constitution</Title><Msg>Congressmen, presidents and Supreme Court justices take an oath of office swearing to uphold and defend the U.S. Constitution. As if the Constitution itself isn't clear about what they must do, in Federalist Paper No. 45, James Madison, the acknowledged father of the Constitution described the document thusly: "The powers delegated by the proposed Constitution to the federal government are few and defined. Those which are to remain in the State governments are numerous and indefinite. The former will be exercised principally on external objects, as war, peace, negotiation, and foreign commerce. . . . The powers reserved to the several States will extend to all the objects which in the ordinary course of affairs, concern the lives and liberties, and properties of the people, and the internal order, improvement and prosperity of the State." Both Madison's statement and the Constitution leave no doubt about the "few and defined" powers delegated to the federal government and the "numerous and indefinite" powers retained by the people and the states. I'd like to ask our 535 congressmen, our president and our nine Supreme Court justices which word or phrase in Madison's statement they find beyond comprehension, and which phrase in Article I, Section 8 of the Constitution, that outlines what Congress is permitted to do, they find beyond comprehension. While congressmen, presidents and Supreme Court justices don't have much understanding, they aren't stupid, which isn't to say they're not ignorant about the Constitution and other matters. Let's explore the most charitable explanation for their day-to-day violations of both the letter and the spirit of our Constitution, namely that they're ignorant. But, I seriously doubt the suitability of ignorance as an explanation. Why? If ignorance were the explanation, I'd be optimistic. I'd simply send the president, congressmen and Supreme Court justices James Madison's Federalist Paper No. 45, explaining the Constitution. After that they'd mend their ways and eliminate most federal programs, state mandates and other gross constitutional violations. You say, "Williams, if you think they'd do that, you've got to be crazy!" You're right; I would be crazy. The only other explanation for what presidents, congressmen and justices do is that they have contempt for the Constitution. But that's only a tiny part of the sad story. Imagine if James Madison or Thomas Jefferson were campaigning for the presidency in 2000. What would you think about their chances? They'd clearly lose if they expressed the constitutional values and respect they had when the document was written. They'd clearly be denounced by most Americans and possibly risk assassination. Therefore, before we rush to lay the complete blame for constitutional contempt at the feet of politicians and judges, we might want to look at ourselves - we the American people. That is, politicians are doing what we elect them to office to do and if our Constitution stays in the way, it's the Constitution that must yield. The Constitution stands in the way of government programs such as: business bailouts, food stamps, Social Security, Medicare, Title I education programs and thousands of other federal acts. You might ask, "Why should we pay any attention to a two hundred year document?" I'd say to escape Thomas Jefferson's prediction that, "The natural progress of things is for government to gain ground and for liberty to yield." After all if we ignore the constitutional protections found in Article I, Section 8 why not ignore other constitutional protections and make them just as meaningless? If we continue our current path, future generations will curse us for squandering unprecedented liberty. Walter E. Williams</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356064196953</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 23:29:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356064402185-129</Id><Topic><Title>Constitutional Corruption</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356063746209</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 23:22:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I could also bring up the "Federal Reserve Act" of 1913...As being the real end of the Republic.... In addition you cannot have an EMPIRE and a REPUBLIC...this idea goes back to the time of Plato...and the founding Fathers warned us about trusting Private central bankers to control the issue of currency instead of Congress (as mandated by the constituion) ...we also see the military industrial security complex controlling our lives....the Global Elite WANT limited war because they can control the slaves....WE are the slaves.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356064402185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 23:33:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356064670845-130</Id><Title>Is It Them Or Us?</Title><Msg>I'm not one to defend politicians even though only few exhibit honesty, statesmanship and respect for our Constitution. On the other hand, we all have complaints about what Congress does. In my more cynical moments, I feel that Americans deserve what we're getting, including the diminution of our liberties. Let's look at it. What kind of things make us feel good about our particular congressman? Just listen to political advertisements. Among the criteria we use to judge whether our congressman is doing a good job are: Does he support federal expenditures for more teachers? Has he supported punitive taxes on cigarette smokers? For mid-westerners, has he supported agricultural subsidies? For the elderly, has he supported Social Security and Medicare payment increases? Nowhere in the U.S. Constitution is there a speck of authority for congress to make expenditures for those activities. Moreover, making those expenditures come at the expense of personal liberty. In other words, Congress has no resources of its very own. The only way they can give a farmer or a senior citizen one dollar is to first, through intimidation, threats and coercion, confiscate it from some other American. The very last criteria we use to judge whether our congressman is doing a good job is whether he's respectful of the U.S. Constitution and seeks to protect our liberties. The supreme tragedy is that a congressman who lived up to his oath of office by respecting the Constitution would be viewed with contempt by most Americans. Imagine Williams was your senator. During my re-election campaign, I tell my constituents that I voted against congressional measures that would take their money to give to someone else. I voted against measures that encroached on state sovereignty. I voted against the education bill because not even the word education appears in the Constitution. Needless to say, I'd go down in blazing defeat, possibly tarred and feathered as well. Most constituents would view my respect for the Constitution with contempt. Even those who had a modicum of constitutional respect would confront me with a practical issue saying, "Williams, if you don't fight for our share of aid to higher education, agricultural handouts and federally-financed teachers, it doesn't mean we'll pay lower federal taxes. All it means is that some other state will get the money instead. You're expecting us to commit hari-kari." What could I say in response? They'd be absolutely right. The reason is due to a phenomenon known as "the tragedy of the commons." Once legalized theft or constitutional disrespect begins, it's in everybody's private interest, at least economic interests, to participate. The person or politician who abstains becomes a loser. Even more ominous about the process is the tendency for legalized theft to beget more legalized theft and more constitutional disrespect to beget more constitutional disrespect. "Williams," you say, "what can we do?" The first step is that we must stop the charade of blaming politicians. Politicians do precisely what we elect them to office to do: promote programs that allows one American to live at the expense of his fellow American. We must demand constitutional accountability from our politicians by demanding they give us specific constitutional authority for what they do and don't let them get away with that "welfare" and "commerce" clause nonsense. I'm not optimistic, Americans will do that. Therefore, the most likely scenario is for us to see our liberties diminish and Washington despotism grow. If we truly cared about our children and future generations. Instead of demagoging about them, we'd worry more about saving liberty than saving Social Security. Walter E. Williams</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356064670845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 23:37:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356064767359-131</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Taqiyya = Islamic Duplicity. Not sure if it is applicable here Bob. I have not been a huge proponent of "Muslims are going to cut off our heads with a rusty blade in our sleep" guys...I think the threat has been overblown.....and we have paid for it with our freedoms....but AlQaeda has been a tool of the CIA ever since Bin Ladin was overthrowing the Soviets in Afganistan.....and the Bushs have been dealing with them for years. This is the important thing you have to understand Bob....If Obama is giving guns to AlQaeda the the WHOLE NARRATIVE ABOUT THE THREAT OF TERRORISM collapses....and the Global elite know it. Thats why they have to have a NEW THREAT....and the new threat is Caucasion Billy Bob Rednecks with guns and returing veterans etc....You see it right now with the NEW talking points about demonizing guns ...the cult members have their marching orders.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356064767359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 23:39:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356065002276-132</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The majority, oppressing an individual, is guilty of a crime, abuses its strength, and by acting on the law of the strongest breaks up the foundations of society." -- Thomas Jefferson</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356065002276</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 23:43:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356065094711-133</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming is a Hoax - Russia's Coldest winter in 70 years</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356036807826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"-50 degrees Celsius is equal to - 50 degrees Fahrenheit." Still awaiting Mir's efforts to dig out of that one.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1356065094711</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 23:44:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356065498570-134</Id><Title>An ignorant people ignores the words of the wise</Title><Msg>Life, faculties, production—in other words, individuality, liberty, property—this is man. And in spite of the cunning of artful political leaders, these three gifts from God precede all human legislation, and are superior to it. Life, liberty, and property do not exist because men have made laws. On the contrary, it was the fact that life, liberty, and property existed beforehand that caused men to make laws in the first place. When under the pretext of fraternity, the legal code imposes mutual sacrifices on the citizens, human nature is not thereby abrogated. Everyone will then direct his efforts toward contributing little to, and taking much from, the common fund of sacrifices. Now, is it the most unfortunate who gains from this struggle? Certainly not, but rather the most influential and calculating. Government is the great fiction through which everybody endeavors to live at the expense of everybody else. People are beginning to realize that the apparatus of government is costly. But what they do not know is that the burden falls inevitably on them. Law cannot organize labor and industry without organizing injustice. The plans differ; the planners are all alike... Now, legal plunder can be committed in an infinite number of ways. Thus we have an infinite number of plans for organizing it: tariffs, protection, benefits, subsidies, encouragements, progressive taxation, public schools, guaranteed jobs, guaranteed profits, minimum wages, a right to relief, a right to the tools of labor, free credit, and so on, and so on. All these plans as a whole—with their common aim of legal plunder—constitute socialism. Claude Frédéric Bastiat Words as true today as they were 160 years ago.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356065498570</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 23:51:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>