<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346040686293-1</Id><Topic><Title>new message board</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346021355362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:49:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are interested in finance &amp; stocks, the Morningstar board is very good, Their Closed End Fund (CEF) board has some seriously well informed people on it - no politics.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1346040686293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:11:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346068679000-2</Id><Topic><Title>God Bless Charlie Crist</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346062420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 06:13:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brave and wise man. I thank him.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346068679000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 07:57:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346069040000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 297, Romney 212</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1345993880000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:11:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell us why you think Romney will change anything. Has he said he would remove the troops from Afghanistan?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346069040000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:04:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346071089626-4</Id><Topic><Title>new message board</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346021355362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:49:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Much like the faces of Mitt Romney, there appear to be two different BA Finance Message Boards operational at the same time.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1346071089626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:38:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346071334000-5</Id><Title>The Two BA Message Boards</Title><Msg>There is this board which has always been around, and there is the new experimental board which contains completely different massages?</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1346071334000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346075498000-6</Id><Topic><Title>God Bless Charlie Crist</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346062420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 06:13:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is, if the republicans fail in suppressing the votes they don't like. I find it amazing how republicans claim rampant voter fraud exists but can't show any Attorney General indictments or convictions of such a prolific crime.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346075498000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:51:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346075615000-7</Id><Title>Bring Back Herman, Michelle and Rick</Title><Msg>The repubs ought to showcase these worthies at their convocation. The public can use a little light comedy.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1346075615000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346075857510-8</Id><Title>Bring back the comedians</Title><Msg>Herman, Michelle and Rick used to bring on gales of laughter during the repub debates. C'mon repubs , lighten up and bring back the clown car circus for your convocation.,</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1346075857510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:57:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346076387000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Rich Daddy Dudes</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1345984991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:43:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh! and did I mention that Paul Ryan also comes from rich daddy stock. And did I mention that he has identical beliefs to Todd Akin the co-sponsor of his "Forcible Rape" bill in congress.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1346076387000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346078621000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Rich Daddy Dudes</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1345984991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:43:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They want to legalize forcible rape? Man, that is disgusting</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346078621000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:43:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346078793651-11</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing 777X</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1346000152451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:55:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>on what page in the 10Q will I find your 34B of debt?</Msg><Username>makboe</Username><Timestamp>1346078793651</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:46:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346080021000-12</Id><Title>All the bad people left</Title><Msg>I love this new BA board.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346080021000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:07:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346082125944-13</Id><Title>This really is a different board than the old one</Title><Msg>anyone know how this works?</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346082125944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346082204761-14</Id><Title>I noticed most of the Right Wing Wackos</Title><Msg>Can't figure out how the board works so they left.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346082204761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:43:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346083190464-15</Id><Topic><Title>I noticed most of the Right Wing Wackos</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346082204761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:43:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>any group which would plan a convention during August in florida much be questioned. They would have made a better choice to meet in Harlem. In GOP they are all daft and have lost their way!! Kamakure</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1346083190464</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346084038931-16</Id><Topic><Title>I noticed most of the Right Wing Wackos</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346082204761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:43:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You never were trust worthy.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346084038931</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:13:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346084774845-17</Id><Title>how are those orders working for you now- Apple up !</Title><Msg>Attention Boeing bashers,pumpers and spammers as I have told you for several years, you need to forget pumping BA stock, it is still flat and a dead cat bounce stock. For more than the past 15 years I have owned apple and it has beat BA stock all the way. No difference short term, last week Boeing was down 3.42% last monday open at $73.61 and last friday it closed at $71.09 while apple went from 650 to 664 a gain of 2%. Today it is up another over 2%. Next month apple will bring out 2 new products on time and on budget, and the stock will go up. So last week I told you apple had gained over 60% this year and now I can report apple is up over 64% while BA boeing is still a 0.00% gainer for the year . So as usual all you BA pumpers are losers for your opinion on BA the only person making any money on Boeing is the CEO, McNearney well, he got more than you shareholders paid in taxes for all of Boeings business last year. When the CEO pays himself first then the shareholders then you need to stay out of that stock. This means the CEO is not working for the shareholders, that is a given in investing. The CEO of Apple when alive, Steve Jobs took 1 dollar for his job as pay per year, the rest he made only if the stock price went up, so the shareholder had to make money in order for Steve to make any money. Attention all Boeing shareholders you make more in dividends now with apple too, so another Hint, last year, the past 15 years or now or next year when you drop your faulty opinion on Boeing being a stock to own and go with apple then you too can become rich.</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1346084774845</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346086704482-18</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing 777X</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1346000152451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:55:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10Q is thgat you IQ? makboe(ing) as a Boeing pumper are you too dumb to be here ? How is that apple stock price today and for the past over 15 years doing for me. My credibility is on my stock picks not your #$%$ lack of reality 10-IQ question on the real costs of the 787. But since you want to play or are dumb-Boeing's business model for the 787 relies heavily on outsourcing, so the costs are baked into the big sections that arrive from suppliers around the globe. To reduce costs, Boeing will have to renegotiate pricing contracts. As a Boeing pumper and spammer you apparently are not at all familiar with a financial statement, you should get at least a MBA from Gonzaga or any credible school. “The important thing to remember a financial statement, or any income statement, , is that it represents a period of time. Or a balance sheet , which represents a single moment in time. Finally any financial statement by Boeing only covers GAAP principals and then only lists what Boeing want to report, Since the costs on the 787 are mainly from contractors , the total costs will not be listed on the Boeing company financial reports, they do not have to list them , that, like you apparently think does not mean they do not have to be paid. Finally Boeing can estimate its costs and be wrong to the low side. So look all you want in the wrong places, that does not change the 4 years late and very unhappy customers who get a huge discount for large 787 orders, and then a discount for late delivery and then get a discount for a 787 plane reworked so the profit margin is not less than 6% it is more like minus 10% for each 787 plane upon delivery . If you knew how to invest or read a balance sheet you would be with Apple stock up over 2% today and not BA Boeing said it will need to deliver 1,100 Dreamliners on time and clean, at best to break even on the cost of building them. The projection doesn't imply that the troubled jet program, plagued by earlier disastrous setbacks, will recover heavy upfront development costs and make money overall. Analysts believe that may never happen. Because suppliers were so heavily hit by the program's delays, Boeing had to raise the prices it paid them for the early units that cost so much to build. "At some point in the future, that contractual price is something Boeing hopes to negotiate lower," Copeland said. With so much in the hands of suppliers, he said, the pace of overall cost reduction is harder to predict from outside. That will likely take at least an additional 700 deliveries beyond the initial 1,100 jets. Even then, Boeing still won't be in the clear. Long before 2021, it will have spent billions more to develop at least two further variants of the jet, the 787-9 and 787-10. Yet Wall Street analysts — taking the view of an investor considering whether to buy Boeing shares today — ignore that financial mess in the 7 rearview mirror and look strictly ahead. From the 787's program's inception, "it's probably not a positive investment return," said Barclay's. "</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1346086704482</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:58:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346087383000-19</Id><Topic><Title>All the bad people left</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346080021000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:07:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_T/threadview?m=tm&amp;bn=51268&amp;tid=584834&amp;mid=584834&amp;tof=16&amp;frt=1</Msg><Username>vaclav_havel_fan</Username><Timestamp>1346087383000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:09:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346088094415-20</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing update</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1345951069615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 23:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so yesterday I said ka ching for me on apple and today apple is up over 2%, Boeing despite all the boeing pumper,spammer and basher with all the airplane orders which mean nothing as the 787 is over 34 billion in total cost debt and the 747 which was over 2 billion in debts, the 767 tanker which is fixed cost ( will not make any money) and the spares will be profit only for the contractors, and the 737max will be a loser due to cost over runs and the 777x will be delayed and the competition (airbus) will take away that customer base like they did when McNerarny said the customer will wait for the 737 to be developed, that cost Boeing shareholders 1000 neo orders and two customers who went from 737 to neos. this Boeing Company is a loser, go with apple , better dividends too, you Boeing pumpers should be gone in a perfect market all your balony comments about airplane orders would come with a warning that this statment is without considering the cost over run on the 787, the 747, the 767 tanker the 737 max cost over runs mean zero stock appreciaton and tha tis the trught Boeing has made 0.00% for the year to date while apple has gained 64% year to date stock price appreciation and next month will deliver two new products on time and on budget and the apple stock price will be over 700 dollars and still no split so unlike msft it will continue to be a real value .</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1346088094415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:21:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346088312000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Just Stepped In It</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1345834538000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 14:55:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What principles?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1346088312000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346088589000-22</Id><Topic><Title>COPS Will Have Fun with the 99%ers at the R.N.C.</Title><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1345916950000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:49:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone focused on the Republican National Convention?? Doesn't seem like the 99%ers "March on the R.N.C." is very well followed(by the Mainstream anyway). http://www.google.com/search?aq=f&amp;hl=en&amp;gl=us&amp;tbm=nws&amp;btnmeta_news_search=1&amp;q=march+on+the+rnc</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346088589000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:29:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346088989000-23</Id><Title>Is the WHOLE STREET FOR ITSELF?</Title><Msg>OF COURSE. All the Financial BANKS(the Brokerages-THE STREET), &amp; of course the Commercial BANKS that now OWN THEM ALL, are for themselves at their "customers"(FOOLS)expense. Unless of course you've got at least $200 or $300 million, minimum.</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346088989000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:36:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346089318000-24</Id><Title>Goldman Thread Still a Bit Active</Title><Msg>Lots of I srael-Firster j ews still after your money over there. http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_T/forumview?bn=8089 p.s. That's where tranny(transatlantic2011- that nazi i sraeli)came from, overhere to the Boeing thread.</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346089318000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:41:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346089941719-25</Id><Title>Romney; ‘Nobody likes me’</Title><Msg>It's a notable choice even as Romney bluntly acknowledges in both the USA Today interview and in a separate interview with Politico that some voters just don't like him. He accuses President Barack Obama and his allies of "personal vilification and demonization"—and admits their attacks have been effective. "There are plenty of weaknesses that I have, and I acknowledge that," Romney tells USA Today. "But the attacks that have come have been so misguided, have been so far off target, have been so dishonest, that they surprised me. I thought they might go after me on things that were accurate that I've done wrong, instead of absurd things." ...... But while Romney assailed the Obama campaign for its attacks, the presumptive Republican nominee has grown more aggressive on the trail in recent weeks. Two weeks ago, he slammed Obama for running a campaign based on "division and anger and hate." He's accused Obama of trying to undo historic welfare reforms requiring recipients to work and of using Medicare funds to pay for so-called "Obamacare"—two lines of attack that have been disputed by independent fact-checkers. On Friday, Romney made a birth certificate joke during a rally in Michigan that was widely interpreted as a dig at conspiracy theories that Obama wasn't born in the United States—though Romney later insisted it wasn't a joke about Obama.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346089941719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346090732000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Goldman Thread Still a Bit Active</Title><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346089318000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:41:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.ynetnews.com/articles/0,7340,L-4273028,00.html rabbi PRAYS for DESTRUCTION of Iran. These I sraeli j ews are guilty of what they accuse the moslems of. The U.S.'s support of this j ewish RELIGIOUS STATE is incredibily stupid. Just as stupid as supporting a moslem theocracy would be. Why are We in the Middle East with all these WARS FOR I SRAEL?? The Middle East Arab OIL goes mainly to the Orient &amp; Europe. They are the ones that need to "support" the region- not Us.</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346090732000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:05:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346091056993-27</Id><Topic><Title>Romney; ‘Nobody likes me’</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346089941719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what are ye hiding willard, show us the tax data. Perchance then we will love ye! Kamakure</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1346091056993</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:10:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346091111000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Goldman Thread Still a Bit Active</Title><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346089318000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:41:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>re&gt;Dumbocrats are grow more fascist by the day&lt; You got that right but fail to mention the Dems CANNOT KEEP UP BEING AS FASCIST AS THE REPUBS! Our system of Corporate Capitalism is TRULY FASCIST &amp; getting more obviously so all the time.</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346091111000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:11:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346091316000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Rich Daddy Dudes</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1345984991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:43:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryan is the hinge on the lid of the Pandora's box of Repub plans to craft a highly restrictive and easily manipulated society. Todd Akin gave just a hint of what the GOP has in store for Americans.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346091316000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:15:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346091670338-30</Id><Title>update, BA supporter ,</Title><Msg>By black_mariah777.2 hours 49 minutes ago, you said BA has already made a gain today? for Monday now an update - update apple now is a 676 dollar stockand Boeing is still a $71 dollar stoc that is a gain of 54 dollars in a very short time, get it now ! IF you must be a Boeing supporter, at least take your blinders off, Boeing was a 75 dollar stock a few days ago and is a 71 dollar stock today. A YTD view on BA Boeing - on the first trade day of 2012 Boeing was a $72.92 stock, now a $71.09 dollar stock down 2.51% for the YTD Compare this to apple AAPL for the start of the year aapl was a 409 dollar stock , today it is a 622 dollar stock and has gained more in the last 20 days than Boeing has historically been worth, so you just missed a 100 dollar gain. The highest adjusted close stock price for Boeing was October 2,2007 at $92.88 so while you look at the wrong statistics black-mariah777, apple shareholders have made over 61% gain since january of this year on apple while you made nothing long or short term on . or try HD or aapl , both stocks have beat BA allt he way from a 5 day to a month to 3 months to 1-2-05 and max use the Yahoo finance comparison stock chart , any Boeing shareholder is a loser compared to apple or HD. get it now ! update apple now is a 676 dollar stockand Boeing is still a $71 dollar stock</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1346091670338</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346091755000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Plays The Race Card</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346090208000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:56:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Repub party's Southern strategy for the past 40+ years has been all about pitting the angry and disaffected white lower class against people of color.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346091755000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:22:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346091862545-32</Id><Topic><Title>Romney; ‘Nobody likes me’</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346089941719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did you feel the need to change from the factual "some voters don't like me..." to the lying "Nobody like me"... You are nothing, but a Lying Liberal. Shame on you!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346091862545</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:24:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346092396000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Plays The Race Card</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346090208000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:56:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What We need is more diversity. We truely need a National Association for the Advancement of UNcolored People, NAAUP. Then We could have a bunch of fat(Carl Rove for one comes to mind)UNcoloreds running that organization. Lets hear it for Uncolored Power! p.s. Is Obama a racist every time he showes his face in the Black House?</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346092396000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:33:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346092593600-34</Id><Topic><Title>I noticed most of the Right Wing Wackos</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346082204761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:43:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, booger boy, you are the true stupid wacko... stop eating your boogers?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346092593600</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346092607415-35</Id><Topic><Title>Romney; ‘Nobody likes me’</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346089941719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryan and Rmoney's policies of more tax cuts for their wealthy families and friends while cutting "entitlements" for the rest of us is a policy of 'only some people are expected to make sacrifices'. Sacrifices, like accountability in their minds, are for suckers, losers and average, hardworking Americans.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346092607415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:36:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346092985000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Plays The Race Card</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346090208000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:56:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>re&gt;p.s. Is Obama a racist every time he showes his face in the Black House?&lt; LOL, my brother says he thinks it's The OutHouse!</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346092985000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:43:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346092985736-37</Id><Topic><Title>Romney; ‘Nobody likes me’</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346089941719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imshocked, No wonder you don't like Romney... you would lose you "entitlements"... your food stamps, welfare.. you are a maggot on Society. Get off your xxx and go to work. Pathetic!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346092985736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:43:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346093227000-38</Id><Title>Where'd all the Boeing NewsHawks GO</Title><Msg>http://companies.einnews.com/news/boeing-news</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346093227000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:47:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346093506500-39</Id><Title>Rmoney's To Do List</Title><Msg>Rmneys to do list includes Cheat the country out of tax revenue. Cheat the waitress out of tips. LIE then change the LIE. Get hair cut. Deduct hair cut. Whine about deficits.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346093506500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346094110000-40</Id><Title>US arms sales hit record</Title><Msg>US arms sales hit record high of $66.3bn in 2011 The United States’ weapons sales tripled in 2011, reaching to a record high of USD 66.3 billion, with Persian Gulf Arab countries as the main customers, a new Congressional report said. A new report from the Congressional Research Service said that the country’s weapons sales in 2011 was an “extraordinary increase” over the USD 21.4 billion in deals in 2010. The report also said that the figure was the largest single-year sales total in the history of US arms sales. The former high record was in 2009, when the country’s arms exports reached to USD 31bn. Saudi Arabia was the largest customer of the US arms, as it bought USD 33.4bn worth of weapons, including 84 advanced F-15 fighters, ammunition, missiles and logistics support. The Kingdom’s arms deal with the US also included dozens of Apache and Black Hawk helicopters and upgrades of 70 of the F-15 fighters in the current fleet. The United Arab Emirates spent USD 3.49 billion to purchase a Terminal High Altitude Area Defense, which is an advanced anti-missile shield containing radars. The Arab nation also bought 16 Chinook helicopters for USD 939 million. Oman also spent USD 1.4bn last year to buy 18 F-16 fighters. Other significant customers for the US arms were India with a USD 4.1bn deal for 10 C-17 transport planes and Taiwan with USD 2bn for Patriot antimissile batteries, that has angered Chinese officials. http://www.presstv.ir/detail/2012/08/27/258350/us-arms-sales-hit-record-high-of-663bn/ McDonnell F-15s BRING HOME THE BACON for Boeing</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346094110000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:01:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346094213000-41</Id><Topic><Title>US arms sales hit record</Title><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346094110000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:01:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>p.s. The Saudis also want to buy NUKE MISSILES from China too</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346094213000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:03:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346094333471-42</Id><Topic><Title>Romney; ‘Nobody likes me’</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346089941719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mr imaccom - i titled the subject to what I want... is that a Lie?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346094333471</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:05:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346094562395-43</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney's To Do List</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346093506500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and Lose the Election..!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346094562395</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:09:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346095884746-44</Id><Topic><Title>Romney; ‘Nobody likes me’</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346089941719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your post was not the truth, little stickman... and, yes, it is a lie and we all know it, eh? Pathetic!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346095884746</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:31:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346096299215-45</Id><Title>Obama's Hopelessness and Hate not Selling</Title><Msg>Obama continues to sink in the Polls... now losing in Ohio and Florida... It's the Economy, Stupid! Unemployment above 8% for three (3) plus years.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346096299215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346097219130-46</Id><Title>Obama is a Fake!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Obama has millions of fake Twitter followers Comments By David Jackson, USA TODAY Updated 3d 4h ago CAPTIONAP photos President Obama's Twitter account has 18.8 million followers -- but more than half of them really don't exist, according to reports. A new Web tool has determined that 70% of Obama's crowd includes "fake followers," The New York Times reports in a story about how Twitter followers can be purchased. "The practice has become so widespread that StatusPeople, a social media management company in London, released a Web tool last month called the Fake Follower Check that it says can ascertain how many fake followers you and your friends have," the Times reports. "Fake accounts tend to follow a lot of people but have few followers," said Rob Waller, a founder of StatusPeople. "We then combine that with a few other metrics to confirm the account is fake." Notes the Times: If accurate, the number of fake followers out there is surprising. According to the StatusPeople tool, 71 percent of Lady Gaga's nearly 29 million followers are "fake" or "inactive." So are 70 percent of President Obama's nearly 19 million followers. Republican opponent Mitt Romney has far fewer Twitter followers -- not quite 900,000 -- but it's a good bet that some of them are fake as well. Both campaigns have denied buying Twitter followers</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346097219130</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:53:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346097452196-47</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Hopelessness and Hate not Selling</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346096299215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:38:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congress needs to pass a budget and maybe something to spur job growth instead they spend all their time on vacation and naming post offices or trying to dismantle healthcare for women.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346097452196</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:57:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346098412569-48</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Hopelessness and Hate not Selling</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346096299215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:38:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rockstar, you are unintelligible Unemployment over 8% for more than three Years.... Obama will get crushed in November!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346098412569</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346101918089-49</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Hopelessness and Hate not Selling</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346096299215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:38:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>congress should be crushed they have done nothing they said they would if voted into office, Obama is the President he does not make laws or pass budgets CONGRESS DOES Obama wins the electoral vote and that is the only one that matters. everything else is just something to put before or after a commercial for your favorite condom company</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1346101918089</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346104265916-50</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid's Lie about Romney paying Zero Taxes...</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1345414393000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 18:13:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HOW did the vulture get 100 million into his IRA? No 6000 limit for him ? And converting ordinary income into cap gains should put him in jail ..If there was a God</Msg><Username>eddiew37</Username><Timestamp>1346104265916</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346105026354-51</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid's Lie about Romney paying Zero Taxes...</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1345414393000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 18:13:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, dummy, it is called earnings/CapGains.... but Liberals like you are too dumb to understand basic Economics, eh? Pathetic ignorant Liberal!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346105026354</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:03:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346105860789-52</Id><Topic><Title>Romney; ‘Nobody likes me’</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346089941719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romey's a putz.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1346105860789</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:17:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346106478680-53</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Hopelessness and Hate not Selling</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346096299215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:38:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Charlie Crist will deliver Florida and Ohio is easily Democratic this November.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1346106478680</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:27:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346107190992-54</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Hopelessness and Hate not Selling</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346096299215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:38:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess that depends on the poll. Watching CNN and Obama is winning in both states</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346107190992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:39:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346109002455-55</Id><Topic><Title>I noticed most of the Right Wing Wackos</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346082204761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:43:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What! Are you in third grade, or something? Typical neocon POS.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1346109002455</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:10:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346110436093-56</Id><Topic><Title>I noticed most of the Right Wing Wackos</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346082204761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:43:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In typical Dim fashion, Simple minded Booger can't figure out how something works so he throws it over the fence in a feeble attempt top blame a Pub. Not unlike he and Diks WON trying to figure out Economic 101!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1346110436093</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346110690769-57</Id><Topic><Title>I noticed most of the Right Wing Wackos</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346082204761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:43:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow...not only are URL links no longer allowed on this Commie Yahoo baord, but I see now that included quotes are no longer allow either. Welcome to the WONS 2016 folks! For futher proof of Boogers ingnorance, scroll down a few posts to the one is he asking how this new one asks!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1346110690769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:38:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346115323776-58</Id><Title>Do You Know Me?</Title><Msg>I have been around on this BA board near its inception, in one nick or form or the other. I have been transformed into phantomfield. I carry the American Express Card. Don't leave home without it.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1346115323776</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346115513848-59</Id><Title>Obama Cratering in the Polls!</Title><Msg>Obama is cratering in the polls as more and more Americans realize how his Economic policies have created an Unemployment Rate above 8% for more than three years! People want jobs, not Hoplessness and Hate! Obama has failed the American People! It is the Economy, Stupid, err, Obama". One in the same, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346115513848</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:58:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346116481215-60</Id><Topic><Title>Neil Armstrong dies . . .</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1345927443000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 16:44:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>History books already record Neil Armstrong, Buzz Aldrich &amp; Michael Collins on par with Christopher Columbus in expanding mankind's reach to the unknown. I know I am phantom.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1346116481215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:14:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346117663458-61</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Hopelessness and Hate not Selling</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346096299215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:38:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's only on CNN and MSNBC. Vote for Obama if you support organized chaos in America. That's his plan.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1346117663458</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:34:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346118511200-62</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Hopelessness and Hate not Selling</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346096299215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:38:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Senate is stone walling every bill the house passes.</Msg><Username>divielover</Username><Timestamp>1346118511200</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:48:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346118685040-63</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Cratering in the Polls!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346115513848</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:58:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is like a flat tire. BLK and useless. Time for a change.</Msg><Username>divielover</Username><Timestamp>1346118685040</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:51:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346123280713-64</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Cratering in the Polls!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346115513848</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:58:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Man you guys are losers wow</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1346123280713</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 23:08:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346123389824-65</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing update</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1345951069615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 23:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dell George lives again with one of his many IDs LMFAO</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1346123389824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 23:09:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346125250560-66</Id><Title>Romney-Ryan Medicare Plan Would Cost 29-Year-Olds $331,200</Title><Msg>If Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan have their way, then Americans of all ages may be spending more on health care during their retirement. If Romney becomes president and repeals the Affordable Care Act as promised, then retirement would cost $11,100 more for the average 65-year-old and $18,600 more for the average 55-year-old because of higher Medicare premiums and drug costs, according to a report from Harvard economist David Cutler, an Obamacare architect, and the Center for American Progress. Romney's plan would cost younger Americans even more, since Romney and Ryan want to turn Medicare into a voucher system for Americans under 55 for when they qualify for Medicare. The report estimates that 48-year-olds would have to pay $124,600 more for Medicare during retirement under Romney's plan, 39-year-olds would have to pay $216,600 more during retirement, and 29-year-olds would have to pay $331,200 more during retirement in total. That's because the vouchers would not keep up with rising health care costs. For those 29-year-olds, the extra costs would consume 62 percent of their lifetime Social Security benefits. For his part, Romney claims that the Affordable Care act is a tax increase and hurts job creation at small businesses. He also claims that more competition among health care plans would lead to lower premiums. But the promise of lower premiums is a fantasy, according to Peter Orszag, a former budget director for President Obama. Orszag recently said that Ryan's plan relies on the "health care competition tooth fairy" and would shift costs to consumers from the government, rather than reducing costs overall.</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346125250560</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 23:40:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>