<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352699679005-1</Id><Topic><Title>Just before I began campaigning for Obama I had a 30-minute conversation with God...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1352673281259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:34:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Caligula, a supposed narcissist as well, also attempted to increase the scope and breadth of his power - which did not work for him in the end. Enjoy the next four years, call it good, and then we will try to see if we can salvage the country after he is gone. Unless it is too late.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1352699679005</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 00:54:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352700692467-2</Id><Topic><Title>Just before I began campaigning for Obama I had a 30-minute conversation with God...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1352673281259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:34:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>= R folks angry at Gov Christie and God. Won't help---election over.= LOL :))) He who laughs last... I would assume that God™ is laughing as well.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1352700692467</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 01:11:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352701338756-3</Id><Topic><Title>LET US NEVER FORGET THOSE WHO SERVED</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352688978395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:56:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump it up</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352701338756</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 01:22:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352707869930-4</Id><Topic><Title>deliveries thru 10 November</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1352676183371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 18:23:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check the math. Is it 16 or 23?</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1352707869930</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 03:11:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352714194350-5</Id><Topic><Title>deliveries thru 10 November</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1352676183371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 18:23:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Appreciate the update.</Msg><Username>mrstock52</Username><Timestamp>1352714194350</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 04:56:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352726671066-6</Id><Topic><Title>what all this means is gas prices which took a dip around election time will be going back up, you guessed it Obama cutting drilling on gov. land again</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1352693028097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 23:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be familiar with the CBS News report that discovered that many of the "green" energy firms that were granted guarenteed federal loans were tied to financial interests in the Obama Administration. Der Spiegel a top German news magazine is reporting German families will be hit with more energy increases. Last winter 200,000 Germany families were unable to afford heat for their home and this year the number is estimated to be 600,000 families. German families will soon be paying over 40 cents/kWh for electriy which is 1000% higher than what I pay here in the USA. Crop based biofuels are expensive and divert resources needed for food in order to create fuel. Using food for fuel on a planet that requires more food is not sustainable.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352726671066</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:24:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352726763946-7</Id><Topic><Title>what all this means is gas prices which took a dip around election time will be going back up, you guessed it Obama cutting drilling on gov. land again</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1352693028097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 23:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I neglected to mention that the green energy transition in Germany was the cause of rising energy prices.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352726763946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:26:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352727490587-8</Id><Topic><Title>Just before I began campaigning for Obama I had a 30-minute conversation with God...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1352673281259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:34:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I guess it'a true; a man who lays with another man should be stoned." Was Obamer stoned when he layed with other men?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352727490587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:38:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352729087950-9</Id><Topic><Title>Just before I began campaigning for Obama I had a 30-minute conversation with God...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1352673281259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:34:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>George, could you talk to the #$%$ at the Washington Post about this. Those #$%$ don't think that the storm was an act of God like you. They think it was caused by man and that a carbon tax will prevent further storms and bad weather. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352729087950</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:04:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352730647905-10</Id><Topic><Title>LET US NEVER FORGET THOSE WHO SERVED</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352688978395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:56:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you, veterans, for giving your service to our country.</Msg><Username>bissell33</Username><Timestamp>1352730647905</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:30:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352730739119-11</Id><Title>Republicans=Nazzies%Commies</Title><Msg>Republicans have promoted every anachronistic backward looking nostrum availabel for the ills of the nation since about 1865-- thats why they are going extinct just like the Whigs</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1352730739119</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:32:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352731167986-12</Id><Topic><Title>Tonight is Lobster Night at the Petroleum Club</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352498245518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:57:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Several great ideas came out after the feast of lobsters. BTW Main lobsters usually have sweeter meat than the Australian Rock lobster but our chef does some things with Louisiana crab boil seasoning that makes them almost indistinguishable. Back to Preserving and expanding our wealth. The fist suggestion was to buy a couple of politicians – known as the “Warren Buffett method.” Although politicians are relatively inexpensive investments with fantastic returns, most didn’t think it was very sporting. A few thought hoarding more gold and silver was a way to go but most people using gold as a store of value already have plenty and that’s why the price has quit moving even when a new crisis pops up. Several thought we should just be tight fisted with our wealth – Don’t hire “fire and contract.” This is rather cruel but since most of us started with nothing and became very wealthy, we thought it might be entertaining to watch the “have nots” trying to build a “culture of opportunity” through insane regulation and high taxation. Many other ideas were floated but none of them involved letting one legged women make of with half our fortunes.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352731167986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:39:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352731304428-13</Id><Topic><Title>deliveries thru 10 November</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1352676183371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 18:23:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry, 23 total.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1352731304428</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:41:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352732029129-14</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans=Nazzies%Commies</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1352730739119</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:32:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fascist and Communist at the same time? How is that possible? Anyway there is a nice article today about Angelina Jolie and Brad Pitt owning firearms. The best way to prevent Fascism and Communism is a well armed public. ;-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352732029129</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:53:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352732278892-15</Id><Topic><Title>Tonight is Lobster Night at the Petroleum Club</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352498245518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:57:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All the time bellyaching about paying taxes which can be used for things like welfare. The citizen who has gained wealth has a CHRISTIAN duty to his fellow citizens to assist the old, sick and poor- that means paying his taxes. That citizen who resists is a slacker and a taker and a moocher willing to let others carry the load for him and he is grossley unpatriotic even tho he be wealthy</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1352732278892</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:57:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352732335702-16</Id><Title>What's Behind Obama's Obsession Over Raising Taxes</Title><Msg>First … know this. It’s not about raising revenue. It’s about punishing the wealthy. Obama was raised to believe – and believes to this day – that people only become wealthy by oppressing, exploiting and taking advantage of others; unless, of course, you’re an athlete or an entertainer. His obsession over raising taxes on the high-achievers is born of a desire for revenge rather than a need to raise revenue. There was no better illustration of Obama’s obsession for punishing the wealthy than his appearance years ago on Charlie Gibson’s TV show. Obama then, as now, wanted to raise capital gains taxes. Gibson told Obama that history shows that increases in capital gains taxes generally result in a reduction of capital gains tax collections. Obama told Gibson it wasn’t about raising revenue, it was about fairness. Are you hearing this? Obama didn’t care about the revenue! He didn’t even care if the government got LESS revenue. His focus was on making sure that the people who earned that money were forced to give more of it up. Resentment of high achievers is not going to grow our economy and restore America’s economic vitality. Elections have consequences. NBN</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352732335702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:58:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352732426296-17</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans=Nazzies%Commies</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1352730739119</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:32:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your ideas about gun ownerships unmasks you as a gun nut and mental aberrant . If all you have is guns to make you feel good you just as well use one on yourself</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1352732426296</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:00:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352732563428-18</Id><Topic><Title>What's Behind Obama's Obsession Over Raising Taxes</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352732335702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:58:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>crybbaby RWNJs still bellyachin about having to pay their fair share of taxes. People like this do not deserve to be citizens of this country</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1352732563428</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:02:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352732861101-19</Id><Title>You Don't Believe in Government!</Title><Msg>On Friday, I got a call from LC. His phone call started off very reasonable, until he came out with this one line that seems to be pervasive amongst ignorant liberals (redundant?): “You don’t believe in any government.” This is such the standard rhetorical absurdity liberals love to use in response to conservatives, and they use it in response to a breadth of issues. Let’s take healthcare, for example. When conservatives say that they are opposed to ObamaCare – which I promise you are going to hate – generally it is because conservatives support private sector, competitive free market approaches to healthcare instead of more government. So you tell a liberal that this how you think we should solve our healthcare problems in this country and their response generally sounds like this, “Oh, so you don’t want people to have healthcare!” Huh?? Uh, no. Why is it that liberals seem to assume that government and bureaucracy are the only proper ways to provide a service? The private sector can do an even better job of providing this service, yet liberals reduce this down to “Oh, so you don’t want people to have healthcare.” Amazing. The same can be said for environmental policy. If you point out the fact that EPA regulations have gone too far or their application sometimes lack common sense, “Oh, so you are for dirty air! You want dirty water!” That is so typical for how liberals argue with conservatives. And it is this lack of liberal logic which ultimately dooms their success in talk radio. Trust me, I would LOVE to have more competition in talk radio. Heck, I even donated to keep Air America afloat because I truly believe that the more competition the better. But the fact is that the liberals couldn’t compete. Why? Because of their inability to approach a subject logically. They are incapable of discussing legitimate, responsible ways to reduce the role of government so they immediate jump to this idiotic line, “Oh, so you don’t want government .. or you want dirty air.” And after a few days of listening to that nonsense, people simply tune out. They quickly realize that these proggies are #$%$ and thus their liberal talk shows fail. Boortz</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352732861101</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:07:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352733278510-20</Id><Topic><Title>What's Behind Obama's Obsession Over Raising Taxes</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352732335702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:58:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is "fairness" then. The debt is about $1.2 trillion/year and the yearly aggregate income in the United Staters, according to the IRS, is about $8 trillion. 1.2/8 = 15%. That is the amount that needs to be added in taxes - across the board - to everyone, from the billionaire at the top of income earning down to the guy who only made $1000. Only the LWNJs - the mathematically impaired - believe that the deficit spending can be resolved by taking it only from the rich. The so-called 1% ($250K and up) only earn $800 billion/year. The solution has to come from EVERYONE - including and especially those that voted for Obama.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1352733278510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:14:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352734006595-21</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1352559355282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 09:55:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now that we expressed sympathy... should we send them back to the hell they came !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352734006595</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:26:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352734110928-22</Id><Topic><Title>Tonight is Lobster Night at the Petroleum Club</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352498245518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:57:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>father, Have you noticed that there is a large segment of the people that do not complain at all about paying taxes? That is because they do not pay any. When they go into the secrecy of the voting booth, mistakenly, they feel that it is their "Christian duty" to tax others to pay for their "free stuff". Or so they rationalize. While they declare that others have a "Christian duty" to do this or that, they have their "Tenth Commandment Violating" eye on others money. "Thou shalt not covet anything of thy neighbor's". BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1352734110928</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:28:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352734148485-23</Id><Topic><Title>What's Behind Obama's Obsession Over Raising Taxes</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352732335702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:58:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamer himself is an admitted underacheiver. He admits to being lazy and it is clear from his words and actions that he identifies more with lazy people than he does those that have built a country to shelter/protect lazy and stupid people who need help. The difference is that it used to be repugnant to take government money whereas now we have a poser pop culture that finds it repugnant to succeed on your own. In Chicago only 20% of graduates from Chicago Public Schools meet/exceed the levels of math science and English needed for college. Only in government is an 80% failure rate considered acceptable performance. On a global level Chicago Public Schools are ranked with third world countries. Yet there are private schools that consist of the same demographic student makeup as the Chicago Public Schools, who prepare 90+% of graduates to meet/exceed math, science and English needed for college and they are using far less dollars per student to achieve this result. Obamer was a key contributor of the failed Annenberg school project in Chicago. We have become a nation where tribalism has become more important than accomplishment and it is OK to promote failure as long as you make people feel better about themselves.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352734148485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:29:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352734328008-24</Id><Topic><Title>Why Mitt Romney Lost !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352483187601</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:46:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reason # 9, they came light... need more that Koch Bros and Fox News to unseat the champ...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352734328008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:32:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352734681626-25</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Gods plan for America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352488627039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bb, you're missing reveres point; '.. the end should be greeted with joy..' ... understand..? Everything thats happened is ' Gods Plan '... - installing Mitttens into the white house is Not Gods plan for Mittens. God has another plan for him in the Cayman islands... and later in hell !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352734681626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:38:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352734959921-26</Id><Topic><Title>LET US NEVER FORGET THOSE WHO SERVED</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352688978395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:56:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump !</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352734959921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:42:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352735103970-27</Id><Topic><Title>as the spiritual leader of America Billy Graham stated Romney a righteour man Demonized by the Party of Hattred and Division</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1352611154331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 00:19:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kingdome? That's dust now, isn't it? #$%$ to ashes ...</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1352735103970</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:45:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352735260129-28</Id><Topic><Title>Just before I began campaigning for Obama I had a 30-minute conversation with God...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1352673281259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:34:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jesus spare me. Unless there are gated communities in heaven for people like bulky.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1352735260129</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:47:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352735445550-29</Id><Topic><Title>Tonight is Lobster Night at the Petroleum Club</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352498245518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:57:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jesus never said "though shalt not steal unless by majority vote." In the parable of the Good Samaritan the Samaritan took money out of his own pocket to help the man in need. The Democrats would like to rewrite that parable so you would believe the Samaritan robbed the next passerby and gave most of the money to help the man in need.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352735445550</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:50:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352735533153-30</Id><Topic><Title>They Watched It Go Down the Toidy</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1352645909547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 09:58:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is like a turd that won't flush.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1352735533153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:52:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352735626454-31</Id><Topic><Title>what all this means is gas prices which took a dip around election time will be going back up, you guessed it Obama cutting drilling on gov. land again</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1352693028097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 23:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Negativism and constant #$%$. didn't work for you during the election campaign. Do you persist in it because it's all you've got?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1352735626454</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:53:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352735799451-32</Id><Title>Quotes of the Day - Twofer</Title><Msg>Socialism, like the ancient ideas from which it springs, confuses the distinction between government and society. As a result of this, every time we object to a thing being done by government, the socialists conclude that we object to its being done at all. We disapprove of state education. Then the socialists say that we are opposed to any education. We object to a state religion. Then the socialists say that we want no religion at all. We object to a state-enforced equality. Then they say that we are against equality. And so on, and so on. It is as if the socialists were to accuse us of not wanting persons to eat because we do not want the state to raise grain. Here I encounter the most popular fallacy of our times. It is not considered sufficient that the law should be just; it must be philanthropic. Nor is it sufficient that the law should guarantee to every citizen the free and inoffensive use of his faculties for physical, intellectual, and moral self-improvement. Instead, it is demanded that the law should directly extend welfare, education, and morality throughout the nation. Claude Frédéric Bastiat (1801-1850)</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352735799451</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:56:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352735803473-33</Id><Topic><Title>What's Behind Obama's Obsession Over Raising Taxes</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352732335702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:58:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"People like this do not deserve to be citizens of this country" You're projecting again. It is unfortunate people like you think others aren't paying their fair share when in fact they pay more than their fair share.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352735803473</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:56:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352735937919-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Gods plan for America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352488627039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stick, I got the point - at least to the extent that it could be devined from "revere's" statement. I do believe that God is "in control" - whether by His direct action or allowance. Thus, God allowed Obama to win. The point of my post(s) is that Obama plays a role - and it is not clear who his "master" is - in preparation for the end and the final judgment on mankind. Witting or unwitting Obama is taking the country down. The American people voted the guy in not just once but twice. Eyes wide open. And the temper of the country has moved in the direction of hating and blaspheming God, hating Israel, loving sin, and extreme covetousness. Thus, the quote of 2 Thessalonians 2:11. As to Romney going to hell: 1) you do not have that knowledge, only God does; and 2) that you glee at that notion of him going to hell is a sad thing for you. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1352735937919</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:58:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352735958746-35</Id><Topic><Title>They Watched It Go Down the Toidy</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1352645909547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 09:58:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm watching people that used to have jobs going down the toidy with president AWOL running the show.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352735958746</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:59:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352736050190-36</Id><Topic><Title>They Watched It Go Down the Toidy</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1352645909547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 09:58:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone as full of it as you are probably has experienced a lot of those.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1352736050190</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:00:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352739220666-37</Id><Title>Valerie Plame For CIA Director</Title><Msg>It would be poetic justice.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1352739220666</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:53:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352739253783-38</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Gods plan for America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352488627039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bb dont you get high and mighty with me; We all know where the rich man is going (thought you read the good book)... and it doesn't matter who is Obama's master... The only thing that matters is what bb...?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352739253783</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:54:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352739396025-39</Id><Topic><Title>They Watched It Go Down the Toidy</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1352645909547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 09:58:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All told the repub/baggers flushed over $2,000,000,000 down the toidy. Pity. Eh!</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1352739396025</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:56:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352739528921-40</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Gods plan for America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352488627039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I give thanks to the almighty for flushing the baggers down the toidy!</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1352739528921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:58:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352739657395-41</Id><Title>Republicans worship poop !!</Title><Msg>they must worship poop...when all the do is talk crap !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352739657395</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:00:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352739995663-42</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1352559355282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 09:55:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Baggers are obviously low information dupes. After Willard went down the toidy on election night he called a meeting of his advisors telling them to fashion a new campaign for 2016 :"I want to run as several liberal. Start the repub propaganda machine to soften up the dumb baggers".</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1352739995663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:06:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352740389389-43</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans worship poop !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352739657395</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:00:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Grover Norquist is fascinated by "poop": "The president was committed; elected on the basis that he was not Romney and Romney was a poopy head and you should vote against Romney ," Grover told CBS' "This Morning" today.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1352740389389</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:13:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352740582795-44</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a worthless loser like the rest of bloodthirsty rightwingers</Title><Username>awesome_turk</Username><Timestamp>1352601600942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 21:40:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amen!</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1352740582795</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:16:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352740899843-45</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1352559355282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 09:55:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"SEVERE LIBERAL" He wants torun as a severe liberal.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1352740899843</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:21:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352741621749-46</Id><Topic><Title>What's Behind Obama's Obsession Over Raising Taxes</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352732335702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:58:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure it is about raising revenue,,,$100B/yr = $1T over 10 years,,, combined with $4 in spending cuts for every dollar raised. It's called a 'balanced approach',,, and not some right-wing or Mittens pipe-dream plan,,,</Msg><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1352741621749</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:33:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352742173826-47</Id><Title>Shorted BA</Title><Msg>Per my newsletter mention, I shorted BA today at 74.15. I am using a 75.10 stop loss and have a 67.60 objective. I am risking $95 to pick up $655 per 100 shares. It is a 6-1 risk/reward ratio. My rating on the trade is a 3.5 on a scale of 1-5 with 5 being the highest.</Msg><Username>luckyone581</Username><Timestamp>1352742173826</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:42:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352742456140-48</Id><Title>Where are the Patriotic Businessmen?</Title><Msg>When the top marginal tax rate was at 91% under Eisenhower no millionaires jumped out of windows in despair or packed up and left the US for Bermuda or the Caymans. Instead of paying those rates, they reinvested their money in THIS country, in their businesses, in higher wages and benefits for their employees, in new equipment and in research and development. America had the greatest expansion of the middle class in history. Amazing. Wonder where those patriots went?</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1352742456140</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:47:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352742647480-49</Id><Title>End The Pledge</Title><Msg>Put Grover norquist out of the 'business' of politics. Bring back negotiation and compromise to Congress. It worked well enough during the Raygun-Tip O'Neil era (despite the Raygun doubling of the national deficit) and it worked even better during the Clinton/Gingrich era. How this Grover Norquist can hold sway over so many t-baggers and republicons is unfathomable and bad medicine for America and Americans!</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1352742647480</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:50:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352742860201-50</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hails verterans but cuts all their benefits how hypocritical is that</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1352692061379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 22:47:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't have clue what you are talking about due you. Military and Veteran benefits are at an all-time high compared to pre Operation Desert Storm and the post VN era...</Msg><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1352742860201</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:54:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352742913982-51</Id><Topic><Title>Billy Graham support Romney on Biblical Principle full page ads in the Wall Street Journal</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1352740479137</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:14:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares? BG is one MAN. A MAN not God. He is not always right and just because he thinks something does not meany any more, or any less, than what another MAN thinks. If you were not such a lemming, you would know this. You also would need about 90 more IQ points.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1352742913982</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:55:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352743068111-52</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hails verterans but cuts all their benefits how hypocritical is that</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1352692061379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 22:47:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Expecting gregjanetommax to have any facts, or grasp on reality, is just totally unrealistic. If it is not in the GOP bubble and approved by the party, he will never acknowledge it.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1352743068111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:57:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352743413317-53</Id><Title>U.S. to Become Largest Oil Producer, Energy Independent: Big Implications</Title><Msg>U.S. to Become Largest Oil Producer, Energy Independent: Big Implications Daily Ticker A new report by the International Energy Association says the U.S. will become the world's largest oil producer by 2017, overtaking current leaders Saudi Arabia and Russia.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1352743413317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:03:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352743462849-54</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the Patriotic Businessmen?</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1352742456140</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:47:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are no foreclosed homes in the priciest enclaves. There elite restaraunts are still fully booked. Corporate seats and sky-boxes at all sporting venues( except the NHL) are packed for every game. Cutting their taxes will not create a single job. Raising the taxes on the most wealthy amongst us will not cut one job. A fair and balanced approach to taxation and deficit reduction ala the Obama/Democrat tax plan is the best hope for America! Where are the Patriotic Businessmen? Indeed</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1352743462849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:04:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352743551828-55</Id><Title>BA 73.96+0.71(0.96%) 1:04pmEST</Title><Msg>This bird wants to FLY</Msg><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1352743551828</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:05:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352743594716-56</Id><Title>What is the objective of these liars from the Republican Party on this board now?</Title><Msg>Don't they understand they can no longer influence the election? Do they think that posting lie after lie about Obama is going to have any affect on his presidency?</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1352743594716</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:06:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352743668099-57</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. to Become Largest Oil Producer, Energy Independent: Big Implications</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1352743413317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:03:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad too much will be exported to the 'open' market</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1352743668099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:07:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352743774383-58</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hails verterans but cuts all their benefits how hypocritical is that</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1352692061379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 22:47:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't the recent VA bill stalled by the Rethugs?????</Msg><Username>windyhorn</Username><Timestamp>1352743774383</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:09:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352743875411-59</Id><Topic><Title>What is the objective of these liars from the Republican Party on this board now?</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1352743594716</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:06:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to one right-wing poster, bulky-bob the bearer of false-witnessing, it is God's plan to denigrate the Obama Presidency and promote right-wing fascism and evilness</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1352743875411</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:11:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352743906136-60</Id><Topic><Title>Billy Graham support Romney on Biblical Principle full page ads in the Wall Street Journal</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1352740479137</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:14:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Billy Graham and his stooge son have turned into as big a set of cranks as the rest of the homophobic, muslim haters on TVpreacherland.</Msg><Username>windyhorn</Username><Timestamp>1352743906136</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:11:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352743972765-61</Id><Topic><Title>What is the objective of these liars from the Republican Party on this board now?</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1352743594716</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:06:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hopefully their objective will remain the same , they will be lost in this idealistic fog it will will continue to keep them from accepting facts and they will continue to lose elections.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1352743972765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:12:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352744406235-62</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a worthless loser like the rest of bloodthirsty rightwingers</Title><Username>awesome_turk</Username><Timestamp>1352601600942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 21:40:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe we will keep Virginia, as a buffer-zone and of course the peninsular Florida area, despite it's highest point being only 200 ft. above sea-level, just for the oranges</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1352744406235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:20:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352744516246-63</Id><Topic><Title>Billy Graham support Romney on Biblical Principle full page ads in the Wall Street Journal</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1352740479137</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:14:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"many feel Billy Graham is Gods representative on Earth " Many more don't. "including Obama who has made several visits to him during his first term" You have no idea if the President believes that, it's politic to confer with BG to appease lemmings like you. According to the Bible marriage is between one man and MANY women. We don't follow that either.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1352744516246</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:21:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352744885238-64</Id><Topic><Title>Billy Graham support Romney on Biblical Principle full page ads in the Wall Street Journal</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1352740479137</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:14:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not quite on the same level as the Jim and Tammy Bakker bible-thumpers, the Coral-Ridge-Hour/Truth In Action crowd, nor the Ralph Reed devil worshippers...but when their is blood money to be made off the guiliibility of the sheep...Let their be Blood, heck the BG crusade appovers of female preachers especially in the case of BG's daughter</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1352744885238</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:28:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352745136139-65</Id><Topic><Title>End The Pledge</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1352742647480</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:50:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Back off the fiscal-cliff repubublicon 'leaders' and do not kick the can down the road again thinking aboput the 2014 elections you losers. OR ELSE! v</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352745136139</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:32:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352745329381-66</Id><Title>What happened to imacon loser...</Title><Msg>self-destructed and nobody noticed just another bad robot or the dark side of the hoozdik personna</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352745329381</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:35:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352745503407-67</Id><Title>It took Petreaus over a year to see that PB stamped on her forehead</Title><Msg>and it didn't stand for paula broad-well but for Psycho Beyatch I guess that republican fascist is only human,,,</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1352745503407</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:38:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352745930381-68</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the Patriotic Businessmen?</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1352742456140</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:47:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The repub shills in congress have the audacity to ask us to sacrifice what we worked hard to achieve over decades of dedication and loyalty to the system that made them millionaires and saw the great masses of the public’s salary stagnate as we waited for the trickle to begin. Did the trickle ever begin? If so why are many now having to work 2 jobs to cling on to the middleclass, when 30 years ago, a single worker household could buy a home, a new car every few years, put their kid’s through college and have a nest egg to retire on?</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1352745930381</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:45:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352746411510-69</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the Patriotic Businessmen?</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1352742456140</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:47:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hmmm... Their, the repube shills, silence is almost deafening except for the fact that they are the 'cling-ons' to a lost, unafair, and unbalanced approach</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1352746411510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:53:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352746690959-70</Id><Topic><Title>Maintaining the target price of $80!</Title><Username>stocker4949</Username><Timestamp>1352405171749</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 15:06:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have no maney candb01</Msg><Username>trieschexecpc.com</Username><Timestamp>1352746690959</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:58:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352746846235-71</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Gods plan for America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352488627039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stick - "don't you get high and mighty with me; We all know where the rich man is going (thought you read the good book)... and it doesn't matter who is Obama's master... The only thing that matters is what bb...?" Here is a list of some of the richest men in Biblical history: Solomon, David, Saul, Abraham, Lazarus (raised from the dead by Jesus), and Job. By your reckoning, I gather, simply by being wealthy, such a person therefore goes to hell. Yet, the "good book", as you call it, that is, the Word of God, says no such thing. And Abraham was certainly in heaven when the unredeemed "rich" man was in torments in hell. And God counted Job, the richest man in the neighborhood at the time, as "righteous" in His eyes. In fact, He said, "none was like him (Job), he is blameless and upright, a man who fears God and shuns evil". When Satan accused Job before the Lord, there was no discussion of Job's wealth. In fact, Job's friends said that Job was pretty much not a generous person. I think that there is some more studying of God's word that would be of benefit to you. And you will find that it is the "love of money" that is the source of evil (1 Tim 6:10). And, by the way, those folks that vote in the secrecy of the polling booth, poor or not, that have their covetous eyes on other people's money to "tax the rich" (and especially not themselves) and "make them pay their 'fair share' " are exactly what this passage of scripture is talking about. You guys need to look at yourselves and get right.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1352746846235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:00:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352746919925-72</Id><Title>Sir Paul McCartney is Okay after near mid-air disaster</Title><Msg>May 3rd, 2012 Sikorsky S-76C Air accident investigators have launched a "serious incident" probe over reports that Paul McCartney and his wife, Nancy Shevell, were just two feet away from disaster when a pilot of their helicopter became "disorientated" in bad weather and almost crashed into tree tops, the Daily Mail reports. On May 3, 2012, McCartney and Shevell were traveling back home to East Sussex, England, when the Sikorsky S-76C they were riding in plummeted towards trees as it was trying to land on the singer's private helipad. Luckily, an accident was avoided when at the last minute, the pilot reportedly pulled the helicopter back up and flew to a nearby airport safely. The incident is now being investigated by the government's Department of Transport after the Air Accidents Investigation Branch classified it as a "serious incident". Flying conditions that night were reported as "low cloud base, poor visibility and rain." A spokesman for Air Harrods, the company which runs the helicopter service, tells The Mail, "Harrods Aviation can confirm that an incident took place on May 3 involving an Air Harrods helicopter. We are working in full cooperation with the AAIB which are currently investigating the incident." A rep for the Beatle told the paper, "Paul has been spoken to. It has been put to him, everything. It's a no comment."</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352746919925</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:01:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352747171226-73</Id><Topic><Title>Billy Graham support Romney on Biblical Principle full page ads in the Wall Street Journal</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1352740479137</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:14:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Reverend Billy Graham tells of a time early in his ministry when he arrived in a small town to preach a sermon. Wanting to mail a letter, he asked a young boy where the post office was. When the boy had told him, Dr. Graham thanked him and said, "If you'll come to the Church this evening, you can hear me telling everyone how to get to Heaven." "I don't think I'll be there," the boy said. "You don't even know your way to the post office."</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1352747171226</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:06:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352747672058-74</Id><Topic><Title>Just before I began campaigning for Obama I had a 30-minute conversation with God...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1352673281259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:34:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris said: "Jesus spare me. Unless there are gated communities in heaven for people like bulky." Jesus "sparing you" is what I would pray for as well - but you have to decide to receive Him. As to the "gated community", it will be nothing like we have seen. Read John chapter 14, verses 2 and 3, "In my Father's house are many mansions ... I go to prepare a place for you ... that where I am, there you may be also." But, Jesus went on to say there was a "catch" in the 6th verse: "I am the way, the truth, and the life, no man comes unto the Father but by me." – BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1352747672058</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:14:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352747703972-75</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. to Become Largest Oil Producer, Energy Independent: Big Implications</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1352743413317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:03:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"U.S. energy policies initiated by the George W. Bush administration and implemented by President Barack Obama have moved the U.S. toward energy independence and away from Middle East energy sources. U.S. oil production has risen rapidly since 2008 and oil imports are at their lowest level in two decades." We owe thanks to Bush 42 and Bush 43 for making this possible. :-) We should be thankful that Bush 43 ignored the progressive eco-loons who wanted him to shut down the oil and gas industries. We will have the EU by the balls as they are becoming ever more reliant on oil and coal and the dollar will gain value over the Euro and remain the world currency. We will also have the advantage of becoming the country with the lowest energy costs, and manufacturing jobs will begin to shift back to the USA.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352747703972</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:15:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352747887856-76</Id><Topic><Title>LET US NEVER FORGET THOSE WHO SERVED</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352688978395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:56:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please remember -</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352747887856</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:18:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352748186649-77</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. to Become Largest Oil Producer, Energy Independent: Big Implications</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1352743413317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:03:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, uh-huh, a mittens supporting loon is now you an expert what about the soon to be sub-arctic arctic regions of the planet, how much easily burning oozy stuff is there to be exploited for record profits and furether decimating our man-made climate changes, chimp ?</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352748186649</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:23:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352748339502-78</Id><Topic><Title>LET US NEVER FORGET THOSE WHO SERVED</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352688978395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:56:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>forget-me-nots is for Memorial Day, thanks for NOT serving, you</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352748339502</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:25:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352749173267-79</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans=Nazzies%Commies</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1352730739119</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:32:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't own a weapon yet but I'm very interested and assure you that if I do buy one I would only use it to protect my family and I from fascists and communists who would try to take away our rights and freedoms. You can't possibly be against that idea can you?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352749173267</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:39:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352749272595-80</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Gods plan for America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352488627039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RE; Again I tell you, it is easier for a camel to go through the eye of a needle than for a rich person to enter the kingdom of God. i guess some of us pick &amp; choose which piece of scripture to use... and with 40years of reading you become good at being selective... aint that right bulkyB !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352749272595</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:41:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352749463466-81</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans=Nazzies%Commies</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1352730739119</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:32:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans=Nazzies100%Commies0%</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1352749463466</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:44:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352749639307-82</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Gods plan for America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352488627039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PROBABLY UPSIDE DOWN BY THE TOES OVER FLAMING PILES OF POO unless* he come to presidiaent Obama's 'economic summit' with his 'great plans'...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1352749639307</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:47:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352749711565-83</Id><Title>Israel Israel Israel !!</Title><Msg>testing to see how long before yahoo deletes *************************************************** Tel Aviv Israeli tanks on the Golan Heights fired on and hit a Syria artillery battery on Monday in response to cross-border mortar fire, marking the first time after 18 months of watching the Syrian conflict from the sidelines that the Jewish state has allowed itself to participate. ~ CSM</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352749711565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:48:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352749785786-84</Id><Title>Sammy Davis Jr.</Title><Msg>woulda voted for Obama as would have the entire Rat Pack/Oceans 11</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352749785786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:49:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352750011340-85</Id><Topic><Title>Israel Israel Israel !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352749711565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:48:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that a problem? " in response to cross-border mortar fire"</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1352750011340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:53:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352750113313-86</Id><Topic><Title>Sammy Davis Jr.</Title><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352749785786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:49:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a one-eyed black jew about 5' 6'' tall shells into Syria</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352750113313</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:55:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352750145631-87</Id><Topic><Title>Sammy Davis Jr.</Title><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352749785786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:49:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is this gonna end ?</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352750145631</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:55:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352750193784-88</Id><Topic><Title>Sammy Davis Jr.</Title><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352749785786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:49:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I heard he did vote for Obamer. Sammy is burried in one of those Dem counties that had a 140% voter turn out. ROTF</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352750193784</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:56:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352750295132-89</Id><Topic><Title>Israel Israel Israel !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352749711565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:48:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Golan Heights looking west modern artilllery can sink ships in the Mediateranean Ocean looking east... only mortar postions firing so far</Msg><Username>swrordfishiii</Username><Timestamp>1352750295132</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:58:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352750552091-90</Id><Topic><Title>Israel Israel Israel !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352749711565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:48:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>freed.. looks like the Israel post by "spartaloon" disappeared... or i need glasses !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352750552091</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:02:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352750835303-91</Id><Topic><Title>deliveries thru 10 November</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1352676183371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 18:23:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>................</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1352750835303</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:07:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352750953541-92</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hails verterans but cuts all their benefits how hypocritical is that</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1352692061379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 22:47:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a $500 pair of shoes* over a tailors bunion* was low-cost effective ? first, primary care physician second, primary care physcian, it still bothers me, what is it,,,gout third, podiatrist 4th, 5th, 6th prosthetic specialist with custom bi-lateral insoles (no metion of the shoe maker at all) 2+ years and still got the tailors bunion* muy excellente</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352750953541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:09:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352751661722-93</Id><Title>Elmo accused of gay sex with a minor</Title><Msg>Big Bird may have to testify. LMAO</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352751661722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:21:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352751906511-94</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Gods plan for America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352488627039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"RE; Again I tell you, it is easier for a camel to go through the eye of a needle than for a rich person to enter the kingdom of God. i guess some of us pick &amp; choose which piece of scripture to use... and with 40years of reading you become good at being selective... aint that right bulkyB !!" Stick - You did not read the entire passage.Neither did you comprehend what I said in the prior post regarding Job and Abraham. That leads one to conclude that you are spiritually discerned. So, the "picking and choosing" is being done by you, not me: "(23) Then Jesus said to his disciples, “I tell you the truth, it is hard for a rich man to enter the kingdom of heaven. (24) Again I tell you, it is easier for a camel to go through the eye of a needle than for a rich man to enter the kingdom of God.” (25) When the disciples heard this, they were greatly astonished and asked, “Who then can be saved?” (26) Jesus looked at them and said, “With man this is impossible, but with God all things are possible.” (Matt 19:23-26) First, you should note the words: Jesus simply said "it is easier" for the camel, etc. He did not say that it was "not possible" for a "rich man to get to heaven". And second, He further elaborated on the point in verse 26 that anything is possible with God - and in that context, that means that wealthy people, who have placed their faith and trust in Jesus, are going to heaven. It is only this wicked, covetous, and sinful generation that take verses of scripture out of context in order to establish a secular, not Godly, social ethic.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1352751906511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:25:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352752182172-95</Id><Topic><Title>Elmo accused of gay sex with a minor</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352751661722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:21:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you think you were being funny? About as successful as Romney's presidential bid.</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1352752182172</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:29:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352752281993-96</Id><Title>The 'acting' president, CEO, and COO of LMT</Title><Msg>sucks hot-dogs...but is not a toatal psych-beyatch yet</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352752281993</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:31:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352752403075-97</Id><Topic><Title>Israel Israel Israel !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352749711565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:48:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fire, fire on the mountain... -the Grateful Dead</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352752403075</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:33:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352752685902-98</Id><Title>Our AF killed more Canadian artillerymen on the outskirts of Kabul</Title><Msg>than all those lost in Benghazi by the anti-film protestors turned terrorsist who will be hunted down like the vermin that they are for trying to relieve their brothers from our CIA-annex prison/interrogation center which we do not have a anymore in the fog of war no more</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1352752685902</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:38:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352753060067-99</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. to Become Largest Oil Producer, Energy Independent: Big Implications</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1352743413317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:03:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So when do we turn off the spigot from Hugo Chavez?</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1352753060067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:44:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352753525749-100</Id><Topic><Title>They Watched It Go Down the Toidy</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1352645909547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 09:58:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least I know what an #$%$-hole is supposed to be used for.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1352753525749</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:52:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352753562731-101</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. to Become Largest Oil Producer, Energy Independent: Big Implications</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1352743413317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:03:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So when do we turn off the spigot from Hugo Chavez? ...about the time he needs Halliburton help, for parts/replacements Anymore questions... Que ?</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352753562731</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:52:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352753818382-102</Id><Topic><Title>They Watched It Go Down the Toidy</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1352645909547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 09:58:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A retarded HIV infected chimpanzee could do your job better! And longer too! Repubes wanna back-off the fiscal-cliff and kick the can down the road, again ? Feeling Bad, kick them off the cliff, and make the cans biggers</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352753818382</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:56:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352753822314-103</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. to Become Largest Oil Producer, Energy Independent: Big Implications</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1352743413317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:03:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are gas prices so much lower in mexico?</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1352753822314</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:57:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352754121889-104</Id><Topic><Title>What's Behind Obama's Obsession Over Raising Taxes</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352732335702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:58:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you has a spending problem the Democrats will always say- raise taxes on the rich. When it becomes obvious to all there's a spending problem the Democrats will always cry for a "balanced approach" which still mean raise taxes but offer a reduced rate of spending increase in the future to make it sound like they're being reasonable at solving the problem.</Msg><Username>ballen310</Username><Timestamp>1352754121889</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:02:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352754157943-105</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. to Become Largest Oil Producer, Energy Independent: Big Implications</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1352743413317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:03:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>el cheapo brando won;t float the needs of a high octane sucking high perfomance machino for very longo marlon, marlin hunting off the coast of baja days are almost li'll be long gone by boz sacggs and the late duane allman, et al on this light trading day post oabma -win for the hard digesting ones</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352754157943</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:02:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352754846961-106</Id><Topic><Title>What's Behind Obama's Obsession Over Raising Taxes</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352732335702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:58:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You might be more than right except that every president since Nixon has 'doubled' our national debt except Clinton, Carter, and Obama under the guise of "deficits do not matter' "smaller government" "uber-fascism" yo ho yo ho' it;s a pirates life for me</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352754846961</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:14:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352755359323-107</Id><Topic><Title>Quotes of the Day - Twofer</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352735799451</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:56:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great Quotes: Bastiat eloquently confronted the obvious. It just shows that history will just keep repeating its self and long as people refuse to learn from it. It also shows throughout history that when some people see others with things they want they will always find it easier to take it by force than earn it.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1352755359323</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:22:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352755373381-108</Id><Title>Obama Mafia gets rid of Petraeus before he could testify!!</Title><Msg>word from right wing conspirators; Petraeus was slated to testify before Congress next week on the murder of four Americans, including Ambassador Chris Stevens, in Benghazi, Libya. Bret Baier of Fox News just tweeted, "With Petraeus’ resignation effective immediately, he will not testify next week &amp; lawmakers are said to be 'stunned' by the announcement."</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352755373381</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:22:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352755609792-109</Id><Title>Grover Remembers Romney</Title><Msg>Mr.Grover Norquist on TV today claimed that the President identified Mr Romney as a "poopy-head". I believe the President's description of Mr Romney, if indeed that is what he said, was not entirely accurate. The more accurate description would be that Mr Romney is a shlthead..</Msg><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1352755609792</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:26:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352755997823-110</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Mafia gets rid of Petraeus before he could testify!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352755373381</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:22:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rep. Jason Chaffetz (R-Utah) acknowledged on Wednesday that House Republicans had consciously voted to reduce the funds allocated to the State Department for embassy security since winning the majority in 2010. On Wednesday morning, CNN anchor Soledad O'Brien asked the Utah Republican if he had "voted to cut the funding for embassy security." "Absolutely," Chaffetz said. "Look we have to make priorities and choices in this country. We have…15,000 contractors in Iraq. We have more than 6,000 contractors, a private army there, for President Obama, in Baghdad. And we’re talking about can we get two dozen or so people into Libya to help protect our forces. When you’re in tough economic times, you have to make difficult choices. You have to prioritize things.”</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1352755997823</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:33:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352756046065-111</Id><Topic><Title>Just before I began campaigning for Obama I had a 30-minute conversation with God...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1352673281259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:34:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr Bulky, what was it Jesus said about the money changers in the temple?</Msg><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1352756046065</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:34:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352756141451-112</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1352559355282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 09:55:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First of all my congrats to Paddy Chaikevyski for the book/screenplay kudos to william holden once again, for holding up his end., and the beautiful faye dunaway/julie christie didn't get the dicey part she wanted* lol Jensen = Murdoch Beale = Hannity et al Beale didn't wake anybody up or break any trance. The point of the movie is that a republican network like Fox co-opts and distortst messages by the very nature of their omnipotence. Fascism doesn't work, it only breeds right-wingism uber-RETARDS and transgender man-haters like like annie coulturless sniffeing her fingers after touching the crotch between her armpits</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352756141451</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:35:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352756209412-113</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1352559355282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 09:55:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>duh-bya 41 a wimp ?</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1352756209412</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:36:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352756374778-114</Id><Topic><Title>Grover Remembers Romney</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1352755609792</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:26:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr Norquist thinks that Mr Romney lost the election primarily because the President supposedly called him a "Poopy-head". Not so. Mr Romney and the right wing republican party lost the elections because they were liars who believed their own bullshlt.</Msg><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1352756374778</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:39:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352756640614-115</Id><Title>A male friend of the young Monika Lewinsky said she was going there</Title><Msg>to get some presidential DIK Mr. Petraeus,,, one of the best hopes for the RWNJ presidency in 20167 lets hope NEVER Eight More Progress EMP's</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1352756640614</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:44:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352757117284-116</Id><Topic><Title>Grover Remembers Romney</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1352755609792</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:26:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The comical part is the fact that romney thought he was going to win! Delusional, not even close! Thanks teabaggers! Druid</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1352757117284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:51:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352758628117-117</Id><Topic><Title>Just before I began campaigning for Obama I had a 30-minute conversation with God...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1352673281259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:34:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Majac, Jesus was railing because some folks had defiled His Father's house of worship by making it into place of trade - relative to livestock and exchange of currency. He drove them out by force using a whip, overturning tables, and particularly pointed to those that sold doves. Presumable the doves would be sacrificed by worshipers as part of their obedience to Mosaic law. Outside of the Temple would have been fine. The issue does not appear to be the commerce, per se, but that it occurred within the Temple - as Jesus never did this elsewhere, nor did He otherwise complain about it. If you study in the Old Testament (i.e., Exodus and Leviticus) the somber and reverent discussions of how one was to approach and enter the Temple (and Tabernacle), it would have been unthinkable for someone to be selling anything - whether or not in support of worship - within those confines. This is precisely the reason why Christians should not, by virtue of these examples, make the church a place of commerce. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1352758628117</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:17:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352758714539-118</Id><Title>republicon fascists frothing at the mouth</Title><Msg>same as last week now they want tp preten d nice for the 2014 midterm electiond fray their collective #$%$ while we have a change eom</Msg><Username>republicanfascists</Username><Timestamp>1352758714539</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:18:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352759091986-119</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1352559355282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 09:55:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mighta had to struggle to take ray-gun down to the mat but not the chimp I or II the gorilla got angry at me last time at the zoo too and alerted the other animals including the flamigo's human's who needs them bipbop</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1352759091986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:24:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352760095382-120</Id><Topic><Title>republicon fascists frothing at the mouth</Title><Username>republicanfascists</Username><Timestamp>1352758714539</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:18:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fray flay fillet and fry you speaky chinaman-pro in espearanto no</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1352760095382</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:41:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352760592664-121</Id><Topic><Title>What's Behind Obama's Obsession Over Raising Taxes</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352732335702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:58:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I understand. It's a pivot point for you. And, the balance is weighing negatively. Save your soul, productive members of society all, by the skin of our noses save YOU sou:l and a higher EQ</Msg><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1352760592664</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:49:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352762014280-122</Id><Title>The new AUsterity plan</Title><Msg>tax the rich feed the poor those who l;abour earnestly in the fields of yore Abel</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1352762014280</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:13:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352763424004-123</Id><Title>We don't have a Huge Deficit because we Tax too little.......</Title><Msg>......we have a huge deficit because we spend too much. So why do Democrats want to solve the spending problem by raising taxes?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1352763424004</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:37:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352764289323-124</Id><Topic><Title>We don't have a Huge Deficit because we Tax too little.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1352763424004</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:37:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alert the OCD internet police: there is an alienated, disafffected, RWNJ put there asking retarded questions who goes by the name pay4itypourself so we shot him -Wyatt Earp</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1352764289323</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:51:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352765921733-125</Id><Topic><Title>Comeback Burger Stand is a laid-off aircraft worker’s fallback plan</Title><Username>rolandsteph</Username><Timestamp>1267824485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2010-03-05 16:28:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TELL ME MORE</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1352765921733</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:18:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352766895545-126</Id><Topic><Title>What's Behind Obama's Obsession Over Raising Taxes</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352732335702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:58:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your fallacy in logic is only looking at % as in doubling the debt. This is the wrong metric and you should be looking debt to GDP ratio in equalized dollars in order to evaluate debt increases for comparison.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352766895545</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:34:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352767694900-127</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Gods plan for America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352488627039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spartacus, God bless you in your path to seeking God's love and wisdom. God does indeed hear and answer prayer - it just may not always be by what we prescribe as "the solution". BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1352767694900</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:48:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352767975193-128</Id><Title>Obama looking more like Nixon every day</Title><Msg>His legacy will be that he was as big a liar as Nixon and as poor a performer as Carter. ;-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352767975193</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:52:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352768118993-129</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Gods plan for America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1352488627039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:17:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chrissy, You haven't posted anything close to a rational thought yet. But keep trying, putz.</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1352768118993</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:55:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352769324634-130</Id><Topic><Title>Comeback Burger Stand is a laid-off aircraft worker’s fallback plan</Title><Username>rolandsteph</Username><Timestamp>1267824485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2010-03-05 16:28:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's hope he has enough customers who still have jobs.</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1352769324634</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:15:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352770873458-131</Id><Title>political idiots on this board</Title><Msg>the lockheed board has no politics -- none. i hope no one on this board builds the airplanes i ride in.</Msg><Username>aerodog1</Username><Timestamp>1352770873458</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:41:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352772719044-132</Id><Topic><Title>Comeback Burger Stand is a laid-off aircraft worker’s fallback plan</Title><Username>rolandsteph</Username><Timestamp>1267824485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2010-03-05 16:28:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you hate job creators stupid?| A man obviouly trying to put his life back together after losing his job due to the W_O_N_S failed economic policies even?</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1352772719044</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:11:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352775057415-133</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. to Become Largest Oil Producer, Energy Independent: Big Implications</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1352743413317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:03:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In final question..... Lazy bones lying in the sun how do you expect to get your days work done?- Leon Redbone</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1352775057415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:50:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352775501131-134</Id><Title>We need a tax cut for the rich......</Title><Msg>....the high achievers know how to use the money a lot better than a bunch of government bureaucrats.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1352775501131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:58:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352775775655-135</Id><Topic><Title>We need a tax cut for the rich......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1352775501131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:58:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and they will see as unemployment will be over 10% next year. what fools they are....</Msg><Username>hirtuism</Username><Timestamp>1352775775655</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:02:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352776593207-136</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. to Become Largest Oil Producer, Energy Independent: Big Implications</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1352743413317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:03:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have no idea what you are talking about. Obama is a chimp too because he supports energy indepemdence and embraced Bush energy policies. That's why I made sure I provided the truth that both Bush and Obama get credit for taking steps to assure the energy independence of the USA. Here's your chance to show me that you know more about climate change than me. 1) Why is the Antarctic gaing both ice mass balance and sea ice extension? 2) How much will the temperature be lowered by 87 years from now if the USA went to zero CO2 emissions tomorrow according the avaerge of the 22 IPCC climate models? 3) When was the last time that the Arctic was ice free during summers. This is a timed test and you get 1 hour to show me you're not the chimp. :-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352776593207</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:16:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352776596120-137</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. to Become Largest Oil Producer, Energy Independent: Big Implications</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1352743413317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:03:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because you can't drink the water.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1352776596120</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:16:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352776699050-138</Id><Title>Liberals, Let's Not Get Into Math ...</Title><Msg>... spelling, and politics make you look plenty 'tarded as it is . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1352776699050</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:18:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352776898861-139</Id><Topic><Title>Bev Harris, Author of "Hacking Democracy" on the Latest Voter Fraud in Key states</Title><Username>spartacus8463</Username><Timestamp>1352776718555</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:18:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, that conspiracy theory didn't take long to adopt you, spartapus.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1352776898861</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:21:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352777264034-140</Id><Topic><Title>We need a tax cut for the rich......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1352775501131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:58:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are a Repub and you think that that's true, then wouldn't it make sense to let president Obama raise taxes? Wouldn't Repubs benefit in the midterms and 2016 if unemployment went over 10%?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1352777264034</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:27:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352777332844-141</Id><Title>The Monroe DocTrine</Title><Msg>me and the cat zzzzzzzzzzzzzz'in</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1352777332844</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:28:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352777420488-142</Id><Topic><Title>Bev Harris, Author of "Hacking Democracy" on the Latest Voter Fraud in Key states</Title><Username>spartacus8463</Username><Timestamp>1352776718555</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:18:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As usual, you misremember everything you don't jujst make up.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1352777420488</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:30:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352777629429-143</Id><Topic><Title>Quotes of the Day - Twofer</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1352735799451</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:56:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We say we are against high taxes, Liberals think they won't get a check, and therefore they are for high taxes . We say we are against excessive government borrowing, Liberals think they won't get a check, and therefore they are for excessive government borrowing . We say national defense comes first, Liberals think they won't get a check, and therefore they are against military spending . We say we are against illegal immigration, Liberals think that means dims won't get elected, and therefore they won't get a check, so of course they are for illegal immigration ... but they'll call it the "dream act ." etcetera, etcetera, add nausium . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1352777629429</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:33:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352777976783-144</Id><Topic><Title>The Monroe DocTrine</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1352777332844</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:28:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there is zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz'in while on the cat bird seat inside the window there is zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz'in half awake and there is zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz'in can't raise the dead self/buddy aid a stick in the ground</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1352777976783</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:39:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352778310143-145</Id><Topic><Title>Bev Harris, Author of "Hacking Democracy" on the Latest Voter Fraud in Key states</Title><Username>spartacus8463</Username><Timestamp>1352776718555</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:18:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, when sparty showed back up, he appeared to be sane, but the sanity lasted about a day. Back to the goofus doofus zoofus kooky toony loony weird conspiracy-theory-infested ways. Relapse is too bad in your case as several folks had hopes for your recovery. Back to spartaloon.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1352778310143</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:45:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>