<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-30"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354254867439-1</Id><Title>A .36 and the Pretenders</Title><Msg>acoustics</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1354254867439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 00:54:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354254946865-2</Id><Topic><Title>A .36 and the Pretenders</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1354254867439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 00:54:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>some band from ohio</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1354254946865</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 00:55:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354255497838-3</Id><Topic><Title>A .36 and the Pretenders</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1354254867439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 00:54:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there were no station no .36 the pretenders</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1354255497838</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 01:04:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354256285911-4</Id><Topic><Title>A .36 and the Pretenders</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1354254867439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 00:54:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Patti Smythe</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1354256285911</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 01:18:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354263683569-5</Id><Title>Boeing Change needed</Title><Msg>How bad, the Boeing Company wants a labor(federal?) mediator on the SPEEA labor contract, if that would be a US Federal employee? Obama is pro union, does Boeing think that is a smart move? Kind of like filing a lawsuit agains Airbus for being supported by their governments and the result was Boeing is now required to pay 12 billion as they are supported more by the US taxpayer, go figure the court is in Europe der! How is the stock price working for Boeing shareholders ? Answer , under water by 25% for anyone holding for 5 years and for this year up 1% year to date. Clearly, a buy and hold does not work for any Boeing shareholder. As I pointed out during the election run off, since Romney was a coal guy and the coal industry was at a low price generally, a suggestion made then was to learn how to read a stock chart, even a coal company stock that is out of favor with Obama on a short term trade several times per year is better than Boeing. It is so easy, so once more JRCC, a coal company, as an example of just how bad Boeing stock is, JRCC is not a very good coal company, but for the last five days up 47%. When Romney was running against Obama in a very short time all coal stocks ran up, many over 40% until Romney lost, shorting after the election was even better, like any over bought stock shorting is easy too. . . So if you can read a stock chart,( support and resistance) it was a easy industry and stock to pick . Now in just 5 days , from over sold , JRCC is up another 47% profit .. . Today, JRCC has pretty much had the dog part of the run up and is at resistance .. On Boeing look aat the CEO selection of Boeing's McNerney, , if Jack Welch fired James McNerney and kept Inmet then Welch must have noticed McNerany was not the guy for the GE job, McNerney's next job was with MMM and post its would not qualify Jim for a Boeing job,(BTW- GE makes jet engines not airframes) oh wait a guy with no aerospace experience hired James to replace Stonechipher who was fired and he replaced Phil Condit who was fired by letter of resignation, go figure. And Alan Mulally was forced out to Ford a guy who knew airplanes but was caught up in the antiunion mantra and to everyones surprise worked with the UAW and Ford did better, Mulally learned to work with unions after being turned out for the CEO job at Boeing. If SPEEA and the IAM were allowed to build the 787 per their original offer at 5 billion the 787 plane would not have been made with" cost effective outsourced employee's" so now the 787 is 3 years late and 30 billion over budget due to that cost effective employee outsourcing, AKA the MD-BA management failure business plan. The last SPEEA-IAM plane was the 777, built on time and one budget and not a single fatality to date a perfect record of flight. James McNerney you have met your contract on July7, 2005 you had to stay with Boeing 5 years to make at least 53 million , as usual you failed at Boeing but you satisfied taking up space, so FBI worked for you. James you had friends,brothers and in-laws help you get the job and no SKA, skill, knowledge or ability to do the job. Now please retire and get out of the way. You are a slap in the face of every present,past, and future working American. NO comparing a Puget sound working wage to a area that requires less to live on is not a competitive factor, if you want to pay less go to china you can get workers like Airbus did for 50 dollar per month and a lot of corporate consideration from china. If you can't or will not move then pay the price in Puget Sound, or did you forget food, shelter and clothing and cost of education in Washington State must be a factor in what you pay and the benefits package you offer . .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1354263683569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 03:21:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354276980101-6</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura - Conspiracy Theories: the oz of ark</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1354216843958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 14:20:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YA got to admire the guy though. On another note...did you notice that the Ventura is being vindicated on his Navy Seal Trial...ya know the one where Ventura says the guy lied about punching him out. In court yesterday Ventura was totally vindicated. Turns out the Navy Seal had no witness's...and Ventura was telling the truth all along. Won't see THAT on TV either. They had to DESTROY Ventura in the press to keep him from running as a third party candidate. Its how it works in the New Amerika.</Msg><Username>spartacus8463</Username><Timestamp>1354276980101</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 07:03:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354288718705-7</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Change needed</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1354263683569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 03:21:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The next plane will be called the “Twinkie”</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1354288718705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:18:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354288753451-8</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Change needed</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1354263683569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 03:21:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW JRCC was up 47% in 5 days as of yesterday , see above today now up another 7.91% is Boeing up 57% in 6 trade days , learn to read a chart forget Boeing a dead cat bounce failed stock and company</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1354288753451</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:19:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354289333688-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Host Pig at White House !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1354219609273</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 15:06:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>piggy got a free lunch... !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1354289333688</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:28:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354290426039-10</Id><Title>It’s All About Scott Brown, Not Susan Rice</Title><Msg>Easy. If Kerry is appointed Secretary of State, Massachusetts will have to hold a special election for his Senate seat. The Republicans believe that they can get Scott Brown back in the Senate with that special election, since it was a special election to replace the late Sen. Ted Kennedy that got Brown elected the first time. That would raise the Republican number to 46 in the Senate. Right now the Senate is 53 Democrats, 2 Independents caucusing with the Democrats and 45 Republicans. The Republican Party still doesn’t understand the demographics of this year’s election. If they seriously believe that they can throw a competent, capable, experienced black woman over a cliff for a rich white man and then get the state of Massachusetts to elect another white guy to the Senate, they have their collective heads up their butts. Okay, so Elizabeth Warren only beat Scott Brown by 229,228 votes, 53.7% to 46.3%, but that was head to head, without the added onus of sacrificing Susan Rice to put Brown back on the ballot.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1354290426039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:47:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354291178815-11</Id><Topic><Title>I wake up in the morning and Barack Obama is President.</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351095306051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:15:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>still loving it !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1354291178815</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:59:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354293333308-12</Id><Topic><Title>I wake up in the morning and Barack Obama is President.</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351095306051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:15:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm thankful we have a check and balance form of government to protect us from mistakes like Obama.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1354293333308</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 11:35:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354295028338-13</Id><Title>Republicans Are Ruining the Country</Title><Msg>To protect the less than 1% Super Wealthy the Republicans are holding the middle class hostage and are willing to throw the country over the fiscal cliff and prevent a national economic recovery. In the guise of protecting future generations they will ruin the economy for the now living. They lost the elections and seek to punish us all for it. Throw them all out next election.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1354295028338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:03:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354295114270-14</Id><Title>November deliveries</Title><Msg>So far the deliveries look pretty average. They might get a few more today to close out the month but we will have to wait and see. So far: 45 deliveries. 29 737's 3 747's 2 767's 6 777's 5 787's The major issue going forward is the potential strike by the engineers union. While it wont stop production or deliveries, it can significantly slow them down.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1354295114270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:05:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354295897459-15</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Are Ruining the Country</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1354295028338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>= Throw them all out next election = Hear, hear!</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1354295897459</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:18:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354297456052-16</Id><Topic><Title>$240k and up grew criticism, this arrogant president is now raising taxes on 200k and up. even Clinton and Reid criticised it at first</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1354297157303</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:39:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BFD. Sinclair is a pathological liar. Why are you so obsessed with Obama's se*ual orientation? What does it matter?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1354297456052</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:44:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354298180830-17</Id><Topic><Title>It’s All About Scott Brown, Not Susan Rice</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1354290426039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whom it seems quite a few Republicans are eager to support for Sec State. Doesn't pass the smell test.....</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1354298180830</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:56:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354298771181-18</Id><Topic><Title>It’s All About Scott Brown, Not Susan Rice</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1354290426039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please write a coherant sentence so your question, point can be addressed.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1354298771181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:06:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354299047111-19</Id><Topic><Title>$240k and up grew criticism, this arrogant president is now raising taxes on 200k and up. even Clinton and Reid criticised it at first</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1354297157303</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:39:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only a stupid libtard would support the notion of higher taxes on those making $250,000 and up. It has already been determned that 900,000 small businesses would qualify for the tax hike, and some 700,000 jobs eliminated because of the hike. And the tax on those businesses given that the owners file their businesses as an individual would be a cost to do business increase. The services, and the produces they sell would have to have their prices raised, and the consumer, the middle class, and the poor would pay their taxes. Is that too hard for a libtard to understand? Carville says it is..most are just stupid.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1354299047111</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:10:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354299196505-20</Id><Topic><Title>$240k and up grew criticism, this arrogant president is now raising taxes on 200k and up. even Clinton and Reid criticised it at first</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1354297157303</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:39:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is English your second language?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1354299196505</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:13:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354300274422-21</Id><Topic><Title>Why taxing the rich will not happen</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1354119817995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 11:23:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They will not only increase taxes on the rich, but also on the rest of us. We will probably go over the fiscal cliff in a month, and that will mean increased taxes for everyone. It's a democrat dream come true. Wait and see! Then we can talk about tax reform and reducing taxes on the middle class. That will make good talking points for dems in the next election. The current recession can also be blamed on the republicans as well because they took us over the cliff. It's all good for the dems. You have to wonder how Republicans can be so stupid, but there is no question about it.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1354300274422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:31:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354300327103-22</Id><Topic><Title>$240k and up grew criticism, this arrogant president is now raising taxes on 200k and up. even Clinton and Reid criticised it at first</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1354297157303</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:39:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4%. No one's asking for anyone's first born.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1354300327103</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:32:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354300992191-23</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Are Ruining the Country</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1354295028338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Throwing them all out is Not enough... prefer total Annihilation !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1354300992191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:43:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354301059624-24</Id><Topic><Title>It’s All About Scott Brown, Not Susan Rice</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1354290426039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...in the context it is perfectly clear what he means. I believe it's YOU who has a problem with coherency. His comment is coherent with YOUR previous post of 10:57. Idiot.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1354301059624</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:44:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354303004891-25</Id><Topic><Title>It’s All About Scott Brown, Not Susan Rice</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1354290426039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Throw here over the cliff? When she now admits she lied on 5 tv. shows? She will have to fess up as to who told her to lie. No country wants a sec. of state that lied about the deaths of 4 of their citizens.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1354303004891</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 14:16:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354303159923-26</Id><Topic><Title>It’s All About Scott Brown, Not Susan Rice</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1354290426039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And there is another concern. Mrs. Rice's wealth is valued at $20 million dollars. Fine with that, but...much of the wealth is in stock she owns, and a major holding is in the Canadian co. that would build the Keystone Pipeline. Mrs. Rice would vote on that proposal. Sounds like a conflict of interest to me.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1354303159923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 14:19:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354303236324-27</Id><Topic><Title>It’s All About Scott Brown, Not Susan Rice</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1354290426039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the demographics are..Oama doesn't have a mandate on anything. He's a lameduck who 48% of the country voted against. That's the demographics.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1354303236324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 14:20:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354303546869-28</Id><Topic><Title>Why taxing the rich will not happen</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1354119817995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 11:23:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"'Republicans can be so stupid,'" I agree with you here for the first time.</Msg><Username>lucid_luke</Username><Timestamp>1354303546869</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 14:25:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354307495848-29</Id><Topic><Title>Sad Prediction, Boehner and His Cast of Cronies Is Going Kamikaze</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1354306267594</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intelligent folks are supposed to believe that the party that took us down huge debt path who created the massive debt who now won't offer any spending cuts, and massive cuts have to be made...is the GOP problem, and the GOP has to come up with solutions? Do libdems think all Americans are as dumb as they are? Twer I a Republican in congress, I would not vote for anymore debt level extensions, nor would I vote for tax increases that will only hurt the economy. Let's head over the fiscal cliff, and maybe braindead libtards can then understand what the cost will be, how much suffering will take place because of them.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1354307495848</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:31:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354307709926-30</Id><Topic><Title>It’s All About Scott Brown, Not Susan Rice</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1354290426039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's not how the Constitution works, if you'd ever care to read it. 48 percent is LOSING. Hahahahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1354307709926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:35:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354308093308-31</Id><Title>The Pirates Behind The Campaign To Fix The Debt</Title><Msg>There are many more important topics out there than The Deficit, the scary, hairy monster that haunts the dreams of David Gregory and only the blood of the poor and elderly can appease its wrath. Climate change comes immediately to mind, as do income inequality, the vast inequities of our tax code, the ongoing upward translation of the nation's wealth, why more bankers aren't in federal prison, and whatever did I do to the baby Jeebus that he allowed Notre Dame to play for a national championship. But the biggest reason why we should shut the national piehole on the topic is not that we have more serious problems, or even that any discussion violates the blog's first rule of economics - Fk The Deficit. People Got No Jobs. People Got No Money. The real reason we should stop talking about it for a while is that the people who are insisting that it will eat us and our posterity on toast are lying swine who would sell your white-haired granny to the Somali pirates for another three points on the Dow. Until we all acknowledge the fact that organized wealth in this country has become downright sociopathic in the heedless damage it does, any discussion of The Deficit can and will be hijacked by that quarter in order to gain absolution for its grievous sins and the right to go on committing them against the rest of us, over and over again. Listening to these people talk about the national economy is like listening to a burglar tell you that you should really polish the silver more often. The latest confirmation of this obvious truth comes from the good folks at the Institute Of Policy Studies, who took a look at the various plutocrats and pirates who are behind Fix The Debt, the latest scam from the phony deficit scolds, albeit one made up almost exclusively of people who helped threw the national economy into the abyss for a decade, and then came looking for government handouts when it all went to hell. In a sensible world, the whole notion of taking seriously the economic proposals emanating from this particular bag of rancid marsupials would occasion an immediate takeout order from Wanda's House Of Tar And Feathers. Instead, we have the people at IPS, to whom none of our courtier press will pay attention, but who have done us the invaluable service of showing us in detail how the folks behind Fix The Debt do business in their day jobs. These are the people, of course, who are so concerned about The Deficit because of the impact it will gave on their children and grandchildren, most of whom, of course, will not have to work a day in their lives, because Grampy stole the country back in the day. The report is a truly remarkable look at who's really running things. The 71 Fix the Debt CEOs who lead publicly held companies have amassed an average of $9 million in their company retirement funds. A dozen have more than $20 million in their accounts. If each of them converted their assets to an annuity when they turned 65, they would receive a monthly check for at least $110,000 for life. The Fix the Debt CEO with the largest pension fund is Honeywell's David Cote, a long-time advocate of Social Security cuts. His $78 million nest egg is enough to provide a $428,000 check every month after he turns 65. Forty-one of the 71 companies offer employee pension funds. Of these, only two have sufficient assets in their funds to meet expected obligations. The rest have combined deficits of $103 billion, or about $2.5 billion on average. General Electric has the largest deficit in its worker pension fund, with $22 billion. (Cote is the sweetheart to whom Gregory gave such an elaborate private dance in the VIP Room of his show on Sunday. When it comes to speaking mush to power, there's nobody quite like the Dancin' Master.) Look at those numbers. Only two - ! - of these gombeens run companies that intend to fulfill the bargains they have made with their workers. They have feathered their own nests so luxuriously that they make the Ottoman sultans look like Franciscans. And they now have organized themselves to lobby for a program that will cut Social Security and Medicare, and they are trotting it out in public, and nobody has yet greeted them with the flying clumps of horse manure that are really the only answer to this shameless audacity. My god in heaven, the average Social Security recipient receives a little over $1200 a month, or roughly 400 times less than will David Cote who, on Sunday, said this to David Gregory who, alas, declined to spit on him. We have a significant problem with entitlements. Medicare, Medicaid in - in particular. Those things need to get resolved together. If we could actually develop a four trillion dollar credible market credible plan that would cause everyone out there to say, wow, we can govern again. It is hard to believe, given the very real look into how these people think that was the essence of the Romney campaign, that so many people now covering our politics seem unwilling to admit what is plainly in front of their face. We need government more than ever to protect us and our political commonwealth from a rapacious business and financial elite that sees the country as something to be pillaged, and that doesn't have the basic patriotism that god gave the common sea slug. These people have no more business directing the politics of the country than does your drunk uncle who watches Fox News. These people ought to have less influence in our politics than do the people who leave the mints on their pillows every night. There is nothing for the rest of us but self-government, which occasionally must show the right people its fangs so they do not wreck the country and loot what's left. It is all that the rest of us have. -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- By Charles Pierce, Esquire 30 November 12 Charlie has been a working journalist since 1976. He is the author of four books, most recently "Idiot America." He lives near Boston with his wife but no longer his three children.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_spaz</Username><Timestamp>1354308093308</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:41:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354308190463-32</Id><Topic><Title>Sad Prediction, Boehner and His Cast of Cronies Is Going Kamikaze</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1354306267594</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>double, You need to learn to comb your hair differently. That big L on your forehead is showing.</Msg><Username>eggs_acklee</Username><Timestamp>1354308190463</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:43:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354308505343-33</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Are Ruining the Country</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1354295028338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the time the taxes on the 1% are increased, they will have already left the country and the higher taxes will have to be covered by you moocher/looters. Better hide your food stamps as the government will be coming after them in the not too distant future. You libdum clowns are a hoot. Like frogs put in a pot with cold water over a fire. By the time they realize the water is boiling, it is too late.</Msg><Username>locost7777</Username><Timestamp>1354308505343</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:48:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354308795160-34</Id><Topic><Title>Sad Prediction, Boehner and His Cast of Cronies Is Going Kamikaze</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1354306267594</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP created the massive defecit. or did you forget nice try though</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1354308795160</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:53:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354309117253-35</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Are Ruining the Country</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1354295028338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:03:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the sooner they leave the country the better... take your bratty kids and don't come back !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1354309117253</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:58:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354309309460-36</Id><Topic><Title>Sad Prediction, Boehner and His Cast of Cronies Is Going Kamikaze</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1354306267594</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The GOP created it? Do you live in WA ST. and are taking advantage of their new marajuana laws? Smoke up libtard! Bush got the tax cuts passed, and the economy grew at record levels, and tax revenues overflowed the state and fed. coffers. It wasn't until you libs took over congress in the last years of Bush's term that the debt rose to such high levels. Not as high as Obama has taken it by far, but high, and because you libs decided banks had to provide mortgages to flakes that couldn't pay back their loans.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1354309309460</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:01:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354309651879-37</Id><Topic><Title>November deliveries</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1354295114270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:05:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Matbe they should look at twinkies before the demands get out of control.</Msg><Username>mrstock52</Username><Timestamp>1354309651879</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:07:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354310395541-38</Id><Topic><Title>November deliveries</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1354295114270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:05:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Number is now 48. 3 more 737's delivered today 11-30.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1354310395541</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:19:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354312034570-39</Id><Topic><Title>Sad Prediction, Boehner and His Cast of Cronies Is Going Kamikaze</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1354306267594</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 15:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and the "P" is showing on yours..........putz.</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1354312034570</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:47:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354312533540-40</Id><Title>Genna- Re: Jeanie's Belly Button</Title><Msg>[You talk like the repressive 50s &amp; 60s were the "Good Ol Days."] - Genna Genna, I need to answer you this way because there is no reply option to your post. My post was more of a tongue in cheek reponse. Bring on Victoria Secret's Angels and the truth be known I wouldn't have cared much for seeing Lucy and Desi in bed together. I suppose I have been about as happy during all phases of my life except for the past 3 years which have been a real Obummer. As far as your "REPRESSIVE 50s" comment why don't you say that to the progressive idoit on this board who keeps saying we need to go back to the 90% tax rate during the Eisenhower administration?</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1354312533540</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:55:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354315425959-41</Id><Title>Quote From European Newspaper On US Election</Title><Msg>Some people have the vocabulary to sum-up things in a way that you can quickly understand them. This quote came from the Czech Republic. Someone over there has it figured out. It was translated into English from an article in the Prague newspaper Prager Zeitungon: "The danger to America is not Barack Obama, but a citizenry capable of entrusting a man like him with the Presidency. It will be far easier to limit and undo the follies of an Obama presidency than to restore the necessary common sense and good judgment to a depraved electorate willing to have such a man for their president. The problem is much deeper and far more serious than Mr. Obama, who is a mere symptom of what ails America. Blaming the prince of the fools should not blind anyone to the vast confederacy of fools that made him their prince. The Republic can survive a Barack Obama, who is, after all, merely a fool. It is less likely to survive a multitude of fools, such as those who made him their president."</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1354315425959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 17:43:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354317661341-42</Id><Topic><Title>Quote From European Newspaper On US Election</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1354315425959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 17:43:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Post of the year!</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1354317661341</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 18:21:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354318169618-43</Id><Topic><Title>Quote From European Newspaper On US Election</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1354315425959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 17:43:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And these are statements coming from countries that feel the need to look up to our leaders, and our role as a super power. They know the dangers of communism, and the dangers of terrorism. But libs want to lie about what countries like the Czech Republic think about us saying these countries luv Obama, and his leadership. No they don't. And they don't like what he has done to America.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1354318169618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 18:29:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354318279461-44</Id><Topic><Title>In the US, an Insecure Economy Needs a Stronger Safety Net</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_667</Username><Timestamp>1354317006206</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 18:10:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why the lengthy posts from socialist hooz? The safety nets are being destroyed by the left, and the over the cliff debt they have created leaving these safety nets unfunded.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1354318279461</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 18:31:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354320608705-45</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA don't be Plied with Higher raises.</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1354241676931</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 21:14:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry to burst your bubble Pauline, but your rage against sane American tax payers is really unbecoming of you! Please take two Midols and call me in the morning if you so desire!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1354320608705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 19:10:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354320636571-46</Id><Topic><Title>Quote From European Newspaper On US Election</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1354315425959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 17:43:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go to Snopes and search for "Prager Zeitungon" and find out just how much invention right-fringers will accept as truth. It's been around since 2009 and not always credited to this mythical newspaper. Desperate for backup -- even from Czechs.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1354320636571</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 19:10:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354320912865-47</Id><Topic><Title>Quote From European Newspaper On US Election</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1354315425959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 17:43:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you a left-fringer?</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1354320912865</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 19:15:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354321335858-48</Id><Topic><Title>Quote From European Newspaper On US Election</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1354315425959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 17:43:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't call cowpies daisies and I don't think people who ask vacuous questions are intellectuals. Does that make me a left-fringer? Because it sure as he** makes me different from you.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1354321335858</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 19:22:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354321692624-49</Id><Title>Never Fear Rich Guys I will be here to Lead you Through the Depression</Title><Msg>Just as I have made many,,,,,and I do mean many, people on this board very rich with my free tickets to wealth I will now turn to guiding them on how to not only protect and preserve their wealth in spite of our Marxist government, but how to make it continue to grow. The U.S. economy is headed for collapse not matter what kind of can kicking tactics congress and the president employee. The collapse of the U.S economy will lead to a major world wide depression that will be far, far worse than the great depression of the 1930s. The stock market will collapse and pensions, 401-Ks and brokerage accounts will be near worthless. Riots and unrest will lead to threats of war. Governments will turn to more Marxist/Socialist policies not less. Sounds gloomy but there are always opportunities for us rich guys. That's what depressions are for.......taking from those who benefited from the government taking it from you and giving it to people who didn't earn it. Depressions are wealth transfer vehicles.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1354321692624</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 19:28:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354321997138-50</Id><Title>Ever hear of the has-been singer who married a one legged woman......</Title><Msg>....he thought he had a leg up on her so didn't get a prenupt and she hopped off with half his fortune.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1354321997138</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 19:33:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354322335804-51</Id><Title>Rich Guys like Myself Make Things Happen.......</Title><Msg>....some watch things happen, while others voted for Obama and don't have a clue what will be happening.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1354322335804</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 19:38:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354322687685-52</Id><Topic><Title>Quote From European Newspaper On US Election</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1354315425959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 17:43:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe he put his fringer in the wrong hole.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1354322687685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 19:44:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354322841264-53</Id><Title>Tonight is Lobster Night at the Petroleum Club.....</Title><Msg>....rich oil men always make good company.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1354322841264</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 19:47:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354323240685-54</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA don't be Plied with Higher raises.</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1354241676931</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 21:14:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 2002 to 2005 ( approx) I had a shareholder proposal to BA in the Annual meeting. And got between 8 and 12 percent of the votes ( approx 50 million shares ) which was the approx number of shares held in boeing vip It was to give all employees the choice between the heritage pension and the pension value plan ( cash balance ) at time of retirement or leaving the company Then PVP has elements of a 401k, but technically is a defined benefit plan. It made the plan a bit more portable. The company fought it with lots of PR bullpucky- In 2005 speea started to agree to the total conversion to PVP - but I pointed out in a council meeting that it had bad effects on the older, and good effects on the younger- ( but did not mention it secretly eliminated a 10 year limit on credited service for staff ex- employees on Union leave of absence ) AND also moved the 100 percent retirement age to 65 instead of 60. When the members found out about those gotchas- they nearly rioted and the N team had to drop the total conversion bit. And the idea of choice - never got much support from speea- due to the idiocy of a certain executive director who was so put out by what i was doing- he pushed a kangaroo court to hammer me.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1354323240685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 19:54:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354325252513-55</Id><Topic><Title>November deliveries</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1354295114270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:05:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a 777 delivery later today brings the number to 49.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1354325252513</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:27:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354326122934-56</Id><Title>Boeing should take a lesson from Ford</Title><Msg>Henry Ford did not have much compassion for the average factory worker. And yet to retain his workforce Ford did double his employees’ wages to over his competition, not out of the kindness of his heart. Ford did nothing out of the kindness of his heart. He instituted the first $5 a day wage in 1914 for the company’s benefit rather than for his employees’ benefit. The $5 a day wage was more than twice the daily wage of the average factory worker in 1914. Specifically, due to constant improvements in and optimization of Ford’s assembly line, and overall reduction in costs, the Model T’s cost declined through the years until it cost less than $300 in the 1920s. $300 in 1927, adjusted for inflation, would be approximately $3,800 in today’s dollars How would you like to pay under 4000 for a new Ford today( Mulally are you listening ?) If Boeing management was any good they would come up with a better way to assemble airplanes and not do the smoke and mirrors final assembly moving line. All that is about is moving more assembly parts farther back in the factory so less work to do on the factory floor. If you listen to Boeing management all the way up to contract time they brag about assembly improvements, faster build times more planes built per month and then at contract time Boeing Management claims they need to be competitive with Airbus. Well Airbus pays their employee’s more money , gives them more vacation and the government gives a better pension and medical than the USA gives here. It is the failure on Boeing managements part that seems to generate a need to cut the employee’s labor package. If Boeing management had not got it wrong on outsourcing the 787 plane , then Boeing shareholders would not be holding the bag for being 3 years late and 30 billion over budget while the executives still give themselves big pay and bonus raises for their planning failure.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1354326122934</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:42:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354326608509-57</Id><Topic><Title>Quote From European Newspaper On US Election</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1354315425959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 17:43:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This post bears repeating: "The danger to America is not Barack Obama, but a citizenry ( Dumbo-Krats The Govenment School Gulag has co-opted 7 generations of students. Wresting the School System from the LibDumbs is essential for the life of America</Msg><Username>locost7777</Username><Timestamp>1354326608509</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:50:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354327195391-58</Id><Topic><Title>$240k and up grew criticism, this arrogant president is now raising taxes on 200k and up. even Clinton and Reid criticised it at first</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1354297157303</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:39:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4%. No one's asking for anyone's first born. Not just yet...not just yet...Give your W_O_N some time though would ya? Fruition is the word I believe!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1354327195391</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:59:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354327713983-59</Id><Title>Repeat of previous post</Title><Msg>"The danger to America is not Barack Obama, but a citizenry ( Dumbo-Krats The Govenment School Gulag has co-opted 7 generations of students. Wresting the School System from the LibDumbs is essential for the life of America “The Republic can survive a Barack Obama, who is, after all, merely a fool. It is less likely to survive a multitude of fools, such as those who made him their president."</Msg><Username>locost7777</Username><Timestamp>1354327713983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 21:08:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354328845315-60</Id><Topic><Title>$240k and up grew criticism, this arrogant president is now raising taxes on 200k and up. even Clinton and Reid criticised it at first</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1354297157303</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:39:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Print this post and take it to your mental health counselor. Your life doesn't have to be like this. You can get better.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1354328845315</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 21:27:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354329863237-61</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing should take a lesson from Ford</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1354326122934</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:42:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where does this 30 billion number that keeps being quoted come from. All I ever read is that it is billions overbudget without specifying how many</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1354329863237</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 21:44:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354331030221-62</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing should take a lesson from Ford</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1354326122934</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:42:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>However Henry FORD was violently anti union until after WW2- and was so afraid of kidnapping he gave no work jobs to the local mob - and beat up any who even suggested unions. Mulally at least knew-knows how to work WITH unions . . Not much difference between Henry FORD and the Jack welch- wannabees on the BA bored of Directionless in that respect except they no longer use billy clubs and whips Just plain bullying and similar threats</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1354331030221</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:03:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354331758530-63</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing should take a lesson from Ford</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1354326122934</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:42:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well Airbus pays their employee’s more money , gives them more vacation and the government gives a better pension and medical than the USA gives here... And for decades, EADS-Airbust productivity by their own measure ( $$ sales/employee) has been LESS than that of the U.S Aerospace industry try a 36 hour work week- a month of vacation for virtually all employees ( new and old ), and in italy- france - strike at the drop of a cigarette or wrench or just a bad hair day !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1354331758530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:15:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354332045580-64</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing should take a lesson from Ford</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1354326122934</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 20:42:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Psst, Ford's union workers recently took pay freezes and cuts along with benefit cuts.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1354332045580</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 22:20:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>