<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-29"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351483578886-1</Id><Topic><Title>Was General Hamm fired for wanting to help in benghazi ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1351479619910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 23:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DonS and BB are stumped, but then they manage to unnerve Whste by pointing out a flaw in his race baiting logic. They had stated that General Ham and Admiral Gaouette were not due to be transferred off their respective assignments but, after Obama's personal 9-11 debacle, the President and SecDef Panetta reportedly sought retribution, but also stated that they are honorable men who otherwise always follow orders – just that they were "suspected of inappropriate leadership judgment". Ham and Gaouette apparently said, "wow, we were thinking the same about the President." Under heavy pressure from DonS and unnerved by being caught in one of his own non sequiturs, Whste furiously declares, "You can't handle the truth! You pukes and ignorant racist redneck sweethearts." From the movie, "A Few Good Posters".</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351483578886</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 00:06:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351488633096-2</Id><Topic><Title>Was General Hamm fired for wanting to help in benghazi ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1351479619910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 23:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SEARCH ON content/benghazi-october-surprise Note that Hillary had total control over certain parts of security teams - did not need Obuma approval IF what the source min this article says is true- all helll will break loose and perhaps a few jail terms and if elected again - impeachment !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1351488633096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 01:30:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351489837202-3</Id><Title>There were funny people living across the street in the late 1950's, they were Catholic not Mormon</Title><Msg>ate soup out of funny bowls didn;t complain about the basset hound very much put butter on their sa almi sandwiches and they wore their mommas underwear nonetheless bot not only my lips are sealed</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1351489837202</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 01:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351489982469-4</Id><Title>FGood Luck</Title><Msg>mission buenaventura wrote them nice people 4 pictures of wooden bells</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1351489982469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 01:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351490793969-5</Id><Title>ola</Title><Msg>that is very white of you you bet your sweet #$%$ it is almost astronomical odds in a fair game (is there no other ?) dealer, and cut the cards to the right</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1351490793969</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 02:06:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351501397815-6</Id><Topic><Title>Spain's Push For Green Economy Leads To Unemployment Over 25%</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351362044457</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 14:20:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whsteffanmsn - have you ever heard of the concept of electrical overload. What happens when more power surges through a circuit than the circuit can handle? Windmills Overload East Europe’s Grid Risking Blackout: Energy By Ladka Bauerova and Tino Andresen - Oct 25, 2012 6:01 PM CT "Germany is dumping electricity on its unwilling neighbors and by wintertime the feud should come to a head. Germany installed more than 8,885 megawatts of wind energy since 2007, mostly in the north. Photographer: Michele Tantussi/Bloomberg . Central and Eastern European countries are moving to disconnect their power lines from Germany’s during the windiest days. That’s when they get flooded with energy, echoing struggles seen from China to Texas over accommodating the world’s 200,000 windmills. Renewable energy around the world is causing problems because unlike oil it can’t be stored, so when generated it must be consumed or risk causing a grid collapse. At times, the glut can be so great that utilities pay consumers to take the power and get rid of it. “Germany is aware of the problem, but there is not enough political will to solve the problem because it’s very costly,” Pavel Solc, Czech deputy minister of industry and trade, said in an interview. “So we’re forced to make one-sided defensive steps to prevent accidents and destruction.” The power grids in the former communist countries are “stretched to their limits” and face potential blackouts when output surges from wind turbines in northern Germany or on the Baltic Sea, according to Czech grid operator CEPS. The Czechs plan to install security switches near borders by year-end to disconnect from Europe’s biggest economy to avoid critical overload. "</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351501397815</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 05:03:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351501703490-7</Id><Topic><Title>Spain's Push For Green Economy Leads To Unemployment Over 25%</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351362044457</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 14:20:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spain made green jobs and green energy a major platform in building a new green economy. How did it work out for them?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351501703490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 05:08:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351502079089-8</Id><Topic><Title>Spain's Push For Green Economy Leads To Unemployment Over 25%</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351362044457</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 14:20:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Before I go to the trouble would you accept Der Spiegel as a source of information because that is the German paper where I read the story? If you want to have an exchange and discuss facts I'll be happy to provide them but if all you have is angry remarks I don't want to waste my time trying to engage you in adult conversation.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351502079089</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 05:14:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351502854508-9</Id><Topic><Title>Was General Hamm fired for wanting to help in benghazi ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1351479619910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 23:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is that racist, you ignorant liberalnazi?</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1351502854508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 05:27:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351516851208-10</Id><Title>Obama Supporters Uncivilized - turn to violence and vandalism</Title><Msg>Have you noticed the uptick in violence or vandalism on the part of ObamaBots against Romney supporters? I guess that was to be expected. After all, what legitimate reasons could people possibly have for supporting Barack Obama? None. So instead, all they have are emotional responses and defacing the opponent. Here are some examples from just the last few days … * A truck affixed with "Obama" stickers dumped a ton of nails in the parking lot of a tea party rally for Romney-Ryan * Vandals change a church sign to read “Romney Hates Women” and “Christ Voted Democrat” in Indiana *ObamaBots key “Obama” into cars outside a home with Romney yard signs *ObamaBots fly a banner calling the GOP “Sexist” And “Racist” over a Romney rally in Florida This is all that these people can come up with, because they know that they have no real reason to support Obama this time around.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351516851208</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:20:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351517329089-11</Id><Title>This is Funny - Obama Supporters Actually Hate Obama's Policies</Title><Msg>A guy by the name of Luke Rudkowski, of We Are Change, went out on the streets of New York to interview self-proclaimed supporters of Barack Obama. Here’s the deal … Luke asked these supporters about various Obama policies, but presented them as things that Mitt Romney has pledged to do if elected. At the end of the interview, Luke reveals that these are actually all things that Obama has already done. That is when you start to see the ObamaBots panic!. To see video go to youtube and search for "Obama Supporters Actually Hate Obama's Policies."</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351517329089</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351518166424-12</Id><Title>The Incredible Shrinking President</Title><Msg>‘We’re going to have that person arrested and prosecuted that did the video,” said Hillary Clinton. No, not the person who made the video saying that voting for Barack Obama is like losing your virginity to a really cool guy. I’ll get to that in a moment. But Secretary Clinton was talking about the fellow who made the supposedly Islamophobic video that supposedly set off the sacking of the Benghazi consulate. And, indeed, she did “have that person arrested.” By happy coincidence, his bail hearing has been set for three days after the election, by which time he will have served his purpose. These two videos — the Islamophobic one and the Obamosexual one — bookend the remarkable but wholly deserved collapse of the president’s reelection campaign. You’ll recall that a near-month-long attempt to blame an obscure YouTube video for the murder of four Americans and the destruction of U.S. sovereign territory climaxed in the vice-presidential debate with Joe Biden’s bald assertion that the administration had been going on the best intelligence it had at the time. By then, it had been confirmed that there never had been any protest against the video, and that the Obama line that Benghazi had been a spontaneous movie review that just got a little out of hand was utterly false. The only remaining question was whether the administration had knowingly lied or was merely innocently stupid. The innocent-stupidity line became harder to maintain this week after Fox News obtained State Department e-mails revealing that shortly after 4 p.m. Eastern, less than a half hour after the assault in Benghazi began, the White House situation room knew the exact nature of it. We also learned that, in those first moments of the attack, a request for military back-up was made by U.S. staff on the ground but was denied by Washington. It had planes and special forces less than 500 miles away in southern Italy — or about the same distance as Washington to Boston. They could have been there in less than two hours. Yet the commander-in-chief declined to give the order. So Glen Doherty and Tyrone Woods fought all night against overwhelming odds, and died on a rooftop in a benighted jihadist hellhole while Obama retired early to rest up before his big Vegas campaign stop. “Within minutes of the first bullet being fired the White House knew these heroes would be slaughtered if immediate air support was denied,” said Ty Woods’s father, Charles. “In less than an hour, the perimeters could have been secured and American lives could have been saved. After seven hours fighting numerically superior forces, my son’s life was sacrificed because of the White House’s decision.” Why would Obama and Biden do such a thing? Because to launch a military operation against an al-Qaeda affiliate on the anniversary of 9/11 would have exposed the hollowness of their boast through convention week and the days thereafter — that Osama was dead and al-Qaeda was finished. And so Ty Woods, Glen Doherty, Sean Smith, and Chris Stevens were left to die, and a decision taken to blame an entirely irrelevant video and, as Secretary Clinton threatened, “have that person arrested.” And, in the weeks that followed, the government of the United States lied to its own citizens as thoroughly and energetically as any totalitarian state, complete with the midnight knock on the door from not-so-secret policemen sent to haul the designated fall-guy into custody. This goes far beyond the instinctive secretiveness to which even democratic governments are prone. The Obama administration created a wholly fictional story line, and devoted its full resources to maintaining it. I understand why Mitt Romney chose not to pursue this line of argument in the final debate. The voters who will determine this election are those who voted for Obama four years ago and this time round either switch to the other fellow or sit on their hands. In electoral terms, it’s probably prudent of Mitt not to rub their faces in their 2008 votes. Nevertheless, when the president and other prominent officials stand by as four Americans die and then abuse their sacrifice as contemptuously as this administration did, decency requires that they be voted out of office as an act of urgent political hygiene. At the photo-op staged for the returning caskets, Obama et al. seem to have been too focused on their campaign needs to observe even the minimal courtesies. Charles Woods says that at the ceremony Joe Biden strolled over to him and by way of condolence said in a “loud and boisterous” voice, “Did your son always have balls the size of cue balls?” One assumes charitably that the vice president is acknowledging in his own inept and blundering way the remarkable courage of a man called upon to die for his country on some worthless sod halfway across the planet. But the near-parodic locker-room coarseness is grotesque both in its inaptness and in its lack of basic human feeling for a bereaved family forced to grieve in public and as crowd-scene extras to the political bigshot. Just about the only formal responsibility a vice president has is to attend funerals without embarrassing his country. And this preening buffoon of pseudo-blue-collar faux-machismo couldn’t even manage that. But a funny thing happened over the next six weeks: Obama’s own cue balls shriveled. Biden had offered up a deft campaign slogan encompassing both domestic and foreign policy: “Osama’s dead and General Motors is alive.” But, as the al-Qaeda connections to Benghazi dribbled out leak by leak, the “Osama’s dead” became a problematic boast and, left to stand alone, the General Motors line was even less credible. Avoiding the economy and foreign affairs, Obama fell back on Big Bird, and binders, and bayonets, just to name the “B”s in his bonnet. At the second presidential debate, he name-checked Planned Parenthood, the General Motors of the American abortion industry, half a dozen times, desperate to preserve his so-called gender gap. Yet oddly enough, the more furiously Obama and Biden have waved their binders and talked up Sandra Fluke, the more his supposed lead among women has withered away. So now he needs to enthuse the young, who turned out in such numbers for him last time. Hence, the official campaign video (plagiarized from Vladimir Putin of all people) explaining that voting for Obama is like having sex. The saddest thing about that claim is that, for liberals, it may well be true. Both videos — the one faking Obamagasm and the one faking a Benghazi pretext — exemplify the wretched shrinkage that befalls those unable to conceive of anything except in the most self-servingly political terms. Both, in different ways, exemplify why Obama and Biden are unfit for office. One video testifies to a horrible murderous lie at the heart of a head of state’s most solemn responsibility, the other to the glib shallow narcissism of a pop-culture presidency, right down to the numbing relentless peer pressure: C’mon, all the cool kids are doing it; why be the last hold-out? If voting for Obama is like the first time you have sex, it’s very difficult to lose your virginity twice. A flailing, pitiful campaign has now adopted Queen Victoria’s supposed wedding advice to her daughter: “Lie back and think of England.” Lie back and think of America. And then get up and get dressed. Who wants to sleep with a $16 trillion broke loser twice? Mark Steyn</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351518166424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:42:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351518773588-13</Id><Title>Academia Getting More Liberaler and more liberaler</Title><Msg>While it’s no secret that most college professors lean to the left, even more academics self-identity as “far left” or “liberal” today than did four years ago, a new survey found. The survey, released by the Higher Education Research Institute at UCLA, asked 23,000 faculty members at 400 different universities to answer a variety of questions, including one about their political leanings. Respondents could identify as either far left, liberal, middle of the road, conservative, or far right. Some 12.4 percent of respondents chose far left. Another 50.3 percent identified as liberal. Just 11.5 and 0.4 percent of respondents indicated they were conservative or far right, respectively. Is it any wonder that Socialized government education is turning out students who think mores of the founders of modern communism than they do of America's founding fathers?......or that they will vote for candidates promoting Marxist policies......like Obama.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351518773588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:52:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351519047430-14</Id><Title>Most Transparent President in History twice refused to answer questions.......</Title><Msg>In an interview with a Denver TV reporter Friday, Obama twice refused to answer questions as to whether the Americans under siege in Benghazi were denied requests for help.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351519047430</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351519580618-15</Id><Title>From a Democrat: Why I’m voting for Mitt Romney.</Title><Msg>Each time I mention that I voted for Barack Obama in 2008, I get a blast from some who didn’t. “How could you be so dumb?” is a typical response to my confession. It is certainly a confession — of error. Obama fooled me once, but not twice. I’m voting for Mitt Romney Nov. 6th. To understand why I’m switching, it helps to understand why I backed Obama four years ago. I am a Democrat, but vote as an independent. I see people, not parties, so Obama’s label played no role. My choice involved a simple calculation. Would John McCain or Obama be more likely to forge a consensus on big issues? America was dangerously polarized, and unable to act in ways that even 60 percent of the public could support. History shows that paralysis leads to disaster. The war on terror was falling out of favor, despite the continuing threat. Good ideas were getting thrown out with the bad and Republicans had squandered the chance to govern. When the financial crisis hit, McCain stumbled. He wanted to postpone a debate and rushed back to Washington — but had nothing to say or do. Obama kept silent and followed the lead of congressional Democrats. While not exactly great statesmanship, he at least looked steady. McCain, a genuine American hero, often revealed his maverick streak, his choice of Sarah Palin being Exhibit A. Despite doubts about her readiness, I found myself defending her against the vicious attacks from the left, especially by women. McCain was my real problem. Mavericks make good whistleblowers and lousy CEOs. Upsetting the apple cart is not a qualification for the Oval Office. Obama’s soaring rhetoric enticed me at first, and I agreed that a restoration of the Clinton presidency would be a bad idea. Still, I got a jolt of Messiah Alert when he said his rise marked the moment “when the planet began to heal.” Where he totally fooled me was his claim to be a pragmatist, not an ideologue. He spoke of uniting the country and I believed he was capable and sincere. That he won 70 million votes and more than two-thirds of the Electoral College spoke to his appeal. He failed as president because he is incompetent, dishonest and not interested in the actual work of governing. His statist policies helped consign millions of Americans to a lower standard of living and his odious class warfare further divided the nation. He had no intention of uniting the country — it was his Big Lie. I don’t hate him. But I sure as hell don’t trust him. As for the desperate charge that opposition to Obama makes me a racist, let me note that he was black when I voted for him. By MICHAEL GOODWIN</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351519580618</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351520607059-16</Id><Title>Benghazi - Was it Incompetence, a Coverup or Both?</Title><Msg>"You know, this administration is very good at touting and giving all the details like when they got Bin Laden. But now, we know that there were tapes, recordings inside the consulate during this fight, and they've gotten—they came—the F.B.I. finally got in and took those, and now they're classified as "top secret." Why would they be top secret? So the president went on various shows, despite what he said he said in the Rose Garden, about terrorist acts, he went on several programs, including "The View" including "Letterman" including before the U.N., where he continued to refer, days later, many days later, to this as a spontaneous demonstration because of a hateful video. We know that is patently false. What did the president know? When did he know it? And what did he do about it? McCain said for "literally days and days" the White House "told the American people something that had no basis in fact whatsoever." Newt Gingrich, on ABC's This Week: But the bigger issue is, whether it’s unemployment or it is what happened in Benghazi, where we’ve had this strange situation over the weekend that the Secretary of Defense apparently refused to obey the President’s order, if the president is telling the truth and he actually instructed his assistants to get aid to Benghazi, we're now being told that the Secretary of Defense canceled that. And I think these kinds of things all drag down the Obama campaign. Ohio senator Rob Portman talked on Fox News Sunday about a "shocking breakdown" with regard to the Obama administration's response: This is not about politics. This is about a huge national security issue that affects all of us and there was a shocking breakdown, operationally, not to have the security there in the first place. And then not to respond to these guys, in their pleas for help for 7 hours, during a firefight. It’s unbelievable and now, we are hearing that the president of the United States, based on his own words, issued a directive immediately after he found out about the firefight, saying that he wanted to be sure those people on the ground were safe and they were getting what they needed. It didn't happen. This means either that the president's order was not followed, which would be a breakdown in terms of the White House procedure, or, it means the order wasn’t issued. We need to find out about this, it is not about politics, it is a very serious situation. After the fact, of course, there’s also been a lot of confusion about what happened and why it happened. Here's Senator Ron Johnson of Wisconsin, also on Fox News Sunday: Chris, the American people have the right to know. And that is what they are demanding here in Wisconsin. I mean, let's face it. What was the president doing during those 7 hours? Did he give that directive? Or didn't he? Did Leon Panetta directly defy his directive? I mean, what happened? Who sent out, who sent Ambassador Rice out five days later when they knew it was a terrorist attack, that it was pre-planned, sent her out on the Sunday talk shows to say that in fact this was a spontaneous reaction to of course the video? Virginia governor Bob McDonnell, on CNN's State of the Union: The mishandling of the situation in Benghazi. No answers, no transparency, 45 days after the fact is a great concern. Either the president gave an order that was disobeyed by the Secretary of Defense to provide support in Benghazi or he didn't, and I think people want answers before this election on that, so that's what's going to determine the outcome. And Republican National Committee chairman Reince Priebus on CNN: There are two things people are talking about. They’re talking about the economy, and they're talking about what happened in Benghazi. Why after a cry for help to Leon Panetta and after the President gave a directive to protect – he claims he gave a correct directive to protect those people Panetta got a cry for help. Panetta now claims that he didn't – he told the personnel to stand down. So either the President didn't give the directive or the president isn't being truthful or perhaps Leon Panetta acted as commander in chief. That’s what -- this is the subject right now that people are talking about, and the economy. On NBC's Meet the Press, Carly Fiorina fought back against Obama's latest "trust" attack on Mitt Romney by turning the question into one on Libya: On the issue of trust, what is going on with regard to Libya? I mean here we have an extraordinary thing where the President comes out on Friday and says I directed that everything possible should be done to aid our embassy under attack. That attack went on for seven hours, we now know that Secretary Of Defense saying he denied requests for help over that seven hours. Where is the leadership? But it's a trust issue, it’s a trust issue.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351520607059</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:23:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351521096593-17</Id><Title>What Happens When Governments Raise Taxes on Businesses</Title><Msg>For the latest tutorial on lousy tax policy, cast your eyes down—way down—to Australia, where the country's windfall mining tax has produced a gusher of . . . zero revenue in its first three months. Julia Gillard's Labor-led government projected that its "minerals resource rent tax" on large iron-ore and coal companies (effective rate: 22.5%) would raise 10.6 billion Australian dollars over three years and allow Canberra to redistribute the gains of the country's China-fueled mining boom. The money was also supposed to help dig Australia out of a budget deficit that Ms. Gillard and her predecessor, Kevin Rudd, created through a spending spree. When questioned in March about the wisdom of such a levy as China's growth was slowing, Ms. Gillard responded, "as a nation we're going to be earning a lot out of our mineral wealth. The question is should we share it or should we give it to a privileged few?" This is the kind of crack economics that kept Australia in the league of poor democracies until the Labor Party moved to the center and liberalized trade and investment in the 1980s and 1990s. Now the economy is decelerating, mining company profits are declining, investment is going elsewhere, and there's less revenue for Canberra to seize. Ms. Gillard and Treasurer Wayne Swan are walking back their revenue projections and may have trouble balancing the federal government books. This is what happens when government tries to raid business to fill a budget hole, rather than lower taxes to promote economic growth and rake in more revenue the easy way. WSJ</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351521096593</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:31:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351521251663-18</Id><Title>What kind of logic is this?</Title><Msg>Americans defending themselves from attackers in Benghazi and the White House refusing to send help until they knew exactly who they were. Why not join the battle and ask question later? Are enemies of the United States considered enemies no matter who they are.? Man, they were shooting at us, what else do you want to know? Their photo IDs?</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1351521251663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:34:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351521504552-19</Id><Title>Without government healthcare spending, America’s debt would be almost non-existent.</Title><Msg>(via Peter Suderman): As a thought experiment, let’s suppose that medical expenditures had been self-financed since the inception of government health care in the 1960s. What would our debt and deficit look like today? To answer this question, I simply added the medical care expenditure deficit back into the total government deficit. The result is depicted in [the figure below[ and is astounding (at least to me). Outside of medical expenditures and revenues, the Federal government sometimes ran a surplus and sometimes ran a deficit from 1966 until 1980. Starting in 1980, and lasting until 1994, the government consistently ran a deficit outside of medical spending, but from 1995 until 2010, it consistently ran a surplus. In 1994, the cumulative excess spending would have reached a bit over $1 trillion. But by 1999, debt due to sources other than medical spending would have been completely eliminated by surpluses! The government wouldn’t have needed to borrow again until 2011. Government has long promoted health insurance, and health care, as a third-party responsibility for Americans. Most Americans aren’t the direct customer for their health care. The bills go to their insurance companies. And most Americans aren’t the direct customer for their health insurance policies either. Employers provide health insurance for the bulk of Americans, with government coming in second. This disconnect between Americans and their health insurance/health care is what is creating the health care cost bubble that is, in turn, clearly the primary driver of US national debt. We need to get the government out of health care. I’d only add that the unfunded liabilities represented by Social Security, which is already obligated to pay more in benefits than it is receiving in tax payments and is being forced to rely on a trust fund that was long ago replaced by government bonds, are significant as well though don’t show up in the budget.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351521504552</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:38:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351522185899-20</Id><Topic><Title>what the spectre gunship could have done</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1351305950401</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 22:45:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It only takes one stray to take out an innocent in the that zone" - As opposed to doing NOTHING and letting them get killed by the attackers ANYWAY. Maybe that same rule could be applied to a person's house when armed, gun blazing burglers are invading and trying to break in; the police "stand down" so as to ensure that one of their own bullets don't kill the innocent occuupants FIRST.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351522185899</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:49:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351522422245-21</Id><Topic><Title>From a Democrat: Why I’m voting for Mitt Romney.</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351519580618</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No Democrat in the right mind would vote for Mitt Romney. What a bunch &amp;*#*&amp;%@#Q #$%$!</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1351522422245</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351523087275-22</Id><Title>Ohio: Romney 50%, Obama 48%</Title><Msg>The race for Ohio’s Electoral College votes remains very close, but now Mitt Romney now has a two-point advantage. The latest Rasmussen Reports telephone survey of Likely Ohio Voters shows Romney with 50% support to President Obama’s 48%. One percent (1%) likes some other candidate, while another one percent (1%) remains undecided.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351523087275</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 11:04:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351523624127-23</Id><Topic><Title>From a Democrat: Why I’m voting for Mitt Romney.</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351519580618</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good for you! McCain would have been a worse choice than Obama, but not by much. Obama doesn't have only one big lie. He has many.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1351523624127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 11:13:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351524991461-24</Id><Title>The Pirate Scowl "Obama" is listing badly</Title><Msg>Nationally: Romney 51%, Obama 46% Ohio: Romney 50%, Obama 48% Swing State Tracking: Romney 50%, Obama 46% North Carolina: Romney 52%, Obama 46% Wisconsin Senate: Thompson (R) 48%, Baldwin (D) 47% 54% Favor Repeal of Obama’s Health Care Law 60% Say Federal Government Does Not Have the Consent of the Governed</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351524991461</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 11:36:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351528508581-25</Id><Title>Obama vs. Romney Electoral Map</Title><Msg>Obama vs. Romney Electoral Our latest estimate has Obama at 277 electoral votes and Romney at 206. ... hundreds of state-wide and national opinion polls</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351528508581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 12:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351529619439-26</Id><Topic><Title>Without government healthcare spending, America’s debt would be almost non-existent.</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351521504552</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:38:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have had competition by insurance companies since the 1600's. It never lowered the premiums before. So that is a paper lion arguement that can't be sustained.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351529619439</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 12:53:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351529718275-27</Id><Title>Hi! I'm not Dik Hertz</Title><Msg>My guy is ahead nationally, in swing states, in Florida, in Ohio and with electoral count. As usual the Dik has his head in the sand, his toes in a pan with lilac scented bubble bath and he's whining because he doesn't have enough money for a beer. Life is good.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351529718275</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 12:55:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351530146532-28</Id><Topic><Title>Without government healthcare spending, America’s debt would be almost non-existent.</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351521504552</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:38:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nonsense burger_barn......only a communist still believes the fantasy that competition doesn't keep prices lower that monopolies. In what socialized government school were you educated.......er indoctrinated?</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351530146532</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351531041865-29</Id><Topic><Title>From a Democrat: Why I’m voting for Mitt Romney.</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351519580618</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry you have changed, but I'll forgive you. Healthcare is not going away. Either we pay for it by sharing or we go broke. The hospitals cannot do it alone, going to the Er. is the most expensive way to deliver health care and will drive many hospitals out of business. Good luck.</Msg><Username>jevanst2003</Username><Timestamp>1351531041865</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351531400525-30</Id><Topic><Title>Ann Coulter 'Retard' Remark Unconscionable</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351495806485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 03:30:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What makes you think "people" like Coulter have a conscience?</Msg><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1351531400525</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:23:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351531757536-31</Id><Topic><Title>What kind of logic is this?</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1351521251663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:34:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Man, they were shooting at us, what else do you want to know? Their photo IDs?" As long as the liberals are in charge, we are not even allowed to ask for Photo IDs. That would be terrorist suppression. Can't have that.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351531757536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:29:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351532160721-32</Id><Topic><Title>From a Democrat: Why I’m voting for Mitt Romney.</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351519580618</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>McCain might have been a hero during the Viet Nam era, but for the last 20 years he has morphed into a senile Puke who should have retired from the Senate years ago.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1351532160721</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:36:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351532328850-33</Id><Topic><Title>From a Democrat: Why I’m voting for Mitt Romney.</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351519580618</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Harry, care to comment on the CBO analysis that says that Romney's economic plan is mathematically #$%$?</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1351532328850</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:38:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351533449812-34</Id><Topic><Title>Ann Coulter 'Retard' Remark Unconscionable</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351495806485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 03:30:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We should be more understanding! Nobody knows more about the issues associated with being a retard than a typical lefty freak. If they want to be refered to as #$%$, then we should listen and try to understand. They have an unpleasant life to live and we shouldn't add to their burden.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1351533449812</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:57:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351533755768-35</Id><Title>Obama Sacrificed 4 Americans Lifes for Political Gain</Title><Msg>Not only should he be impeached, he should be tried for the murder of the four Americans.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351533755768</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:02:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351534370167-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Is Right</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351533671266</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:01:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you would "clear" you glasses you would relize that the rich do pay more taxes. The fact is they (the rich) pay the majority of the taxes collected while the lower and middle class for the most part pay no Federal taxes. Amazing how those who pay no taxes want those who do to pay more. Fairness, you say?</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351534370167</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:12:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351534408437-37</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing loses federal labor case in South Carolina</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1351457129635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 16:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CEO Jim McNerney noted Wednesday that the company is facing increased competition and other pressures. He's reaching out key suppliers to work on costs. However, “this is not a matter of stealing margin from our partners,” McNerney said Right Jim , I know let's call it being a "team player" and if in your direct talk to your suppliers , if they don't agree then you can pull the contract and move to another location, it is all their choice. BTW how is that excessive pay package working for you ? so far Total Compensation 5-Year Compensation $65.55 mil</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1351534408437</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:13:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351534885352-38</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing loses federal labor case in South Carolina</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1351457129635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 16:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just a matter of time, I always have said 5-7 years is all it would take for SC to go to union shop.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351534885352</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351534966869-39</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Sacrificed 4 Americans Lifes for Political Gain</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351533755768</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:02:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you are giving Bush and Cheney a free pass?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351534966869</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:22:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351536079861-40</Id><Title>The President doesn't owe you an Explanation!</Title><Msg>my dear Republicans, The US President doesn't owe you an Explanation for Anything.... fyi - there are a set of laws that we follow here in the USA... its called a US Constitution... please try to keep up...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351536079861</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351536441095-41</Id><Topic><Title>Obama vs. Romney Electoral Map</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351528508581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 12:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama 280</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351536441095</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:47:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351536723200-42</Id><Title>Message for Obama Supporters.</Title><Msg>Obama is a Marxist and there is more than enough evidence to support this fact. He is a statist and a collectivist and his policies reflect that. Obama has shown over and over again he will throw anyone under the bus if they get in his way of accumulating more and more power....his preacher of 20 years, his good friends like Bill Ayers, even his Grand mother. This is not a new mentality, it is the mentality of most Marxists. It is the same mentality that caused communist leaders in the USSR to kill more than 20 million of their own countrymen, it is the same mentality that caused Che Guevara and Fidel Castro to murder more than 6 million Cubans and it is the same mentality that caused Mao to kill more than 90 million of his fellow countrymen. Many of those dead souls thought that it was “cool” to have “change” that fed off of poverty, class warfare, hatred, jealousy and envy. Only too late, did they discover the “cool guys” offering change, were far worse than they bargained for. The really shocked ones were the ones that thought they were safe because they were in with the “cool guys” and part of the change force. These were the useful idiots of which Stalin spoke. But their property was taken too and their relatives were killed and sent to gulags too. And when these “useful idots” objected they were killed too. They were simply a means to an end with dictatorial totalitarianism being the end. Obama supporters don’t think they won’t come for you, if you get in their way. And don’t think the good guys who will have the task of taking back the country from these animals will have any sympathy you who empowered the elitists who want to rule your lives. I know, I grew up in Russia and came to this country 48 years ago. Ask any immigrant from a communist country and they will tell you the same thing. Those of us who came from such environment see the same thing happening here. Just watch how violent, vulgar and uncivilized Obama supporters are getting. Get rid of this guy and the people who embrace the Marxist ideology before it’s too late.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351536723200</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351536749339-43</Id><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Angry Democrat Pat Caddell Condemns 'No Honor' Media and Obama Discussing Benghazi, Pat Caddell says the press has "been in the tank on this in a way I've never seen... I am appalled right now. This White House, this President, this Vice President, this Secretary of State, all of them, are willing apparently to dishonor themselves and this country for the cheap prospect of getting reelected...willing to cover up and lie. The worst thing is the very people who are supposed to protect the American people with the truth - the leading mainstream media...they have become a threat, a fundamental threat to American democracy and the enemies of the American people... these people have no honor... cover-up is too nice of a word..." Bigger than Watergate: Proof that the President is Lying about Benghazi? Having a back and forth with a former legendary Delta operator. Here is the gist of what he is implying: The news is breaking today but there is a small bit that is being overlooked. According to the statements from Fox News: The security officer had a laser on the target that was firing and repeatedly requested back-up support from a Specter gunship, which is commonly used by U.S. Special Operations forces to provide support to Special Operations teams on the ground involved in intense firefights. The fighting at the CIA annex went on for more than four hours — enough time for any planes based in Sigonella Air base, just 480 miles away, to arrive. Fox News has also learned that two separate Tier One Special operations forces were told to wait, among them Delta Force operators. Everyone is reporting this but they are missing a key point. From the retired Delta operator: EXCLUSIVE: CIA operators were denied request for help during Benghazi attack, sources say 'Stand Down': U.S. Had Two Drones, AC-130 Gunship, and Targets Painted in Benghazi BOMBSHELL: US Security Forces Would Not Have Been Painting Targets on Ground Unless There Was Air Support Overhead – But White House Called It Off CIA Team Was Ordered Not to Help US Embassy Staff in Benghazi READ ALL about IT Where "The REAL News Matters"!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351538008530-44</Id><Title>dividend info</Title><Msg>CHICAGO, Oct. 29, 2012 /PRNewswire/ -- Boeing [NYSE: BA] Chairman, President and Chief Executive Officer Jim McNerney reports that the board of directors declared a regular quarterly dividend of forty-four (44) cents per share. The dividend is payable December 7, 2012, to shareholders of record as of November 9, 2012.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351538008530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:13:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351538056800-45</Id><Topic><Title>The Most Important Message Ever To My Fellow Obama Supporters</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351537809392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:10:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for posting I had missed the article</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351538056800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:14:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351538482499-46</Id><Topic><Title>The Most Important Message Ever To My Fellow Obama Supporters</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351537809392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:10:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's Only 8 Days LEFT for THE Worst "LIBERAL" to EVER Occupy the WH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! I Wonder who Obama is going to Pardon Before Leaving the WH and Filing for "*****Unemployment*****"!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351538482499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:21:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351538962011-47</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>making crap up. Oh wait. I forgot. That's what you and Fox News do. Never mind.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351538962011</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:29:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351539564230-48</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>KEEP Drinking the "Kool-Aid" Fool while Your "***Man Child***" make Like Jimmy(I Like Peanuts)Carter and Loses his BUTT next Tuesday!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Those Articles are from Multiple National Media Sources!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351539564230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:39:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351539933523-49</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Angry """***Democrat***""" Pat Caddell Condemns 'No Honor' Media and Obama Cut this Headline and WATCH the Fricking Video FOOL!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! I Called it a "Cover UP" before nearly Anyone in the Press began to Question what was the ""Truth""!!!!!!!!!!!!! Benghazi Libya GOT It Right Again!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Oct. 7th America, Obama and HILLARY are LYING their FRICKING #$%$ Off about the "***MURDER***" of Ambassador Stevens!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351539933523</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351539964685-50</Id><Title>Report: Further Evidence of Holder's Fast and Furious Coverup</Title><Msg>New Report: Holder Planned to Attend Fast and Furious Press Conference Prior to Border Agent Murder House Oversight Committee Chairman Darrell Issa and Ranking Member of the Senate Judiciary Committee Charles Grassley have just released another report, in a series of three, about Operation Fast and Furious. The latest report details failures by and knowledge of Department of Justice officials involved in the fatal scandal. The first report was released in July and a third report is expected in the next few weeks. The most recent report contains damning information and documentation showing Attorney General Eric Holder's Deputy Chief of Staff Monty Wilkinson and DOJ Official Patrick Cunningham discussing plans for Holder to participate a press conference announcing the "take-down" or the end of Operation Fast and Furious before Border Patrol Agent Brian Terry was killed on December 15, 2010. Guns from the Fast and Furious program were left at Terry's murder scene. Holder claims he didn't know about Operation Fast and Furious until May of 2011. The email below was sent on December 14, 2010 at 12:28 pm, just 12 hours before Terry's murder.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351539964685</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351540143353-51</Id><Title>Unreal: Labor Department May Delay Jobs Report Until After Election</Title><Msg>The U.S. Labor Department on Monday said it hasn’t made a decision yet on whether to delay Friday’s October jobs report, the final reading on the labor market before next week’s federal elections. A Labor official said the agency will #$%$ the schedule for all its data releases this week when the “weather emergency” is over. Labor is scheduled to release the employment report on Friday, third quarter employment costs on Wednesday and weekly jobless claims on Thursday. The U.S. Census Bureau also said it hasn’t made a decision on whether to delay economic reports it plans to release this week, including construction spending on Thursday and factory orders on Friday.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351540143353</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351540571108-52</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Further Evidence of Holder's Fast and Furious Coverup</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351539964685</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:46:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can Presidential pardons be given prior to being convicted?</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351540571108</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:56:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351543491892-53</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How come you folks were so silent about Americans being killed for 8 years under Bush? THOUSANDS OF THEM!!! trying to make it political hey? disgusting! and you folks once more prove what weasels you are.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351543491892</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:44:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351544419905-54</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I put your lame post on par with far lefties after 911 blaming President Bush for the attacks on the twin towers and pentagon, arm chair #$%$</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351544419905</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351545051266-55</Id><Topic><Title>Ann Coulter 'Retard' Remark Unconscionable</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351495806485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 03:30:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>King Lutefisk doesn't give a damn about anything but his money.</Msg><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1351545051266</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351546957824-56</Id><Title>book of mormon</Title><Msg>anyone who reads this..will understand why mormons are not christians..they are mormons....to call this christianity is a joke.......and this love of money to a point where even the church is into evading taxes....is a product of growing up angry in america...angry with the christians</Msg><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1351546957824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:42:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351547146864-57</Id><Topic><Title>book of mormon</Title><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1351546957824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:42:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but now there is more money to be made by pretending that smith did not refer to christian creeds as "abominations" and "devil cults"</Msg><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1351547146864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:45:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351548506294-58</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YO "Rock for BRAINS," OBL Attacked America and Hussein was Violating just about EVERY Accord to "HIS" Surrender after Gulf War I along with EVERY UN Resolution that Restricted his Development and Production of WMDs!!!!!!!!!!!!! Details you LIBERALS continue to Forget about!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Youtube...........Cut and Paste and DEAL with the FACTS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ""Democrats on Iraq + WMD's (Weapons of Mass Destruction)""</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351548506294</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:08:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351550780235-59</Id><Title>Haven't you right wing nut cases figured a way</Title><Msg>To blame Sandy on Obama?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1351550780235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:46:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351551124776-60</Id><Title>Let's Talk About Obama's Christian Faith</Title><Msg>Obama believes in killing innocent babies. Jeremiah Wright had fellowship with Louis Farrakhan. Obama thinks it's OK to lie for political purposes. Does Obama worship the same God that destroyed Sodom and Gomorrah?</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1351551124776</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:52:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351551231237-61</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Thanks to Obama, Americans DIED while Obama Campaigned to keep his JOB putting Himself ahead of the LIVES of Americans Working FOR HIM!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! McCain: Obama Might Be Conducting ‘Massive Cover-Up’ With Libya Attack</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351551231237</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351551247660-62</Id><Topic><Title>dividend info</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351538008530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:13:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>let me bumb this for my boy mrrstock</Msg><Username>mrstockdad54</Username><Timestamp>1351551247660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:54:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351551249203-63</Id><Topic><Title>Let's Talk About Obama's Christian Faith</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1351551124776</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:52:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney lies every single time he speaks so shut up about that, pal.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1351551249203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:54:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351552004551-64</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sincere apologies to a great musician, Albert Hammond. But I couldn't resist. (To the tune of "Free Electric Band" :-) My father was a gov'nor, he was a family man My mother works for charity whenever she can They were both good clean Americans who abided by the law And they both stuck up for liberty and they both backed the war My happiness was paid for when their checkbook they did ope For my summers in a summer camp and winters on the slopes My future in the system they planned and talked about But I gave it up for money and a numbered Swiss account. I went to school in hand-washed shirts with neatly ordered hair And the school was big and newly built and filled with light and air And the teacher taught us values that we had to learn to keep But he didn't seem to mind it if instead I went to sleep Then my father organized for me a college in the east But I headed off to France, for the baguettes and to preach My parents and my lecturers thought it a massive pain When I gave it up for money and to go to work for Bain. Well, they used to sit and speculate upon their son's career A lawyer or a doctor or a civil engineer Just give me bread and tax breaks, and the money I was leant 'Cause all I need is money and to be the president My father sent me money, and I spent it very fast On a girl I met in Provo in a social science class Yes, and we learned about her body, but her mind we didn't know Until deep rooted attitudes and morals began to show She wanted revolution to suport the weak and poor And I knew her well enough by now to clearly see the score She'd settle for socialism and a patch of common land So I gave her up for money and instead I married Ann.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351552004551</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 19:06:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351552448069-65</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Okay, you wanna play that game? Fine. Let's talk about 9/11. No, not the one in 2012, the original one, the one in 2001. Republicans held the majority in the House and Senate and a Republican occupied the White House. We all know what happened. All that to say, you and your Republican brethren are in no position to be saying jack sh#t about what happened in Libya. You guys are just trying to "make hay" because Obama stands a better chance of winning the election (i.e. more paths to 270 votes in the electoral college) than Romney. You guys are pathetic ... and apparently quite desperate.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351552448069</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 19:14:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351552453787-66</Id><Topic><Title>dividend info</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351538008530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:13:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just wondering if you have the deliveries for Boeing? FYI, Boeing has a production cycle number listed per month for all A/P lines, so why , foulmouther, do you waste bandwidth listing delivered planes? .This embellised information is not some kind of secret that the whole world does not already know about prior to your user comment , like the "floodgates of delivery" that is such a embellishement, the production per line is already known, it is a cycle of plane production per month rate! any ramp up is given by the company not a secret or a big deal. However you missed as usual and par for the coarse, the late and over budget delivery of all of the 747 and 787 airplanes, and yet you feel compelled to list the obvious cycle deliveries, exculding that all the 747 and 787 delivered are at a loss of revenue to the shareholders! The duopoly of failure to communicate any real information continues between you two Boeing ussers here, the part truth postings without the real deal for the shareholder, that is a unethical approach, foulmouther and mrstock it really is a very sad attempt to embellish the true picture of Boeing . the stock price is the acid test 65 to 75 and fail for 15 years now it went to 80 one time very briefly and then right back to 65 to 75 and has gone down to 55 in fact this stock can make a short investor more money than a long most of the time if you do day or swing trades or go with BAC or other better stocks</Msg><Username>mrstockdad54</Username><Timestamp>1351552453787</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 19:14:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351552839664-67</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Republican brethren are in no position to be saying jack sh#t about what happened in Libya."? REALLY? MAYBE, BUT ONLY IN YOUR DREAMS!!</Msg><Username>le_idiot_savant</Username><Timestamp>1351552839664</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 19:20:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351553264115-68</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Is Right</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351533671266</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:01:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like a good idea to me. Let's tax ourselves to prosperity, LOL.</Msg><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1351553264115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 19:27:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351553904420-69</Id><Title>I see a pattern developing</Title><Msg>Fast and Furious, Benghazigate, and now Obama's going to release unemployment figures after the elections and not before. What doesn't corrupt Obama have his fingers in? I'm sick to my stomach! It must be the Obamaflu!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351553904420</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 19:38:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351554531581-70</Id><Title>Damning Emails Link White House to Another Green Flop</Title><Msg>Just-revealed emails confirm that the Obama administration, and the president himself, have misled Americans about the White House's role in fast-tracking a $400 million "stimulus" loan guarantee to a politically-connected "green energy" firm. If you followed the Solyndra saga, this will come as no surprise to you -- nor will the fact that Obama has been spreading misinformation about his White House's culpability in the matter. Revealing Politics boils this scandal down into a digestible one minute clip, the crux of which is the smoking-gun email that directly contradicts Obama's smirking denial that "politics" had anything to do with Abound Solar's taxpayer-funded windfall: In emails unearthed by Colorado-based reporter Todd Shepard, one DOE official overseeing the loan program warns another that they'd better get the ball rolling on the Abound Solar taxpayer cash infusion: "You better let him know the WH wants to move Abound forward." The "him" appears to be a Treasury Department advisor connected to the process. The same initial DOE Senior Credit Advisor later refers to the White House's meddling as the "transaction pressure under which we are all now operating." See the raw emails here and here. Mary Katharine Ham puts this story into further context: Abound Solar, which counts major Obama bundler Pat Stryker among its early backers, is now under criminal investigation for misleading investors. It went bankrupt in mid-2012, leaving employees out of work and taxpayers with the bill. The company had gone through $70 million of a federal loan guarantee worth $400 million. It was supposed to create 1,500 permanent jobs, according to the president’s 2010 announcement of the loan. Say, were this company's balance sheets packed with red flags prior to taxpayer cash being doled out? You bet. Replace "Solyndra" with "Abound," and "George Kaiser" with "Pat Styker," and it looks as though we have another Washington-engineered, utterly corrupt "green jobs" failure. It doesn't take a great leap to suggest that this loan was all about politics. But at the very least, we know that Obama's contention on Denver television last week that the deal had "nothing to do" with political considerations is patently, verifably false. Parting thought: Guess what's one of the central elements of Obama's cobbled-together, last-minute second term "agenda." You guessed it -- more taxpayer-funded "green energy" adventurism. Which deep-pocketed Democrat donors would stand to benefit next time?</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1351554531581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 19:48:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351554596483-71</Id><Topic><Title>NATE SILVER: Obama's Odds Of Winning Have Now Surged Back To 75%</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351547504459</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:51:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two interesting new national polls today. Pew shows a 4 point Obama gain since their last poll, and GWU/Politico shows a 3 point shift to Obama. Sure looks like a loss of ROmentum.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1351554596483</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 19:49:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351555316845-72</Id><Topic><Title>The Most Important Message Ever To My Fellow Obama Supporters</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351537809392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:10:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1351555316845</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:01:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351555516940-73</Id><Topic><Title>NATE SILVER: Obama's Odds Of Winning Have Now Surged Back To 75%</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351547504459</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:51:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's lead is growing every second.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1351555516940</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:05:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351555642985-74</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Looks In Mirror, Spots Voter Fraud</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351553012357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 19:23:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hurting Little, Dik? As Romney Soars and Obama Plumments!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351555642985</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:07:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351555796312-75</Id><Topic><Title>NATE SILVER: Obama's Odds Of Winning Have Now Surged Back To 75%</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351547504459</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:51:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing "surging" right now is the tide. Not unlike avoiding the high tide by Sandy, by seeking higher ground, the nation needs to pull its collective pant legs up and step out what Obama has laid before its feet.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351555796312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:09:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351556727673-76</Id><Title>Warning stay at W seattle Hotel</Title><Msg>My friend come to visit me. He stay at W seattle Hotel rooms #2501. He put his valet on table. In his valet have $350. He went out. When he come back the room were clean but in his valet no wing and he lost $300. Couple month ago my other friend come visit me stay at W Seattle Hotel room # 2521. He put his watch on table. He go out to buy cup coffee. When he come back his watch gone. What out when you stay at W Seattle Hotel.</Msg><Username>helenburn</Username><Timestamp>1351556727673</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351556828264-77</Id><Title>Obama Sucks</Title><Msg>.....that is all.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1351556828264</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351556864659-78</Id><Topic><Title>This One Is Ours To Win</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351546686447</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:38:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Certainly Appears Obama Lost this One! Romney Soaring, Hussein Plummenting!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351556864659</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:27:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351556966636-79</Id><Title>Obama Worst President in American History</Title><Msg>....he said Obamacare was a higher priority than jobs.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1351556966636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:29:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351557280027-80</Id><Title>Romney Has it in the Bag</Title><Msg>...leads in all categories</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1351557280027</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:34:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351557426310-81</Id><Title>There Will be Weeping and Nashing of teeth by Democrats.....</Title><Msg>....on Nov. 6</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1351557426310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:37:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351557543282-82</Id><Topic><Title>book of mormon</Title><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1351546957824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:42:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hwar: You are a Religious Bigot!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351557543282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:39:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351557567282-83</Id><Topic><Title>This One Is Ours To Win</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351546686447</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:38:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great job Mr POTUS with helping all those Republican govenors with their disaster readiness. It was good to see Christie praise you. "Party hardy" Ginger</Msg><Username>vampyrr</Username><Timestamp>1351557567282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351557918979-84</Id><Topic><Title>There Will be Weeping and Nashing of teeth by Democrats.....</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1351557426310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:37:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dik and his Panicking Aliases are Already Weeping and Nashing Their Collective Teeth</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351557918979</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:45:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351558042432-85</Id><Topic><Title>book of mormon</Title><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1351546957824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:42:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I was an evangelical I would not vote for a Mormon. I would just stay home on election day or vote for the other guy - President O'Bama.</Msg><Username>vampyrr</Username><Timestamp>1351558042432</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:47:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351558084617-86</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill(I Like Cigars with my Interns)Clinton had 3 Opportunities to takeout OBL and "*****FAILED*****" as Commander in Chief to Order the HIT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! 9/11 Belongs to Clinton not Bush!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351558084617</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:48:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351558194527-87</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm Dick Hertz...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351557766866</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:42:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, Dik, you Nitwit, Romney Leading in Almost All Swing Streets and Getting Stronger as Hussein Weakens.... PS: We Can Care Less Who You Are!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351558194527</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:49:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351558250720-88</Id><Topic><Title>There Will be Weeping and Nashing of teeth by Democrats.....</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1351557426310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:37:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(Weeping) Tears of joy and (nashing of teeth) #$%$ smiles Party hardy Ginger</Msg><Username>vampyrr</Username><Timestamp>1351558250720</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:50:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351558370920-89</Id><Topic><Title>Billy Joel the nations musical leader supports Obama on Every Principle</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351558279074</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:51:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shocked, we are Just Shocked....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351558370920</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:52:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351558394656-90</Id><Topic><Title>Billy Graham the nations spiritual leader supports Romney on Biblical Principle and has posted this support in the WSJ</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351558101276</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:48:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that old fart still sane</Msg><Username>vampyrr</Username><Timestamp>1351558394656</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:53:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351558641932-91</Id><Title>Romney pins all his hopes</Title><Msg>for Ohio on his continuing LIE that Jeep is movings its production offshore. No character. No hope. Change back to the old days.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351558641932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:57:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351558714356-92</Id><Topic><Title>I Must Admit To You That Republicans Have Discipline</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351558571035</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:56:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Making Fun of Over Weight Peope, eh? Dik, You are a Prejustice Fool! Michael Moore Anyone?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351558714356</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:58:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351558930885-93</Id><Topic><Title>Romney pins all his hopes</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351558641932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:57:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny as it is the Obama Down Playing the Importance of Ohio as Romney Takes the Lead in Ohio! Dik, You are Behind the News Curve!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351558930885</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 21:02:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351562386108-94</Id><Topic><Title>I Must Admit To You That Republicans Have Discipline</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351558571035</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:56:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least Christie is doing his part in trying to help Hostess out of bankruptcy plus it makes a job for a truck driver.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351562386108</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 21:59:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351563091024-95</Id><Topic><Title>Haven't you right wing nut cases figured a way</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1351550780235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:46:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wall Street/DOW flatlined. Obama gets what he wanted............at least for a day or two.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351563091024</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:11:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351563145096-96</Id><Topic><Title>Billy Graham the nations spiritual leader supports Romney on Biblical Principle and has posted this support in the WSJ</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351558101276</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:48:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Greg/checkn/max/jane/tommy Little or no skill with which to ply a meaningful trade, marginal literacy, homophobe, scared spitless by anybody not exactly his "type," susceptible to lies simply repeated, virtually zero prospects for a better life. Must really be miserable inside that "life." A typical Republican voter.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1351563145096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:12:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351563877981-97</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Peedrool lives! Last time he was this excited it was right after the bin Laden raid. Peedrool's air raid theme: OBAMA LOSES HELICOPTER. Welcome back, Peedrool. Or not.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1351563877981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:24:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351563935349-98</Id><Topic><Title>I Must Admit To You That Republicans Have Discipline</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351558571035</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:56:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have long suspected that the Dik was Genna but not after this comment. Geez, if I had made such a remark about a fat guy he would be on me like he goes after a school bus full of white kids thinking it is a big Hostess Twinkie.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351563935349</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:25:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351564021168-99</Id><Topic><Title>The Plus Side of SANDY!!</Title><Username>locost7777</Username><Timestamp>1351562081624</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 21:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney has a chance to best Reagan's 49 state victory over Mondale by eight states ! Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351564021168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351569132377-100</Id><Title>Save the Wutang</Title><Msg>Wu - I heard NY is dark and you might be sitting around with no NBC to get your lib talking points and I feel for you dude, Just remember you are only 12 meals away from your peace &amp; love, vegetarian lib neighbor busting your skull for the last can of Spam in your kitchen. I would send you a slurpy but your nanny lib mayor has outlawed them. Maybe you can use the down time to think of ways that Bush caused this storm to happen and I will leave you with the words of your hero Obama who declared in a June 8, 2008 speech, that his presidency will be “the moment when the rise of the oceans began to slow and our planet began to heal.”</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1351569132377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 23:52:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351569334149-101</Id><Topic><Title>Ann Coulter 'Retard' Remark Unconscionable</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351495806485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 03:30:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well the fact that he is working as opposed to watching Judge Judy reruns &amp; cashing welfare checks makes it probable he isn't a lib</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1351569334149</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 23:55:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>