<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348805246222-1</Id><Topic><Title>Everett seeks branch campus from WSU, not UW</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1348775900372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:58:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pretty sure its right.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1348805246222</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 00:07:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348805693453-2</Id><Topic><Title>Al Queda strikes our embassy</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348782407537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harry, There is only one possibility for Obama to not actually be lying, as follows: First, he has concocted his own version of truth with his preconceived notions. Normally, we call that delusional. Second, he has not received the daily intelligence briefing in so long (and especially recently) that he was not actually aware that al Qaeda was a threat to our embassy in Libya. Third, he simply does not care. All three would have to be true for him to not be a liar. Either way, he needs to go. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1348805693453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 00:14:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348806112661-3</Id><Title>Airbus lands safely</Title><Msg>tis a miracle . It was a miracle on Runway 31L. Frightened passengers braced for a crash landing at Kennedy Airport today when the nose gear failed on their flight from Rio de Janeiro. But the gear on the Airbus A330 amazingly locked into the correct position as the plane was just 50 feet above the runway. “It was like the hand of God turned the wheel,” said a Port Authority rescuer who was part of the disaster response crew put in place for the incident. ..</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1348806112661</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 00:21:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348809198855-4</Id><Topic><Title>Everett seeks branch campus from WSU, not UW</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1348775900372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:58:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh boy. Are you actually going to start this wild paranoia again? You must be a right-fringer -- you want so much to drag us backward.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1348809198855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 01:13:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348814494251-5</Id><Topic><Title>Why will Liberals vote for more debt?????</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348779129874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:52:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WELL SAID!</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1348814494251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 02:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348815838306-6</Id><Title>Obama ahead of Willard by 56.2 percent points on Intrade</Title><Msg>Awesome! Willtard, pack your bags. And take Ryan with you leave -- we never want to see either of you ever again.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1348815838306</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 03:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348815847740-7</Id><Title>Obama ahead of Willard by 56.2 percent points on Intrade</Title><Msg>Awesome! Willtard, pack your bags. And take Ryan with you when you leave -- we never want to see either of you ever again.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1348815847740</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 03:04:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348817048293-8</Id><Topic><Title>Why will Liberals vote for more debt?????</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348779129874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:52:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for demonstrating so clearly again that the right wing has no arguments whatsoever, unless they make up little stories like yours, creating strawman demons that bounce back and forth in the RWNJ echo chamber until you all believe the specious crap. Guess you learned that MO from the most over-rated president in US history, Ronnie Raygun. Fortunately the majority of Americans sees through your pathetic lies.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1348817048293</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 03:24:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348817057425-9</Id><Topic><Title>Why will Liberals vote for more debt?????</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348779129874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:52:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for demonstrating so clearly again that the right wing has no arguments whatsoever, unless they make up little stories like yours, creating strawman demons that bounce back and forth in the RWNJ echo chamber until you all believe the specious crap. Guess you learned that MO from the most over-rated president in US history, Ronnie Raygun. Fortunately the majority of Americans sees through your pathetic lies.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1348817057425</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 03:24:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348822729468-10</Id><Topic><Title>Al Queda strikes our embassy</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348782407537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush lied thousads died</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1348822729468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 04:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348825823904-11</Id><Topic><Title>Everett seeks branch campus from WSU, not UW</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1348775900372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:58:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you one of those looney nutjobs that likes the Communist propaganda term "forward"?</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1348825823904</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 05:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348825896713-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why will Liberals vote for more debt?????</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348779129874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:52:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You play the role of the BA board psychopath to a T.</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1348825896713</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 05:51:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348826048816-13</Id><Topic><Title>Al Queda strikes our embassy</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348782407537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Thousads"? What the F is that? Besides, who cares, you're still an idiot.</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1348826048816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 05:54:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348830816520-14</Id><Title>Google: Larry Sinclair</Title><Msg>EOM !!</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1348830816520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 07:13:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348830920748-15</Id><Topic><Title>Al Queda strikes our embassy</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348782407537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps AlQaeda is working for the CIA and are Agent Provacatuers - just like 9-11</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1348830920748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 07:15:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348831442851-16</Id><Topic><Title>Why will Liberals vote for more debt?????</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348779129874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:52:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You play the role of analgonqueer to a T.</Msg><Username>alan_gonquin_is_queer</Username><Timestamp>1348831442851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 07:24:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348832079712-17</Id><Title>Where IS analgonqueer, now that we could some some comic relief?</Title><Msg>Rmoney is starting to repeat himself a lot, and his lines have lost their luster... Good ol' Anal could surely break things up a bit.</Msg><Username>alan_gonquin_is_queer</Username><Timestamp>1348832079712</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 07:34:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348833559843-18</Id><Topic><Title>Al Queda strikes our embassy</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348782407537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Panetta said, "It took a while to really get some of the feedback from what exactly happened at that location." Somebody tell Leon that "feedback" was given by the terrorists in the form of RPGs, mortar and AK-47 rounds. And this guy is our Defense secretary.</Msg><Username>commishfree1</Username><Timestamp>1348833559843</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 07:59:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348837714189-19</Id><Title>Boeing to cut managment by 50% in five years and imporve productivity?</Title><Msg>Here is a challenge for all of Boeing. Let's cut the management structure by 50%, while improving productivity by 50% over the next 5 years It is a shame that it seems Boeing management has lost touch with it's workforce (regardless of union affiliation), lost touch with its products and services, and lost touch with its customers and suppliers. Executives getting huge bonuses and salaries while the rest of us including the non union folks take cut after cut making management richer and richer. They add absolutely no value to the product whatsoever. I can't tell you how many worthless managers there are at Boeing. It sickens me how much crap we have to deal with because of these people who became managers now making stupid decisions. Not listening to people when they should have. Stupid decisions have cost this company untold amounts of money. Yet those people who make those stupid decisions keep getting rewarded. When was the last time you heard a customer say they want to buy a Boeing airplane that has a lot of management built into it? NEVER!!!!! Customers want a product that is state of the art Engineering, using the latest lightweight, high strength materials. They want a product that is built with high quality, and is stable. They want a product that they can get in as short a time as possible</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348837714189</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:08:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348838288273-20</Id><Title>Why do States with Republican Governors...../</Title><Msg>.....have balanced budgets, low unemployment, low taxes and a high number of people moving into them from states with Democrat governors.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348838288273</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:18:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348838643618-21</Id><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Msg>Watch them reach for any speck of data or out right lie to support the empty suit Mitt Romney for President. It is hard for me to believe that he made so much money when he can't seem to make a coherent sentence in his stump speeches even though he has been running for one office or another for the past 15 years. The well oiled weather vain is going down.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348838643618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:24:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348838944245-22</Id><Title>Two little peaks into the mind of Barack Obama and how he views wealth. Are you ready?</Title><Msg>The first is at a recent campaign stop. Obama told a crowd of ObamaBots, “The country doesn’t succeed when only the rich get richer. We succeed when the middle class gets bigger.” Wrong. We succeed when more people in the middle class become rich! It’s called income mobility … and until Obama came along the statics showed that the reason the middle class was growing smaller was because the middle class was moving on up! Our Dear Ruler doesn’t comprehend this because he is predisposed to despise the rich, and can’t believe that those people who are, to him, the focus of all that is evil were once middle class --- or poor. He believes that rich people became rich by taking away money from someone else. This is why his goal has never been to grow the size of our economic pie but merely to redistribute the current pie. And at the rate we are going, the pie (especially for those in the middle class) is shrinking. Median household income is down by $4,520 since Obama took office. This isn’t because evil rich people are stealing their portion of the pie … it’s because there is not enough confidence and capital for people to create businesses and hire workers, produce products and services and earn wealth. Another one occurs in a new Obama campaign ad. Here’s a rough transcript of part of that ad … “Fourth, a balanced plan to reduce our deficit by four trillion dollars over the next decade on top of the trillion in spending we've already cut, I'd ask the wealthy to pay a little more. And as we end the war in Afghanistan let's apply half the savings to pay down our debt and use the rest for some nation building right here at home. It's time for a new economic patriotism. Rooted in the belief that growing our economy begins with a strong, thriving middle class …” We’ll get to this “economic patriotism” in a minute, but first … Are people still buying this idea that if taxes increase on wealthy Americans, that we could even come close to reducing our deficit? I would love for one of these camera crews to interview Obama supporters and ask them the following question: If you could impose a 100% tax on all the earnings of every rich person in America earning at least $250,000 a year, how much money would you get? The answer is $1.4 trillion. I doubt that any of these ObamaBots would recognize that this is about the same as the deficit Obama has run every year since he’s been in office. So we’re talking over $4 trillion in deficits under Barack Obama. So taking all of the earnings of these evil rich people would not even make a dent in the increases in spending that Obama is responsible for, much less any reduction. $250,000 a year, all of the profits of the greedy corporations and all of the wealth acquired by America’s filthy billionaires, and that would only be enough money to fund our current federal government for eight months. That’s it! We can’t even fund an entire year of spending, much less reduce our deficit by any significant margin. Obama wants these rich people to pay a little bit more, and yet the share of the income tax burden paid by the top 1% of taxpayers has almost doubled since the 1970s. Considering that to be the case, the problem doesn’t seem to be taxes, it seems to be spending. Oh and about this “economic patriotism” nonsense. Why is it that Barack Obama believes it is patriotic to plunder the pockets of productive Americans? Is that what he truly values as patriotic? Neal Boortz</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348838944245</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:29:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348839222173-23</Id><Title>Liberals think plunder of other people's property and possessions should be legal</Title><Msg>.....especially those that have more than them.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348839222173</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:33:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348839414985-24</Id><Title>If Obama thinks Rich People are so Evil.......</Title><Msg>.....why does he hang around them so much. None of his close friend are poor people......or even middle class.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348839414985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:36:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348839570063-25</Id><Title>France Enacts Tax on Super Rich to Cut Deficit</Title><Msg>The French government confirmed a temporary 75 percent super-tax rate for earnings over one million euros and a new 45 percent band for revenues over 150,000 euros. Higher tax rates on dividends and other investments, plus cuts to existing tax breaks. Business will be hit with measures including a cut in the amount of loan interest which is tax-deductible and the cutting of an existing tax break on capital gains from certain share sales VIVE LA FRANCE</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1348839570063</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:39:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348839952221-26</Id><Title>Don't you just love the hypocrisy........</Title><Msg>.....when our president flies around in a big jet paid for with other people's money, lives in a big fancy house paid for with other people's money, eats his gourmet meals paid for with other people's money and has a whole crew of servants to take care of his every need.....all paid for with other people's money........so he can go out and demonize people who can do the same thing with their own money that they actually earned.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348839952221</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:45:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348840210317-27</Id><Topic><Title>France Enacts Tax on Super Rich to Cut Deficit</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1348839570063</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:39:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why not raise taxes in a crisis on the people who have benefitted the most from their country's freedom ? The super rich will not feel that tax increase - but no !!!! We can't do that . We can't ask more of those who have taken the most. We can't ask people to be Patriots. In WW2 the tax rate on the rich was 93%. We won the war.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1348840210317</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:50:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348840856074-28</Id><Topic><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348838643618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:24:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's secret weapons: 1. Bill Clinton 2. Mitt Rmoney</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1348840856074</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:00:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348841926783-29</Id><Topic><Title>Don't you just love the hypocrisy........</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348839952221</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:45:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the stupidity of your post is beyond belief. You can actually smell the panic.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1348841926783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:18:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348842498462-30</Id><Topic><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348838643618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:24:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rather misspell a word than be sycophant for the republican lying machine. Sure I went to public school, so what? Tell me #$%$, what private school did you attend? Who was your head master? Tell us three teachers you had there. C'mon MOUTH....back up your hyperbole.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348842498462</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:28:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348842595141-31</Id><Topic><Title>Do Americans truly understand 'redistribution of wealth'?</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1348842042255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:20:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Usual distortion. He was talking about redistribution of money within government programs. Stupid #$%$!!!</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348842595141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:29:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348842663135-32</Id><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Msg>Well oiled weather VANE. Feel better? Well, do ya punk?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348842663135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:31:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348843001460-33</Id><Topic><Title>Don't you just love the hypocrisy........</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348839952221</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:45:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So the Republican governor of Ohio is campaigning on a jobs platform and how successful he has been creating jobs in Ohio and Romeny comes there and tells everybody how horrible it is in Ohio. Pretty Comical stuff like Pay4ityouself.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348843001460</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:36:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348843561971-34</Id><Topic><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348838643618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:24:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's secret weapons: 1. Bill Clinton 2. Mitt Rmoney 3. Ryan 4. (Spreading) Santorum 5. Cain 6. Batsh*t Bachman 7. Harrydokes 8. Tommaxgregjanedoofus 9. Akin 10. Perry 11. Somebody with an IQ.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1348843561971</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:46:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348845050763-35</Id><Topic><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348842663135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Want to make a bet on this? If Obama wins you leave the board forever. If Mitt wins I leave the board forever. No new aliases. Of course we know you don't work for Boeing so that is no big hardship for you.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348845050763</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:10:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348845114012-36</Id><Topic><Title>Welcome to Socialism: 75 Percent Tax For Rich Passed in France</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1348844903988</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I say we put a 110% tax on all republican motor mouths on the Boeing board.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348845114012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:11:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348845335753-37</Id><Title>Romney memo seeks to lower debate expectations</Title><Msg>Washington (CNN) – If it wasn't already clear that Mitt Romney and his allies are trying to lower expectations heading into next Wednesday's debate against President Obama in Denver, the campaign is now making it official. In a memo about the debates distributed to campaign surrogates and provided to CNN on Thursday, longtime Romney adviser Beth Myers outlines a series of reasons why the president is likely to emerge as the winner of the first debate. Among them: – President Obama is "widely regarded as one of the most talented political communicators in modern history." – "This will be the eighth one-on-one presidential debate of his political career. For Mitt Romney, it will be his first." – "Four years ago, Barack Obama faced John McCain on the debate stage. According to Gallup, voters judged him the winner of each debate by double-digit margins, and their polling showed he won one debate by an astounding 33-point margin." Myers argues that Obama will "use his ample rhetorical gifts and debating experience to one end: attacking Mitt Romney." "We fully expect a 90-minute attack ad aimed at tearing down his opponent," she writes in the memo. Pushing back against emerging conventional wisdom, Myers concludes that the debates will not, in fact, decide the election: "It will be decided by the American people," she says. Read the full memo below: From: Beth Myers, Senior Adviser To: Interested Parties Date: September 27, 2012 Re: 2012 Presidential Debates In a matter of days, Governor Romney and President Obama will meet on the presidential debate stage. President Obama is a universally-acclaimed public speaker and has substantial debate experience under his belt. However, the record he's compiled over the last four years – higher unemployment, lower incomes, rising energy costs, and a national debt spiraling out of control – means this will be a close election right up to November 6th. Between now and then, President Obama and Governor Romney will debate three times. While Governor Romney has the issues and the facts on his side, President Obama enters these contests with a significant advantage on a number of fronts. Voters already believe – by a 25-point margin – that President Obama is likely to do a better job in these debates. Given President Obama's natural gifts and extensive seasoning under the bright lights of the debate stage, this is unsurprising. President Obama is a uniquely gifted speaker, and is widely regarded as one of the most talented political communicators in modern history. This will be the eighth one-on-one presidential debate of his political career. For Mitt Romney, it will be his first. Four years ago, Barack Obama faced John McCain on the debate stage. According to Gallup, voters judged him the winner of each debate by double-digit margins, and their polling showed he won one debate by an astounding 33-point margin. In the 2008 primary, he faced Hillary Clinton, another formidable opponent – debating her one-on-one numerous times and coming out ahead. The takeaway? Not only has President Obama gained valuable experience in these debates, he also won them comfortably. But what must President Obama overcome? His record. Based on the campaign he's run so far, it's clear that President Obama will use his ample rhetorical gifts and debating experience to one end: attacking Mitt Romney. Since he won't – and can't – talk about his record, he'll talk about Mitt Romney. We fully expect a 90-minute attack ad aimed at tearing down his opponent. If President Obama is as negative as we expect, he will have missed an opportunity to let the American people know his vision for the next four years and the policies he'd pursue. That's not an opportunity Mitt Romney will pass up. He will talk about the big choice in this election – the choice between President Obama's government-centric vision and Mitt Romney's vision for an opportunity society with more jobs, higher take-home pay, a better-educated workforce, and millions of Americans lifted out of poverty into the middle class. This election will not be decided by the debates, however. It will be decided by the American people. Regardless of who comes out on top in these debates, they know we can't afford another four years like the last four years. And they will ultimately choose a better future by electing Mitt Romney to be our next president.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1348845335753</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:15:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348845367589-38</Id><Topic><Title>Over the top</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348843804878</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:50:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice delusion. You can try all the dreaming, wishful thinking, disinformation, distortion, and out right lying you want, but it won't matter. Mitt showed everyone who he really is, and it is not going down well.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1348845367589</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:16:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348845480489-39</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Supporter are Mental Zombies</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1348843528981</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:45:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Down to just full out name calling now lol Sounds like you folks have coincided the election already.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348845480489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:18:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348845658690-40</Id><Topic><Title>Over the top</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348843804878</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:50:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who are you trying to convince? Yourself?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348845658690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:20:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348846793214-41</Id><Title>"my heart aches"</Title><Msg>Romney made a bad situation worse with his totally insincere "my heart aches" comments. No one (not even his wife) believed that pile of excrement. All it did was solidify how honest he was being when he trashed almost half the country.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1348846793214</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:39:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348846892808-42</Id><Topic><Title>Over the top</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348843804878</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:50:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you mean to say that Willtard is more truthful than Obama? Google "the lies of mitt romney" and tell us what you find. Among other things, you'll find the following in pole positon: ============ Mitt Romney tells 533 lies in 30 weeks, Steve Benen documents them I’ve written about or linked to a great deal here “chronicling Mitt’s mendacity” — to borrow Steven Benen’s phrase. Mitt Romney says many, many things that are not true. He says this despite being in possession of the correct facts of the matter. Which is to say that Mitt Romney lies. A lot. He lies more than any other national candidate for office in my lifetime. And I was born before the Nixon administration. This is documented. Proven. Validated, verified, demonstrated, catalogued and quantified. Mitt Romney lies. Here are 30 — 30! — of Benen’s weekly “chronicling” posts. These are all backed up and sourced. These are not assertions, interpretations or allegations. These are facts, actual instances. Over the past 30 weeks, Mitt Romney has told lie after lie after lie:[30 links, one for each week] Click those links. Read the lists. List after list of lie after lie. Hundreds of them — 533, to be exact, although Benen does not make any claim to providing a comprehensive chronicle. This is unprecedented. “We’re not going to let our campaign be dictated by fact-checkers,” Romney’s pollster, Neil Newhouse, said. This has produced what James Fallows calls the “post-truth” age — a relentlessly dishonest onslaught of brazen falsehoods with which the media and the political system are struggling to cope. What do you do when every article, every “fact-check,” every arbiter denounces a lie and corrects it, but then a politician just keeps repeating it? It’s remarkable to behold. etc... etc...</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1348846892808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348848055672-43</Id><Topic><Title>France Enacts Tax on Super Rich to Cut Deficit</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1348839570063</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:39:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agent, There are two possible reasons that you believe that the "super rich" can and should pay more in taxes: 1) that you honestly think that it would make a difference (presumably to relieve the deficit problem) or 2) it is borne out of some sort of belief that it is unfair that they have and make such money. There is no point to address the second because that would be your own problem. Hopefully that is not the case. Assuming that you think that it would make a difference, let’s look at the facts. The IRS posts tax and income data, in massive detail. However, it is only current up to the year 2009 (not sure why). In that year, there were 140.5 million “wage earners”, yet only 81.7 million with income sufficient to pay any taxes. Thus, the claim of 50%, the so-called 47%, etc. that are the only ones paying any taxes is approximately correct. The folks making above $1 million are in number about 236.9K or 0.17% of the population. The total “adjusted gross income” of all wage earners was $7,262.4 billion and for the $1 Million Club earned it was $729.6 billion, or 10% of the total earned income. They also paid, on average, 26.3% to 29.4% in federal taxes on their adjusted gross income, or a total of $177 billion in federal taxes (20% of the $866 billion in federal taxes paid). The nation average tax percent was 17.8% with numbers ranging between 6.6% ($10K AGI) and 28.8% (below $1M AGI). Now, to address the $1400 billion deficit problem: If the $1M Clubber’s taxes were raised by 10% points, that would increase revenue by (10/28) x $177B or about $63 billion. Simply a drop in the bucket. If you looked at the income of folks making $200K and up, that AGI total is $1964.3 billion. Basically, you would have to take 71% of these people’s money in order to support the level of run away spending that is conducted by the federal government. Unfortunately, it is an erroneous notion that taxes can truly be driven up to that level or the so-called 94% tax during WW2 and make the economy work. Or you drive up the corporate tax and drive all businesses out of the United States, with the ensuing drop in individual income. If we must spend money like a drunken sailor, then EVERYONE will have to pay more, and a lot more, not just the rich. A recent poll indicated that the vast majority of Americans believe that everyone should at least pay 1%. Still not enough. To cover this level of deficit spending, the taxes, on average, have to be increased, across the board, by nearly a factor of three. Those not paying any taxes at all then would have to pay their fair share. That would demonstrate their patriotism as well. To me, the only solution is to first reduce spending (significantly), then make some modest changes to the individual tax rates – all every level, and finally, perhaps most important, grow wealth by growing business and employment. We’ll see in November what the collective intelligence of the United States decides is the right answer. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1348848055672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:00:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348848188985-44</Id><Topic><Title>Why do States with Republican Governors...../</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348838288273</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:18:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libtards can't bring themselves to admit socialism /communism doesn't work nearly as well as freedom/capitalism.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348848188985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:03:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348848338976-45</Id><Topic><Title>Election results</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348845899947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:24:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My heart aches for your stupidity. Life is difficult for one who can't deal with reality. There are many suicide helplines for deranged, whackos like you.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1348848338976</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348848356082-46</Id><Topic><Title>Leno: 'We Wasted Four Years Waiting For Obama To Do Something About The Economy'...</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1348845802181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:23:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how many Job legislation bills have the house passed for the President to sign? what is the house doing today about jobs? probably out on the golf course its a vacation day!!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348848356082</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:05:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348848380511-47</Id><Topic><Title>Two little peaks into the mind of Barack Obama and how he views wealth. Are you ready?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348838944245</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:29:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama disdains capitalism and individual freedom. He is all about the collective with elite socialists telling everyone how to live. He has absolutely no respect for private property rights.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348848380511</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348848510887-48</Id><Topic><Title>Why do States with Republican Governors...../</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348838288273</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:18:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Government subsidies to big business is why.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348848510887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:08:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348848676382-49</Id><Title>The house has passed 13 jobs bills and 6 budgets......</Title><Msg>....but Democrat Harry Reid has refused to bring a single one up for an up or down vote. Fascism is alive and well in the Democrats controlled senate.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348848676382</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:11:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348848720556-50</Id><Title>Boeing and the three CEO's</Title><Msg>The Boeing business plan at work is for Management to threaten to move work out of Puget Sound?!? Isn't that the threat they made to the state legislature when they want yet another tax break? You're barking up the wrong tree - when McNerney is making 10 times what Wilson or Shrontz made, maybe you guys should shut up and point the finger elsewhere - labor isn't the issue - bloated executive pay is. Maybe you should outsource McNerney back to 3M where he was not any more successful in the tape and paper industry. Just take a peek at those at the helm and their backgrounds: 3M, GE and McDonnell Douglas A comparison to the Three Stooges would be an insult to the three stooges Moe, Larry and Curly actually had a long and money making career for their studio, unlike the head employee of the Boeing shareholders and as usual the stock price is down today.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348848720556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:12:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348848807868-51</Id><Topic><Title>The house has passed 13 jobs bills and 6 budgets......</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348848676382</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:11:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the Republican controlled house where most legislation gets started and who 2 yeas ago ran on a platform of Job creation what are they doing today about jobs?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348848807868</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:13:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348848876981-52</Id><Topic><Title>If Obama thinks Rich People are so Evil.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348839414985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:36:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama lives to spend other people's money.......poor people don't have any for him to spend.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348848876981</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:14:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348849186343-53</Id><Topic><Title>The house has passed 13 jobs bills and 6 budgets......</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348848676382</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:11:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have passed 13 jobs bill and Democrats have obstructed them all the way. Democrats refuse to pass jobs bills from the house. We need to get control of the senate out other hands of the Democrats to have any chance of getting the economy moving again.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348849186343</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:19:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348849424708-54</Id><Title>Why Democrats Can't Create Jobs</Title><Msg>The whole philosophy of Democrat's governance is find more way to plunder the wealth others create.....not to make it easy for others to create wealth.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348849424708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:23:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348849660526-55</Id><Title>Boeing is in business to make money not airplanes ,get it!</Title><Msg>Alfred Sloan, said "General Motors is not in business to make cars, we're in business to make money". With an attitude like that, it's a wonder it took the company so long to fail. But, fail they did. When you don't care about your product, when you don't care about your customers, when you don't care about your employees and other stakeholders, there's no way to avoid failure. This is exactly the Boeing problem or reason for failure ! BTW Boeing a DJ stock is down 4.72% for the year , but the Dow jones average of stocks is up 10% for the year, that puts Boeing shareholders on notice your stock value sucks</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348849660526</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:27:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348849682771-56</Id><Title>delivery floodgates open</Title><Msg>As of Thursday evening, BA has delivered 47 planes. Seventeen of those in the last 8 days. Thirty one 737's. Two 747's. Two 767's. Five 777's. Seven 787's. With three days left in September, and two of those being weekend days, today and Saturday should be the days of opportunity to meet or exceed the 2012 record of 53 deliveries set in March. But the significant increase in 787 deliveries is very important. They are making progress on turning the rework planes into cash. And yesterday there was an article that the 747 GE engine that failed was not due to a cracked shaft so that helps ease that risk but we have no info yet on why that engine failed. So things are looking much better but the ability to maintain increased deliveries that at least match the production increases is critical.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348849682771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:28:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348849910780-57</Id><Title>Why Obama Hate's Your Employer: An Objective View</Title><Msg>Every day, we hear President Obama explain how he will reduce our current $1.2 Trillion deficits... he will raise taxes on those who have the most investment capital... eg: the wealthiest Americans. As it turns out, those Americans are also our country's primary employers (along with corporations, which, in the U.S., currently pay the planet's highest corporate income taxes). The question is, WHY does President Obama single these people out? Why does he hate them so much? The answer reaches back many years. Mr. Obama's father, who, in his book, he cherished, was an avowed "anti-colonialist". His father hated how one country could dominate and exploit another via a colonial relationship. Further, Mr. Obama's stepfather, was an outspoken communist (Frank Davis). Mr Davis hated how he felt capitalism's "profit motive" compelled business owners to "exploit" their employees. As a result, President Obama's core belief is that a business owner's yearning for profits in his or her business compels them to exploit their workers... to essentially "trickle down" the fruits of their labors and hoarde the bulk of those profits for themselves. That belief is consistent with everything Mr. Obama ever learned in his life. The bottom line is that Mr. Obama believes that the only fair and compassionate employer, is the government. The problem is, every society that followed a path toward such government dominance of the labor markets, was a failed society. Soviet Russia, Cuba, etc. etc. all followed that path, and succumbed to poverty. Conversely, societies that harnessed the power of capitalism via the profit incentive have historically thrived... Hong Kong, Singapore... the United States 100 years ago. This election, boiled down to it's CORE DIFFERENTIATOR... is a candidate with a philosophy of capitalism... and empowering the private sector... VS socialism... and empowering the public sector. Historically, the former works well, and the later doesn't. You Decide. S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348849910780</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:31:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348850806218-58</Id><Title>delivery floodgates fail the truth about fowl reporting of Boeing delivery statistics</Title><Msg>.” It is just fowl to claim that the floodgates are opening all that is happening is late and over cost and no profit planes like the 787 and the 747-8, are being delivered at a profit, not true, the delivery is at a cost to the shareholder, that is why BA stock is down 5% for the year while the DJ average is up 10% for the year , It is just a fowl report ! Anytime you’re building an airplane such as the 787, out of sequence and late with rework that did not meet the original budget, or contracted specifications well, , the amount of rework that’s required goes up by a factor of 10, because they have to unbuild all the things you built on top of whatever you have to change, and then build it all back,”,. “ the cost that will be added to production and make the likelihood of a profit on this program over the next dozen years very, very low.” It’s like they’re dragging a boat anchor equivalent to 25 percent of their sales, which is at the expense of the profitability “It’s bloated with inventory, and somebody has to pay for that, and it’s the shareholder</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348850806218</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348850810427-59</Id><Title>delivery floodgates fail the truth about fowl reporting of Boeing delivery statistics</Title><Msg>.” It is just fowl to claim that the floodgates are opening all that is happening is late and over cost and no profit planes like the 787 and the 747-8, are being delivered at a profit, not true, the delivery is at a cost to the shareholder, that is why BA stock is down 5% for the year while the DJ average is up 10% for the year , It is just a fowl report ! Anytime you’re building an airplane such as the 787, out of sequence and late with rework that did not meet the original budget, or contracted specifications well, , the amount of rework that’s required goes up by a factor of 10, because they have to unbuild all the things you built on top of whatever you have to change, and then build it all back,”,. “ the cost that will be added to production and make the likelihood of a profit on this program over the next dozen years very, very low.” It’s like they’re dragging a boat anchor equivalent to 25 percent of their sales, which is at the expense of the profitability “It’s bloated with inventory, and somebody has to pay for that, and it’s the shareholder</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348850810427</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:46:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348851183318-60</Id><Title>Obama's Acceptance Speech</Title><Msg>Will run like this. Thank you again America for showing your confidence on me. I promise that if I cannot turn the economy in one year, I am going to retire at the end of my term.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1348851183318</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:53:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348851393734-61</Id><Topic><Title>Why Democrats Can't Create Jobs</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348849424708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:23:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's true, but Romney is in the same business. I think Romney's a lot smarter than Obama. Obama is so stupid he's determined to kill the American way of life, and when that happens all hell will break loose. O's got to go in November or we are all in big trouble, and the poor dumb leftys will be the ones to suffer the most. They better pray Romney gets elected.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1348851393734</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:56:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348853245385-62</Id><Topic><Title>The house has passed 13 jobs bills and 6 budgets......</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348848676382</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:11:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you list the 13 jobs bills? Love to see them.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348853245385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:27:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348855539172-63</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Acceptance Speech</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1348851183318</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:53:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, The sad part is O supporters will think this is a very sincere and caring statement. They are such sleep walking sheep they can't understand anything.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1348855539172</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:05:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348855570230-64</Id><Topic><Title>Why Democrats Can't Create Jobs</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348849424708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:23:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will take praying.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1348855570230</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:06:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348855720584-65</Id><Topic><Title>delivery floodgates fail the truth about fowl reporting of Boeing delivery statistics</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348850810427</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:46:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne, your post proves that two people are reading your stuff. Oops, make that one. I'm putting you on ignore because you sound like Herman and the Hermits' "Henry the Eighth." Second verse, same as the first.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1348855720584</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:08:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348855934689-66</Id><Title>It’s no Surprise than Obama has Been an Total Failure</Title><Msg>He never had the slightest qualification to be president.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348855934689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:12:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348856215123-67</Id><Title>Republican Fear Too Many Perople are Falling for Socialism......</Title><Msg>.....and don't place any value on individual liberty.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348856215123</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:16:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348856494716-68</Id><Title>up next is the 767 tanker a budget cut deal on the chopping block</Title><Msg>A budgetary stalemate in Congress could affect the Boeing Co.'s 767-based tanker program in Everett; Automatic government spending cuts of about 10 percent will go into effect Jan. 1, included the tanker on a list of programs subject to the cut, known as sequestration and called by some the "fiscal cliff."whether sequestration would lead to cut back or cancellation of the tanker program. Is unknown "I don't want to break my contract, and I'm fearful sequestration may force me to do that," Maj. Gen. John Thompson, tanker program executive officer and KC-46 program director Aerospace analyst Richard Aboulafia, with the Teal Group, said, the Air Force might have to void its contract with Boeing.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348856494716</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:21:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348857558150-69</Id><Topic><Title>delivery floodgates fail the truth about fowl reporting of Boeing delivery statistics</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348850810427</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:46:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris I can count on you not reading from now one then ! and your point is ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348857558150</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:39:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348858003238-70</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Fear Too Many Perople are Falling for Socialism......</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348856215123</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:16:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing republicans fear is people thinking. A thinking person knows that nothing the GOP says makes any sense.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1348858003238</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:46:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348858046855-71</Id><Topic><Title>The house has passed 13 jobs bills and 6 budgets......</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348848676382</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:11:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has told Reid to not process any more bills because his "autopen" is not working. Since he has forgotten where the White House is located, he depends upon the autopen to sign all legislation. His staff at the White House, knowing that he is lost, have rigged up an "Easy Button" for him to press which remotely controls the autopen. So far he has searched for the White House at all of the fund raising events and only recently has asked Whoopie Goldberg on the View if she can see it, since her program is all about giving great "insight" to the American public. Of course, Obama thinks of himself as "eye candy", though that does not seem to help his "eye sight" and ability to locate 1600 Penn Ave. Hopefully, his ability to find his home in Chicago after November will clear all of that up.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1348858046855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348858961772-72</Id><Title>Why a first termer has an edge over a second termer</Title><Msg>If both get it right, the country has four years to enjoy it under the second termer while it may last twice as long with the first termer.Think about it.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1348858961772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348859290602-73</Id><Topic><Title>Why a first termer has an edge over a second termer</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1348858961772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:02:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your desperation is hitting new, unforeseen, levels. Pretty funny.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1348859290602</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:08:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348860828294-74</Id><Topic><Title>Why a first termer has an edge over a second termer</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1348858961772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:02:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Happening everywhere you look. Trading veterans for rookies,firing old workers and hiring young ones. Need a fresh start with new actors.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1348860828294</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348862505903-75</Id><Topic><Title>"my heart aches"</Title><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1348846793214</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:39:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another dumbocrat led down the union road by the nose. How do you know how the guy feels? Like Obama gives a rat's *** about you? Keep drinking the socialist kook-aid.</Msg><Username>naarocked</Username><Timestamp>1348862505903</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:01:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348862611240-76</Id><Topic><Title>"my heart aches"</Title><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1348846793214</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:39:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no $hit</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1348862611240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:03:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348862648555-77</Id><Topic><Title>Why Democrats Can't Create Jobs</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348849424708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:23:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Romneys of the world create jobs overseas while they destroy jobs in the USA.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1348862648555</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348862721546-78</Id><Topic><Title>American Awakening</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1348746814109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 07:53:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice!!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1348862721546</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:05:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348862876044-79</Id><Topic><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348842663135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they reek of fear !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1348862876044</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:07:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348863466147-80</Id><Title>Why are Liberals so spineless?</Title><Msg>They're wimps.</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1348863466147</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348863500593-81</Id><Topic><Title>up next is the 767 tanker a budget cut deal on the chopping block</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348856494716</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:21:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since Boeing low balled the bid for this contract, a cancellation might actually be good for Boeing</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1348863500593</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:18:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348863593772-82</Id><Title>Is there anything funnier than a Liberal</Title><Msg>trying to act tough? Nope.</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1348863593772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:19:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348864048680-83</Id><Topic><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348842663135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Skunked, Forget the political fear for a moment. Here is fear for someone who is a Christian: "The Future Must Not Belong To Those Who Slander The Prophet Of Is.lam". Our President, who claims to be a Christian, stands before a world audience at the U.N. and said those words, thus defending and endorsing the work of Satan. Mo.hammad wrote two things in the Koran that should make a Christian shudder: 1) "that Jesus was not the Son of God" and 2) "that Jesus was not crucified." I cannot envision two more important thrusts of the entire Bible than those. Countless times this man protects Islam. His whole Middle East policy and indeed his "success" has been to undermine the security of Is.rael. His "spiritual advisor" blasphemed God from his pulpit. The failure of the economy is almost unimportant compared to where Obama is really leading this nation. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1348864048680</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348865103810-84</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Liberals so spineless?</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1348863466147</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:17:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are spineless because they know if they speak out against the waste er in Chief they will lose their seat on the LibDim gravy train and heaven knows getting a job and being responsible for themselves and their family is diametrically opposed to the brainwashing they gobbled up in the Government Operated School Gulag. They, as happy little lemmings, will follow the Chicken-Fried-Marxist over the cliff of financial ruin.</Msg><Username>hoodickhertz</Username><Timestamp>1348865103810</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:45:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348866858891-85</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Liberals so spineless?</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1348863466147</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:17:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They all talk with an extended pinky and a lisp.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348866858891</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:14:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348866998565-86</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything funnier than a Liberal</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1348863593772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:19:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing funnier than a liberal is watching who's dumb enough to think Obama can make socialism work.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348866998565</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:16:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348867802523-87</Id><Title>39 days...</Title><Msg>...until Obama is re-elected in a landslide and the 10 cent per post RWNJ koch-suckers shut their filthy, lying, stupid pie-holes</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1348867802523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:30:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348868172051-88</Id><Topic><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348842663135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and what does your beloved Israel say about Christ being the Son of God?</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1348868172051</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:36:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348868173858-89</Id><Topic><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348842663135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and what does your beloved Israel say about Christ being the Son of God?</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1348868173858</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348868175680-90</Id><Topic><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348842663135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and what does your beloved Israel say about Christ being the Son of God?</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1348868175680</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:36:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348868204491-91</Id><Topic><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348842663135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and what does your beloved Israel say about Christ being the Son of God?</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1348868204491</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:36:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348870016048-92</Id><Topic><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348842663135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fats, Anyone who rejects Jesus is condemned already (John 3:18). Is.real, as a nation, will repent, embrace Jesus as Savior, and play a key role in the future at the time of the final judgment, which seems to be hastening. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1348870016048</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 18:06:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348871742363-93</Id><Title>another satellite launch contract</Title><Msg>The U.S. Defense Department on Friday awarded United Launch Alliance, a 50-50 joint venture of Lockheed Martin Corp (LMT.N) and Boeing Co (BA.N) a contract valued at $1.17 billion to provide satellite launches using its Delta IV and Atlas V rockets. The Pentagon said the contract would run through September 30, 2013. The venture provides launch services to send U.S. military and intelligence satellites into space under the Evolved Expendable Launch Vehicle (EELV) program.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348871742363</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 18:35:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348871878524-94</Id><Topic><Title>delivery floodgates open</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348849682771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Add two more 737's delivered this morning and it looks like the 747 for Atlas air was delivered as well. That makes for deliveries so far. More deliveries may occur before the day (Friday) is over.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348871878524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 18:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348874533862-95</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama and his chief of staff Rahm Emanuel are lifetime members of the same gay bath house in uptown Chicago</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348873983605</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 19:13:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More proof that you Repukes are incredibly pathetic human beings Wow!</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1348874533862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 19:22:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348876803313-96</Id><Topic><Title>Yet another Fox 'apology'...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_777</Username><Timestamp>1348869430184</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:57:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fox is a joke. It isn't news, it's entertainment.</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1348876803313</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:00:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348876870872-97</Id><Title>When you start bringing up gay bath houses</Title><Msg>You are throwing in the towel. Obama wins easily.</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1348876870872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:01:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348877385824-98</Id><Topic><Title>On Polls...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_777</Username><Timestamp>1348865541932</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post. The Goopers are in denial.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1348877385824</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:09:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348877612403-99</Id><Topic><Title>39 days...</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1348867802523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1348877612403</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348878053891-100</Id><Topic><Title>When you start bringing up gay bath houses</Title><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1348876870872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uncle Al, you have spent too much time in the barrel. It is apparent your best position is bending over and grabbing your ankles! A new perk for you moochers has just been announced. DimBammer will be providing you with unlimited Obamma-lube.</Msg><Username>tminusten</Username><Timestamp>1348878053891</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:20:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348878367243-101</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama and his chief of staff Rahm Emanuel are lifetime members of the same gay bath house in uptown Chicago</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348873983605</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 19:13:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go get some help right now. Take a copy of this post to the mental health counselor. If you can't afford it, say so and I'll pay for the evaluation. Promise not to hurt yourself when the President is re-elected. s/ Orly</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1348878367243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:26:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348878585552-102</Id><Topic><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348842663135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Loading_Dock, Fortunately, you are alive and breathing and can make the right choice at this time (I am not talking about the election here). Who knows what tomorrow will bring? Say, though, you were never apprised of the consequences of unbelief. Would you not be angry? So, here, I come along, loathed I am sure by many for whatever reason, but I tell you guys what is the truth (about the Bible). Here, ignore me then, and read your Bible. Read John chapter 3 and John 14:6. I know that sometimes I come off as dire, but there is no reality "game" associated with eternity. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1348878585552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:29:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348879167520-103</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything funnier than a Liberal</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1348863593772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:19:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another thing more pathetic is a liberal who's dumb enough to think Obama can make socialism work. Only a Marxist/Socialist can believe Obama's Marxist/Socialism is middle of the road and will be accepted by Americans. By the time the LibDums come out of the Zombie Trance they are operating under, they will be over the Obammer cliff and spreading their intelligence all over the rocks below!</Msg><Username>tminusten</Username><Timestamp>1348879167520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348880024093-104</Id><Topic><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348842663135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No taker</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348880024093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:53:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348880065716-105</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything funnier than a Liberal</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1348863593772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:19:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You haven't seen my dog take a c-r-a-p have yeah?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1348880065716</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348880329522-106</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama and his chief of staff Rahm Emanuel are lifetime members of the same gay bath house in uptown Chicago</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348873983605</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 19:13:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now, he a Muslim, Kenyan, noncitizen, socialist, communist, gay, compulsive liar trying to bring on the Biblical end of times. Do I have all your complaints correct? Where does he find the time?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348880329522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348883151019-107</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything funnier than a Liberal</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1348863593772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:19:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh my Gawd- soshulism- !!!!!! as if there were any socialist countries on the face of the earth except Cuba--tminusten you have got to be the most stoooopid SOB on the planet- get yourself a brain transplant quick its your only hope</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348883151019</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 21:45:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348886762257-108</Id><Topic><Title>Is there anything funnier than a Liberal</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1348863593772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:19:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes there is - a fool with an ID alangonquin11 refusing to acknowledge his boy Romney is doing ACTUALLY as the polls indicate and trying to smear liberals as being "soft"</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1348886762257</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 22:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348890411397-109</Id><Topic><Title>Just So You Know: Voting Democratic Places the Eternal Salvation of Your Soul In Serious Jeopardy</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_777</Username><Timestamp>1348864842842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:40:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some of the greatest lib progressives in history have been soulless, Stalin, Jim Jones, Pol Pot; however in your case it is your brain that you should be worried about.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1348890411397</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 23:46:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348890738547-110</Id><Title>Boeing is getting sufsidies and Airbus wants the taxpayer to pay</Title><Msg>EU wants $12B a year from US over Boeing aid The European Union said Thursday it is asking the World Trade Organization to impose up to $12 billion per year in sanctions on the U.S. as part of a long-running dispute involving government subsidies to plane-makers Airbus and Boeing.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348890738547</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 23:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>