<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347533046421-1</Id><Topic><Title>deliveries</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1347485676993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:34:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the update.</Msg><Username>mrstock52</Username><Timestamp>1347533046421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 06:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347535984376-2</Id><Title>Protesters storm U.S. Embassy in Yemen</Title><Msg>The new tighter security? ======================================= SANAA, Yemen (AP) -- Chanting "death to America," hundreds of protesters angered by an anti-Islam film stormed the U.S. Embassy compound in Yemen's capital and burned the American flag on Thursday, the latest in a series of attacks on American diplomatic missions in the Middle East. The protesters breached the usually tight security around the embassy and reached the compound grounds but did not enter the main building housing the offices. Once inside the compound, they brought down the U.S. flag, burned it and replaced it with a black banner bearing Islam's declaration of faith -- "There is no God but Allah." Before storming the grounds, demonstrators removed the embassy's sign on the outer wall, set tires ablaze and pelted the compound with rocks. It was similar to an attack on the U.S. Embassy in the Egyptian capital of Cairo on Tuesday night. A mob of Libyans also attacked the U.S. consulate in the eastern city of Benghazi on Tuesday, killing American Ambassador Chris Stevens and three other Americans. In Egypt, protesters were clashing with police near the U.S. Embassy in the capital Cairo for the third day in a row. The violence has raised worries that further protests could break out around the Muslim world as anger spreads over the movie. Yemeni security forces who rushed to the scene fired in the air and used tear gas to disperse the demonstrators and were eventually able to drive them out of the compound. It was not immediately clear whether anyone was inside the embassy at the time of the attack. The Yemeni Embassy in Washington condemned the attack and vowed to ensure the safety of foreign diplomats and to step up security measures around their missions in the country. Yemen is home to al-Qaeda's most active branch and the United States is the main foreign supporter of the Yemeni government's counterterrorism campaign. The government on Tuesday announced that al-Qaeda's No. 2 leader in Yemen was killed in an apparent U.S. airstrike, a major blow to the terror network. The movie, "Innocence of Muslims," came to attention in Egypt after its trailer was dubbed into Arabic and posted on YouTube. The video-sharing website blocked access to it Wednesday. The trailer depicts Muhammad as a fraud, a womanizer and a madman in an overtly ridiculing way, showing him having sex and calling for massacres.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1347535984376</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 07:33:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347542047334-3</Id><Title>Obama is on track to have the worst jobs record of any president since World War II.</Title><Msg>August’s abysmally weak job growth proved yet again that President Obama’s economic policies are a miserable failure that will continue to undermine our country until he leaves office. The government’s report that the economy added just a minuscule 96,000 jobs last month came at the end of the Democrats’ defensive national convention, where the president, Bill Clinton and other party luminaries made extravagant claims that things will get better if Mr. Obama is re-elected to a second term. But analysts at the Federal Reserve Board, economists and business leaders say Mr. Obama’s declining economy is not going to get significantly better this year, next year or the year after that, until there are dramatic changes in the nation’s fiscal policies. Changes Obama Democrats refuse to make. The deepening weaknesses in the employment picture also were underscored by revisions in the June and July job numbers, which found 41,000 fewer jobs were created than was reported previously.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1347542047334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:14:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347542532062-4</Id><Title>Obama was never a Constitutional law professor, nor was he offered tenure.</Title><Msg>Barack Obama was never offered tenure, despite the assertions of a New York Times reporter who covers the president and the first family. “Other faculty members dreamed of tenured positions; [Obama] turned them down,” wrote Times White House Correspondent Jodi Kantor, author of “The Obamas,” in a July 30, 2008 profile of the president’s twelve years as a lecturer at the University of Chicago Law School. And yet, according to longtime University of Chicago law professor Richard Epstein, Obama was never actually offered a tenured faculty position. “I have no idea where Jodi got her story” about the tenure offer, said Epstein, adding that he immediately wrote Kantor to tell her she was wrong. Epstein was, then, a member of the faculty, not the school’s dean</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1347542532062</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:22:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347544015178-5</Id><Title>Jobless claims rise to 382,000 in latest week...</Title><Msg>Initial claims for state unemployment benefits rose 15,000 to a seasonally adjusted 382,000, the highest in two months, the Labor Department said on Thursday. The prior week's figure was revised up to show 2,000 more applications than previously reported.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1347544015178</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:46:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347544248287-6</Id><Title>RASMUSSEN POLL: ROMNEY JUMPS BACK INTO LEAD...</Title><Msg>R: 47% O: 46%</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1347544248287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:50:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347544533057-7</Id><Topic><Title>RASMUSSEN POLL: ROMNEY JUMPS BACK INTO LEAD...</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1347544248287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:50:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney will Crush Obama in November.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347544533057</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:55:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347544781775-8</Id><Title>Obama rejects Netanyahu meeting, invites Egypt's Muslim Brotherhood president to talk...</Title><Msg>Unbelievable!… Barack Obama invited Muslim Brotherhood Egyptian President Mohammad Morsi to meet with him in New York next week. But… Barack Obama won’t meet with Israeli leader Netanyahu over Iran row. He’s going to be campaigning and on Letterman. Reuters reported:</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1347544781775</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:59:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347545440764-9</Id><Topic><Title>RASMUSSEN POLL: ROMNEY JUMPS BACK INTO LEAD...</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1347544248287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:50:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rasmussen is the least respected poll out there. It is a FOX viewers favorite thing, biased and tells them what they want to hear. Rasmussen and Bias After the 2010 elections, the New York Times statistics wizard, Nate Silver, analyzed the polls produced by various polling organizations, including Rasmussen Reports, which is the house pollster for Fox News. Silver's analysis covered only polls taken during the final three weeks of the campaign and compared them to the actual election results. For polls taken much earlier, say in June, no one knows what the true sentiment of the electorate was, so there is no way to tell if the polls were accurate or not. Also, any pollster deliberately falsifying the results for partisan advantage would be advised to reduce the bias as the election neared. After all, no one can tell if a June poll is accurate but everyone can tell if a poll released the day before the election is accurate. Silver analyzed 105 polls released by Rasmussen Reports and its subsidiary, Pulse Opinion Research, for Senate and gubernatorial races in numerous states across the country. The bottom line is that on average, Rasmussen's polls were off by 5.8% with a bias of 3.9% in favor of the Republican candidates. There is much to criticize about Rasmussen's methods. All polls are conducted within a 4-hour window, the person who answers the phone (even a child) is sampled, phones that are not answered are not called back, and much more. All of Rasmussen's polls are done by computer; live interviewers are never used. However, other firms that do robopolling such as SurveyUSA and PPP get much more accurate results with no bias, so the problem is not the robopolling per se. Just to look at one methodological issue, if no one answers the phone, Rasmussen picks a different random phone number instead of calling back two, three, four or more times as other pollsters do. Why does this matter? Because 20-somethings (who skew Democratic) are often out, whereas 60-somethings (who skew Republican) are often in. By not being persistent in finally getting through to a randomly chosen phone number, the sample is inherently biased towards Republicans because they are easier to reach. This may not have been intentional but it is understandable if you want to finish your survey in 4 hours. Nevertheless, cutting corners in the name of speed and cost don't improve accuracy. Unlike companies like Strategic Vision, which most likely made up the data (but not very well) and also Research 2000, which probably did as well, no one is suggesting that Rasmussen is making up numbers without actually doing polling. There are many reports of people called by Rasmussen. The problem with Rasmussen is most likely its model of the electorate. Very briefly, if a pollster believes that in a certain state, say, 40% of the voters are Republicans and the actual survey just happens to turn up 35% Republicans, each Republican interviewed will be given a weight of 40/35 to correct for the undersampling of Republicans. All pollsters do this to correct for under- or oversampling by party, gender, age, race, income, and other factors. This is not only legitimate, but necessary with the small samples all the pollsters use. The issue here is whether Rasmussen's model of the electorate has more Republicans in it than in reality there are (not to mention whether this is accidental or deliberate). You can read more about Silver's analysis here and here. The conclusion is that some people do not believe in Rasmussen's polls any more.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1347545440764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:10:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347545551289-10</Id><Title>Two do-nothing persons</Title><Msg>The President and Bernanke. Get busy .</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347545551289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347545775366-11</Id><Title>U.S. State Dept. alerts travelers in wake of embassy protests</Title><Msg>Thanks a lot Obama and Democrats. You screwed up everything here now you've up everything internationally so we can't travel.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1347545775366</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:16:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347545830212-12</Id><Topic><Title>RASMUSSEN POLL: ROMNEY JUMPS BACK INTO LEAD...</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1347544248287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:50:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on Good Post. How does a poll like Ramussen change 5% both ways in a matter of 4 days? Zero credibility period!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1347545830212</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:17:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347546874109-13</Id><Topic><Title>RASMUSSEN POLL: ROMNEY JUMPS BACK INTO LEAD...</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1347544248287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:50:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you advocate having a Pres and VP who have zero Foreign Policy experience, insulted our number 1 ally and consider Russia as our number 1 enemy. Worse than having a minor league pitchers first game being the 7th game of a world series. You talk about a disaster waiting to happen!</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1347546874109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:34:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347547083191-14</Id><Topic><Title>O screws up again</Title><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1347501821903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope you aren't right, but it looks like you are. The main stream media shouldn't be forgiven for leading America to this. I just hope the election votes are counted correctly this time, but I wouldn't really count on it.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1347547083191</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:38:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347548094459-15</Id><Topic><Title>O screws up again</Title><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1347501821903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get real. He hasn't manufactured a war, like Iraq, that cost a trillion dollars and accomplished nothing but move Iraq closer to Iran. We don't need troops on the ground in Syria. Iran and war. Not something that can be won. It is the next North Korea.</Msg><Username>nuthead48</Username><Timestamp>1347548094459</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347549743440-16</Id><Title>Current foreign policy</Title><Msg>Install security system in your house only after it was burglarized. Do not do it before that.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347549743440</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347550318067-17</Id><Topic><Title>Current foreign policy</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347549743440</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:22:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like fire back at our enemies if they shoot us first. But if none of us get hit or hurt, do not shoot back because they might just be shooting at us with blanks. Understand?</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347550318067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347551907962-18</Id><Topic><Title>RASMUSSEN POLL: ROMNEY JUMPS BACK INTO LEAD...</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1347544248287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:50:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An increase in support from women as well as independents gives Barack Obama a post-convention advantage over challenger Mitt Romney. The president receives a five percentage-point bounce among women and a 12-point bounce among independents, in a Fox News poll released Wednesday.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1347551907962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:58:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347552280239-19</Id><Topic><Title>RASMUSSEN POLL: ROMNEY JUMPS BACK INTO LEAD...</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1347544248287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:50:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya ever notice how #$%$ never say anything about Rasmussen polls when O is ahead but they go ballistic when Romney is in the lead. All other polls will follow Rasmussen a week later. The Fact is he is on of the most respected and accurate pollsters out there. Democrats and other atheists just slither back into their kill the messenger mentality when the message isn't what they want to hear.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1347552280239</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347552801996-20</Id><Topic><Title>deliveries</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1347485676993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:34:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>air china just confirmed purchase of 5 747-8</Msg><Username>hirtuism</Username><Timestamp>1347552801996</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347554128104-21</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Failed and Shameful Economic Policy</Title><Username>clowncramer</Username><Timestamp>1347503518855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:31:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sen. Bernie Sanders asked on Wednesday where President Obama stands on protecting Social Security. In a radio interview with Ed Schultz, the senator questioned whether the president still stands by positions he staked out in his 2008 campaign. Four years ago, Obama was clear. He pledged in a Sept. 6, 2008, speech to AARP that he wouldn't raise the retirement age or change how yearly cost-of-living adjustments are calculated. "John McCain's campaign has suggested that the best answer for the growing pressures on Social Security might be to cut cost-of-living adjustments or raise the retirement age. Let me be clear: I will not do either," Obama said back then. This year, the president has barely mentioned Social Security. Sanders earlier pressed the president to clarify his position today on Social Security in a July 24 Senate floor speech. "I do not believe that we should cut Social Security," Sanders said. "I would like to know, and I think the American people would like to know, if President Obama feels the same way. It is past time that the president told the American people in no uncertain terms that he will not cut Social Security on his watch." Social Security needs to be improved and that is easy to do just by eliminating the cap.After all why should high income earners avoid the FICA tax?To be fair everyone should pay FICA tax on all incomes!</Msg><Username>sistersara89</Username><Timestamp>1347554128104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:35:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347554212565-22</Id><Title>Obama's Failed Foreign Policy!.. Marine Security Guards in Egypt Not Allowed Live Ammo</Title><Msg>Obama and His Foolish Foreign Policy is Putting American Lives at Risk! REPORTS: No Live Ammo for Marines Marine blogs say U.S. embassy did not authorize service members to carry ammo Anne Patterson / Wikimedia Commons BY: Adam Kredo September 13, 2012 10:36 am U.S. Marines defending the American embassy in Egypt were not permitted by the State Department to carry live ammunition, limiting their ability to respond to attacks like those this week on the U.S. consulate in Cairo. Ambassador to Egypt Anne Patterson “did not permit U.S. Marine guards to carry live ammunition,” according to multiple reports on U.S. Marine Corps blogs spotted by Nightwatch. “She neutralized any U.S. military capability that was dedicated to preserve her life and protect the US Embassy.” U.S. officials have yet to confirm or comment on the reports. Time magazine’s Battleland blog reported Thursday “Senior U.S. officials late Wednesday declined to discuss in detail the security at either Cairo or Benghazi, so answers may be slow in coming.” If true, the reports indicate that Patterson shirked her obligation to protect U.S. interests, Nightwatch states. “She did not defend U.S. sovereign territory and betrayed her oath of office,” the report states. “She neutered the Marines posted to defend the embassy, trusting the Egyptians over the Marines.” While Marines are typically relied on to defend U.S. territory abroad, such as embassies, these reports indicate that the Obama administration was relying on Egypt’s new Muslim Brotherhood-backed government to ensure American security, a move observers are questioning as violence in Cairo continues to rage.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347554212565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347554215725-23</Id><Title>mid september 787 stats</Title><Msg>Per the NYC787 blog: counting all of the 787's thru those in final assembly, there are a total of 81 planes. 6 are used by Boeing for testing etc. 7 are in final assembly. 17 are in storage awaiting change/rework. 12 are in change/rework. 9 are in pre-flight prep.. 7 are in pre delivery flight test. 2 are ready for delivery. 21 have been delivered. We should see a number of planes delivered in September and October.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1347554215725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:36:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347554330744-24</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Failed and Shameful Economic Policy</Title><Username>clowncramer</Username><Timestamp>1347503518855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:31:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clown, You are So Stupid! Great Moniker for You.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347554330744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:38:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347554612427-25</Id><Title>Obamaville, Jobless Claims Soar Consumer Prices Rise</Title><Msg>We Need to get This Idiot, Named Obama, Out of the WH Weekly Jobless Claims Jump; Producer Prices Gassed Up Published: Thursday, 13 Sep 2012 | 9:21 AM ET Text Size By: Reuters The number of Americans filing new claims for jobless benefits rose more than expected last week, with several states reporting an increase related to Tropical Storm Isaac. Michael Nagle | Bloomberg | Getty Images In a separate report, a sharp rise in gasoline costs drove up wholesale prices last month by the most in more than three years. But outside energy and food, price gains were mild. Initial claims for state unemployment benefits rose 15,000 to a seasonally adjusted 382,000, the highest in two months, the Labor Department said on Thursday. The prior week's figure was revised up to show 2,000 more applications than previously reported. Economists polled by Reuters had forecast claims rising to 370,000 last week. A Labor Department official said Tropical Storm Isaac, which drenched parts of the country, accounted for about 9,000 of the claims filed last week. The number is unadjusted. But even accounting for the storm, the report suggested little improvement in the labor market after job growth slowed sharply in August. The four-week moving average for new claims, a better measure of labor market trends, climbed 3,250 to 375,000, the highest since the middle of July. RELATED LINKS Highest-Paying JobsImport Prices RiseMost Expensive States Employers added 96,000 jobs last month, a step down from July's 141,000 count. While the unemployment rate dropped to 8.1 percent in August from 8.3 percent, it was because Americans gave up the search for work. The sluggish labor market is seen prompting the Federal Reserve to announce a third round of bond purchases at the end of a two-day policy meeting later on Thursday. The unemployment rate has been stuck above 8 percent for more than three years, the first time this has happened since the Great Depression. The number of people still receiving benefits under regular state programs after an initial week of aid fell 49,000 to 3.28 million in the week ended Sept. 1, the claims report showed. Producer Price Index Higher The Labor Department says that the producer price index, which measures price changes before they reach the consumer, jumped 1.7 percent in August. The increase was mostly because gas prices soared 13.6 percent, the biggest gain in three years. Food prices rose 0.9 percent, driven up by steep increases in the cost of eggs and dairy products. Excluding the volatile food and gas categories, core wholesale prices rose only 0.2 percent, below July's increase. In the past 12 months, wholesale prices have increased 2 percent, a mild gain and far below the recent peak of 7.1 percent in July 2011.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347554612427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:43:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347554913241-26</Id><Title>Feds Say Obama Cabinet Member a Crook! Violated FederaL Law.</Title><Msg>Feds: Sebelius violated federal law by campaigning for Obama Published September 13, 2012 Health and Human Services Secretary Kathleen Sebelius violated federal law when she campaigned this winter for President Obama, federal investigators announced Wednesday. Sebelius broke the law by making “extemporaneous partisan remarks” during a speech in February at a Human Rights Campaign Event in Charlotte, N.C., according to the Office of Special Counsel (OSC). She made the comments in the city that would later host the Democratic National Convention. "One of the imperatives is to make sure that we not only come together here in Charlotte to present the nomination to the president, but we make sure that in November, he continues to be president for another four years," Sebelius said, according to the agency and reported first by The Hill newspaper. The agency said Sebelius’ comments violated the Hatch Act, which prohibits public officials from campaigning in an official capacity. The agency said the Department of Health and Human Services after the event reclassified the trip from official to political and that the federal government was reimbursed for related costs. However, the OSC still concluded Sebelius had violated federal law and has sent the report to the president -- the procedure for a government official appointed by a president and confirmed by the Senate. OSC spokeswoman Ann O’Hanlon said there is no formal rule for dealing with an appointed official in violation of the act. However, the agency investigates at least 100 cases such cases annually with “a great majority” of them being resolved internally and violators getting a suspension. O'Hanlon said the remaining cases are sent to the Merit System Protection Board, which can decide to terminate the employment of non-appointed federal employees or give them a 30-day suspension. Still, Maureen Ferguson and Ashley McGuire of the Catholic Association are calling for Sebelius’ resignation. “Throughout her tenure at Health and Human Services, most of Secretary Kathleen Sebelius' actions have advanced the president's political interests,” they said in a joint statement. Sebelius could not be reached late Wednesday afternoon, but her response to the findings is supposed to be in the report forwarded to the president. She also discussed state politics in the Feb. 25 speech, urging voters to defeat a ballot proposal opposing gay marriage and to elect a Democratic governor, according to The Hill.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347554913241</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:48:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347555157395-27</Id><Title>Obamaville, Inflation Highest in Three Years</Title><Msg>Gas Sends Wholesale Prices Up The Most In 3 Years by THE ASSOCIATED PRESS EnlargePaul Sakuma/AP A sign shows prices at a gas station in San Francisco. Wholesale gasoline prices soared 13.6 percent in August, the biggest gain in three years. text size A A A September 13, 2012 A sharp rise in gasoline costs drove up wholesale prices last month by the most since June 2009. But outside energy and food, price gains were mild. The producer price index, which measures price changes before they reach the consumer, jumped 1.7 percent in August, the Labor Department said Thursday. The increase was mostly because gas prices soared 13.6 percent, the biggest gain in three years. Food prices rose 0.9 percent, driven up by steep increases in the cost of eggs and dairy products. Excluding the volatile food and gas categories, core wholesale prices rose only 0.2 percent, below July's increase. In the past 12 months, wholesale prices have increased 2 percent, a mild gain and far below the recent peak of 7.1 percent in July 2011. Low inflation means consumers have more money to spend, which helps the economy. It also gives the Federal Reserve more leeway to keep interest rates low in an effort to spur economic growth. If prices were to begin rising rapidly, the Fed might be forced to raise rates in response. The severe drought in the Midwest may have begun to impact wholesale food prices in August. The dry weather has harmed a range of crops, including corn and soybeans. Higher corn prices raise costs for many different foods on grocery store shelves. Corn is used to make everything from cosmetics to cereal, soda, cake mixes and candy bars. It is also used as a feed for cattle and hogs. That means more expensive corn can also push up beef and pork prices</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347555157395</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:52:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347555422349-28</Id><Title>Obama DOW Soars - Double Bush DOW</Title><Msg>YES, YOU ARE BETTER OFF! 10 GOOD REASONS to be thankful that Obama is our President... 1. Killing Bin Laden! 2. Having a sane foreign policy with no crazy wars. Romney’s first foreign policy misadventures were a “Blooper Reel.” Hopefully we never experience his “Bloopers Real” 3. Saving GM and Chrysler and millions of good-paying middle class jobs! 4. Giving the USA has the BEST (still terrible, but the best) economy in the advanced world. Meanwhile, much of Europe is in or heading into recession due to austerity at the wrong time! 5. After inheriting a $1 trillion yearly deficit, Obama didn’t do a Herbert Hoover and make it worse with destructive austerity and a depression! 6. Enabling American business to have record profits and record cash-on-hand of over $2 trillion! The S&amp;P500 stock market has doubled thanks to Obama-Bernanke. 7. NOT doing stupid things as Romney-Ryan would do, such as supply-side economics all over again! Fool us twice, shame on us! Or as George Santayana put it, "Those who cannot remember the past are condemned to repeat it!” 8. TRYING to bring a large, economically healthy, and growing middle class back to health after 8 years of Bush43 trickle-down devastation! It's a long road back. 9. OPPOSING Paul Ryan's immoral budget! 10 The right man to endure all the hatred of being President Jackie Robinson Obama!</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347555422349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347555840918-29</Id><Topic><Title>Quote Of The Day</Title><Username>the_loading_dock</Username><Timestamp>1347490068963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 18:47:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those Libyan radicals who murdered the US Ambassador will soon join Bin Laden.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347555840918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:04:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347555880382-30</Id><Topic><Title>Obama DOW Soars - Double Bush DOW</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347555422349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting, But Ask the Millions of Americans Out of Work Under Obama!!!! Un-Employment above 8% for Over Three Years, Inflation Heating UP, and Gas Prices Soaring! Obama is a Foreign Policy Buffoon! Yep, Americans Can Thank Obama for All of the Above! Obamaville!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347555880382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347556128981-31</Id><Topic><Title>Quote Of The Day</Title><Username>the_loading_dock</Username><Timestamp>1347490068963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 18:47:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, the SEALs Got America's Enemy Number One, the Electorate Will Get America's Enemy Number Two in November! Bye, bye, Obama!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347556128981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:08:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347556189472-32</Id><Topic><Title>Two do-nothing persons</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347545551289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:12:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finally Ben did something. That leaves only one.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347556189472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:09:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347556429912-33</Id><Title>Under Obama, America "Leads" from Behind! Or Nor at All.</Title><Msg>What a Weak, Pathetically Weak, President Obama is! Obama Looks Foolish and Hopeless on the International Stage. Obama is Shaming Americans!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347556429912</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:13:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347556646290-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obama DOW Soars - Double Bush DOW</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347555422349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney closed US business's, outsourced the jobs overseas, robbed the pensions, stashed the cash in foreign countries and he claims to be a patriot.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347556646290</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:17:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347556687228-35</Id><Title>Obama Says Bye, Bye Florida as Mitt Gains</Title><Msg>‘Whose Democratic Party?’ New ad questions Obama's relationship with Israel BY: Adam Kredo September 13, 2012 12:39 pm A new advertisement scheduled to run in Florida makes the case that President Obama has pushed the Democratic Party to embrace anti-Israel policies, according to a copy of the ad obtained by the Free Beacon. In the coming days, the Emergency Committee for Israel, a pro-Israel advocacy organization, will release an ad entitled, “Whose Democratic Party?” The spot, which will air during Sunday’s football game between the Miami Dolphins and the Oakland Raiders in what is being described as a “significant ad buy,” accuses Obama of leading his party to weaken the U.S.-Israel alliance. Coming on the heels of the Democrat’s controversial omission and contentious reinsertion of language in the party platform declaring Jerusalem as Israel’s capital, the ECI ad asks voters: “Is this still your Democratic Party?” Following footage of DNC delegates vociferously booing the pro-Israel declaration, the ad reminds viewers in the critical swing state that the Obama administration has on multiple occasions refused to state that Jerusalem is Israel’s capital. ECI Executive Director Noah Pollak told the Free Beacon that ECI wants Democratic voters to ask themselves if they are comfortable with the party’s direction under Obama. “The debacle at the DNC signifies where Obama is going in a second term. The first four years have been bad enough, but what happens when he has more ‘flexibility?’” Pollak wondered.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347556687228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:18:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347556722184-36</Id><Title>Air China 747 order</Title><Msg>CHICAGO (AP) -- Boeing Co. has locked in orders for five 747s for Air China. The plan for the order was first announced in March 2011, but it still needed Chinese government approval. Air China is one of China's three major state-owned airlines. Including this order, BA has 111 747's on order and has delivered 27 so far.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1347556722184</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:18:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347556838518-37</Id><Topic><Title>Obama DOW Soars - Double Bush DOW</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347555422349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agent, you are a Typical Brainwashed Liberal Nitwit! Got any Facts to Support your Nonsense?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347556838518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:20:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347556997738-38</Id><Title>Boeing CEO not worried?</Title><Msg>Boeing's CEO Jim McNerney said his company was not threatened by merger discussions between Europe's EADS , the parent of Airbus, and Britain's BAE Systems Plc ., not worried? Wow--- And of all the Dow Jones stocks today one only BA Boeing is down on the day, so far, with a 100 point ( the fed is doing QE run up), der James McNerney , if EADS gains a defense contractor they will have a 50-50 split instead of a 88-12 split in the total business model, so the military side of the EADS business now on par with the very last gravy train to BA the military contracting side. So Jim,, is this another “the customer will wait” management command ruling, put your head back in the sand Jim forget reality.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347556997738</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:23:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347557364573-39</Id><Topic><Title>Obama DOW Soars - Double Bush DOW</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347555422349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which facts are you most ignorant of:? Romney bankrupted business's? Romney outsourced jobs overseas? Romney robbed worker pensions? Romney stashed the cash in foreign countries? Romney dodged the military draft? Romney evaded taxes? Romney profited off the abortion business? There are much more but I wouldn't want to strain your tender sensibilities.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347557364573</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:29:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347557540963-40</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing CEO not worried?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347556997738</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whats EADS and BAE stocks doing?</Msg><Username>makboe</Username><Timestamp>1347557540963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:32:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347557548414-41</Id><Topic><Title>Obama DOW Soars - Double Bush DOW</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347555422349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got Any Facts to Support Your Nonsense... Didn't Think So Go Away, Little Nitwit.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347557548414</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:32:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347557618745-42</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing CEO not worried?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347556997738</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Easy. Not happy, sell quietly.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347557618745</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:33:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347557803691-43</Id><Title>Ryan Had to Put Up 10 Years of His Tax Returns</Title><Msg>For Mitt's VP vetters, 10 yrs tax returns were good for the goose, but they still won't give America a gander at HIS!</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347557803691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:36:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347557964121-44</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Had to Put Up 10 Years of His Tax Returns</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347557803691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:36:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why Won't the Affirmation Action Queen, Obama, release His College Grades Like All Other Presidentisl Candidates? What is Obama Hiding?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347557964121</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:39:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347558417360-45</Id><Title>Today's Gallup Tracking Poll</Title><Msg>PRINCETON, NJ -- President Barack Obama leading with 50% of registered voters now saying they would vote for him if the election were held today, up from 47%. With the concomitant two-point drop in Mitt Romney's support, Obama's advantage has expanded from one percentage point to six points.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347558417360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:46:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347558489549-46</Id><Title>Obama's World Collapsing Around Him!</Title><Msg>Now Behind in the Polls, Record UnEmployment, High Inflation, Soaring Gas Prices, and His Failed Foreign Policy Exposed! Americans are Dying Because of his Policies. Obama Looks Confused. Obama is a Hopeless Fool, Totally Lost and Overwhelmed. We Need Change in November, if Not Sooner.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347558489549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:48:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347558557204-47</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Had to Put Up 10 Years of His Tax Returns</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347557803691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:36:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are College Transcripts in the same bagger league as birth certificates?</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347558557204</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:49:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347558675289-48</Id><Topic><Title>Under Obama, America "Leads" from Behind! Or Nor at All.</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347556429912</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:13:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you want us to do in Syria Send in troops.....no Declare a no fly zone .....no Fund rebels with $$$ and supply some weapons.....maybe Work with others who have an interest if not more on what finally happens in Syria ......yes Bomb Syria - then Iran........no, not yet Put operatives on the ground to help rebels......possibly doing now Condemn the Assad regime.....already has What did I miss .....you add more and change some of my replies where you would differ</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1347558675289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347558753156-49</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's World Collapsing Around Him!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347558489549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:48:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What has this got to do with Boeing and why should I care what you have to say ??</Msg><Username>gpd8252</Username><Timestamp>1347558753156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:52:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347559380946-50</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's World Collapsing Around Him!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347558489549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:48:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Prez Romney sends troops in to Syria, Libya, Egypt, etc etc is he gonna keep his promise to cut taxes..............</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1347559380946</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:03:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347559443246-51</Id><Topic><Title>Today's Gallup Tracking Poll</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347558417360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:46:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>personally hope it gets to double digits</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1347559443246</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:04:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347559472081-52</Id><Title>What does the Air China order mean to BA shareholders?</Title><Msg>Boeing shareholders, here is a reason your stock has gone down 3% this year. The 747 has 111 orders, if none are cancelled, the Boeing “key statistics” shows a profit margin of 5.71% the 747-8 is 2 billion(2000 million) over budget and 2 years late (meaning the full 5.71% profit margin is less due to late delivery charges which will lower the shareholders stock price. The 747-8, a new plane, two years late to market, is priced at 350 million @5.71% full profit margin that would be a net of 20 million profit per delivered plane , if on time with no rework. So . taking the 2 billion over budget so far to develop the 747-8( , that is 2000 millions) and dividing by the profit of 20 million per plane at maximum profit, well that means it will take 100 plane delivered on the 747-8 model sold on time and without any rework and no discount for large plane orders just to break even! So the latest China delivery and those 111 other ordered 747-8 planes will not cover the costs to date. So thanks for the update on the 111 orders from the user who thinks building 747-8 on a late and over budget basis will mean anything to the shareholders except more no money in stock price BTW apple is up 68% year to date and Boeing is down 2.75 year to date. The 787 is about 20 to 30 billion over budget and 4 years late, so much worse than the 747-8, it will never make a profit. The Boeing company will go bankrupt like MD did, it will take 5 years.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347559472081</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:04:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347559566396-53</Id><Topic><Title>Quote Of The Day</Title><Username>the_loading_dock</Username><Timestamp>1347490068963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 18:47:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He would love to be able to answer that question....even if his answer would be NO but in his current (and lasting state) he can't express anything</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1347559566396</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:06:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347559972886-54</Id><Topic><Title>Today's Gallup Tracking Poll</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347558417360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:46:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No worriers Doc the debates are next month and Romeny is a horrible debater, only thing that got him though the Republicans debates was Money, Debating Obama he will look like a spoiled little schoolboy not getting his way. and we all Know how well Obama does speaking and debating should be quite entertaining I think.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1347559972886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:12:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347560753366-55</Id><Title>IMACCON AND THE OTHER RIGHT WINGERS</Title><Msg>Have gotten so ridiculous they are not worth conversing with. they know nothing and say nothing of importance.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1347560753366</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347561133608-56</Id><Title>Diplomatic killings</Title><Msg>Of four Americans is being handled now as a domestic violence instead of a major international incident. Sending the wrong message everywhere.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347561133608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347561580404-57</Id><Topic><Title>RASMUSSEN POLL: ROMNEY JUMPS BACK INTO LEAD...</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1347544248287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:50:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read Bonehead: "After the 2010 elections, the New York Times statistics wizard, Nate Silver, analyzed the polls produced by various polling organizations" "Silver analyzed 105 polls released by Rasmussen Reports and its subsidiary, Pulse Opinion Research, for Senate and gubernatorial races in numerous states across the country. The bottom line is that on average, Rasmussen's polls were off by 5.8% with a bias of 3.9% in favor of the Republican candidates." No one said anything about 2008. Way to point out your own idiocy.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1347561580404</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:39:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347561632787-58</Id><Title>Romney's Knee Jerk</Title><Msg>Romney’s irresponsible reaction to violence in the Mideast shows he plans to repeat the mistakes of George W. Bush</Msg><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1347561632787</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347562271105-59</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's Knee Jerk</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1347561632787</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely Not. Romney Rightfully Called Out Obama's Failed Foreign Policy... Obama is getting Americans Killed! Shame on Obama!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347562271105</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347562336592-60</Id><Title>Gold up $37</Title><Msg>Panic in the Financial and banking industry. QE-3 on the way - More phoney money being created without any wealth being created to back it up. Just more kicking the can down the road - the collapse is coming. Good luck to all you young people who think Obama is so cool. The ultimate bill will be yours to pay off. What will be really cool is for rich guys like myself to watch you living in poverty and despair while we live a live of ease on our gold and silver in foreign vaults. You envy and jealousy will be very entertaining.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1347562336592</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:52:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347562456942-61</Id><Topic><Title>Diplomatic killings</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347561133608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Last Time a Diplomat was Killed on Duty was in 1979... Yep, You Guessed Right, Jimmy Carter was President! Obama is a Foreign Policy Buffoon.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347562456942</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:54:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347562774232-62</Id><Topic><Title>Raygun had a recession and ran the debt to 4 trillion</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346422579112</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who was in the saddle?? seems to me that the responsibility was on Raygun who unfortunately couldnt operate a low budget movie production let alone the USA</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347562774232</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347562830545-63</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Most Americans think Obama will win</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347562552836</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:55:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are Getting More and More Ridiculous, Dik... Getting a Little scared, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347562830545</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:00:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347563123651-64</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing CEO not worried?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347556997738</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>never buy int he first place go with better stocks like apple up 68% year to date eh !" sell quietly" hummmmmm sounds like a BA person not wanting the truth to be known!</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347563123651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347563316310-65</Id><Title>Boeing Is Watching</Title><Msg>Why Bank of America Crushed the Market Today and Boeing Didn't By Anders Bylund | More Articles September 13, 2012 | Comments (0) The Dow Jones Industrial Index (INDEX: ^DJI ) jumped 0.9% when the Fed committed to buying $40 billion of mortgage debt a month until the job market bounces back. Federal interest rates will stay at today's record-level lows until at least 2015. These actions are obviously great news for American banks. Bank of America (NYSE: BAC ) jumped 3.5% on the news, JPMorgan Chase (NYSE: JPM ) added 1.5%, and American Express (NYSE: AXP ) took a 2% leap. But the Fed's action goes far beyond just lifting the burden of troubled mortgage loans off the bankers' shoulders. Twenty-nine of the 30 Dow components are trading in positive territory today as I write this. That's a rare show of broad market health. The lone laggard? Boeing (NYSE: BA ) fell ever so slightly, trading down a modest 0.1% at the moment. The defense and aerospace giant is staring down a proposed merger between European rivals BAE Systems and European Aeronautic, Defence &amp; Space. If approved, that deal would create a huge competitor that could leverage sheer economies of scale into fresh pressure on Boeing's largest contracts around the world.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1347563316310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:08:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347563375349-66</Id><Title>Obama Doesn't Know if He is Afoot or Horseback in Foreign Policy</Title><Msg>White House clarifies Obama’s statement that Egypt is not an ‘ally’ Posted By Josh Rogin Thursday, September 13, 2012 - 12:30 PM Share President Barack Obama didn't intend to signal any change in the U.S.-Egypt relationship last night when he said Egypt is not an "ally," the White House told The Cable today. In an interview with Telemundo Wednesday night, Obama said that the U.S. relationship with the new Egyptian government was a "work in progress," and emphasized that the United States is counting on the government of Egypt to better protect the U.S. Embassy in Cairo, which was attacked by protesters on Sept. 11. "I don't think that we would consider them an ally, but we don't consider them an enemy," Obama said. "They're a new government that is trying to find its way. They were democratically elected. I think that we are going to have to see how they respond to this incident." That comment had Egypt watchers scratching their heads, especially since technically, Egypt was designated as a Major Non-NATO Ally in 1989 when Congress first passed the law creating that status, which gives them special privileges in cooperating with the United States, especially in the security and technology areanas. White House spokesman Tommy Vietor told The Cable Thursday that the administration is not signaling a change in that status. "I think folks are reading way too much into this," Vietor said. "‘Ally' is a legal term of art. We don't have a mutual defense treaty with Egypt like we do with our NATO allies. But as the president has said, Egypt is longstanding and close partner of the United States, and we have built on that foundation by supporting Egypt's transition to democracy and working with the new government." Vietor referred to Obama's Wednesday phone call with Mohamed Morsy, during which Obama pressed the Egyptian president to ensure the safety and protection of U.S. personnel and facilities in Egypt. Morsy agreed to do so, according to a White House statement on the phone call. "The President said that he rejects efforts to denigrate Islam, but underscored that there is never any justification for violence against innocents and acts that endanger American personnel and facilities," the statement said. "President Morsi expressed his condolences for the tragic loss of American life in Libya and emphasized that Egypt would honor its obligation to ensure the safety of American personnel." Administration sources told The Cable that Obama's "ally" comment was not pre-arranged or prepared by staff and that the question was not anticipated. Nevertheless, Middle East experts said Obama's word choice and tone is likely a reflection of the administration's feeling that Morsy's reaction to the attacks has not been forceful enough. "I think it's a message from Obama that taking a less than assertive position on this is going to cost the [Egyptian] leadership at least rhetorically in the short term," said Andrew Tabler, senior fellow at the Washington Institute for Near East Studies. "We heard that the Muslim Brotherhood was going to be a cooperative partner and their actions and statements yesterday were not a good example of that." Pre-planned or not, the comments carry weight, Tabler said. He also noted that Obama was surely crafting his message not only for the Egyptians, but also for his American audience as well. The White House has come under fire for a press release from the Cairo embassy issued before the protest started that Republican challenger Mitt Romney slammed as an "apology for our values." As The Cable reported Wednesday, State Department officials in Washington objected to that statement before it was issued -- and the White House later disavowed it -- but it has nevertheless become an issue in the presidential campaign. "It's important to remember, Obama's comment happened in both a security and political context," Tabler said.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347563375349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:09:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347563425895-67</Id><Title>Obumer in Big Trouble - Bounce turns to dead thud.</Title><Msg>Romney is now supported by 18% of white Democrats. Romney has solidified the GOP vote and holds a 77-point lead among Republicans. That’s slightly larger than Obama’s 72-point advantage among Democrats. When “leaners” are included, it’s Romney 49% and Obama 47%. It is also important to note that Republicans are slightly more enthusiastic about voting in November than Democrats: Perhaps most significantly, Republicans are once again more engaged in the election than Democrats. Forty-nine percent (49%) of GOP voters are following the race on a daily basis. Among Democrats, just 42% are that interested.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1347563425895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347563473682-68</Id><Topic><Title>mid september 787 stats</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1347554215725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:36:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With two 787's delivered so far this month, the NYC787 blog indicates there is potential for another six 787's to be delivered this month. United (one), ANA (2), Qatar, JAL, Ethiopian.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1347563473682</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:11:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347563480785-69</Id><Topic><Title>Obumer in Big Trouble - Bounce turns to dead thud.</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1347563425895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:10:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What else can you pull out of your hat Mir?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1347563480785</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:11:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347563571700-70</Id><Topic><Title>Obumer in Big Trouble - Bounce turns to dead thud.</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1347563425895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:10:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>African Americans Will Stay Home in November as Their UnEmployment Rate is 18%... Pathetic, Mr. President!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347563571700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:12:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347563624495-71</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing CEO not worried?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347556997738</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>makboe or is that MD Boeing supporter then, , humm you want to know how EADS and BAE are doing ? the best answer if you want a comparison to BA is to compare BA to AAPL, which is up 68% year to date, BA is down about 3% why would you ask a question about BAE humm,any point here other than maybe---- if EADS can get it cheap and they do a lot of business with the USA government military programs then EADS who own Airbus can finally break into the Boeing share of defence contracting, Airbus has already taken about 50% of Boeings public transportation market share , so if EADS / BAE can take 50% of the military work from BAlike Airbus took away 50% of the Boeing transportation business, then BA stock price will decrease from 65 to 75 to about 35 to 45 , finally if EADS can get BAE at a cheap price then great for EADS , and do you have another point or is that good?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347563624495</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:13:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347563912951-72</Id><Topic><Title>Only One Question Now Remains...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347563754918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:15:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, Romney will Win in November... Ever Wonder Why Obama's Camp has Thousands of Lawyers on Standby? Obama's Campaign is Very Scared and for Good Reason.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347563912951</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347563996084-73</Id><Topic><Title>S &amp; P Pushing 1500 Today</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347563683338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Easy, When the Fed Prints More Money... Guess What, Dik, That Devalues the Dollar. Nitwit!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347563996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:19:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347564463194-74</Id><Topic><Title>mid september 787 stats</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1347554215725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:36:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get management, labor and suppliers on the same page and execute. It can be done.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347564463194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347564781050-75</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Is Watching</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1347563316310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sayuthink, good post. apple up 68 % ytd, BA down about 3% ytd, I purchased BAC at the start of the Fed speek today and did it 4 days ago too, it is easy to make 5-8% in a day but not on a dead cat bounce stock like BA., down about 3% for the year. it is so easy to trade a good stock or own a long term stock like AAPL and AAPL now has the new phone out on time with great reviews and going to sell and then maybe china will go with that phone now compatible for their largest phone company. So now appl is now set for huge run up. It does not matter that the fed is creating a huge problem down the road , with QE4, you make money on the current situation and then get out, it is simple. The election is comming and the fed chariman wants to keep his job and the current president wants to stay in office so guess which way the stock market will be going into the election ! BA 2 years late and 2 billion over budget on the 747-8, 787 20-30 billion over budget and 4 years late simple to figure out !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347564781050</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:33:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347564788727-76</Id><Topic><Title>Obumer in Big Trouble - Bounce turns to dead thud.</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1347563425895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:10:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO imaccom you are about the most clueless poster I ever seen is that why you hide from Demfasict these days?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1347564788727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:33:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347564882000-77</Id><Topic><Title>Gold up $37</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1347562336592</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ will still think Obama, Democrats and their massive debt is cool until reality hits them in the face like a baseball bat. The brainless think that some how they can spend and spend and force the rich guys to pay for all their insane spending. No matter what they do the debt will still end up on the backs of the middle class. I'm beginning to think they deserve it. You can call it trickle down debt or trickle up poverty but the results will be the same.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1347564882000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:34:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347565116154-78</Id><Topic><Title>Obumer in Big Trouble - Bounce turns to dead thud.</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1347563425895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:10:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who's Hiding? Maybe Obama is Hiding His Shame as His Foreign Policy Has Killed Four Americans.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347565116154</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347565273638-79</Id><Title>ALERT BA BEHIND DOW FOR 300 POINTS, !!!!</Title><Msg>LATER UP BACK 75+</Msg><Username>patrickstock</Username><Timestamp>1347565273638</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347565369830-80</Id><Topic><Title>RASMUSSEN POLL: ROMNEY JUMPS BACK INTO LEAD...</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1347544248287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:50:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's almost hilarious to watch Obama's clueless faithful retreat into denial.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1347565369830</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:42:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347565435736-81</Id><Topic><Title>Gold up $37</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1347562336592</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh yes you envy and you jealousy the bill was created by Bush Jr. Clinton handed him a surplus. pound sand you fake</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1347565435736</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:43:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347565562752-82</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's World Collapsing Around Him!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347558489549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:48:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do you get your information, the National Enquirer? Apparently you haven't seen the latest Gallup tracking poll. It shows Obama up 7 points over Romney. : ) Personally, I'm hoping for double-digit lead which shouldn't be hard given all the mistakes Romney's making.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1347565562752</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347565815924-83</Id><Title>Dems Still Support Islamic Egypt... Wants to Give Your Hard Earned Money to Them!</Title><Msg>And Dems Say They care About Women... The Fascist Islamics Will Take Away Women's Rights... Treat Women Like Dogs! What Hypocrisy! Pelosi: I Still Support U.S. Aid to Egypt 1:56 PM, SEP 13, 2012 • BY JOHN MCCORMACKSingle PagePrintLarger TextSmaller TextAlerts During a press conference in the Capitol on Thursday, Nancy Pelosi said that she opposes efforts to end U.S. aid to Egypt. "If they’re suggesting we should cut off assistance to Egypt," Pelosi said of some Republicans in Congress, "I don’t agree with that." "I think that the administration and even our friends in the region have said it’s really important for all parties, that is the private sector as well as the public sector, to invest in Egypt, because its economic success is important to the stability of the country, and that's important to the stability of the region, and the world, and global peace,” said Pelosi, leader of the House Democrats. The United States will send $1.5 billion in aid to Egypt this year.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347565815924</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:50:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347565964337-84</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's World Collapsing Around Him!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347558489549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:48:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Depends on Which Legitimate Poll One Believes.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347565964337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:52:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347566139333-85</Id><Topic><Title>Obumer in Big Trouble - Bounce turns to dead thud.</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1347563425895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:10:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how many Americans did Bush`s Foreign Policy Kill?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1347566139333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:55:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347566287360-86</Id><Title>Boeing is stron</Title><Msg>If it takes two foreign companies to join forces just to compete with Boeing, it is strong.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347566287360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:58:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347566417110-87</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is stron</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347566287360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:58:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry for typing error.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347566417110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:00:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347566479194-88</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's World Collapsing Around Him!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347558489549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:48:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I certainly Hope Romney Cuts Taxes for Every Tax Paying American. But, it Is Kind of Hard to Cut Taxes on About 50% of Tax Filing Americans That Do Not Pay Any Taxes, eh? The Dems Big Lie!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347566479194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:01:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347566495225-89</Id><Topic><Title>Gold up $37</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1347562336592</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The debt was created by Cheney-Bush and their cost-plus Iraq War. We do not need a Ryan-Romney cost-plus Iran War. We need the top 1% to pay their fair share of taxes! Perhaps revert to the tax rate Republican President Eisenhower had before Regans trickle down started!</Msg><Username>sistersara89</Username><Timestamp>1347566495225</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347566980307-90</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Is Watching</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1347563316310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing shareholders, here is a reason your stock has gone down 3% this year. The 747 has 111 orders, if none are cancelled, the Boeing “key statistics” shows a profit margin of 5.71% the 747-8 is 2 billion(2000 million) over budget and 2 years late (meaning the full 5.71% profit margin is less due to late delivery charges which will lower the shareholders stock price. The 747-8, a new plane, two years late to market, is priced at 350 million @5.71% full profit margin that would be a net of 20 million profit per delivered plane , if on time with no rework. So . taking the 2 billion over budget so far to develop the 747-8( , that is 2000 millions) and dividing by the profit of 20 million per plane at maximum profit, well that means it will take 100 plane delivered on the 747-8 model sold on time and without any rework and no discount for large plane orders just to break even! So the latest China delivery and those 111 other ordered 747-8 planes will not cover the costs to date. BTW apple is up 68% year to date and Boeing is down 2.75 year to date. The 787 is about 20 to 30 billion over budget and 4 years late, so much worse than the 747-8, and may never make a profit</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347566980307</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:09:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347567724791-91</Id><Title>Obama is a Foreign Policy Buffoon! Getting Americans Killed</Title><Msg>Bowing and Apologizing to the World Has Lead to The Murders of Four Americans in Muslim Countries! Obama is a Disgrace to Himself and to America.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347567724791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:22:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347567742880-92</Id><Title>Another Dumb Obama Gaff</Title><Msg>In an interview with Telemundo Wednesday night, Obama said that the U.S. relationship with the new Egyptian government was a "work in progress," and emphasized that the United States is counting on the government of Egypt to better protect the U.S. Embassy in Cairo, which was attacked by protesters on Sept. 11. "I don't think that we would consider them an ally, but we don't consider them an enemy," Obama said. "They're a new government that is trying to find its way. They were democratically elected. I think that we are going to have to see how they respond to this incident." That comment had Egypt watchers scratching their heads, especially since technically, Egypt was designated as a Major Non-NATO Ally in 1989 when Congress first passed the law creating that status, which gives them special privileges in cooperating with the United States, especially in the security and technology areanas.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1347567742880</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:22:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347568050715-93</Id><Topic><Title>Another Dumb Obama Gaff</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1347567742880</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:22:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Panic is setting in for the right wingers. Take a pill and relax! LoL</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1347568050715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347568368710-94</Id><Title>Democrats: Let's ban Profits</Title><Msg>Democrat Delegates are totally ignorant about even rudimentary economics. If there was ever any doubt their party has drifted into the hands of those with a communist mentality this video should clear that up for you. Just go to youtube and type in "Democrats: Let's Ban Profits! "</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1347568368710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:32:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347568503373-95</Id><Topic><Title>IMACCON AND THE OTHER RIGHT WINGERS</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1347560753366</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The right wing baggers are in a state of palpable desperation and panic. They see their idols self immolating before their very eyes yet they cling to fantasy and repeat the lies they are being force fed by the repub propaganda apparatus.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347568503373</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:35:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347568747324-96</Id><Topic><Title>S &amp; P Pushing 1500 Today</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347563683338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a stupid observation. Obviously you learned your econ from the repub propaganda apparatus.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347568747324</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:39:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347568852970-97</Id><Topic><Title>IMACCON AND THE OTHER RIGHT WINGERS</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1347560753366</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You Libs Getting Worried About November,eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347568852970</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:40:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347568890044-98</Id><Topic><Title>Obama up 10 points in Michigan, poll shows</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347562852171</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:00:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is leading everywhere except in the former slave states and low information rural areas..</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347568890044</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347568991478-99</Id><Topic><Title>S &amp; P Pushing 1500 Today</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347563683338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually from a Non Government School... and a Well respected One at That?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347568991478</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347569082285-100</Id><Topic><Title>Today's Gallup Tracking Poll</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347558417360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:46:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The key thing he is leading in the electoral college. The states with high levels of education and income are going strong for the President.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347569082285</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347569158964-101</Id><Topic><Title>Another Dumb Obama Gaff</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1347567742880</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:22:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, Panic is Setting in Within the Obama Campaign One Gaffe after Another</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347569158964</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:45:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347569248914-102</Id><Title>Great! Obama Administration said No Live Ammo for Marines</Title><Msg>U.S. Marines defending the American embassy in Egypt were not permitted by the State Department to carry live ammunition, limiting their ability to respond to attacks like those this week on the U.S. consulate in Cairo. Ambassador to Egypt Anne Patterson “did not permit U.S. Marine guards to carry live ammunition,” according to multiple reports on U.S. Marine Corps blogs spotted by Nightwatch. “She neutralized any U.S. military capability that was dedicated to preserve her life and protect the US Embassy.”</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1347569248914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:47:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347569296856-103</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's Knee Jerk</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1347561632787</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rmoney's advisors are virtually all Bush administration rethreads. The same people who gave us "WMD's"</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347569296856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:48:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347569298208-104</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is a Foreign Policy Buffoon! Getting Americans Killed</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347567724791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rmoney's disrespect for the murdered American foreign service workers, and the Libyans who died trying to defend them, disqualifies him as a Xtian. When he disrespects our president, he disrespects me and all Americans and disqualifies himself as a patriot. In total he has disqualified himself as a Man who should or could be president</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1347569298208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:48:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347569402249-105</Id><Title>Dick Cheney Father of: fake weopons of mass destruction cost plus Iraq War</Title><Msg>In November 1962 Cheney was convicted of driving while intoxicated (DWI). He was arrested for DWI again the following year.No one knows for sure how many times this drunkard drove drunk! When coward Cheney became eligible for the draft, during the Vietnam War, he received five draft deferments thanks to his clout! Halliburton reportedly allowed Cheney to retire, with a package estimated at $20 million.War Monger Cheney thanked them with many cost plus contracts! Do not allow Ryan to outdo Cheney with a centrifuges cost plus Iran War! We cannot afford another cost plus war!</Msg><Username>sistersara89</Username><Timestamp>1347569402249</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347569643590-106</Id><Title>Romney Looks Like Richard Nixon</Title><Msg>He has revealed himself as having the same character.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347569643590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:54:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347569702881-107</Id><Topic><Title>Dick Cheney Father of: fake weopons of mass destruction cost plus Iraq War</Title><Username>sistersara89</Username><Timestamp>1347569402249</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:50:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did Bill Clinton, Hillary Clinton, and John Kerry also Say Saddam Had and Previously Used WMDs Sister, Did You Fail History or Just Attend a Government Run School, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347569702881</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:55:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347569822089-108</Id><Topic><Title>Today's Gallup Tracking Poll</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347558417360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:46:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everybody except baggers know Rasmusson is in the employ of the repub propaganda apparatus.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347569822089</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347569920044-109</Id><Title>Obama Looking More and More the Guber Farmer, Jimmy Carter</Title><Msg>Obama Will be a Failed One Term President Like Peanut! Iran Helped Bring Down Carter....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347569920044</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:58:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347569987198-110</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Had to Put Up 10 Years of His Tax Returns</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347557803691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:36:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't stop you from talking birth certificates, did it.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347569987198</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:59:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347570095166-111</Id><Topic><Title>Obama DOW Soars - Double Bush DOW</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347555422349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You appear to be out of work. How long since you got fired?</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347570095166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347570345435-112</Id><Topic><Title>Obama DOW Soars - Double Bush DOW</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347555422349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, I'm a Happily Retired CFD Engineer. And, you???</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347570345435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347570442021-113</Id><Topic><Title>IMACCON AND THE OTHER RIGHT WINGERS</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1347560753366</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see your attitude is "What? Me Worry".</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347570442021</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:07:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347570658577-114</Id><Topic><Title>S &amp; P Pushing 1500 Today</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347563683338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ignorance of these cretins is unbelieveable. They parrot El Flushbo et al and claim they went to school.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347570658577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:10:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347570886476-115</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Looks Like Richard Nixon</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347569643590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:54:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nixon may have been an unscrupulous liar but at least he wore the uniform during WW2. Romney is an unscrupulous liar who has never served his country.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347570886476</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:14:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347571226440-116</Id><Title>How's Obama's Fundamental Transformation Working Out for You America?</Title><Msg>High unemployment Highest 4 year Deficits Middle Class families lose $4,000 a year. The world hates us Down Graded Bond Rating Yup, Obumer has the US of A fundamentally looking more and more like the old Soviet Union.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1347571226440</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:20:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347571298310-117</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Looks Like Richard Nixon</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347569643590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:54:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Which Branch of the Military Did the Affirmative Action Queen, Obama, Serve? You Libs are Too Easy!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347571298310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347571394273-118</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Looks Like Richard Nixon</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347569643590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:54:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama never served his country but he has served several communist and fascist countries.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1347571394273</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347571732917-119</Id><Topic><Title>How's Obama's Fundamental Transformation Working Out for You America?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1347571226440</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:20:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's Plan is Working Like All Socialist Economic Plans... All Total Failures Unless You Don't Count North Korea or Cuba... People are Eating Grass to Survive.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347571732917</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347571873686-120</Id><Title>Mitt Romney’s Total Neocon Meltdown</Title><Msg>Romney’s irresponsible reaction to violence in the Mideast shows he plans to repeat the mistakes of George W. Bush. Does the GOP really think that’s what the American people want? We know that we saw something appalling yesterday, in Mitt Romney’s response to the violence in Cairo and Benghazi, but let’s not lose sight of the fact that we’re witnessing something historic too. This isn’t simply the end of the Republican Party’s decades-long political advantage on foreign policy that we’re observing. Rather, we are simultaneously able to see how the party is reacting to and dealing with the disappearance of that advantage. It’s like those villains in the movies who not only are dying, but who register on their face that they can’t comprehend they’re dying, that Hell has finally called their malevolent number, like Julia Roberts’s husband in Sleeping With The Enemy. God, it’s fun to watch. But it’s also a reminder of the danger of handing power to this man and the people he would bring in with him. Marx would be completely dead if we didn’t have the Republicans around to prove him right every so often. Yet here we are in 2012, able to say definitively that the moment of greatest apparent Republican foreign-policy triumph—spring and summer of 2003—contained, in good Marxian fashion, the seeds of its own destruction. That’s when neoconservatism and its grand theories seemed to be on the cusp of a great vindication. The Iraq effort became disastrous, but even into 2005, with the advent of the great uprising in Lebanon and the blessed end of the Syrian occupation, for which Bush deserved and received some credit, no honest liberal skeptic could be completely sure that Wolfowitz &amp; co. had everything wrong. [...] Source, the dailybeastdotcom.</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1347571873686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:31:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347572019742-121</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Looks Like Richard Nixon</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347569643590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:54:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney fled the country when it was at war in VietNam.. He sought four deferments to evade military service during a time of war. He is a pig who inherited a fortune and used it to feast on Americans and hid the gains in foreign lands. He has never paid his dues to this country.. President Obama was six years old during VietNam..</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347572019742</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:33:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347572237710-122</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Looks Like Richard Nixon</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347569643590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:54:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Clinto Fled to Where to Void Viet Nam, ummm?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347572237710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:37:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347572452780-123</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Looks Like Richard Nixon</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347569643590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:54:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Romney looked weak today, At one point, he had a certain slight grimace on his face when he was taking tough questions from the reporters, and I thought, 'He looks like Richard Nixon.'" Peggy Noonan, Republican Reporter</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347572452780</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:40:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347572472070-124</Id><Topic><Title>Dems Still Support Islamic Egypt... Wants to Give Your Hard Earned Money to Them!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347565815924</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:50:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your made up lie about Democrats and the conclusions you reach are the product of your mild paranoid schizophrenia. Medical science can help you with all the new medications available for psychotics like your self. So get your butt off this board and go get treated</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347572472070</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:41:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347572534593-125</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney’s Total Neocon Meltdown</Title><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1347571873686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney Righfully Called Obama to Account for Apologizing to the Terrorists Rather than Initially Condemming the Terrorists. Obama's Foreign is a Total Mess It is Obama That is in a Total meltdown!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347572534593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347573141985-126</Id><Title>Obama's Total Failure to Lead</Title><Msg>Obama' Foreign Policy Failures are Embarrassing and Getting Americans Killed. Obama has Become ten Joke of the World... All World Leaders Laugh at Him! The Buffoon in Chief!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347573141985</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:52:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347574061816-127</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: Rash. Crass. Shameful. Craven. Contemptible. Irresponsible. BAD.</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347573862737</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:04:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Deserved to Be Called into Account for His Failed Foreign Policy... Apologizing to the Terrorists? Obama is Shameful</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347574061816</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:07:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347574395746-128</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing CEO not worried?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347556997738</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Comparing AAPL to BA is like comparing apples to oranges.AAPl makes products that are mass produce and available to the public at affordable prices while BA makes airplanes and defense products that mostly cannot be mass produced and their customers are limited to airlines and government and large corporations. In my lifetime, I maybe able to buy several AAPL products but I bet you that I can never own a Boeing airplane although just fly in some of them as a passenger.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347574395746</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:13:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347574601133-129</Id><Topic><Title>Mind-Boggling (Again)</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347574177046</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:09:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's Failed and Pathetic Foreign Policy is, in part, to Blame for the Deaths of Four Americans... When Will Obama Learn that Bowing and Apologizing Doesn't Work and Only Makes Obama Look Weak! Which He Is.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347574601133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:16:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347574886013-130</Id><Topic><Title>Dems Still Support Islamic Egypt... Wants to Give Your Hard Earned Money to Them!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347565815924</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:50:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You leftys are all insane. You need help to understand things.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1347574886013</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:21:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347574977402-131</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Total Failure to Lead</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347573141985</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has everyone one on food stamps so they will vote for him. o has convinced everyone to get food stamps and not work or get and education. obama sucks</Msg><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1347574977402</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:22:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347578211046-132</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney Is 'Likely To Lose'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347577888949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:11:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So What Just Another Biased "Opinion" From PMSNBC... What's New.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347578211046</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:16:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347578501769-133</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh’s ‘Ringing’ Endorsement, Another Bad GOP Rape Analogy, and More</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347576110817</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:41:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's Campaign in Total Panic Mode... foreign Policy Under Attack... For Good Reason!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347578501769</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:21:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347579267471-134</Id><Title>Obama Brings Hope and Change to the Middle East</Title><Msg>looks more like smoke and flames ...</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1347579267471</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:34:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347579961569-135</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: Rash. Crass. Shameful. Craven. Contemptible. Irresponsible. BAD.</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347573862737</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:04:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you have a link to an Obama apology?</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1347579961569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:46:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347580113477-136</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: Rash. Crass. Shameful. Craven. Contemptible. Irresponsible. BAD.</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347573862737</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:04:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice to see you are consistent in your detachment from reality. Only those who love untruths cling to the "apology" talking point. You and the truth seem to never meet.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1347580113477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:48:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347580159004-137</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh’s ‘Ringing’ Endorsement, Another Bad GOP Rape Analogy, and More</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347576110817</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:41:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got any links that talk about the panic? would love to read it.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1347580159004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:49:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347580591431-138</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh’s ‘Ringing’ Endorsement, Another Bad GOP Rape Analogy, and More</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347576110817</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:41:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dims trying to construct mountains from mole hills . BTW, how much did B.O. spend "liberating" Libya ? Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347580591431</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:56:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347580637032-139</Id><Title>Rmoney a "perfectly lubricated weathervane on the important issues of the day..."</Title><Msg>So said John Hunstman(R) and fellow mormon during the GOP debates. Sen. John Kerry, D-Mass., jabbed Romney for his seemingly shifting stance on Libya last week during the Democratic National Convention. “Talk about being for it before you were against it,” Kerry said. “Mr. Romney, here’s a little advice. Before you debate Barack Obama on foreign policy, you better finish the debate with yourself.” More and more evidence of Myth Rmoney as a pathetic excuse for human being.</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347580637032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:57:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347580777834-140</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Brings Hope and Change to the Middle East</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1347579267471</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:34:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The whole place is a terror fest . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347580777834</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:59:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347580859988-141</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney Is 'Likely To Lose'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347577888949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:11:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>imac...you right-wing extremists/neo-cons/baggers are THE true danger to America and everything for which she stands</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347580859988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:00:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347581040601-142</Id><Title>Embassy Warned of Attacks 48 Hours Prior, But Obama Did Nothing</Title><Msg>Shame on Obama as He Now Has American Blood on His Hands. A Do Nothing, Coward President. Bow and Apologize.... Pathetic! Get the Link Yourself, You Lazy Liberals... UK Press, Hint</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347581040601</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:04:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347581174255-143</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Total Failure to Lead</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347573141985</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's how Liberals can afford the time to post slander on a stock message board 24/7 . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347581174255</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:06:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347581189996-144</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney a "perfectly lubricated weathervane on the important issues of the day..."</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347580637032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:57:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We Think You Have Your Facts Scrambled... Like Your Brain!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347581189996</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:06:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347581249964-145</Id><Topic><Title>Embassy Warned of Attacks 48 Hours Prior, But Obama Did Nothing</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347581040601</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:04:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got a link?</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1347581249964</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347581361841-146</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Brings Hope and Change to the Middle East</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1347579267471</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:34:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dimboyjetski, what's the score, Sikh Temple shooting in Wisconsin but then Myth Rmoney doesn't know the difference between a Sikh and a sheik same as most all right-wing faux-news dittohead haters</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347581361841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:09:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347581506824-147</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney Is 'Likely To Lose'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1347577888949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:11:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>iamacommie, what's new is repub insiders now recognize their Great White Hope is a beached whale.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1347581506824</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347581549560-148</Id><Topic><Title>Another Dumb Obama Gaff</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1347567742880</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:22:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What he meant was that he helped put the dims terrorist friends in charge, and now can't figure out why they are not grateful . Liberal theory once again collapses when met with reality . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347581549560</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:12:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347581704325-149</Id><Topic><Title>Embassy Warned of Attacks 48 Hours Prior, But Obama Did Nothing</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347581040601</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:04:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A link wasn't that little boy. And you read the news from a strange site like this? Wierdo</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1347581704325</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:15:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347582078190-150</Id><Topic><Title>Russian ships displayed at DNC tribute to vets</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1347424678756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 00:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's totally hillarious if you consider the farce of dims puffing their chests out, and trying to look like rough, tough warriors, when they are in truth, little weeners . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347582078190</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347582327921-151</Id><Title>Navy Seal Says Biden Reminds Him of "Someone's Drunk Uncle"</Title><Msg>In the Book "No Easy Day" a Seal Team leader, after observing Jumpin Joe Biden in person said he reminded him of "someone's drunk uncle". Biden was Obama's first major decision and it's been down hill ever since</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1347582327921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347582376721-152</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney’s Total Neocon Meltdown</Title><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1347571873686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep up the good work, ChloroxCowboy! The truth hurts, only if it not told!! Myth Rmoneys bushco-era neo-con advisors are as bad his koch-brothers backer as well as his own bad judgement(s)...!!! the dailybapsycho</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347582376721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347582517251-153</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney’s Total Neocon Meltdown</Title><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1347571873686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>imac robot, you are more stinky than a turd left by a FSO or embassy staff</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347582517251</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:28:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347582840962-154</Id><Topic><Title>Washington Post article says Republicans spoke out against Romney but fails to mention who they are. What a rag.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347582262156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:24:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are supposed to aim, then shoot otherwise you end up like myth rmoney and his neo-con, koch-sucking backers and advisors and maybe only shoot yourself in the foot, the biggest appendage below your waist lol</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347582840962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:34:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347583179618-155</Id><Topic><Title>Navy Seal Says Biden Reminds Him of "Someone's Drunk Uncle"</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1347582327921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:25:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden and Obama Fools... SEALs Got America's Number One Enemy, American Voters Will Get America's Number Two Enemy in November!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347583179618</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:39:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347583378074-156</Id><Title>Obama Increases Lead Over Romney</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON, Sept 13 (Reuters) - President Barack Obama widened his lead over Republican challenger Mitt Romney to 7 percentage points in a Reuters/Ipsos poll of likely voters on Thursday, the latest survey to show the Democrat ahead in the run-up to the Nov. 6 election. The daily online poll asked likely voters over the previous four days which candidate they would pick if the vote took place today, with 48 percent choosing Obama and 41 percent picking Romney. The gap has been widening since Obama grabbed the lead in the rolling poll on Sept. 7 when he scooped up 46 percent of likely voters to Romney's 44 percent after the Democratic convention.</Msg><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1347583378074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:42:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347583550662-157</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Increases Lead Over Romney</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1347583378074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:42:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but then who is counting, +10M voters... Obama more likely by 20M</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347583550662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:45:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347584106742-158</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney’s Total Neocon Meltdown</Title><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1347571873686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>greglovestomtomax the raygun/bushco/boltonmoron era response to beirut marine barracks bombing letalone the libya/khaadafy lockerbie bombing etc. seemed to take second base to making secret and illegal deals with iran with weaponry and money for hostages to fight the contras in nicarragua (remember that fiasco and waste of taxpayers monies) not to mention them abandoning of the northern alliance/freedom fighters in afghanistan giving rise to the taliban and al-quaida, and thus 9/11, on top all for oily koch-sucker monies and 20 year oil contracts in Iraq anybody who listens to a neo-con republican fascist or windsock Rmoney is an enemy of the state and responsible for the death of good Americans</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347584106742</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347584107354-159</Id><Title>Where Was Big Dumb AlGore ?</Title><Msg>Why wasn't he at the dim bulb convention ? Is it because he is an even bigger embarrassment than Joe, I got yer chains here, Bison ? Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347584107354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:55:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347584580855-160</Id><Topic><Title>50% Trust Romney More on Economy, 43% Trust Obama More Its all about jobs now that</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347584283950</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:58:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently not. With Mitt doing his best Sarah Palin imitation he is making everyone realize what his true colors are.</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1347584580855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:03:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347585138233-161</Id><Topic><Title>Where Was Big Dumb AlGore ?</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347584107354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:55:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Algore Was Too Busy Spewing Carbon From His Private Jet and Large House That Uses Four times the Energy of a Regular Sized House Gore is the Epitomy of Hypocrisy</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347585138233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347586285237-162</Id><Topic><Title>Under Obama the economy is crashing, The Arab world is now killing US Ambassadors the Muslim Brotherhood is kin to Obama</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347585963311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:26:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's Carefully Planned World is Falling Apart! Record UnEmployment, Surging Gas Prices and Now Blood on His Hands... The Embassy Was Forewarned of Attacks and Obama Did Nothing! Shameful</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347586285237</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:31:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347586311744-163</Id><Topic><Title>Navy Seal Says Biden Reminds Him of "Someone's Drunk Uncle"</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1347582327921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:25:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please provide proof! Lyin' Ryan: "I did a 2 hr, 50 min marathon", in full battle gear then took out a contigent of islamo-basterds alongside of Mittens 'lwho onged to be in VN' Rmoney... - the same year the lyin' 'Ryan claimed to have done his great feat, I was approximatyely 20 years older, and managed to complete a 20KM in full battle gear in under 4 hours and Iam even more fiscally conservative than he, maye I should move to WI and be the VP candidate for Myth Rmoney... Joe Biden did more to save America from the Great Republicon Recession than Myth Rmoney and lyin' Ryan together in a combine accident...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347586311744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347586487491-164</Id><Topic><Title>Navy Seal Says Biden Reminds Him of "Someone's Drunk Uncle"</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1347582327921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:25:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe Biden is a Buffoon!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347586487491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:34:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347586774961-165</Id><Title>Under Obama we are now above the hole where Boosh and republicon-fascists left us</Title><Msg>by all measurable parameters and Myth Rmoney and the RWNJ's want to dig the hole deeper on all parameters including their idioytic foreign policies/// hmmm... the neo-con republicon fascist Plan For The New American Centuryw which Myth Rmoney has adopted, advocated a new Pearl Harbor et voila 9/11 happened, and then they invaded Iraq based 100% on lies... creating the great Boosh Recession/hole FACTS!</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347586774961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:39:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347587103035-166</Id><Title>Myth Rmoney's first cabinet meeting would go like this...</Title><Msg>attack Iran for Israel to make money... not too dissimialer from Boosh43 first caibinent meeting " invade Iraq" a war which will pay for itself via OIL (Operation Iraq Liberation) Never make that mistake again! yet the poor, low-IQ right-wingers will...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347587103035</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:45:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347587189570-167</Id><Topic><Title>Myth Rmoney's first cabinet meeting would go like this...</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347587103035</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:45:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and all the bigots, haters, and playin' stoopid right-wingers</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347587189570</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:46:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347588336441-168</Id><Topic><Title>Under Obama we are now above the hole where Boosh and republicon-fascists left us</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347586774961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not exactly. Obama deepened the hole by extending the illegal wiretapping, authorizing the murder of American citizens, and demanding state secret protections in court far beyond what Bush ever did. You're dreaming.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1347588336441</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347589242710-169</Id><Topic><Title>Where Was Big Dumb AlGore ?</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347584107354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:55:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The dim bulb elite will always have plenty of fuel to burn, and whatever other resources they care to use no matter how much it hurts the environment . It's the masses "under them" that will reduce their carbon foot print for the greater good, just like in the old Soviet Empire . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347589242710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:20:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347589816113-170</Id><Title>Hope and Change Was a Myth</Title><Msg>... and a poorly defined myth at that . What's real is the 16 trillion dollar national debt, of which B.H.O. and the dims in congress are responsible for almost 6 trillion dollars worth in only four years . Change you can quantify, but only with scientific notation on most calculators . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347589816113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:30:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347590351444-171</Id><Topic><Title>Under Obama we are now above the hole where Boosh and republicon-fascists left us</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347586774961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and updating to IE9 while getting less yahooty services the flow of electrons my friend, the flow of electrons "beyond what Bush ever did..." hey did they ever catch the USS Cole bombers, you know the ones, who disintgrated upon impact ala the plane which hit the pent-a-gone, and that field in Pennsylvania</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347590351444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:39:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347591011774-172</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney’s Total Neocon Meltdown</Title><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1347571873686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>7-1 8-2 10-3 0-1 0-2... Re: Mitt Romney’s Total Neocon Meltdown</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347591011774</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:50:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347592014649-173</Id><Topic><Title>Navy Seal Says Biden Reminds Him of "Someone's Drunk Uncle"</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1347582327921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:25:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>B.O. keeps oaf Biden around so he'll look smart by comparison . Biden is also good insurance against assasination . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347592014649</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:06:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347592244716-174</Id><Topic><Title>Under Obama the economy is crashing, The Arab world is now killing US Ambassadors the Muslim Brotherhood is kin to Obama</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347585963311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:26:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Moslem Brohood has played Obammer and the dims for the fools they are . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347592244716</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:10:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347592417590-175</Id><Topic><Title>Navy Seal Says Biden Reminds Him of "Someone's Drunk Uncle"</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1347582327921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:25:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone posted the other day that Joe Biden was worth less than $400K and said he must be doing something Wrong I say he is doing something Right and always had been a much more decent man than lyin' Ryan who stinks more in August in D.C. another 'bad' myth rmonoey choice IMHO you SRWNJMFERS</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347592417590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347592668109-176</Id><Topic><Title>Navy Seal Says Biden Reminds Him of "Someone's Drunk Uncle"</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1347582327921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:25:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's in the book psycho, how am I going to prove it on a message board, the chapter that talks about the aftermath of the raid, Seals weren't too excited about Obama either but "drunk uncle" is the best description of Jumpin Joe I've come across</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1347592668109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:17:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347593546178-177</Id><Topic><Title>Navy Seal Says Biden Reminds Him of "Someone's Drunk Uncle"</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1347582327921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:25:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we do not need your boo-hoo's come the novenmber slasughter of myth rmoney and lyin' ryan what we need is the most good for the most people... le creme rises "Navy Seal Says Biden Reminds Him of.." is for RWNJ #$%$ to continue the thread EADS and something are consolidating according EU myth rmoney rules but then... it is not politccal Watch out for Our Republic, Obama/Biden will, myth rmoney and lyin' ryan will sell it out IMHO what Clint Eastwood said he heard from an empty chair...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347593546178</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:32:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347593639491-178</Id><Topic><Title>Hope and Change Was a Myth</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347589816113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Herr Bummer spent over six times what the "two separate wars" cost in half the time, making Bush look miserly . And what has der Bommer got to show for it ? Zip, that's what . P.S. Just how much did that war in Libya cost us ? ( by "us", I don't mean the nearly 50% of U.S. citizens who pay no federal income tax, probably including Liberals with the time to post dim propaganda 24/7 on a stock message board .) Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347593639491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:33:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347593769160-179</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Looks Like Richard Nixon</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347569643590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:54:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IO was thinking he looks like Errnest Scared Stupid but with a better paint job</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1347593769160</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:36:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347594067392-180</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Looks Like Richard Nixon</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347569643590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:54:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Richard Nixon, you mean the guy who had to pull America out of Johnson's War ? Guys who look like Nixon must be fated to clean up after dim messes . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347594067392</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:41:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347594212047-181</Id><Title>Barak O'bammer Looks Like Edi Amin Dada</Title><Msg>... only skinnier . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1347594212047</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:43:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347594518500-182</Id><Title>Strike Time</Title><Msg>Nuff Said. Time to walk the line - no more waiting til January/February to "bust a move". Oct 7th we vacate the premises unless Boeing comes to their senses.</Msg><Username>ev3044</Username><Timestamp>1347594518500</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:48:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347594678021-183</Id><Title>Strike Time</Title><Msg>Nuff Said. Time to walk the line - no more waiting til January/February to "bust a move". Oct 7th we vacate the premises unless Boeing comes to their senses.</Msg><Username>ev3044</Username><Timestamp>1347594678021</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:51:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>