<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345981325715-1</Id><Topic><Title>787 update</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1345913816133</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 12:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks!!!!</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1345981325715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 07:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345984991000-2</Id><Title>Rich Daddy Dudes</Title><Msg>There is no difference between Willard Mittford Romney and George Bush Jr. Both are out of touch spoiled rich kids who came from rich daddy's, who only look out for their one percenter friends. Did I mention with the exact same policies,</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1345984991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345989688430-3</Id><Topic><Title>Ah, now I understand the neocons on this board!</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1345928786716</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 17:06:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correct, us neocons, homophobs, birthers, racists, etc., want parents to have the authority in what their kids learn, and how they learn it, not the government.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1345989688430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:01:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345992935151-4</Id><Topic><Title>Ah, now I understand the neocons on this board!</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1345928786716</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 17:06:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Faux News Channel and the RWNJ media ain't lairnin', it's republiconned fascists propaganda...</Msg><Username>republicanfascists</Username><Timestamp>1345992935151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:55:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345993943354-5</Id><Topic><Title>Qatar 787 delivery due 8-25 (saturday)</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1345741083488</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 12:58:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1345993943354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:12:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345994031690-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's America 2016 Playing Well... 4th Place</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1345934849563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 18:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2016 as the usher in theatre says, why this when could see the new Bourne film... Chart Rank All Time Domestic 4,691 Top Movies in the Past 365 Days 155 Just like Sarah Palin's movie called the Undefeated, another moeny-losing RWNJ 'blockbuster', total gross $116k, Chart Rank All Time Domestic 8,531 Fahrenheit 9/11 - total gross $119M, opening weeked $23M Chart Rank All Time Domestic 377 Yearly 2004 17</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1345994031690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345994472921-7</Id><Title>Ron Paul on Romney: ‘I don’t fully endorse him’</Title><Msg>but then who would except a goose-stepping republiconned fascist... Mr. Paul, in an interview, said convention planners had offered him an opportunity to speak under two conditions: that he deliver remarks vetted by the Romney campaign, and that he give a full-fledged endorsement of Mr. Romney. He declined. "It wouldn't be my speech," Mr. Paul said. "That would undo everything I've done in the last 30 years. I don't fully endorse him for president."</Msg><Username>republicanfascists</Username><Timestamp>1345994472921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345995314480-8</Id><Topic><Title>Ron Paul on Romney: ‘I don’t fully endorse him’</Title><Username>republicanfascists</Username><Timestamp>1345994472921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:21:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul is the only politician of integrity on either side.</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1345995314480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:35:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345997813348-9</Id><Title>An Inconvenient Truth - Global Warming/Hurricanes/GOP deniers</Title><Msg>Anthropogenic warming over the next century will lead to an increase in the numbers of very intense hurricanes. Anthropogenic warming by the end of the 21st century will likely cause hurricanes to have substantially higher rainfall rates than present-day hurricanes. Global Warming: Effect on Hurricanes Written by YeSeul Kim, Erika Granger, Katie Puckett, Cankutan Hasar, and Leif Francel Hurricanes Effects of Global Warming Hurricanes are affected by a wide range of factors, however the two most important factors in determining the potential intensity of a hurricane are sea surface temperature (SST) and the temperature at the storm top. The equation for maximum wind velocity is as follows (Emanuel, 1999): Graph 2: The part of the equation that is circled in red is the part that we are concerned about. It means that climate temperature affects potential hurricane intensity through the difference between absolute SST and absolute temperature at the storm top (upper troposphere to lower stratosphere) divided by the latter. Therefore if climate change causes SST to rise faster than atmospheric temperature, potential wind velocities should increase, and, therefore, potential hurricane intensity should increase as well. This discrepancy between the rate of change of SST and the rate of change of atmospheric temperature (in the vicinity of the height of the storm top) has been observed in a careful analysis by Kerry Emanuel. This is corroborated by the Board of Atmospheric Sciences and Climate (2000). As hurricanes reach higher intensities, the time it takes for them to build up to those higher intensities and then to dissipate will have increased from that of lower intensity hurricanes (Emmanuel, 2005).</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1345997813348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:16:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345998120000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Neil Armstrong dies . . .</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1345927443000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 16:44:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1345998120000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:22:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345998881996-11</Id><Topic><Title>WE NEED HELP</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345567841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:50:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney is a business problem solver....he has proved this several times, once with a former olympics that was in the red when he took over. he layed out good plans and left it in the black for next group.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345998881996</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346000152451-12</Id><Title>Boeing 777X</Title><Msg>A repeat of the CEO decision on the 737 for the 777X "and the customer will wait", the last time a result of 1000 orders for Airbus and two all 737 carriers switched to airbus,. Boeing has no money to develop the 777X, resulting from the spent 34 billion fixing the 4 year late and outsourced 787. In related stock market news apple is releasing two new products, and the apple shareholders have made over 60% gains year to date while Boeing airplane orders ahve earned the Boeing shareholders a loss for the year. If Boeing shareholders and pump buddies had been in apple for the past month they would have made $18000 on a $100000 investment instead of a loss of money on Boeing. All good for Apple going forward now that samsung lost a judgement for billion dollars going to Apple in the legal fight with apple. Next Apple is pressing forward to take away both samsung and google profits . Finally two new apple products on time and on budget ."plans to unveil its so-called "iPad mini" and its next iPhone at two separate events in the next two months. So that is how to pick a good stock , new products on time and budget, over 25% profit margin,stock beating Boeing from going back 15 years to this year all the time better than Boeing so why are you listing airplane orders and watching a dead cat bouce stock like Boeing ? Paid pumper for Boeing or not very bright, both are not the way to go. So for all the Boeing pumper,spammer,and bashers how are those plane orders working for your stock price? the Boeing company puts out the airplane orders so what are you doing, does any investor care about plane orders when Boeing is 34 billion in debt ona 6% return</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1346000152451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:55:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346003340091-13</Id><Topic><Title>The Choice Is Clear</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1345925091615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 16:04:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right about this one Dik... Either one chooses the non-incumbent candidate that grew up in America and has American values or the incumbent who grew up, err...has values...err...Yes, the choice IS clear! Of course, many of those Americans that O's Scare will "help" are neither deserving or "civilized"! Ask not what you can do for your country, but what can your country do for you right DIM?</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1346003340091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 13:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346004363416-14</Id><Topic><Title>The Choice Is Clear</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1345925091615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 16:04:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Accurate post. Amazing that a man named Obama Soetoro who came out of nowhere was never vetted for the Presidency and even though ineligible should STILL actually BE President staggers the imagination.</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1346004363416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 14:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346005979293-15</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid's Lie about Romney paying Zero Taxes...</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1345414393000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 18:13:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harry Reid is a doofus and a liar.</Msg><Username>j_robert_wallace</Username><Timestamp>1346005979293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 14:32:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346006171215-16</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan, the next Veep, Hammers Obama!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1345663581000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-22 15:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See Obama in all his LYING glory!</Msg><Username>j_robert_wallace</Username><Timestamp>1346006171215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346015508000-17</Id><Title>Gawd Telling Americans Not To Vote For Mexican Mormon Mitt</Title><Msg>it's a miracle, isn't it gawd dogs? http://content.usatoday.com/communities/onpolitics/post/2012/08/gop-convention-cancels-events-hurricane-isaac/1</Msg><Username>yupitsmedex2004</Username><Timestamp>1346015508000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:11:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346021355362-18</Id><Title>new message board</Title><Msg>It took a bit of time to figure out how to delete messages. However, in the old format they would not show on the screen and in the new format they still show in a lighter text. That means you have to search theu the pages for the posts related to BA. I dont know who came up with that idea but they are obviously mot a message board user. They also have a limit on the number of users you can ignore. And I have not found a way to edit the ignore list using the new format to remove really old usernames in the ignore list. So I have to go to a stock mesage board that is not using the new format to get to the ignore list to edit it. So while I am still posting, I am also looking for a new (non yahoo) finance/potfolio source that is better and easier to use. It is a shame that some people change things thinking they are making it better only to drive users away to other providers.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346021355362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346039461743-19</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing 777X</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1346000152451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:55:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>to do the 37NG MAX, all they had to do was hang a good engine on the already developed wing of the NG. for the 777X, they cannot do that, yet. sure, if there is a large enuff development in a large hi bypass engine with enuff thrust, they could hang on the current 77 wing. they dont have the right skills left to come up with a new 77X wing, and that will cause problems for their "new" design.</Msg><Username>wuzafan</Username><Timestamp>1346039461743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 23:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>