<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346472127898-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Retains Lead Through Dismal Puke Convention</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346449686988</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:48:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This recent poll showed Mitt Romney trailing way behind President Obama..." Why not cite a poll or two that did not hugely oversample dumbocrats and that were taken all over, not just the inner cities?</Msg><Username>cws2012wc</Username><Timestamp>1346472127898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 00:02:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346472767949-2</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood Pokes Obama in the Eye</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346379252079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:14:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clint Eastwood is a Boeing guy, he worked as an expiditer on the 727/737 line in Renton long ago. The Outlaw Josey Wales (1976) Josey Wales: Now remember, when things look bad and it looks like you're not gonna make it, then you gotta get mean. I mean plumb, mad-dog mean. 'Cause if you lose your head and you give up then you neither live nor win. That's just the way it is.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1346472767949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 00:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346473312103-3</Id><Topic><Title>Ryans Speech "attempt to set record for greatest number of blatant lies"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346456826975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is mitt going to create jobs. He has not mentioned one specific plan. Remember he is also suppose to decrease the deficit, which means cutting the stimulus, and he also promised to cut taxes. Impossible. He is getting as bad as ryan. And by the way, the last thing fox needs is ryan as vp. Can you imagine the job they will have defending this guy. It was alot easier to criticize obama than it will be to defend ryan.</Msg><Username>flyininmytaxi</Username><Timestamp>1346473312103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 00:21:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346506430690-4</Id><Topic><Title>Ryans Speech "attempt to set record for greatest number of blatant lies"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346456826975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm surprised you leftys have the guts to talk about lying when we all know prez obama has never told the truth ever. He is the king of liars.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1346506430690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:33:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346507421563-5</Id><Topic><Title>The Definition of Insanity</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346459450872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:30:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All I can say to that is remember "Hope and Change" and "Change you can believe in". LOL. Now that's a campaign with a lot of details for leftists to ponder. Unfortunately, O is the lead supporter of the Statis Quo and the banking elite, although he talks like a reformer. He knows in his cold black heart that the best way to stop change is to lead the forces that could bring about change.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1346507421563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:50:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346511606594-6</Id><Topic><Title>Ryans Speech "attempt to set record for greatest number of blatant lies"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346456826975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How is mitt going to create jobs. He has not mentioned one specific plan." Actually, he has mentioned more than one, many times. He won't have to do very much, though. Just instill the confidence in small businss owners that they will be able to make most of their own decisions and keep most of the their hard-earned money. No longer threatened with even higher taxes, the "wealthy" will again invest in our economy. (Tax loopholes for the rich should and will e removed) Put in simplest terms, R&amp;R won't have to do too much. Remove many regulatory burdens (especially by the EPA), take advantage of our OWN natuiral resources while investing in credible, worthwhile alternative energy opportunities (when they become cost effective) and, most important, not be O and B. Voting these two back in is unquestionably the classic definition of insanity. Open your mind, let it, not MSNBC, do the common-sense thinking necessary to accomplish the most importnt goal: to lower our debt, create millions of new jobs, save the future of this country -- not to elect more Democrats out of habit or loyalty.</Msg><Username>dm60010</Username><Timestamp>1346511606594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346513697599-7</Id><Title>Ryan admits to lyin'...</Title><Msg>"I had a two hour and fifty-something" marathon, Ryan said last week an interview. But the Ryan campaign confirmed to Runner's World that he has only run one marathon, the 1990 Grandma’s Marathon in Duluth, Minnesota, which he finished in just over 4 hours. - Gee, only off by +25% What WON'T Ryan lie about!</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346513697599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:34:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346513868511-8</Id><Topic><Title>Feds close criminal investigation on Ariz. sheriff</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1346468374812</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 22:59:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, the time is getting short for the criminals running the Dept of Justice. I think they understand what goes around, comes around.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1346513868511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:37:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346514099375-9</Id><Title>Rmoney to hurricane victim who lost home - "go home, call 211"</Title><Msg>On Friday, Rmoney drove through a town that was flooded by Hurricane Isaac in part because it's still outside the vast flooding protection system built with federal funds after Hurricane Katrina devastated New Orleans. He talked with a local resident, Jodie Chiarello, 42, who lost her home in Isaac's flooding. Rmoney told her "go home and call 211." Chiarello said she will likely seek emergency shelter because her home was submerged in the flooding. She expressed frustration about the town's lack of flood protection and Rmoney's insensitivity and stupidity I can't go home you f-king #$%$ my house is underwater and the phone doesn't work...</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346514099375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346514152870-10</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan admits to lyin'...</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346513697599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:34:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Obama ever ran a marathon the results would be sealed, and we would never be able to know anything about it.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1346514152870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:42:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346514892976-11</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan admits to lyin'...</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346513697599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:34:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And if Rmoney ever ran a marathon, he would not release his results (you people don't need to know) and keep his losing attempt sealed in a security box in a Cayman Island bank. The desparation of the low IQ anti-obama bigot and support of the windsock Willard and lyin' Ryan is enormous.</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346514892976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:54:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346514961000-12</Id><Title>Obama, HUGE FLIP-FLOP</Title><Msg>Four years ago Candidate Obama was PRO-PEACE, let's get the troops out of the Mid-East, END THE WARS, bring them home. NOW, COMMANDER IN CHIEF OBAMA, 10 Years of WARS has made the U.S. STRONGER &amp; MORE RESPECTED!!!!!! That is one huge FLIP FLOP http://www.whitehouse.gov/photos-and-video/video/2012/08/31/president-obama-speaks-troops-fort-bliss</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346514961000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:56:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346515400000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, HUGE FLIP-FLOP</Title><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346514961000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:56:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You'll probably find that Obama never actually said he was pro-peace, he just allowed you to infer it from some deliberately vague remarks. The guy was a Rorschach. People projected on him what they wanted to see. I got wise to him in the summer of 2008 when he promised to filibuster the telecom immunity bill--and then turned right around and voted for it. There were at the time 50 pending lawsuits under which information about the depth and breadth of the illegal wiretapping would have been produced. The telecom immunity bill made all those lawsuits moot, and covered up Bush's wiretapping program. Obama showed right there that he was no friend to liberty and no friend of the Constitution.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1346515400000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:03:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346515516000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346413409000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 07:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's answer is HOPE that the New Obama will be different from the Old Obama, and CHANGE from his failed policies to unstated new policies that will make everything different. Fool me once, shame on you.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1346515516000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:05:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346517624094-15</Id><Title>Rmoney vows to go on 'Jobs Tour' if elected</Title><Msg>nobody knows what a 'Jobs Tour' is... and what has been doing the past eight years while traveling all over the country, saving his big ideas for a rainy day when it it was a torrential downpour of disaster under Bush43.</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1346517624094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:40:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346517944141-16</Id><Title>August delivery totals</Title><Msg>I have found 49 deliveries. Thirty Three 737's. Two 747's. Two 767's. Eight 777's. Four 787's. That brings the YTD number to 381. 219 to go to hit 600 deliveries in 2012.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346517944141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:45:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346518087521-17</Id><Topic><Title>The REPUBLIWHOPPERPALOOZAS</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346426797913</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The latest polling has an empty chair beating Rmoney.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1346518087521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:48:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346518173603-18</Id><Topic><Title>Ryans Speech "attempt to set record for greatest number of blatant lies"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346456826975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While I agree with your post, it is not related to BA so you are on ignore.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346518173603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:49:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346518851000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, HUGE FLIP-FLOP</Title><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346514961000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:56:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>re&gt;I got wise to him in the summer of 2008 ...&lt; I failed to. I got very sick in Spring of '08 &amp; didn't know nothing. I thougnt Candidate Obama was sincere &amp; O.K. &amp; his competition was a war-mongering, old fool. This time I doubt there would be more than a "nickle's worth of difference" between the "bought &amp; paid for" Candidates. And it isn't just the politicians running to Head the Administration. It is most all the "bought &amp; paid for politicians" running for Congress too.</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346518851000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:00:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346519389000-20</Id><Title>I srael ENRAGED with General Dempsey</Title><Msg>I sraeli Vice PM: US ‘Undermining’ Push for Iran War Officials Slam Gen. Dempsey for Opposition to Attack by Jason Ditz, August 31, 2012 I sraeli officials are, as is so often the case these days, furious at the US for what they say is an attempt to undermine their push for a war against Iran, with a number of officials taking shots at Gen. Martin Dempsey for yesterday saying he did not want the US “complicit” in such an attack. The term “complicit” enraged a number of officials, who say that the word has “criminal connotations,” while Vice Premier Moshe Ya’alon bashed the US, accusing them of “undermining” the repeated I sraeli threats to attack. Ya’alon said he believed the US comments, which on occasion are less than enthusiastic endorsement for the attack on Iran, are “in part responsible” for Iran believing I srael’s threats are not credible, and also condemned UN Secretary-General Ban Ki-moon for visiting Iran to attend the Non-Aligned Movement (NAM) summit in Tehran. I sraeli analysts predicted Dempsey’s comments might encourage I srael to attack unilaterally, by convincing them that the Obama Administration is unlikely to follow through on its own repeated threats to attack Iran. http://newsDOTantiwarDOTcom/2012/08/31/i sraeli-vice-pm-us-undermining-push-for-iran-war/ replace the 2 DOTs remove the space in i sraeli</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346519389000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:09:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346519629002-21</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan admits to lyin'...</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346513697599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:34:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Whoppers weren't just being served by Burger King at the RNC this past week. Lyin Ryan delivered a few of his own (with extra cheese).</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1346519629002</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:13:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346528716597-22</Id><Topic><Title>A Message To The American People</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney55</Username><Timestamp>1346526697526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:11:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul (You) should keep to singing as Rosie has learned to keep to Comedy Paul would definitely feel for the Millions of Unemployeed Americans Obama's Policies have caused. At 8% Unemployment Rate... Americans are Hurting while Obama plays Golf! Paul cares, Obama does not!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346528716597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:45:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346528918007-23</Id><Topic><Title>John Lennon Once Told Me</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney55</Username><Timestamp>1346527457992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:24:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a Shameful use of a Great Writer and Singer's Name.... You should be Ashamed of yourself for mocking him! Pathetic!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346528918007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:48:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346531443949-24</Id><Topic><Title>A Message To My Fellow Obama Supporters</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346530553136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:15:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep! What America needs is Obama four more years of Record Unemployment... We have already suffered three Years of Record Unemployment... The American People are tired of Suffering under Obama! Obama is a Total Failure... Makes W look Great! Take a Hike, Barak!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346531443949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:30:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346549139523-25</Id><Topic><Title>August delivery totals</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346517944141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:45:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So they need deliveries of about 55 a month for September thru December to break 600 for the year. Not sure they can do that with their current track record.. Their claims of increasng production rates makes no sense if they cannot increase deliveries. All they will do is increase the number of planes sitting on the sidelines waiting for delivery eating up cash..</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346549139523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:25:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346551369751-26</Id><Topic><Title>Since Romney Murdered a Woman...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346546430426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, you need to check your temperature. Between this post and the one about Obama's babyland sand castle, you are not doing a very good job for the Prez.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1346551369751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:02:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>