<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348116180034-1</Id><Topic><Title>How is BA going to break even on the 747-8 widebody?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347892777363</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 10:39:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is tha talk gong with Paul Allen, still doing that bragging thing, you know Paul Allen har! and the tryst like that would hurt me since you can not compete on the subject of Boeing sucks, but if BA did catch me doing that, I would be a manager now ! lets look at your accomplishement, here you are claiming to "y address may be Everett, but my mansion is actually located over on Widbey Island( sure it is) and I get back and forth with my yacht( the full size scale model?)- I tie up next to Paul Allen a lot( a lot like never !) down in Elliott bay and confer( wow) with him quite a lot-- how do you like that eh ( just like all your other emails,, har, har , har ) I added the () to show the joke is on you wet whistle still the fool eh ! 18-Jun-11 01:42 pm</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348116180034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:43:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348116333061-2</Id><Topic><Title>How is BA going to break even on the 747-8 widebody?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347892777363</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 10:39:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you have to have enough profits to write of 30 billion in failures, the 787 and the 747 failures are greater than the marginal 5.7% net will ever break even that means bankruptcy think not look at who is running BA now look up MD a bankrupt corporation get it now ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348116333061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348116647100-3</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing races to the bottom !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347979750530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:49:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do any of you pumper Boeing twerps care to discuss your problem with my statement, nope you can't make a good point on apple up 22% and BA down 55 can you, facts don't lie then make you money if you can stand to be able to take good advice , there is more another new product coming from apple and right now you should be in and ready to ride the rocket ship appl higher next month and Boeing 1600 cracks on the 99% of the income the 737 and the SPEEA strike and the GE engine problem mean yes lower stock price get apple andcut your losses now</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348116647100</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348117215530-4</Id><Topic><Title>layoff anybody with obama car sticker first</Title><Username>hansy4prez</Username><Timestamp>1348111316736</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:21:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mine's upside-down. Does that count? It says ZIOZ VWVBO</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1348117215530</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 01:00:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348126563375-5</Id><Topic><Title>Why Does Romney Dislike America?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1348090867840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:41:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sdmiller is as sick as they come... and he's Rmoney's base. Go figure.</Msg><Username>alan_gonqueer</Username><Timestamp>1348126563375</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 03:36:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348126955614-6</Id><Topic><Title>Lewinski going to kill Hillarys shot at the Presidency if Obama didn't kill it alreadyby throwing her under the bus</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348102789549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:59:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I find it interesting that you haven't yet realized just how STUPID your boy Rmoney is. Is this because you're so stupid yourself?</Msg><Username>alan_gonqueer</Username><Timestamp>1348126955614</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 03:42:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348127398495-7</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll Gives Obama 8 Point Advantage</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348097770451</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:36:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's BAD for Myth Rmoney is GOOD for the USA and the world.</Msg><Username>the_original_spaz</Username><Timestamp>1348127398495</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 03:49:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348129553027-8</Id><Title>Who Wants an Amateur in the White House?</Title><Msg>Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney appears to have seriously damaged his chances of election with his comments about the "47 percent" of voters who are "dependent" on the state. German commentators are baffled by how a career politician could have made such an embarrassing gaffe. For reasons of data protection and privacy, your IP address will only be stored if you are a registered user of Facebook and you are currently logged in to the service. For more detailed information, please click on the "i" symbol. Has Mitt Romney shot himself fatally in the foot? Many observers are wondering if the Republican presidential candidate can recover from the damage he has done to his own campaign with his remarks that almost half of Americans see themselves as "victims" and live off the state. In the speech, which was secretly filmed at a $50,000-a-head fundraising event, Romney said that the 47 percent of Americans who do not pay income tax would never vote for him. "There are 47 percent who are with (Obama), who are dependent upon government, who believe that they are victims, who believe the government has a responsibility to care for them, who believe that they are entitled to health care, to food, to housing, to you-name-it," Romney said in the recording, which was published Monday on the website of the magazine Mother Jones. He added that his role "is not to worry about those people. I'll never convince them they should take personal responsibility and care for their lives." Romney tried to defend his remarks on Tuesday, telling Fox News that he knew those people who are "dependent on government" would not vote for him and calling the idea of government "redistribution" an "entirely foreign concept." US President Barack Obama made political capital out of Romney's remarks in an appearance on David Letterman's late-night talk show. "One thing I've learnt as president is you represent the entire country," he said. "There are not a lot of people out there who think they are victims." The race remains tight, however, ahead of the Nov. 6 election. A new Associated Press-GfK poll shows that 47 percent of likely voters support Obama, with 46 percent backing Romney. On Wednesday, German commentators analyze the impact of Romney's gaffe. The center-left Süddeutsche Zeitung writes: "Sure, other candidates have also put their foot in it while talking in a supposedly intimate setting. Four years ago, Barack Obama, for example, talked disparagingly about white workers who desperately 'cling to guns or religion.' That comment still haunts the Democrats today …." "But Romney's verbal blunders threaten to leave deeper scars. Even before the latest comments, the once-moderate Massachusetts governor was considered an opportunist. Three-fifths of his countrymen think he is a man who says what he thinks people want to hear instead of the truth. Even if Romney were now to apologize, people will not buy his remorse." "Nevertheless, the election has not yet been decided. Romney still has three opportunities, in the form of the three TV debates with Barack Obama in October. Romney has to hope that many voters will only start paying close attention to him then. But he will be on his own. No touching speech by his wife or million-dollar donation will save him then. He has to help himself. Otherwise, he will soon join the ranks of those who he despises -- the losers." The conservative Die Welt writes: "The vote will be counted on the evening of Nov. 6, but it can already be predicted with a degree of reliability that Mitt Romney has lost the US presidential election. The former Massachusetts governor personally hammered the nail in the coffin of his political career when he told donors that 47 percent of Americans would vote for Barack Obama because they see themselves as 'victims' and rely on the state." "Obama, too, has made his fair share of rhetorical blunders … but by excluding almost half of his compatriots from the American dream, Romney has insulted all those people in question. Romney's 'off-the-cuff speech' is not only quantitatively devastating, it is also qualitatively worse because it provides ammunition for the Democrats' charge that Romney wants to conduct politics for the benefit of the better-off." The center-right Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung writes: "It's not very convincing if a presidential candidate who says he wants to revive the 'American dream' excludes almost half of voters right from the outset because they live on state aid anyway and are not willing to take responsibility for themselves. Mitt Romney may be right when he says that those people will not actually vote for him. Nevertheless, he committed a strategic blunder: Ronald Reagan or George W. Bush certainly gave the impression that they also cared about the fate of those whose lives could not be described as a success story." "It will now be even easier for Obama's people to portray the Republican nominee as a rich man who will conduct politics on behalf of America's rich -- and as a man who commits gaffes and is therefore not capable of holding the country's highest office." The Financial Times Deutschland writes: "Of all the blunders that Mitt Romney has made in the current election campaign, this is the worst. We can ignore the fact that the Republican presidential candidate called the Olympic host Great Britain incapable or attacked the incumbent Barack Obama in sharp tones. But writing off one half of his own country's population? Now that's something. The candidate said that it was not his job to concern himself with the 47 percent of voters who supposedly rely on government assistance and are therefore Obama supporters. It's amazing how a politician can voluntarily brand himself as a cold-hearted capitalist." "We Germans can already hardly understand why many Americans would prefer to vote for Romney. But if we now like to believe that he has stumbled, then that is wishful thinking on our part. The policies that we like -- the welfare state, universal health insurance, a foreign policy of rapprochement-- are the policies that Obama stands for. He is Europe's preferred candidate. But the political culture in parts of the US is different. It is more conservative, more religious, more skeptical about government and more focused on the individual. And some statements that would cause a scandal in Germany are only enough to cause a blip in the polls in the US." The business daily Handelsblatt writes: "A professional politician would never make such comments publicly -- at most, they would talk about it in a small group -- but never at an event for donors, even if they paid $50,000 for their lunch. Yet this is what Mitt Romney did when he chatted all too openly in Florida a few months ago. Hence, it is less the content of his remarks and more the lack of professionalism that surprises us and gives us pause. After all, who wants an amateur in the White House who can't even keep his campaign under control?" "This new scandal could spell the end of Romney, who is already notorious as a capitalist and cold-hearted millionaire. Five years after the Lehman bankruptcy, Americans don't need a president who divides society into the rich and those who live off the state. That also applies to Republican voters. After all, many of them don't pay any taxes." -- David Gordon Smith</Msg><Username>the_original_spaz</Username><Timestamp>1348129553027</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 04:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348131772233-9</Id><Topic><Title>Who Wants an Amateur in the White House?</Title><Username>the_original_spaz</Username><Timestamp>1348129553027</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 04:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's OUTTA here. Good roddance in advance, Myth.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1348131772233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 05:02:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348132375918-10</Id><Title>Air Force Official Slams Lockheed Martin on F-35 Program</Title><Msg>The new deputy head of the Pentagon’s F-35 Joint Strike Fighter program said his office’s relationship with plane manufacturer Lockheed Martin Corp. (LMT) is “the worst I’ve ever seen.” Air Force Major General Christopher Bogdan, on the job five weeks as deputy program executive officer, fired an unusual public salvo at the world’s largest defense contractor for what he described as a poor partnership in managing the Pentagon’s most expensive weapons program. Enlarge image A general view during the United Kingdom F-35 Lightning II delivery ceremony on July 19, 2012 at Lockheed Martin Corporation in Fort Worth, Texas. Photographer: Tom Pennington/Getty Images “We will not succeed on this program until we get past that,” Bogdan said in a discussion on the F-35 at the annual conference of the Air Force Association, a nonprofit civilian organization that promotes aerospace education. “We have to find a better place to be in this relationship. We have to.”</Msg><Username>armageddon_ycqm</Username><Timestamp>1348132375918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 05:12:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348139041061-11</Id><Topic><Title>Who Wants an Amateur in the White House?</Title><Username>the_original_spaz</Username><Timestamp>1348129553027</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 04:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing like watching a GOPig presidential candidate dismantle himself, with no help from the left! LOL! :)))</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1348139041061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:04:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348145629099-12</Id><Topic><Title>Obama apologizes first after the Ambassador had been sodomized, tortured and murdered</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348106521342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:02:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PLEASE......EVERYONE FLAG gregjanetommax POST AS UNACCEPTABLE WHAT A TERRIBLE THING TO SAY ABOUT THE AMBASSADOR!!!</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348145629099</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:53:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348145728335-13</Id><Topic><Title>Who Wants an Amateur in the White House?</Title><Username>the_original_spaz</Username><Timestamp>1348129553027</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 04:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's awesome... even better (and more entertaining!) than McSame and Sarah Plain. And _they_ were hard to top.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dawg</Username><Timestamp>1348145728335</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348145729772-14</Id><Title>gregjanetommax PLEASE GIVE ONE LINK OR POST OF OBAMA APOLOGIZING TO ANY COUNTRY</Title><Msg>If you can't provide proof of him apologizing then #$%$</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348145729772</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348145738019-15</Id><Title>Hey Obama is Keeping at least One Promise</Title><Msg>Obama’s war on coal seems to be working. Another 1200 people out of work. This is one promise Obama kept. He said he would run coal out of business.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348145738019</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:55:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348145792492-16</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Obama is Keeping at least One Promise</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348145738019</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:55:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CAN YOU PROVE HE SAID THAT?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348145792492</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:56:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348145841311-17</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Obama is Keeping at least One Promise</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348145738019</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:55:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It'll hurt 1200 people, sure; but the country as a whole will be much better for it.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dawg</Username><Timestamp>1348145841311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:57:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348145873934-18</Id><Title>OBAMBA HAS NEVER APOLOGIZED TO A FOREIGN COUNTRY</Title><Msg>Never......show a youtube of him apologizing i am tired of hearing the lie</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348145873934</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:57:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348146048091-19</Id><Title>How are entrepreneurs doing in Obama’s “recovery”?</Title><Msg>Entrepreneurs — and the innovation they generate — are the beating heart of the U.S. economy. Or at least they have been in the past. But the heart of America’s economy isn’t doing so well these days. In fact, the sorry state of Startup Nation is just another example of how the supposed recovery is anything but. But the startup jobs rate has collapsed in recent years. In fact, the rate of startup jobs during 2010 and 2011, years that were technically in full recovery, are the lowest on record.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348146048091</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:00:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348146300206-20</Id><Topic><Title>Who Wants an Amateur in the White House?</Title><Username>the_original_spaz</Username><Timestamp>1348129553027</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 04:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>huh spart, new ID dawg?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1348146300206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348146696270-21</Id><Title>Still Don't Believe Obama is a Socialist?</Title><Msg>There is a video of Barack Obama calling for “democracy with a small ‘d,’” while pushing a society based on collectivism and “common good.”</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348146696270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:11:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348147493136-22</Id><Title>"Osama is dead and so is our ambassador."</Title><Msg>Only our totally unbiased watchdog media could turn the burning of U.S. embassies in countries where Barack Obama had recently supported mob revolts into Mitt Romney's blunder. Mitt was right Obama was wrong.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348147493136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:24:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348147575512-23</Id><Topic><Title>Still Don't Believe Obama is a Socialist?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348146696270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:11:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are lying and the video does not say that. he said some money from some government agencies could be redistributed to other agencies to do more good for citizens. Now do you have a problem with American citizens as Romney does, you liar????</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348147575512</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:26:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348147729267-24</Id><Title>Obama video has a single word "distribution" in it and the rightwing tries to tie that to socialism</Title><Msg>when you have no plan of your own, when your campaign is in shambles due to the ineptness of your candidate all you have left are lies and distortions of your opponent. you are sick, twisted and demented.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348147729267</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348148032067-25</Id><Topic><Title>Who Wants an Amateur in the White House?</Title><Username>the_original_spaz</Username><Timestamp>1348129553027</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 04:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who the heck would pay $50,000 to hear him speak for an hour or so and why? what a waste of money. Sounds like his message is quite different behind closed doors than it is on FOX news</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348148032067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:33:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348148032503-26</Id><Title>OBAMACARE TAX TO HIT 6 MILLION... MOSTLY MIDDLE CLASS...</Title><Msg>ax penalty to hit nearly 6M uninsured people By RICARDO ALONSO-ZALDIVAR, Associated Press – 11 hours ago WASHINGTON (AP) — Nearly 6 million Americans — significantly more than first estimated— will face a tax penalty under President Barack Obama's health overhaul for not getting insurance, congressional analysts said Wednesday. Most would be in the middle class. The new estimate amounts to an inconvenient fact for the administration, a reminder of what critics see as broken promises. The numbers from the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office are 50 percent higher than a previous projection by the same office in 2010, shortly after the law passed. The earlier estimate found 4 million people would be affected in 2016, when the penalty is fully in effect. That's still only a sliver of the population, given that more than 150 million people currently are covered by employer plans. Nonetheless, in his first campaign for the White House, Obama pledged not to raise taxes on individuals making less than $200,000 a year and couples making less than $250,000. And the budget office analysis found that nearly 80 percent of those who'll face the penalty would be making up to or less than five times the federal poverty level. Currently that would work out to $55,850 or less for an individual and $115,250 or less for a family of four. Average penalty: about $1,200 in 2016. "The bad news and broken promises from Obamacare just keep piling up," said Rep. Dave Camp, R-Mich., chairman of the House Ways and Means Committee, who wants to repeal the law.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348148032503</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:33:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348148170412-27</Id><Title>Not enough market for two big planes</Title><Msg>And Boeing this week finally added an order for five 747-8s to its books after zero firm orders for more than a year. Even that was a deal that had been pre-announced in March 2011 and was firmed up only now. "The theory was that the combination of rapid growth and airport constraints would force carriers to up-gauge and go to very large aircraft," said Robert Mann, a former American Airlines fleet manager who is now an industry consultant in Port Washington, N.Y. "But for any given airline it becomes a daunting prospect to fill 500 seats with every departure." Two White elephants, the day of the super big airplane is just about over, just as soon as Airbust built their A380 it killed both companies ability to make any money in the super jumbo market, not enough demand for two big planes. . No profit for the 747-8 andBoeing shareholders spent 8 billion to develop the 747-8, already wrote off a 2 billion bill, BA stockholders your money is at risk, better sell and get out before BA goes bankrupt in 5 years , you could have been in apple make huge money for the past 15 years and still can if you move to apple or any other great stock and the apple dividend is much better than Boeing. BA how is that outsourcing working for you now eh ! Apple will pull back a little after this latest run up so jump on it then.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348148170412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:36:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348148401904-28</Id><Topic><Title>Obama video has a single word "distribution" in it and the rightwing tries to tie that to socialism</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348147729267</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:28:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The word in the tape is not "distribution" #$%$...it's the communist/socialist term "redistribution." Free markets "distribute wealth"......socialist governments "redistribute" wealth from people who earned it to people who didn't.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348148401904</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:40:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348148420406-29</Id><Topic><Title>How are entrepreneurs doing in Obama’s “recovery”?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348146048091</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:00:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why pay an American when you can make more profits having a Chinese girl working for a pittance build it?, heck they even have housing right on the factories !</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348148420406</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:40:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348148747473-30</Id><Title>Our ambassador is dead and GM owes us money</Title><Msg>It cost tax payers (not to mention investors) $932,000 for for every UAW thug's $75,000 a year job saved at GM.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348148747473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348148942177-31</Id><Topic><Title>Our ambassador is dead and GM owes us money</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348148747473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only a communist would tell a lie like this one</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348148942177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:49:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348149023553-32</Id><Topic><Title>"Osama is dead and so is our ambassador."</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348147493136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:24:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dont anybody pay attention to rebel rouse - hes a commi and a nazzi</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348149023553</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348149197921-33</Id><Topic><Title>Obama video has a single word "distribution" in it and the rightwing tries to tie that to socialism</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348147729267</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:28:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfree markets, such as we have now, redistribute trillions from the bottom up. That's what Willtard wants to expand on.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dawg</Username><Timestamp>1348149197921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348149531788-34</Id><Title>veteran job bill</Title><Msg>What a joke, These Republicans who did not vote for this need to be voted out ! this is a disgrace they did not pass this bill! . they would rather take more taxes from some poor vet and give it to some rich guy sitting on a yacht in the Bahamas smoking a big fat Cuban cigar and laughing about it. Than they will sit there and complain about Obama and Jobs? , hope these pathetic weasels get voted out, they have spent the last two years doing their best to Keep America down. screw them Vote them out!!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348149531788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:58:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348150131469-35</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing races to the bottom !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347979750530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:49:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>update in just one day make that Boeing has lost 5.59% year to date for all shareholders , and youmight be able to get a great buyin on apple after that last 2 week run up above 700 prior to the next run up of apple to happen very soon but then you should have been in apple 15 years ago at 35 dollars when Boeing was a stock priced much like it is now it was 65 then and now 69 der !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348150131469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:08:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348150205389-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obama video has a single word "distribution" in it and the rightwing tries to tie that to socialism</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348147729267</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:28:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, you and Obama want the kind of free markets Cuba and North Korea have. Well, you're in luck.....Obama has us well on the way to them.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348150205389</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:10:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348150211761-37</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing engineers in a work slowdown directed by the union.</Title><Username>jctuttle12</Username><Timestamp>1348086738831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so you are recomending that shareholders sell Ba and buy apple stock then right !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348150211761</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:10:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348150837093-38</Id><Title>EVERYTHING OK BUY ON DIP 77 COMING</Title><Msg>WITIN 10 DAYS</Msg><Username>billionare_tk</Username><Timestamp>1348150837093</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:20:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348151402652-39</Id><Title>Quizz for Democrat Math?</Title><Msg>The keep telling us Obama has created 4 million jobs, yet there are fewer people working today than when He took office. If they created 4 million jobs and less people are working does that mean using food stamps is is being counted as jobs created?</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348151402652</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:30:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348151501257-40</Id><Topic><Title>Quizz for Democrat Math?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348151402652</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what have Republicans done to create jobs</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348151501257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:31:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348151529139-41</Id><Title>The moves, carried out by “dozens of employees” in clusters along production lines, aren’t organized by the UNION</Title><Msg>Why is you have to lie the way you do? Are you a company shill paid to provide disinformation? I know it is legal for you anti-labor organizations to lie to make your case but don't you find lying for a living humiliating?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348151529139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:32:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348151618393-42</Id><Title>Why Did Obama Want to "Hang out" with the Marxist Professors as he stated?</Title><Msg>Is he one too?</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348151618393</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:33:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348151798565-43</Id><Title>Why did Obama Appoint a known Communist to his Administration?</Title><Msg>Someone they said they had watched for a long, long time? Why does Obama have such a fondness for socialists and communists?</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348151798565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348151814477-44</Id><Topic><Title>Quizz for Democrat Math?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348151402652</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The economy tanked for several months after he took office thanks to the previous republican administration and policies. But you knew this and are just telling lie after lie to try to make a point. The point you ARE making is that you are stupid and a liar and you think others are stupid enough to believe you. Go away if you can't post something true.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348151814477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:36:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348151913933-45</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Senate Repubs Kill Veterans Jobs Bill</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348087027639</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course it doesn't matter to Willard Mittford that his party accomplices screw vets. He's never been one.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348151913933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:38:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348151934177-46</Id><Title>rebel2rouse is a stupid liar and he thinks his readers are stupid enough to believe him</Title><Msg>Just check the facts of what he says. They are lies, half truths, and misquotes, and redacted heavily edited statement taken out of context.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348151934177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:38:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348151935253-47</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing races to the bottom !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347979750530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:49:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry pal just put you on ignore.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1348151935253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348151953083-48</Id><Topic><Title>Still Don't Believe Obama is a Socialist?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348146696270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:11:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. "Common good" sounds an awful lot like "promote the general welfare" which is codified into law.</Msg><Username>gerbilfood4me</Username><Timestamp>1348151953083</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:39:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348151978907-49</Id><Topic><Title>Quizz for Democrat Math?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348151402652</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rockstar, thanks for being the first Democrat to flunk the quizz. Someone should have given you a clue that questions are not answers.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348151978907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152013166-50</Id><Topic><Title>The moves, carried out by “dozens of employees” in clusters along production lines, aren’t organized by the UNION</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348151529139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:32:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Why is you have to lie the way you do?" Please: before you give your opinions you should learn the English language.</Msg><Username>buzzbayliss</Username><Timestamp>1348152013166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:40:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348152061502-51</Id><Title>Baggers in full panic republiwhopper mode</Title><Msg>Stoked up by El Flushbo et al.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348152061502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152098575-52</Id><Topic><Title>The moves, carried out by “dozens of employees” in clusters along production lines, aren’t organized by the UNION</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348151529139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:32:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you understand what I said? I left out the word "it". Pardon me all to hell.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348152098575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:41:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152326013-53</Id><Topic><Title>veteran job bill</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348149531788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:58:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They voted to screw vets because it may have meant their Billionaire employers might have to withdraw a few pennies from their Swiss bank accounts .</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348152326013</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:45:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348152326347-54</Id><Title>Republicans create Far More Jobs than Democrats</Title><Msg>According to the July 2012 BLS data, seven of the 10 states with the lowest unemployment rates have Republican governors, led by North Dakota, with 3.0%.: 1) North Dakota (R) 3% 2) Nebraska (R) 4% 3) South Dakota (R) 4.4% 4) Oklahoma (R) 4.9% 5) Vermont (D) 5% 6) Iowa (R) 5.3% 7) New Hampshire (D) 5.4% 8) Wyoming (R) 5.6% 9) Minnesota (D) 5.8% 10) Virginia (R) 5.9%</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348152326347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:45:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348152621345-55</Id><Title>Where Is Lyin Ryan?</Title><Msg>There is no truth to the rumor that Wafflin Willard strapped him to the roof of the car and drove him to Canada. None at all!</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348152621345</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:50:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152705407-56</Id><Topic><Title>Quizz for Democrat Math?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348151402652</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans have done everything in their power to make sure the Country fails under Obama so your question is null and void!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348152705407</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:51:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348152761807-57</Id><Title>Best States for business have Republican Governors</Title><Msg>According to CNBC's America's Top States for Business 2012 list, 12 of the list's top 15 states have Republican governors. The criteria include rankings for workforce, quality of life, economy, infrastructure and transportation, access to capital and cost of living.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348152761807</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:52:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152960422-58</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans create Far More Jobs than Democrats</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348152326347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:45:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These simpletons are just freaking amazing sometimes.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348152960422</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:56:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348155112177-59</Id><Title>France orders probe after rat study links GM corn, cancer</Title><Msg>GM is genetically modified. served fresh curtsey of Monsanto a chemical company. Search the title for the article.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1348155112177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:31:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348156911918-60</Id><Topic><Title>Best States for business have Republican Governors</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348152761807</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:52:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just more proof capitalism works a lot better than collectivism.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348156911918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:01:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348157252452-61</Id><Title>Breaking: Democrats Refuse to Pass a Budget...</Title><Msg>...For 3 years. Does their Oath of office mean anything to Democrats?</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348157252452</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:07:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348157280559-62</Id><Topic><Title>Jimmy Carters grandson is a dirt boy on YouTube every day looking for Dirt. Sure Jimmy is proud of his</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348157000771</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what do you spend your days on yahoo greg? jeez talk about calling the kettle black . I bet you`re a pretty lame pathetic weasel when you not stuck on stupid?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348157280559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:08:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348157363115-63</Id><Topic><Title>Romney didnt just write off half US, he confirmed who he is: Entitled rich guy w/0 grasp of how people actually live</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1348155588781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you think Carter is a dirt Boy that makes you a Pooper Scooper</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348157363115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348157548301-64</Id><Topic><Title>Jimmy Carters grandson is a dirt boy on YouTube every day looking for Dirt. Sure Jimmy is proud of his</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348157000771</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agree 100%</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348157548301</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:12:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348157744133-65</Id><Title>Makers versus Takers</Title><Msg>The choice is clear. Obama wants to be the champion of takers and Romney wants to free up the makers. Obama wants to take the money makers earn and "redistribute" it to the takers. Romney wants to let the makers keep more of the money they earn and provide an incentive for the takers to get off their collective #$%$ and become makers.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348157744133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:15:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348158032096-66</Id><Title>The Fallacy of Redistribution</Title><Msg>The recently discovered tape on which Barack Obama said back in 1998 that he believes in redistribution is not really news. He said the same thing to Joe the Plumber four years ago. But the surfacing of this tape may serve a useful purpose if it gets people to thinking about what the consequences of redistribution are. Those who talk glibly about redistribution often act as if people are just inert objects that can be placed here and there, like pieces on a chess board, to carry out some grand design. But if human beings have their own responses to government policies, then we cannot blithely assume that government policies will have the effect intended. The history of the 20th century is full of examples of countries that set out to redistribute wealth and ended up redistributing poverty. The communist nations were a classic example, but by no means the only example. In theory, confiscating the wealth of the more successful people ought to make the rest of the society more prosperous. But when the Soviet Union confiscated the wealth of successful farmers, food became scarce. As many people died of starvation under Stalin in the 1930s as died in Hitler's Holocaust in the 1940s. How can that be? It is not complicated. You can only confiscate the wealth that exists at a given moment. You cannot confiscate future wealth -- and that future wealth is less likely to be produced when people see that it is going to be confiscated. Farmers in the Soviet Union cut back on how much time and effort they invested in growing their crops, when they realized that the government was going to take a big part of the harvest. They slaughtered and ate young farm animals that they would normally keep tending and feeding while raising them to maturity. Thomas Sowell</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348158032096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:20:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348158160791-67</Id><Topic><Title>Makers versus Takers</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348157744133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:15:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be somebody instead of a nobody.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1348158160791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348158349840-68</Id><Topic><Title>The Fallacy of Redistribution</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348158032096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:20:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All we hear from Republicans is how trickle down is the only way it works and everything else fails. when has trickle down economics ever worked? only thing that trickles is more money to the top and more jobs out of the country. ITS A CON JOB for the 1% to acquire more wealth and power and make the average person poorer and weaker and more willing to work for less and less . the 1% are not hurting a bit.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348158349840</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348159553488-69</Id><Topic><Title>Jimmy Carters grandson is a dirt boy on YouTube every day looking for Dirt. Sure Jimmy is proud of his</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348157000771</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jimmy Carter was one of the worst Presidents in history with GW Bush, his grandson is probably a dirtbag like his grandfather.</Msg><Username>thegoldude747</Username><Timestamp>1348159553488</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:45:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348160274847-70</Id><Title>September deliveries update</Title><Msg>With 11 days to go in September, the deliveries are looking pretty good. As of the 19th, BA has delivered 30 planes. Twenty 737's. Two 747's. One 767. Four 777's. Three 787's. If they can deliver another 20-25 planes this month, it will be a good sign that they can match deliveries with teh production increases.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348160274847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:57:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348160602247-71</Id><Topic><Title>Romney didnt just write off half US, he confirmed who he is: Entitled rich guy w/0 grasp of how people actually live</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1348155588781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ahkmed on responsiblity....lmao</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1348160602247</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:03:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348160728671-72</Id><Topic><Title>Makers versus Takers</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348157744133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:15:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ahkmed doesn't like your post (he's one o dem takers)...he doesn't care much for dem inconvenient truths i like it, thumbs up</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1348160728671</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:05:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348161008712-73</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Senate Repubs Kill Veterans Jobs Bill</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348087027639</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republican obstructionism on this bill is outrageous, but at the same time it is completely consistent with how they operate: Profess concern for various groups within our society and then do NOTHING to put that "concern" into action.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1348161008712</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:10:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348161030538-74</Id><Title>republican moochers leeches and takers</Title><Msg>takers moochers leeches on society are generally the rich and the corporate world of the republicans who can charge 3 prices for their products and services because of actual or near monopoly</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348161030538</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:10:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348161447560-75</Id><Topic><Title>veteran job bill</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348149531788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:58:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans wave the flag and decorate their vehicles with "support the troops' stickers but when the troops come home Republicans turn their backs. Republicans just spoke to veterans "you are on your own buddy"</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1348161447560</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:17:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348161596805-76</Id><Topic><Title>Baggers in full panic republiwhopper mode</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348152061502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:41:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bagger desperation is palpable.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1348161596805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:19:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348161963426-77</Id><Topic><Title>Romney didnt just write off half US, he confirmed who he is: Entitled rich guy w/0 grasp of how people actually live</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1348155588781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Rmoney campaign is in full damage control mode, feverishly trying to convince Americans that they didn’t hear what they heard, that there was some confusion. Rmoney first said that his comments were “not elegantly stated,” then he tried to pivot to an argument against the redistribution of wealth, saying he believed in an America where “government steps in to help those in need.” He continued, “we’re a compassionate people.” Those in need? Would those be the ones “who believe that they are victims,” the ones who it’s not your job to “worry about,” the ones who you’ll never be able to persuade to “take personal responsibility and care for their lives”? Rmoney’s feeble explanations reek of insincerity and desperation.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1348161963426</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:26:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348162371109-78</Id><Topic><Title>The Fallacy of Redistribution</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348158032096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:20:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Basic Problem with redistribution- it only works in a static model- people will as a group work in their best interest- so sooner or later one runs out of OPM Name a socialist country that stayed with socialism and survived. Even china has now embraced a significant amount of capitalism - like in Hong Kong and is rapidly spreading Nortyh Korea is not doing so well</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1348162371109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:32:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348162548618-79</Id><Topic><Title>Jimmy Carters grandson is a dirt boy on YouTube every day looking for Dirt. Sure Jimmy is proud of his</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348157000771</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>can't hide ahkmed</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1348162548618</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:35:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348162838536-80</Id><Topic><Title>Baggers in full panic republiwhopper mode</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348152061502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:41:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dokeyccomie is in full damage control mode, feverishly trying to convince himself that he didn’t hear what everyone else hears or see what everyone else sees. Pathetic, eh!</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1348162838536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:40:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348162980752-81</Id><Topic><Title>Romney didnt just write off half US, he confirmed who he is: Entitled rich guy w/0 grasp of how people actually live</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1348155588781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now suddenly he's for 100% of Americans. Talk about flip-flopping hypocrisy.</Msg><Username>marxb0uncer</Username><Timestamp>1348162980752</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:43:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348162988504-82</Id><Topic><Title>Romney didnt just write off half US, he confirmed who he is: Entitled rich guy w/0 grasp of how people actually live</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1348155588781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now suddenly he's for 100% of Americans. Talk about flip-flopping hypocrisy.</Msg><Username>marxb0uncer</Username><Timestamp>1348162988504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348163976389-83</Id><Topic><Title>Baggers in full panic republiwhopper mode</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348152061502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:41:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL... wishful thinking has wiped out all your rational thought capability (if you ever had any, that is).</Msg><Username>marxb0uncer</Username><Timestamp>1348163976389</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:59:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348164046293-84</Id><Topic><Title>Romney didnt just write off half US, he confirmed who he is: Entitled rich guy w/0 grasp of how people actually live</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_001</Username><Timestamp>1348155588781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1348164046293</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:00:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348164201444-85</Id><Topic><Title>Baggers in full panic republiwhopper mode</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348152061502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:41:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even the pathetically biased Rasmussen poll today gives Obama the edge:The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Thursday shows President Obama attracting support from 47% of voters nationwide, while Mitt Romney earns 45% of the vote. Three percent (3%) prefer some other candidate, and four percent (4%) are undecided. See daily tracking history.</Msg><Username>beatanydealer</Username><Timestamp>1348164201444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348164941913-86</Id><Topic><Title>should I vote for a Mormon or a psycopathic homosexual Communist who can never take criticism and is willfully leading the countrty</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348161484569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the title I thought you were now running.</Msg><Username>windyhorn</Username><Timestamp>1348164941913</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:15:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348165151236-87</Id><Topic><Title>Jimmy Carters grandson is a dirt boy on YouTube every day looking for Dirt. Sure Jimmy is proud of his</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348157000771</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What can we expect from people that can't even come up with a new name for their kids.</Msg><Username>dc3141592653</Username><Timestamp>1348165151236</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348165189379-88</Id><Topic><Title>Baggers in full panic republiwhopper mode</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348152061502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:41:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hoo boy... what will harrydopes have to say about THAT?</Msg><Username>marxb0uncer</Username><Timestamp>1348165189379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:19:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348166183064-89</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing engineers in a work slowdown directed by the union.</Title><Username>jctuttle12</Username><Timestamp>1348086738831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just another whining unemployed worker that doesn't have the skillset to get a good paying job so he puts down those that are skilled and are being raped by the sames companies mentality that probably costed him his job but couldn't stand up because he wasn't in a Union. Go get an education and a good paying job then you can #$%$ all you want when they take everything away from you but you better be in a union or you'll take it up the butt. I'm sorry you're unemployed but don't be all sour grapes just because we are employed.</Msg><Username>ev3044</Username><Timestamp>1348166183064</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:36:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348166424325-90</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing engineers in a work slowdown directed by the union.</Title><Username>jctuttle12</Username><Timestamp>1348086738831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, and working to rule is quite different from a work slowdown. Perhaps you should do a little research before you shoot off your mouth. People can work to rule (some may try to call it a slowdown). Working to rule means following procedures to the letter. Some people let things slide all in the name of getting things done quickly. Would you rather a house painter took 1 day to paint your house and it looked like crap or they took 3 days and it looked nice but also costed a bit more? Same damn thing.</Msg><Username>ev3044</Username><Timestamp>1348166424325</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:40:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348166733845-91</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing engineers in a work slowdown directed by the union.</Title><Username>jctuttle12</Username><Timestamp>1348086738831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one is doing a work slowdown.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1348166733845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348166929806-92</Id><Title>Even Rasmussen is showing Obama leading</Title><Msg>When the bias Republican Fox poll has MR losing Look out below: The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Thursday shows President Obama attracting support from 47% of voters nationwide, while Mitt Romney earns 45% of the vote. Three percent (3%) prefer some other candidate, and four percent (4%) are undecided. See daily tracking history.</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1348166929806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:48:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348167034335-93</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing engineers in a work slowdown directed by the union.</Title><Username>jctuttle12</Username><Timestamp>1348086738831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems as though my message was cut short in responding to, "no one is doing a work slowdown". The response is..........how can you tell when it comes to union workers.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1348167034335</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:50:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348167405518-94</Id><Title>Pawlenty Jumping Off the Romney Ship</Title><Msg>Former Minnesota governor Tim Pawlenty, previously a GOP presidential and vice-presidential hopeful, has jumped ship and resigned as co-chairman of Mitt Romney's presidential campaign. Romney's team issued a statement incorrectly stating that Pawlenty would take over as chairman and CEO of the Financial Services Roundtable. Pawlenty will actually become president and CEO of the organization, succeeding former Dallas Mayor and Member of Congress Steve Bartlett, who has been serving as president of the Financial Services Roundtable since 1999. Allstate CEO Thomas Wilson is the chairman of the Roundtable. But one wonders whether Pawlenty, who has been on everyone's very short list for a likely high level cabinet post in a Romney White House, has just given up on Romney. Clearly a lot of other Republicans are on edge. Rich Lowry's surprising blast at the GOP candidate is a case in point.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1348167405518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348167492176-95</Id><Topic><Title>One Small Step Backward for Man</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1269303482000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2010-03-22 20:18:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Miro was obviously a Liberal</Msg><Username>cluck_head_00</Username><Timestamp>1348167492176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:58:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348168245492-96</Id><Title>In 2012 there is NO coherent Republican Leadership!!</Title><Msg>In 2012 there is NO coherent Republican leadership that is offering constructive conservative proposals on the key issues; NO leader (including both Romney and Ryan) is standing ready to propose and defend strategic compromises. What we have is NO details amid vague promises and major stroking of the “base,” which appears to be far enough right to be scary. In the new GOP, the “job creators” have achieved sainthood without performing any miracles, at least on the employment front. Their low taxes have allowed them to accumulate, with no requirement to build or invest for progress. The Republican Party has let itself become the captive of conflicting pseudo-religious factions: despising choice in any form, against immigration and immigration reform, fussing over the sanctity of marriage, ignoring voting rights, even espousing vocal libertarians who want to disband the Federal Reserve (Friedman, “We Need a Second Party” NYT 2-11-12). Meanwhile all Republicans are pledging themselves to an anti-tax advocate who wants to drown government in a bathtub while sinking the candidacy of any independent Republican that might swim away. The Party of Lincoln has become aggressively intolerant. Republican “spokespeople” get jobs in the media by being TV beautiful and aggressively anti-Obama, with not much of anything else. Truth is not a requirement, nor is history, research, or real data. Some pundits have observed that it is time for a new Republican Party</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1348168245492</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:10:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348168507324-97</Id><Title>Fox News; President Obama leads Mitt Romney in Battleground States!!</Title><Msg>Fox News released a new poll Thursday showing that President Barack Obama leads Mitt Romney in three battleground states, topping off a week of bad-news polling for the Republican presidential nominee in toss-up states.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1348168507324</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348168882504-98</Id><Topic><Title>One Small Step Backward for Man</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1269303482000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2010-03-22 20:18:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really are a #$%$ aren't you? Read something besides the Swastika Daily Gazette, will ya?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348168882504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:21:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348169297778-99</Id><Topic><Title>veteran job bill</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348149531788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:58:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Better Question to Ask is Why Did the Democratic Controlled Senate Vote Down the Bill? Rockstar, you are an Idiot!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348169297778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:28:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348169598533-100</Id><Topic><Title>veteran job bill</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348149531788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:58:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>imaccom they did not get to vote on it the Republicans filibustered it , do you pay attention to things or do you just stare at FOX news with this blank look on your face all day?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348169598533</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:33:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348169659084-101</Id><Topic><Title>The Fallacy of Redistribution</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348158032096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:20:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The mistake you're making, Don (and it's not insignificant) is equating "redistribution" with "socialism." Redistribution is simply reapportioning NATIONAL assets into NATIONAL priorities rather than parochial ones. To believe this is wrong is to believe that only eastern Washington farmers who irrigate and aluminum companies who use vast amounts of electricity should have paid for Grand Coulee Dam, or that Interstate 405 should have been paid for entirely by Bellevue, Bothell and Kirkland residents. Or that the astronauts should have pungled up for the Apollo program. Or that you and your B2 colleagues and the zoomies should have shouldered the entire cost of the B2 program. The nature of our government has ALWAYS been that all the citizens pay for projects that are a benefit to the SOCIETY, as determined by citizens through their elected reps. (And now you're going to start yelling about "cadavers for Christine", I wager. :-)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1348169659084</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:34:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348169894166-102</Id><Topic><Title>veteran job bill</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348149531788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:58:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who's the idiot here? Republicans said the spending authorized in the bill violated limits that Congress agreed to last year. Democrats fell two votes shy of the 60-vote majority needed to waive the objection, forcing the legislation back to committee. A handful of Republicans joined with Democrats in voting to waive the objection to the bill: Sen. Scott Brown of Massachusetts, Dean Heller of Nevada, Lisa Murkowski of Alaska and Maine's Susan Collins and Olympia Snowe. Brown and Heller are also in tough re-election contests. Your head is up and locked, imacommie.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1348169894166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:38:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348170071226-103</Id><Title>Rmoney: Most immacom's Lack 'Skill Or Experience'</Title><Msg>... I'd like to staple a green card to every Ph.D. in the world and say, 'Come to America, we want you here', he also made a comment dismissing most 'immacom's as completely without skills that make them valuable to the American workforce.</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1348170071226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:41:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170194451-104</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney: Most immacom's Lack 'Skill Or Experience'</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1348170071226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:41:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that is why Rmoney hires immacoms' to clean the pool and as his rwnj messageboard posters</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1348170194451</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:43:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170338066-105</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing engineers in a work slowdown directed by the union.</Title><Username>jctuttle12</Username><Timestamp>1348086738831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stop talking out your backside. Nobody has called for or is engaged in "working to rule" or any kind of slowdown. Also, Boeing can't terminate people just because they feel like it. It has to be "for cause". 20+ year engineer</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1348170338066</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170431818-106</Id><Topic><Title>veteran job bill</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348149531788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:58:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get with the times, shocked. Programs get funded by ther Fed printing money no days.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1348170431818</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:47:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170507147-107</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing engineers in a work slowdown directed by the union.</Title><Username>jctuttle12</Username><Timestamp>1348086738831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please educate yourself on the details. It's not the union who's being unreasonable. 20+ year engineer</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1348170507147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170608992-108</Id><Topic><Title>veteran job bill</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348149531788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:58:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Careful now. Don't mess with genna's golden goose.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1348170608992</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:50:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348170751621-109</Id><Title>Obama Approval Rating Down to 46%... Pathetic!</Title><Msg>Obama Approval Rating Down to 46% Gallup tracks daily the percentage of Americans who approve or disapprove of the job Barack Obama is doing as president. Daily results are based on telephone interviews with approximately 1,500 national adults; Margin of error is ±3 percentage points.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348170751621</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:52:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170863384-110</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Approval Rating Down to 46%... Pathetic!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348170751621</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:52:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Definition of Pathetic? You want pathetic just look at MR's campaign! LOl</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1348170863384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:54:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170920461-111</Id><Topic><Title>The Fallacy of Redistribution</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348158032096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:20:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The farmers went through a worse time. The price of their goods, which was already low, fell further by 50 percent. There were people going hungry but at the same time surplus food could not be sold for a profit. -the republicon fascist great depression</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1348170920461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:55:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170943206-112</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing engineers in a work slowdown directed by the union.</Title><Username>jctuttle12</Username><Timestamp>1348086738831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey verzig - after 20 years you should know that absent a contract - the Supreme soviet socialist state of washington IS an employment at will state . . Under most circumstances, Washington is an at-will state, which means that either the employer or the employee can end the employment relationship at any time, with or without notice and with our without cause. There are numerous exceptions to the at-will doctrine that attorneys who advise employers or employees should be aware of. These exceptions have developed over time and are still evolving. The following are some examples. They are not all-inclusive. Contractual Exceptions to the At-will Doctrine Contractual exceptions to the at-will doctrine generally exist in the context of collective bargaining agreements, employment contracts and employee manuals or other promises of continued employment or specific treatment by an employer. Generally, collective bargaining agreements have a progressive discipline policy for most infractions and a grievance process for appealing from a disciplinary or termination decision. +++++ So for the non union types - absent some obvious violations of civil rights, disabled, etc, Boeing CAN FIRE you for little or no reason - or in some cases a made up reason</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1348170943206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:55:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348171074933-113</Id><Title>More Proof the Dems Have their Heads Where the Sun Don't Shine!</Title><Msg>American Guess that 8% Un-Employment is Normal Under Obama, eh? Pathetic! Study: Only 15 Percent Of Democrats Believe Economic News Is Bad September 20, 2012 12:33 PM WASHINGTON (CBSDC) – With just 47 days before the general election and Mitt Romney attempting to pivot the focus of the election back on the state of the economy, citizens with Democratic leanings are actually doing an about-face on the economy compared to their Republican counterparts, according to a recent study from the Pew Research Center. New data found that just 15 percent of Democrats believe that recent economic news is mostly poor, a percentage that took a significant drop from the 31 percent of Democrats polled last month who did think that economic news was mostly bad. According to the study, the 15-percent clip is among the lowest percentages during President Barack Obama’s nearly four years in offic</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348171074933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:57:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348171468930-114</Id><Topic><Title>More Proof the Dems Have their Heads Where the Sun Don't Shine!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348171074933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:57:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boosh era: GDP from +3% to -8% unemployment from 4% to 10% stock market cut in half = the good 'ol days, to the republicon fascist #$%$br /&gt; I gues that is why they had an angry semi-senile 82 yr. old talk to an empty chair at the RNC instead of Boosh</Msg><Username>republicanfascists</Username><Timestamp>1348171468930</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:04:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348171498520-115</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Approval Rating Down to 46%... Pathetic!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348170751621</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:52:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you`re still stuck in that alternate universe I see , what do you call that place?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348171498520</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:04:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348171598694-116</Id><Title>Dem Senators up for Election Abandoning Obama! Wonder Why?</Title><Msg>Dems Across the America Know Obama is in Trouble Obama's Foreign Policy Crumbling Around Him Sen. Manchin mum on Obama support By Ben Geman - 09/20/12 02:35 PM ET Sen. Joe Manchin (D-W.Va.) declined to say on Thursday whether he’s supporting President Obama’s reelection bid. “I’m not talking about people’s election, I’m talking about West Virginia, the economy, staying here and getting our job done. You should be worried about what we are doing here,” the West Virginia Democrat said in the Capitol when asked whether he’s supporting Obama. Manchin, who's up for reelection in November, spoke to The Hill after a floor speech about the need for solutions to the nation’s fiscal woes. He repeatedly declined to say if he is backing Obama for a second term. Asked a second time, Manchin said, "I believe we should be here working, really working hard. Don’t you? As an American, don’t you think we should be here working?" Asked a third time, he responded, “I’m supporting the American way of life, fixing our budgets, getting our house in order ... I am going to support whoever the next president may be to work with him to commit to fix this country. We need to do that." When asked by The Hill if he was supporting GOP nominee Mitt Romney, the freshman senator said, "No." In his floor speech, the senator encouraged colleagues to stay in Washington and work on the nation's fiscal problems instead of going home to campaign. "Just give the American people the facts and show them the options — the way we did at our fiscal summit last week — and they will do their part to get this country back on the right path. They always have. That’s what makes this country great. So don’t sell them short just because this is an election year. They can tell when you’re dealing straight with them — or when you’re playing politics. And right now is not the time to play politics," he said. West Virginia is tough territory for Obama, and Manchin has distanced himself from the White House</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348171598694</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348171727537-117</Id><Topic><Title>More Proof the Dems Have their Heads Where the Sun Don't Shine!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348171074933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:57:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1-2-2012: Congress will return to session on January 17th. They will work for six whole days this month. Must be nice. Don't expect much Federal job creation during this period. 1-18-2012: Here we GO! On Tuesday, the 17th, the House selected a new as-yet-unnamed Sergeant-At-Arms. On the 18th the House will attempt and fail to vote down Mr. Obama's request for a debt increase. The House will then adjourn until Monday. No jobs were created. 1-23-2012: Not much today. Just a panel discussion on doing business with the military, plus some GOP shenanigans called the Legally Binding Budget Act of 2011. Simply put, it's an attempt to make the president culpable for lousy budgets. No jobs were created. 1-25-2012: Speaker of the House John Boehner claims that the GOP passed 30 jobs bills in the past session of Congress. Well, they passed 30 "somethings" but they certainly had little to do with job creation. Follow the link and laugh. 1-27-2012: The House held hearings on Wednesday trying to cut retirement benefits for federal employees. They also redefined what an "aircraft" is. They then took Thursday off. No jobs were created. 1-30-2012: On Friday, the 27th, the House was in session for a whole four minutes. No jobs were created. 1-31-2012: Today the House voted on a motion to consider the repeal of the CLASS Program, part of the Affordable Health Care Act aimed at helping low-income citizens get health care. It passed on party lines. Don't expect it to escape the Senate. No jobs were created. 2-3-2012: The House proposed a bill that keeps welfare recipients out of strip clubs, casinos, and liquor stores. The actual purpose of the bill was to have Democrats vote against it so that their Republican opponents can claim Democrats are FOR such nonsense. The bill passed 395-27 but it will die in the Senate, so ha-ha-ha, GOP. No jobs were created. 2-6-2012: Last week House Republicans approved language for debate on two bills that would gut Federal programs without having to pass specific legislation. This would, essentially, equal more tax cuts for big business. No jobs were created. 2-8-2012: The consistent upward trend in employment numbers would seem to be an excellent time for the GOP to bask in glory as good shepherds of the economy. But even though they've done absolutely nothing to increase employment for the past year all they can do is grumble that "More should be done". For once, they're right. No jobs were created. 2-10-2012: House Republican's are watering down the insider trading bill so that Democrats will vote against it. Thus, come November, our GOP pals can say that Democrats are actually for insider trading. What more could we expect from these useless conservative sleazebags? No jobs were created. 2-13-2012: Today there will be exactly one hearing about "exploring all energy options." It should be called "exploring oil energy options." Meanwhile, Senate Republicans are trying to kill the Violence Against Women Act. No jobs were created. 2-15-2012: So which party has introduced "the most partisan" and "worst transportation bill that Transportation Secretary Ray Lahood has seen in 35 years"? Go on... guess. (Hint: It wasn't the Democrats.) No jobs were created. 2-17-2012: The House will presumably vote on and pass the payroll tax extension today. Then they'll leave town for ten days in order to celebrate Presidents Day. Cushy gig. No jobs were created. 2-20-2012: Congress is out this week on an extended Presidents Day vacation. Between now and April they're going to take four weeks off. Who the heck made this ridiculous schedule? (Hint: It was the majority party in the House. The idea being, I suppose, that the less Congress is in session, the less gets done.) No jobs were created. 2-27-2012: The Congressional Circus is back in action after a week off for President's Day, and today they'll be considering H.R. 4078, "The Regulatory Freeze of Jobs Act of 2012." It's worse than it sounds as its intent is "to provide that no agency may take any significant regulatory action until the unemployment rate is equal to or less than 6.0 percent." Cue the sad trombone sound. No jobs were created. 2-29-2012: The House failed to pass the Research Works Act, which would have prohibited federal agencies from releasing the result of taxpayer-funded research. No jobs were created. 3-2-2012: Yesterday the House spent most of the day debating and passing the San Joaquin Valley Water Reliability Act. Meanwhile, in the Senate, Democrats, plus Olympia Snowe, fended off the execrable Blunt Amendment. In addition, Speaker Boehner vows to continue contraception fight. Because it's all about jobs, right? No jobs were created. 3-5-2012: On Thursday, the 1st of March, the House unanimously voted to allow itself to give oral histories of the civil rights era, then condemned Iran for finding one of its citizens guilty of apostasy. The House then took Friday off. No jobs were created. 3-7-2012: On Monday the House spent two whole hours naming two federal buildings and then adjourned. On Tuesday they shuffled paper all day regarding a Bureau of Reclamation bill involving hydropower development. No jobs were created. 3-9-2012: The House spent all day Thursday debating H.R. 3606, the "Jumpstart Our Business Startups (JOBS) Act". It is better known as the "Reopening American Capital Markets to Emerging Growth Companies Act". What it actually is, is a financial market deregulation bill. What it REALLY is, is a fake jobs bill. No jobs were created. 3-12-2012: Last Friday, March 9th, members of the House attended a hearing in Saranac Lake, NY, to discuss a farm bill. No jobs were created. Today, the House has scheduled a single hearing on (Are you ready?) "Explosion of Federal Regulations Threatening Jobs and Economic Survival in the West"... in Elko Nevada. DAMN those regulations! No jobs were created. 3-14-2012: The House is in another recess until Tuesday, the 20th of March. No jobs were created. 3-19-2012: The House is theoretically in session. They're back in Washington but nothing much is scheduled this week except for hearings. They might as well be painting their bedroom's black and listening to Led Zeppelin albums. No jobs were created. 3-21-2012: On Monday, the 19th, the House was called to order at 4PM. They then spent the next four hours arguing a bill that would allow Israeli nationals to receive nonimmigrant visas. No jobs were created. On Tuesday, the House convened at Noon. The GOP spent the balance of the day trying to steal a Virginia park to fence to their industrialist buddies. No jobs were created. 3-23-2012: For the past two days the House has been debating H.R. 5, the "HEALTH" bill, which is actually about tort reform. No jobs were created. 3-26-2012: The House took last Friday off. No jobs were created. 3-28-2012: The House debated FCC transparency, baby monitors, and a transportation bill but nothing of note passed. No jobs were created, either. 3-30-2012: The House voted to end Medicare again but, thankfully, they signed a 90-day extension to the transportation bill. No jobs were created. 4-2-2012: The House vacated the premises early last Friday and won't be back in session until the 16th of April. No jobs will be created. 4-16-2012: The House is back in session but it's mostly just nuts-and-bolts stuff this week. Although a vote on another corporate tax cut bill (H.R. 9) is in the offing. 4-18-2012: The House voted down the Buffet Rule, awarded Lena Horne a posthumous Congressional Gold Medal, then argued the rest of the day about rules to "enhance" hunting, fishing, and shooting. No jobs were created. 4-20-2012: The House passed "The Small Business Tax Cut Act" (H.R. 9) but they might as well have named the bill "Ponies For Everyone" because it wasn't about small business, and it will never pass the Senate. No jobs were created today. 4-23-2012: The House was in pro forma session to keep President Obama from assigning badly needed federal judges. No jobs were created. 4-25-2012: The House spent the day dealing with the legislative version of cleaning their room. In this case it meant passing bills that dealt with adjustments to the boundaries of parklands, land swaps, and the like. No jobs or anything remotely like them were created. 4-27-2012: The House pased a couple of suspension bills (The DATA Act and the Small Business Credit Availability Act). They also passed CISPA, which is distressing, but the prez has promised a veto. Looking forward to that. Oh, and no jobs were created. 4-30-2012: On Friday the House approved a bill that lowers the interest on student loans, but tacked on a rider which guts the Health Care Act. It's designed to result in a presidential veto, at which point Republicans can claim that Mr. Obama doesn't care about higher education. To which I say #$%$ these Republicans! #$%$ these horrible, greedy, useless, poisonous bags of #$%$" 5-9-2012: The House is back in session but they only passed a handful of suspension bills. No jobs were created. 5-11-2012: The GOP-led House passed several bills that denied the Obama administration funds to fight for progesssive issues. Read the dismal details here. No jobs were created even though Speaker Boehner again claimed the GOP had a tight focus on jobs... when being specifically asked about why his party is passing so much anti-gay legislation. #$%$ this guy. No jobs were created. 5-14-2012: Last Thursday the House passed the Sequestration Replacement Act, designed to fatten the Pentagon coffers at the expense of the elderly and the poor. It is destined to die in the Senate. No Jobs were created. 5-16-2012: The House was not in session on Monday, but on Tuesday the legislators busied themselves passing noncontroversial suspension bills. Ho-hum. No jobs were created, but you already knew that. 5-18-2012: The House passed a watered-down Violence Against Women Act. Basically, if you're an immigrant or a native American woman, you're fair game for any sadist. They'll pass a major defense funding bill tomorrow and then will take the next week off. No jobs were created. 5-21-2012: On Friday the House passed a bloated defense spending bill, even though they were obligated to cut defense spending as part of the Super Committee agreement. Not only did the new bill include discriminitory language it also included an amendment allowing the government to institute propaganda against the American people. The president has vowed to veto this bill. No jobs were created unless you count the military contractors rolling in effluent streams of your tax dollars. 5-23-2012: Say it with me now: "The House is in recess until the 30th of May. Must be nice to have so many vacations. Oh, how I hate those indolent GOP swine." 6-1-2012: Another day, another abortion bill. This time the "Susan B. Anthony and Frederick Douglass Prenatal Nondiscrimination Act." Which was designed to stop abortions based on sex or race. Seriously. It failed to pass. Apart from that bit of nonsense the day was one long last-minute rush to pass bills that pay the government credit card. No jobs were created. 6-4-2012: Last Friday three Democratic (Hahn, Kaptur, Tonko) amendments to increase funding for energy efficiency and renewable energy failed, while three Republican (Hultgren, Chaffetz, McClintock) amendments to reduce funding of energy efficiency and renewable energy also failed. No jobs were created. 6-6-2012: The House was not in session on Monday but on Tuesday it spent the day amending water and energy bills, mostly shuffling money from one account to another. It was not a job creating event. 6-8-2012: The House passed a bill to repeal a new exise tax on medical devices. The GOP refers to this as a "jobs bill". Another waste of time as the Senate will not consider the bill. In the meantime the GOP is still losing its #$%$ over incandescent lightbulbs, voting to restrict funding for the application of energy-efficient lighting (The GOP evidently believes that CFL's are manufactured in Hell itself.) Job creation was not in evidence. 6-11-2012: On Friday the House voted to cut funding for Open World Leadership Center, the Congressional Research Service, and the Washington Botanic Garden. But, on the bright side, they voted themselves funds to print some snazzy new pocket-sized editions of the U.S. Constitution to hand out to constituents. As always, no jobs were created. The House is in recess until the 18th of June. 6-20-2012: The past two days have seen nothing fancy from the House. Just a couple of suspension bills and some laws aimed at American Indians. No attempt was made to create jobs. 6-22-2012: The clusterfuck that is the Republican-led House of Representatives spent much time dawdling over the transportation bill, the only meaningful jobs bill under consideration. (Don't get your panties twisted about the "jobs" part of this bill. This same bill must be extended each and every year and the only time there's any opposition is when the president is black.) No jobs were created. 6-25-2012: The House adjourned on Friday, the 22nd. No jobs were created. 6-27-2012: The House was pro forma on Monday but was in session until almost 11:30 Tuesday night. Nothing got done. They couldn't even agree to name four post offices. No jobs were created. 6-29-2012: On Thursday, the 28th, the House passed several Homeland Security bills, named a couple of post offices, and voted to hold U.S. Attorney General Eric Holder in contempt of.... something, because the right-wing base is screaming for blood and they must be appeased. No jobs were created. 7-2-2012: On Friday, the 29th, the House grudgingly passed the Transportation Bill, which has never been a problem up until now, and mortgaged the future of college graduates. No jobs were created. The House is now adjourned until the 9th of July.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348171727537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:08:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348172087056-118</Id><Title>Obama Already Preparing Retirement Home in Hawaii for 2013....</Title><Msg>SECRET RETIREMENT PLANS: DOES OBAMA EXPECT TO LOSE? Insider reveals internal polls, luxury Hawaii estate ready for January Published: 20 hours ago by JEROME R. CORSIEmail | Archive Jerome R. Corsi, a Harvard Ph.D $35 million Hawaii estate regarded as possible Obama retirement home Are Obama insiders secretly making retirement plans for the Obamas with the expectation the president will lose his bid for re-election in November? Very quietly, Obama’s chief financier, Penny Pritzker, has entered the Hawaii housing market to buy a retirement home for the president and his family that will be available not in 2016, but in January 2013, according to a confidential source within Pritzker’s Chicago organization Pritzker, a wealthy Chicago business executive and heiress to the Hyatt Hotels fortune, served as national finance chairman for Obama’s 2008 campaign and is the co-chairman of his 2012 effort. The source told WND that highly confidential internal polls conducted by the Obama campaign indicate Obama cannot win re-election, despite public surveys that show him in the lead. “The public polls are mostly political,” the source argued. “Obama radicals want Romney supporters to feel discouraged and give up. Truth is that Romney’s winning.” Fed up with Obama? Get your personally autographed copy of the New York Times bestseller “Fool Me Twice” exclusively from WND! The source further told WND that Pritzker is experiencing frustration in her fundraising efforts, as wealthy donors who contributed generously to Obama in 2008 are not even returning her phone calls. The source said Pritzker is “reminding everyone how generous to their supporters the Clintons were when they left office.” “Everything is for sale. Ambassadorships, government grants, stimulus money – you name it,” the source told WND. “There’s nearly three months between the Nov. 6 election and the Jan. 20 inauguration – plenty of time to hand out goodies to friends from the Oval Office</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348172087056</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:14:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348172150929-119</Id><Topic><Title>More Proof the Dems Have their Heads Where the Sun Don't Shine!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348171074933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:57:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>7-11-2012: The House spent the entire day Tuesday debating the repeal of the Affordable Care Act. This is the 33rd time in 18 months that they've tried this. According to the Congression Research Service these votes have cost the tax-payers $50 million dollars. For the record, the House has voted on exactly one jobs bill in the same time period. No jobs were even remotely created. 7-13-2012: On Wednesday, the 11th, the House voted for repeal of the Affordable Care Act, then stopped to discuss golf. I am not kidding. No jobs were created. 7-16-2012: Having failed to ACTUALLY repeal the Affordable Care Act the House took Friday the 13th off, 'cause it's SCAAAAARY. No jobs were created. 7-18-2012: The House was in recess on Monday the 16th. On the 17th it passed both a Department of State appropriations bill and the Insular Areas Act of 2011. (Insular areas are, generally speaking, small islands which the U.S. claims for itself.) No jobs were created. 7-20-2012: The House spent the 18th and 19th debating the massive Defense Appropriations Bill. No jobs were created. 7-23-2012: The House spent the Friday the 20th debating the massive Defense Appropriations Bill. No jobs were created. 7-25-2012: The House spent the 23th and 24th marking time until the August recess debating various suspension bills (requires a 2/3 vote), one of which prohibits the issuance of new regulations on business until the unemployment rate falls below 6%. Need I add which party authored such a nonsensical piece of tripe? 7-27-2012: On Wednesday the 25th the House voted to require a full audit of the Federal Reserve. On Thursday the 26th the House spent most of the day passing amendments for suspension bills, plus one whole hour to fix one typo. No jobs were created. 7-30-2012: The House took last Friday, the 27th, off because it was SUCH a tough week accomplishing nothing. 8-1-2012: The House was in recess Monday the 30th. On the 31st they took votes on three bills. One was to reduce executive positions subject to Senate approval and one was to make tax delinquents ineligible for federal jobs. These were essentially job-reducing bills, so of course they both passed. The third was an anti-abortion bill. It failed. Negative jobs were created. 8-3-2012: On Wednesday, the 1st, the House passed a series of ho-hum suspension rules and eventually voted down a revision of the Bush tax cuts that would have only taxed earnings in excess of $250k. On Thursday, the 2nd, the House passed a resolution that said the government should keep its grubby mitts off the internet. The House will now be in recess for the next five weeks. 9-10-12 &amp; 9-11-12: The House is finally back in session and the past two days have seen a flurry of voting on various bills, but they all ended on the same note: "Motion to reconsider laid on the table and Agreed to without objection." Meaning "Okay, we voted for this turkey but we're going to give it old skunk-eye once more before passing it along to the Senate." 9-12-12: The House passed bills to: extend the FISA Act, promote competitiveness in American manufacturing (don't get excited), and a land swap in Minnesota. No jobs were created. 9-13-12: The House passed nothing today, and for the first time in modern history, in the midst of a terrible drought, the House will not pass a Farm Bill. Not only have no jobs been created but our nation's farmers are going bankrupt. No jobs were created. 9-14-12: The House reauthorized the Federal Insecticide, Fungicide, and Rodenticide Act, then limited taxpayer exposure to a 2005 Energy Policy Act. No jobs were created. 9-17&amp;18-2012: The House took the first two days of this week off, because they CAN. No jobs were created.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348172150929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:15:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348172172724-120</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Approval Rating Down to 46%... Pathetic!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348170751621</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:52:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMFAO. I live in reality. You and your co-hearts are on another planet. See if Mitt will join you sad sacks after he gets drowned in Nov</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1348172172724</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:16:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348172568176-121</Id><Title>Green Energy Dead... Can't Make it Without Sucking on the Govt Tit.... From NYTs</Title><Msg>Tax Credit in Doubt, Wind Power Industry Is Withering Jessica Kourkounis for The New York Times Gamesa, a major maker of components for wind turbines, has all but shut down its factory in Fairless Hills, Pa., and furloughed 92 workers. By DIANE CARDWELL Published: September 20, 2012 286 Comments FACEBOOK TWITTER GOOGLE+ E-MAIL SHARE PRINT REPRINTS FAIRLESS HILLS, Pa. — Last month, Gamesa, a major maker of wind turbines, completed the first significant order of its latest innovation: a camper-size box that can capture the energy of slow winds, potentially opening up new parts of the country to wind power. A blog about energy and the environment. Go to Blog » Readers’ Comments Share your thoughts. Post a Comment » Read All Comments (286) » But by the time the last of the devices, worth more than $1.25 million, was hitched to a rail car, Gamesa had all but shut down its factory here and furloughed 92 of the workers who made them. “We are all really sad,” said Miguel Orobiyi, 34, who worked as a mechanical assembler at the Gamesa plant for nearly five years. “I hope they call us back because they are really, really good jobs.” Similar cutbacks are happening throughout the American wind sector, which includes hundreds of manufacturers, from multinationals that make giant windmills to smaller local manufacturers that supply specialty steel or bolts. In recent months, companies have announced almost 1,700 layoffs. At its peak in 2008 and 2009, the industry employed about 85,000 people, according to the American Wind Energy Association, the industry’s principal trade group. About 10,000 of those jobs have disappeared since, according to the association, as wind companies have been buffeted by weak demand for electricity, stiff competition from cheap natural gas and cheaper options from Asian competitors. Chinese manufacturers, who can often underprice goods because of generous state subsidies, have moved into the American market and have become an issue in the larger trade tensions between the two countries. In July, the United States Commerce Department imposed tariffs on steel turbine towers from China after finding that manufacturers had been selling them for less than the cost of production. And now, on top of the business challenges, the industry is facing a big political problem in Washington: the Dec. 31 expiration of a federal tax credit that makes wind power more competitive with other sources of electricity. The tax break, which costs about $1 billion a year, has been periodically renewed by Congress with support from both parties. This year, however, it has become a wedge issue in the presidential contest. President Obama has traveled to wind-heavy swing states like Iowa to tout his support for the subsidy. Mitt Romney, the Republican nominee, has said he opposes the wind credit, and that has galvanized Republicans in Congress against it, perhaps dooming any extension or at least delaying it until after the election despite a last-ditch lobbying effort from proponents this week. Opponents argue that the industry has had long enough to wean itself from the subsidy and, with wind representing a small percentage of total electricity generation, the taxpayers’ investment has yielded an insufficient return. “Big Wind has had extension after extension after extension,” said Benjamin Cole, a spokesman for the American Energy Alliance, a group partly financed by oil interests that has been lobbying against the credit in Washington. “The government shouldn’t be continuing to prop up industries that never seem to be able to get off their training wheels.” But without the tax credit in place, the wind business “falls off a cliff,” said Ryan Wiser, a staff scientist at Lawrence Berkeley National Laboratory who studies the market potential of renewable electricity sources. The industry’s precariousness was apparent a few weeks ago at the Gamesa factory, as a crew loaded the guts of the company’s newest model of the component, a device known as a nacelle, into its fiberglass shell. Only 50 completed nacelles awaited pickup in a yard once filled with three times as many, most of the production line stood idle, and shelves rated to hold 7,270 pounds of parts and equipment lay bare. “We’ve done a lot to get really efficient here,” said Tom Bell, the manager of the plant, which was built on the grounds of a shuttered U.S. Steel factory that was once a bedrock of the local economy. “Now we just need a few more orders.” Industry executives and analysts say that the looming end of the production tax credit, which subsidizes wind power by 2.2 cents a kilowatt-hour, has made project developers skittish about investing or going forward. That reluctance has rippled through the supply chain. On Tuesday, Siemens, the German-based turbine-maker, announced it would lay off 945 workers in Kansas, Iowa and Florida, including part-timers. Last week Katana Summit, a tower manufacturer, said it would shut down operations in Nebraska and Washington if it could not find a buyer. Vestas, the world’s largest turbine manufacturer, with operations in Colorado and Texas, recently laid off 1,400 workers globally on top of 2,300 layoffs announced earlier this year. Clipper Windpower, with manufacturing in Iowa, is reducing its staff by a third, to 376 from 550. DMI Industries, another tower producer, is planning to lay off 167 workers in Tulsa by November. Wind industry jobs range in pay from about $30,000 a year for assemblers to almost $100,000 a year for engineers, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348172568176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:22:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348173002929-122</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Approval Rating Down to 46%... Pathetic!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348170751621</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:52:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama should have at least a 47% approval level, which accounts for all government moochers.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1348173002929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:30:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348173334446-123</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Approval Rating Down to 46%... Pathetic!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348170751621</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:52:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all those companies Romney bankrupted , is that not government assistants?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348173334446</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:35:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348173466960-124</Id><Topic><Title>republican moochers leeches and takers</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348161030538</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would you rather have the government set prices on all items.. Your Soviet Union mentallity went out with the birds.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1348173466960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348173646250-125</Id><Topic><Title>Pawlenty Jumping Off the Romney Ship</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1348167405518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>going to be fun listining to all the childish names imaccom can invent from now until election day , that`s about all he has left , nothing he posts is even close to being factual even in an alternate universe.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348173646250</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:40:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348174461364-126</Id><Title>Obama Forced to Eat his Own Words!</Title><Msg>BOOM! Romney tells crowd we’ll give Obama a chance to change Washington from the outside in November! Posted by The Right Scoop on September 20th, 2012 in Politics | 26 Comments Fantastic Romney response to Obama’s claim that he can’t change Washington from the inside, that it can only be changed from the outside. Romney tells the crowd that Obama has already thrown in the white flag of surrender on changing Washington from the inside so we’ll give him a chance to change it from the outside in November. BA</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348174461364</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:54:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348174975898-127</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Forced to Eat his Own Words!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348174461364</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:54:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no longer a poop pusher looks like you have advanced to shlt shoveler lol</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348174975898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:02:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348175108797-128</Id><Title>FOX</Title><Msg>Last night, for the second night in a row, MSNBC beat Fox News in primetime (8-11pm) in the key adults 25-54 demo. On Monday MSNBC averaged 471,000 demo viewers to Fox News Channel’s 469,000. On Tuesday, MSNBC drew 575,000 demo viewers, to FNC’s 526,000. We will have the full ratings numbers in The Scoreboard a little later on. The number one show in the demo on cable news is always, always “The O’Reilly Factor” unless there is some sort of unusual news event or huge booking.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348175108797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:05:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348175294658-129</Id><Topic><Title>Baggers in full panic republiwhopper mode</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348152061502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:41:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The whole mass of voters is starting to shift left. Everywhere you look the polls are showing big gains for Democrats, especially in Senate races. If the shift continues at this pace it will be a landslide election. Pity, eh!</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348175294658</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:08:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348175928726-130</Id><Topic><Title>FOX</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348175108797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:05:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Foxvda polling gives Obama a big lead. Have to give them credit where credit is due. Funny how the baggers never mention the foxvda poll?</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348175928726</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:18:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348176589202-131</Id><Title>GOP; Operation Rescue Romney!!!</Title><Msg>More than 30 Senate Republicans took to the Senate floor this morning in back-to-back coordinated speeches with attacks aimed at President Obama and the Democratically-led Senate. The speeches were one part airing of grievances, one part campaign rhetoric, in a not-so-veiled attempt to influence the message as lawmakers go back to their districts next week. This could be the final day the Senate is open for business before the election. The short one- or two-minute speeches covered a broad range of topics from the budget, to debt, to high unemployment and foreign policy. But no matter the topic, the message that Senate Republicans hoped to send is that Obama and the Senate Democrats have "failed" to lead - and Republicans can offer something "better" for the nation. By Sunlen Miller | ABC OTUS News</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1348176589202</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:29:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348176625043-132</Id><Topic><Title>veteran job bill</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348149531788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:58:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell us more, catfish. The repubs say they "support thr troops". Many Vets are unemployed and need a hand. The repubs voted to filibuster the Veterans Jobs Bill to death. Eh?</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348176625043</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348176923074-133</Id><Topic><Title>veteran job bill</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348149531788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:58:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why Did so Many Dems Vote Against the Bill? Why are you Afraid to a Answer, eh? Seems to be a Revolt in the Dem Party over this Bill !</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348176923074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:35:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348177289938-134</Id><Topic><Title>veteran job bill</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348149531788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:58:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What bill are you talking about, imacommie? Here's what I found The outcome of this vote was a staggering reversal of previous Republican support a week earlier when on a September 11, 2012 vote to move S.3457 forward, the Senate voted overwhelmingly in favor with a 95 Yeas to 1 Nay. All 51 Democratic Senators and both Independent Senators voted for the bill. In addition, five Republicans broke rank with their party to support the measure: Senators Scott Brown of Massachusetts, Susan Collins and Olympia Snowe, both of Maine, Dean Heller of Nevada, and Lisa Murkowski of Alaska. Now, I MUST be wrong, so why don't you enlighten me, GENIUS?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1348177289938</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348177352680-135</Id><Topic><Title>veteran job bill</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348149531788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:58:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In your case, fishbrains, Don't mess with chinkless stupidity.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1348177352680</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:42:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348177664800-136</Id><Topic><Title>GOP; Operation Rescue Romney!!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1348176589202</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:29:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and Your Liberal Friends Sound Really Scared by Your Hysterical Posts, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348177664800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:47:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348178461516-137</Id><Topic><Title>FOX</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348175108797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:05:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Fox" and "news" explain why fox viewers always finish last in the "actually know something" category.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1348178461516</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 18:01:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348180057031-138</Id><Topic><Title>Makers versus Takers</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1348157744133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:15:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ahkmed err takers err truths err spaz err islaMO err ahkmedMO err MOmoMO err spazMO</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1348180057031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 18:27:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348180626046-139</Id><Topic><Title>GOP; Operation Rescue Romney!!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1348176589202</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:29:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still waiting, eniac, for you to tell me how many Democratic senators voted against the veterans' jobs bill.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1348180626046</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 18:37:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348183287540-140</Id><Title>Romney opens up 4 point lead in Ohio and is up by 3 in Florida</Title><Msg>The EIB poll has Obama pulling away in Key states</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1348183287540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:21:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348183440553-141</Id><Title>No Communists have endorsed Romney</Title><Msg>......and no REAL AMERICANS have endorsed Obama......but he does have many....and I do mean many communist supporters.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1348183440553</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348183923710-142</Id><Topic><Title>No Communists have endorsed Romney</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1348183440553</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are no more communists, that was a 1980s thing. USSR is no more.</Msg><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1348183923710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:32:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348184070965-143</Id><Title>State republicans will get hammered</Title><Msg>Most republicans would rather see Obama than another republican disaster as a president. They will sit this one out and wait for 2016</Msg><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1348184070965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:34:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348184560162-144</Id><Title>Lessons learned</Title><Msg>For Obama, you cannot change Washington from the inside. For myself, you cannot vote for Obama again.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1348184560162</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:42:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348186476610-145</Id><Topic><Title>Romney opens up 4 point lead in Ohio and is up by 3 in Florida</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1348183287540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well known political strategist,Dick Morris, who was President Clinton's Chief Political Advisor keeps saying that Gov. Romney is going to win the election. Morris knows polls as well as Scott Rasmassun. I had the privilege of being at a TeaParty meeting where Morris was the keynote speaker. If I were you I wouldn't even show up to vote for your illegal immigrant marxist president. The American people,at least the smart ones, now know the truth about this Anarchist we have as president! It's not about republicans and it's not about democrats. This is about a higher percentage of independents that are going to vote for Romney.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1348186476610</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:14:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348187173890-146</Id><Topic><Title>Romney opens up 4 point lead in Ohio and is up by 3 in Florida</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1348183287540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would be prostitute toe sucking #$%$ artist Dick Morris. He also said McCain was going to win. If you want to listen to somebody listen to Nate Silver. He was closer than anybody last time.</Msg><Username>gerbilfood4me</Username><Timestamp>1348187173890</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:26:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348187931846-147</Id><Topic><Title>Romney opens up 4 point lead in Ohio and is up by 3 in Florida</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1348183287540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was at the meeting you so ineloquently and semiliterately described, and while there was a question of facts, many rubes--er--teabaggers donated handsomely to my "cause." I can always count on a guaranteed take from those rubes. s/ Orly</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1348187931846</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:38:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348188969349-148</Id><Title>Record High Un-Employment and Now Spectacular Failures in Foreign Policy Spell Doom for Obama!</Title><Msg>Hussein is Toast in November... Just Wait Until the Debates...</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348188969349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:56:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348191026790-149</Id><Topic><Title>Romney opens up 4 point lead in Ohio and is up by 3 in Florida</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1348183287540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:21:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah, Now Morris was a Favorite of Slick Willy, wasn't He? My, How Times Have Changed?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348191026790</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 21:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348191442068-150</Id><Topic><Title>State republicans will get hammered</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1348184070965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:34:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Most republicans ... will sit this one out and wait for 2016" Andse, Between Democrats and Republicans, which do you believe is/are more likely to sit on their butts and do nothing? There, you have you answer. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1348191442068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 21:37:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348191872457-151</Id><Topic><Title>State republicans will get hammered</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1348184070965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:34:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, it Will be the African Americans Who Will Set out this Election as They are Experiencing an Un-Employment Rate over 18% Now Obama has made the Hispanics...</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348191872457</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 21:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348192615475-152</Id><Topic><Title>State republicans will get hammered</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1348184070965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:34:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An improvement for BB!! No bald-faced false witness statements this time. Keep up the fine work. See? You really can improve.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1348192615475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 21:56:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348193126170-153</Id><Topic><Title>State republicans will get hammered</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1348184070965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:34:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He may have re-read Matthew 6.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1348193126170</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348195863027-154</Id><Topic><Title>No Communists have endorsed Romney</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1348183440553</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Especially T-Paw, who just a few weeks ago was on the short list for V-P. He just quit his campaign co-chair seat to be a bank lobbyist. A giant poke in the eye to Willard and the remaining sane Republicans are furious at T-paw.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1348195863027</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:51:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348197026433-155</Id><Title>The Liberal Focus</Title><Msg>Over 8% unemployment $16 trillion in debt gas prices out of sight economy in the tank Middle east on fire US ambassador murdered soldiers at risk in Afghanistan so what's the liberal focus and obsession? Romney's taxes ya can't make this stuff up</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1348197026433</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 23:10:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348197494524-156</Id><Topic><Title>The Liberal Focus</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1348197026433</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 23:10:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whats John Boehner handicap?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348197494524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 23:18:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348197996722-157</Id><Topic><Title>State republicans will get hammered</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1348184070965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:34:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Freaking Amazing, Greg you get 4 gold stars tonight ! you got 8 subjects into two sentences . any idea what John Boehner handicap is?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348197996722</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 23:26:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348198299614-158</Id><Topic><Title>State republicans will get hammered</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1348184070965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:34:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you`re funny :)</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348198299614</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 23:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348198805251-159</Id><Topic><Title>No Communists have endorsed Romney</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1348183440553</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet I`m more American than you are. try to explain to me what makes you real?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348198805251</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 23:40:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>