<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-11"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347338826007-1</Id><Title>US "***August***" Budget Deficit Soars To $192 Billion!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>America, YOUR Going to LEARN the HARD WAY that "BIG Government" Ain't YOUR FRIEND!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Obama IS Busting the Budget With Every ""Give Away" He can Find to prevent HIM and his FOOLS that He Brought with him to Washington from becoming Victims of his Economic "IGNORANCE"!!!!!!!!!!!! US August Budget Deficit Soars To $192 Billion, $1.17 Trillion In Fiscal 2012 Read ALL About it Where "The REAL News Matters"!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1347338826007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:47:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347339326352-2</Id><Topic><Title>US "***August***" Budget Deficit Soars To $192 Billion!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1347338826007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If we can "Read ALL About it Where "The REAL News Matters"!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!" why the F do we have to read about it here? Is this a test of your emergency broadcasting sytem?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1347339326352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347339437070-3</Id><Topic><Title>US "***August***" Budget Deficit Soars To $192 Billion!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1347338826007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I reported him to Yahoo for using too many exclamation marks!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>i_like_ike99</Username><Timestamp>1347339437070</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:57:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347346458688-4</Id><Topic><Title>CNN Poll</Title><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1347309991888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:46:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sammy, "Perhaps you could get a life somewhere, instead." As well as yourself. Like you this is one element today of my life. You have your purpose and I have mine. Now, I find it curious that you would post "out of the blue" on this very subject. You once posted the following on this very subject: "I'm surprised that Yahoo lets folks have 2,357 separate identities. Seems like they could control this through I.P. address or something. In any case, "get a life" would seem to apply." So it would seem to me that you would have also advised "pseudo_jumbo" in the same way that I did. Or are you having a "non-consistent day"? BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1347346458688</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 02:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347357780921-5</Id><Topic><Title>US "***August***" Budget Deficit Soars To $192 Billion!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1347338826007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do we have to "read all about" your twisted dogma here? Can't you write a blog for Pravda?</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1347357780921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 06:03:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347359955013-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Lead Widening</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1347323794993</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 20:36:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So it's all going according to Karl Rove's plan. Rove doesn't want Romney to win, because then Romney would only demonstrate that trickle-down doesn't work. What best suits the neocon agenda is Obama in the White House to feed redneck indignance and ensure an obstructionist Congress.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1347359955013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 06:39:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347367295252-7</Id><Topic><Title>US "***August***" Budget Deficit Soars To $192 Billion!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1347338826007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am confused, how do they know how big the budget deficit is if we have not had a budget in 3 years.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1347367295252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 08:41:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347367351666-8</Id><Topic><Title>Are rich politicians harder to bribe?</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347317489253</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:51:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's an old saying, "You can never be too rich".</Msg><Username>gpd8252</Username><Timestamp>1347367351666</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 08:42:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347369696941-9</Id><Topic><Title>Are rich politicians harder to bribe?</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347317489253</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:51:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like what gift can you give to the queen? I said harder not impossible.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347369696941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 09:21:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347372814828-10</Id><Title>Boeing PA facility evacuated</Title><Msg>RIDLEY PARK, Pa. - Part of a Boeing plant in suburban Philadelphia has been evacuated and police are investigating after officials say they received a threat related to the facility. Boeing spokesman Damien Mills says several hundred employees at the facility were evacuated between 7:30 a.m. and 8:30 a.m. Tuesday after officials received some sort of threat. He would not say how the threat was received. Ridley Township police are responding and say it related to some sort of note left in a bathroom.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1347372814828</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347375507447-11</Id><Title>Why is Obama skipping more than half of his daily intelligence meetings?</Title><Msg>President Obama is touting his foreign policy experience on the campaign trail, but startling new statistics suggest that national security has not necessarily been the personal priority the president makes it out to be. It turns out that more than half the time, the commander in chief does not attend his daily intelligence meeting.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347375507447</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:58:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347375617433-12</Id><Title>Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Msg>This is the kind of business sense this administration has used to give us trillion dollar deficits.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347375617433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347376166836-13</Id><Title>The Communist Party endorses Barack Obama</Title><Msg>… on the very same grounds -- even in the same words -- that Obama uses in defense of himself. This is not the first time the CPUSA has officially supported Obama, of course. Alternative media voices have been trying to break through the MSM soundproofing on this matter for some time. (Examples here and here.) The wording of this year's endorsement is particularly full-throated, however, which in itself ought to be disturbing to anyone still on the fence about the nature of the man, his party, and his policies. And while the extreme race-baiting language used in the endorsement is more in keeping with the rhetorical tone of the Weather Underground or MSNBC than with that of "respectable" Democrat sources, is its point any different in principle from many things we hear from elected Democrats every day?</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347376166836</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347376642341-14</Id><Topic><Title>Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347375617433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if we don`t invest in future technology somebody else ( China ) will. and we will continue down the path of failure with stupid thinking like investing in the future is a bad thing.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1347376642341</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:17:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347376992259-15</Id><Topic><Title>Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347375617433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Governments don't invest......they spend. It's the government's job to get out of the way of investors so they will invest.....unless you have the mentality of a communist.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347376992259</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:23:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347377081383-16</Id><Topic><Title>The Communist Party endorses Barack Obama</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347376166836</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:09:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you have a link to support that claim? It's pretty hard for me to believe the CP would endorse a war criminal and murderer who is in bed with Wall Streeters and the the Military Industrial Security Complex.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1347377081383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:24:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347377161463-17</Id><Topic><Title>Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347375617433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Chevy Volt works just fine. I know someone who sold his sports car to buy a Volt, and he's very happy with the Volt.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1347377161463</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347377199559-18</Id><Topic><Title>Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347375617433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you have a link to support your claim, or are you just making shti up?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1347377199559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:26:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347377280102-19</Id><Title>Moody Warns Downgrade Could be Coming</Title><Msg>Moody’s expects to cut US rating without deal to lower debt/GDP ratio Budget negotiations likely to determine AAA rating and outlook If budget talks do not produce downward trend in debt-to-GDP ratio, rating likely to be lowered to AA1 Assumes “relatively orderly” process for increasing debt limit The full Moody’s statement is here For whoever wins the election, getting the votes from the public will be the easy part. Getting the votes in Congress will be painful. Budget negotiations likely to determine AAA rating and outlook If budget talks do not produce downward trend in debt-to-GDP ratio, rating likely to be lowered to AA1 Assumes “relatively orderly” process for increasing debt limit The full Moody’s statement is here For whoever wins the election, getting the votes from the public will be the easy part. Getting the votes in Congress will be painful.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347377280102</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347377619686-20</Id><Topic><Title>Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347375617433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the private sector would rather ship the jobs to china and make more profits than invest in the US . and #$%$ Government has always invested in this country! jeez do a little history.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1347377619686</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:33:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347378018508-21</Id><Topic><Title>Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347375617433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So we develop the technology and then the chinaman copies it and produces it cheaper. Think Solyndra. They couldn't compete against the cheaper Chinese knock-offs.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1347378018508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:40:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347378060329-22</Id><Title>Why the Obama Economy is a Disaster</Title><Msg>In July, a GAI analysis of President Obama’s calendar found that the president has spent just 412 hours in economic meetings of any kind throughout his presidency versus the over 600 hours he’s spent golfing.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347378060329</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:41:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347378150115-23</Id><Topic><Title>Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347375617433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're probably right. So ... should we stop developing new technologies then? What's your suggested solution?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1347378150115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347378280124-24</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Obama Economy is a Disaster</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347378060329</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:41:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How does that compare historically? Such as with Eisenhower? How much time did Dubya spend on preventing terrorism vs. whacking brush in Crawford?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1347378280124</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:44:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347378496659-25</Id><Topic><Title>Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347375617433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please list a couple of the ideas Obama implemented in the Volt.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1347378496659</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:48:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347378992396-26</Id><Title>Heh Moody there is help available for you!</Title><Msg>You sound like you are really suffering. Get help son before you totally lose it!</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1347378992396</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:56:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347379137646-27</Id><Title>Technically speaking</Title><Msg>Is the President playing hooky in the past year on the road campaigning instead of staying at the Oval Office governing and not shy collecting his pay? Only in America.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1347379137646</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:58:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347379453883-28</Id><Title>Bill Clinton Ignores History</Title><Msg>For the first 150 years of this country's existence, the federal government felt no great need to "do something" when the economy turned down. Over that long span of time, the economic downturns were neither as deep nor as long lasting as they have been since the federal government decided that it had to "do something" in the wake of the stock market crash of 1929, which set a new precedent. One of the last of the "do nothing" presidents was Warren G. Harding. In 1921, under President Harding, unemployment hit 11.7 percent -- higher than it has been under President Obama. Harding did nothing to get the economy stimulated. Far from spending more money to try to "jump start" the economy, President Harding actually reduced government spending, as the tax revenues declined during the economic downturn. This was not a matter of absent-mindedly neglecting the economy. President Harding deliberately rejected the urging of his own Secretary of Commerce, Herbert Hoover, to intervene. The 11.7 percent unemployment rate in 1921 fell to 6.7 percent in 1922, and then to 2.4 percent in 1923. It is hard to think of any government intervention in the economy that produced such a sharp and swift reduction in unemployment as was produced by just staying out of the way and letting the economy rebound on its own. Bill Clinton loudly proclaimed to the delegates to the Democratic National Convention that no president could have gotten us out of the recession in just one term. But history shows that the economy rebounded out of a worse unemployment situation in just two years under Harding, who simply let the market revive on its own, as it had done before, time and time again for more than a century. Something similar happened under Ronald Reagan. Unemployment peaked at 9.7 percent early in the Reagan administration. Like Harding and earlier presidents, Reagan did nothing, despite outraged outcries in the media. The economy once again revived on its own. Three years later, unemployment was down to 7.2 percent -- and it kept on falling, as the country experienced twenty years of economic growth with low inflation and low unemployment.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347379453883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:04:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347379719391-29</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing PA facility evacuated</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1347372814828</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Possible gas attack from vapor_plume after he left a message on the bathroom wall when he wrote, "Here I sit broke hearted. Thought I had to chit but only farted".</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1347379719391</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:08:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347379844238-30</Id><Topic><Title>Bill Clinton Ignores History</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347379453883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:04:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raygun quarupled the national debt and you bet the economy took off- of course Raygun never had the smarts to know that national indebitness needs to be paid off.</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347379844238</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:10:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347380104985-31</Id><Topic><Title>Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347375617433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The loss of 49 K per car is very misleading and intentionally so I suspect. 20000 volts sold to date but when that becomes 200,000 volts the loss per car drops to 4,900- this is a number that would be made to go to zero as manufacturing efficiencies take hold on the Volt assy line- so best you drop the cost thing on the Volt and switch to something else to destroy Obama and the Volt</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347380104985</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:15:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347381008837-32</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Obama Economy is a Disaster</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347378060329</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:41:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's OK because although O may be a mediocre golfer, he is a really bad economist. It's probably better that he ignores the economy as much as possible. He would just screw it up.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1347381008837</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:30:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347381514783-33</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Lead Widening</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1347323794993</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 20:36:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except for cutting medicare and social security he Vulture/Voucher ticket has yet to tell us what their plans are for middle class America. We know their plan to reduce taxes for the rich, and incidendty for themselves.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1347381514783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:38:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347381663004-34</Id><Topic><Title>Krugman: GOP Hypocrisy on Jobs</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1347315250000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:14:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harrydokeycom thinks El Flushbo is a peachy keen economist!</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1347381663004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:41:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347381663945-35</Id><Topic><Title>Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347375617433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nuike 'em!</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1347381663945</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:41:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347382720339-36</Id><Title>Kingfish Re: Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Msg>For some (probable glitchy reason) I could not reply to your "nuke em" post (which I assume was a response to mine.) By reply would be "What? And put Wal-Mart out of business?"</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1347382720339</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:58:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347383147423-37</Id><Topic><Title>Kingfish Re: Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1347382720339</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:58:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Punitive sanctions then.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1347383147423</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:05:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347385843955-38</Id><Title>FOREIGN PILOTS (who have never flown the actual plane) TO DELIVER 787</Title><Msg>AMPA Pilots Vote ‘No Confidence’ in Boeing Training &amp; Flight Services Management SEATTLE--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Members of the Airplane Manufacturing Pilots Association (AMPA) have unanimously voted ‘No Confidence’ in their management at The Boeing Company’s Training &amp; Flight Services. A bargaining unit of the Society of Professional Engineering Employees in Aerospace (SPEEA), IFPTE Local 2001, AMPA includes the pilots who deliver Boeing airplanes to customers, including the 787. They also train the pilots of customer airlines. "AMPA pilots took the vote after management abandoned a 50-year practice of only using qualified Boeing pilots and, without telling customers, now plans to use minimally qualified temporary pilots dressed in Boeing uniforms," said Ray Goforth, executive director of SPEEA. "The unprecedented vote came after more than three years of raising concerns and being ignored by Boeing," he added. None of the temporary pilots have flown the 787 and many have not piloted a commercial aircraft in two years, according to SPEEA. According to the union, the temporary pilots have no more preparation on the 787 than the simulator training received by customer flight crews they are being dispatched to train. “787 customers expect experienced flight and training instructors,” said Goforth. “This is flight training roulette for customers who do not know if their pilots will be trained by a genuine Boeing pilot or a temporary contractor dressed in a Boeing uniform. Worse, these temp pilots don’t have any more experience in the 787 simulator than the customers’ own flight crews. When a customer orders a billion dollars worth of airplanes, they don’t expect Boeing to give them a temp flight instructor who has never actually flown a 787.” AMPA pilots said the temporary contract pilots receive none of the additional training and flight time Boeing pilots receive. Boeing Training and Flight Services hired the temporary pilots through Cambridge Communications Limited (CCL), a foreign supplier of contract pilots based on the Isle of Man. While Boeing pilots receive ongoing training and are required to meet stringent flying time requirements in the air and in simulators for each aircraft, Cambridge pilots are not.</Msg><Username>stonewalljeff</Username><Timestamp>1347385843955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347387203822-39</Id><Title>Pentahoax - secrets of the 9-11 false flag. part 2</Title><Msg>"the Pentagon was a crime scene on 9-11. Nothing more. It should have been secured by MP's, and the physical evidence tagged and flagged. Instead, 200 persons swarmed the front lawn and began to scrub it clean of evidence before the fire trucks arrived. On scene personnel were told to "......... read the full story Pentahoax- secrets of the 9-11 false flag.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1347387203822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:13:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347388399451-40</Id><Topic><Title>Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347375617433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Governments invest. They invest in schools, roads, bridges, harbors, hydroelectric projects, museums, basic research. You're balmy.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1347388399451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:33:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347389944693-41</Id><Topic><Title>Pentahoax - secrets of the 9-11 false flag. part 2</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1347387203822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:13:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty, is that you? It sounds all stupid and crazy like you.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1347389944693</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:59:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347390228692-42</Id><Title>Americans for a greater Israeli nation support Romney for President.</Title><Msg>Romney has pledged increased aid, increased military gifts, increased loans and increased sharing of intelligence and military research. Romney is a good mormon who will help America begin a big war in Iran.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1347390228692</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:03:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347390352611-43</Id><Topic><Title>Pentahoax - secrets of the 9-11 false flag. part 2</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1347387203822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:13:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The KEY to ( not) solving a crime is to remove the evidence. Mossad criminal investigation handbook.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1347390352611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:05:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347391775762-44</Id><Topic><Title>Who Really built America</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1347159898016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:04:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HI O.K., unions are a good thing. We currently have too much of a good thing.</Msg><Username>mjs61</Username><Timestamp>1347391775762</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:29:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347392455586-45</Id><Topic><Title>Pentahoax - secrets of the 9-11 false flag. part 2</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1347387203822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:13:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That must be Sparty! Conspiracies and blaming the Israeli's. Like I said crazy and stupid, Sparty's calling card.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1347392455586</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:40:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347392607120-46</Id><Topic><Title>Who Really built America</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1347159898016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:04:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said! romney and his ungodly crew want to move us back to "the good ol' days". Little government with no provisions for the common good, a true oligarchy! It is the old saw: the Golden rule...he who owns the gold makes the rules, it is that simple! Kamakure</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1347392607120</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:43:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347400200252-47</Id><Title>'Brotherhood turning Middle East into Islamist bloc'</Title><Msg>Dichter Warns Against Muslim Brotherhood Takeover Home Front Defense Minister: The Arab world has begun the long journey which ends with Muslim Brotherhood control. Egypt: The Muslim Brotherhood Bomb? By Raymond Stock "We [Egyptians] are ready to starve in order to own a nuclear weapon that will represent a real deterrent and will be decisive in the Arab-Israeli conflict." — Dr. Hamdi Hassan, Spokesman, Muslim Brotherhood Parliamentary Caucus, 2006 IT Begins!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Obama IS another JIMMY Carter!!!!!!!!!!! The Muslim Brotherhood Strikes the U.S. Embassy, Breaches the Embassy WALLS, Tears Down the American Flag, and Raises a Black FLAG with Islamic Inscription in its place!!!!!!!!!!!! And Take NOTE, The Radicals in Cairo did this on the Anniversary of 9/11!!!!!!!!! The ""THIRD Crusade"" IS NOW REAL and can No LONGER Be Ignored by the WEST!!!!!!!!!! America, There "IS" Something REALLY Wrong HERE when Obama Can't Make TIME with America's closes Ally in the Middle East to MEET with ""Prime Minister Binyamin Netanyahu"" and SHOW HIS Support for Israel and make it CLEAR to IRAN that America Stands with Israel Against Iran's Desire of Becoming a Nuclear Power!!!!!!!!!! Thanks to Obama, Global WAR "IS" Coming in this DECADE.............Don't Doubt ME On THIS Folks.............It's Going to HAPPEN!!!!!!!!!! "The REAL News Matters"!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1347400200252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 17:50:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347400456809-48</Id><Title>Should we forget the Bush economy</Title><Msg>I remember when it looked hopeless when Bush announced the banks were failing, do you? Bubbles</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1347400456809</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 17:54:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347400870268-49</Id><Topic><Title>Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347375617433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you think Gov't doesn't invest then I'm sure you'll agree that military spending is a total waste and could easily be cut by 2/3, leaving lots of money to spend on important things.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1347400870268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:01:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347402276268-50</Id><Topic><Title>A 9/11 Thought</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_008</Username><Timestamp>1347401423106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>9-11 was an inside job and Mossad did it. Wake up.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1347402276268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:24:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347403457546-51</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s Health Care Dither</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_008</Username><Timestamp>1347403071236</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:37:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try seeing What Obamacare is going to do to medicare before you keep complaing about What Romney and Ryan are doing to it. Obama has delayed his cuts until AFTER the elections to hide his cuts. Both parties will end up at the same place maybe by different means but it's all BAD for the people (mostly seniors) who rely on Medicare!</Msg><Username>dafarmer9460</Username><Timestamp>1347403457546</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:44:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347403865308-52</Id><Topic><Title>A 9/11 Thought</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_008</Username><Timestamp>1347401423106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, four years after Bush, we still have .... - the Patriot Act - Guantanamo - the TSA - Homeland Security - engagement in Afghanistan Then, Obama added to the mix ... - killing Americans by drone without even a trial - spying on Americans in the United States with drones - covert wars in Africa - ArabSpring enhanced radical regimes in Egypt and Libya - no action against radical regimes in Syria and Iran But, what we did get from our Hope and Change "big speech" Prez is to eliminate pouring water on people's faces for ten seconds.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1347403865308</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347405084183-53</Id><Topic><Title>A 9/11 Thought</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_008</Username><Timestamp>1347401423106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WELL- why is it that the fact that Clinton turned down at least 3 times an OK to terminate OSAMA ? AND OBUMA now gets to spike the ball after taking advantage of about a decades worth of intel and tracking ? And being almost the ONLY positive thing he can say in his acceptance speech</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1347405084183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 19:11:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347406919783-54</Id><Topic><Title>A 9/11 Thought</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_008</Username><Timestamp>1347401423106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don, the 9/11 Commission said there was no truth to the claim that Clinton turned down Osama. However, there is information (not in the 9/11 Commission Report) that in the spring of 2001 Taliban was pursuing inquiries to turn him over. The best research resource about 9/11 is at historycommons.org. All the information there was complied by a Stanford graduate, and it's all from mainstream sources.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1347406919783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 19:41:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347407133969-55</Id><Topic><Title>A 9/11 Thought</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_008</Username><Timestamp>1347401423106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, my understanding is that Obama's "no waterboard" order applied to combat prisoners only--not to terrorist suspects--and so it's really just a case of grandstanding. More than one prisoner has died at Guantanamo under Obama's watch, and he refused to investigate the alleged suicides of three prisoners there shortly before he took office. The policy of rendition--flying prisoners to other countries for interrogation continues. The Boeing subsidiary Jeppeson handles those flights--another reason to expect anti-Boeing boycotts from airline travelers overseas.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1347407133969</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 19:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347409003630-56</Id><Topic><Title>FOREIGN PILOTS (who have never flown the actual plane) TO DELIVER 787</Title><Username>stonewalljeff</Username><Timestamp>1347385843955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Managment at Boeing is only 4 years late in delivering the 787 and 30 billion over budget, so why not allow unskilled pilots to try to fly a basic experimental plane, this fits the Boeing Mangment business plan, if we can make it more risky for the shareholder, lets do it. Now if a catastrophic event ocurs Boeing Mangment can blame the Boeing pilots association for not taking a cut in beenefits since the mangment need more bonus at the shareholder expense, BA stock down over 3% for the year apple stock up 65% for the year Apple has beat Boeing in share appreciation for the past 15 years year over year by a wide margin. Boeing debt is very high apple debit, is zero and they have about half as much money in hte bank than Boeing owes.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347409003630</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:16:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347409408107-57</Id><Topic><Title>A 9/11 Thought</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_008</Username><Timestamp>1347401423106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...to eliminate pouring water on people's faces for ten seconds." I guess I missed that part of the Bible that says it's okay to commit what is internationally recognized as torture on folks. Luke? Acts? Romans? Exodus?</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1347409408107</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347411403443-58</Id><Topic><Title>A 9/11 Thought</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_008</Username><Timestamp>1347401423106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"AND OBUMA now gets to spike the ball after taking advantage of about a decades worth of intel and tracking?" Another falsehood. The previous President disbanded the CIA unit specifically tasked with finding bin Laden. This president specifically re-established said office. QED.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1347411403443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:56:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347411786601-59</Id><Topic><Title>The Hope and Change President is a failure</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347403329002</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:42:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope and Change has Turned into Hate and Panic! Obama and His Economic Policies Have Put Millions of Americans Out of Work! Obamaville</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1347411786601</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 21:03:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347411974800-60</Id><Topic><Title>FOREIGN PILOTS (who have never flown the actual plane) TO DELIVER 787</Title><Username>stonewalljeff</Username><Timestamp>1347385843955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So who cares- every 787 they crash or total out means another 787 order!!!-- Stonewal Jeff kind of sounds like ole Dell George the miscreant who was trying to get revenge for getting fired out of Boeing for getting caught doing special things with his boyfreind in the urinal</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347411974800</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 21:06:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347412027513-61</Id><Topic><Title>FOREIGN PILOTS (who have never flown the actual plane) TO DELIVER 787</Title><Username>stonewalljeff</Username><Timestamp>1347385843955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boy - sour grapes- waynedickenson must be Dell Georges boyfriend</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347412027513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 21:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347412637713-62</Id><Topic><Title>Government Motors is losing as much as $49,000 on each Volt it builds.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347375617433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>timinusten you are stoooopid and ill informed. The wind industry is a very large business in the great plains generating as much as 30% of the electricity used in this area. Furthermore numerous wind farms are under construction in this area. Elon Musk the multi billionaire is building several solar farms in the California area to debug the process before he moves his solar farms out into the great basin states especially Nevada. -As far as the Volt the Prius is a screaming success and so will the Volt be. Union workers do all the work- except where its possible to shanghai illegal immigrants and make them do the work. The most sickening thing about your post is you have no real interest in bashing - you dont have enough money to invest in anything and you have no equity in any of these areas. The only reason you post is to vent your hate.</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347412637713</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 21:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347413473987-63</Id><Topic><Title>A 9/11 Thought</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_008</Username><Timestamp>1347401423106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I guess I missed that part of the Bible that says it's okay to commit what is internationally recognized as torture on folks." Dem666, Perhaps you missed the Bible altogether. Try Revelation: v9:5 - “They were not given power to kill them, but only to torture them for five months. And the agony they suffered was like that of the sting of a scorpion when it strikes a man.” (Future judgment, it is recommend that one get right and be ready.) v14:9-11 - “A third angel followed them and said in a loud voice: ‘If anyone worships the beast and his image and receives his mark on the forehead or on the hand, he, too, will drink of the wine of God’s fury, which has been poured full strength into the cup of his wrath. He will be tormented with burning sulfur in the presence of the holy angels and of the Lamb. And the smoke of their torment rises for ever and ever. There is no rest day or night for those who worship the beast and his image, or for anyone who receives the mark of his name.’ ” (This second quote is something that you need to pay close attention and remember for the not too distant future. Or get right and avoid the issue altogether.)</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1347413473987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 21:31:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347413709101-64</Id><Topic><Title>Bill Clinton Ignores History</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1347379453883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:04:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By being the mouth for Obama at the DNC,Bill puts party ahead of country. Toykyo Rose was sent to an American Prison for being the mouthpiece of Emporer Hirohito</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1347413709101</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 21:35:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347416115387-65</Id><Title>Hi all</Title><Msg>wish I could post a comment, but I must be on the immediate delete list.</Msg><Username>the_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1347416115387</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347418174613-66</Id><Topic><Title>A 9/11 Thought</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_008</Username><Timestamp>1347401423106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So i suppose in the future we give them three goats and just say please will you tell us who is trying to kill us?</Msg><Username>ixceller8</Username><Timestamp>1347418174613</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:49:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347418275708-67</Id><Topic><Title>A 9/11 Thought</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_008</Username><Timestamp>1347401423106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? Mining you have not a clue and my guess is you think there is black helicopters watching you and yours</Msg><Username>ixceller8</Username><Timestamp>1347418275708</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347421019856-68</Id><Topic><Title>A 9/11 Thought</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_008</Username><Timestamp>1347401423106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's probably the most twisted cr*p you have ever posted, here, Mr. Bob. Quoting Revelation for rationale on how to practice war crimes is not a sterling example of your perverted form of Christianity. Perhaps you should try harder to get right with God. Now. Good riddance. Go practice in N. Korea or Saudi Arabia.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1347421019856</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 23:36:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>