<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-05"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346820398907-1</Id><Title>$16T</Title><Msg>Looks like we did it and the empty chair just gave $1B to Egypt for good measure.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1346820398907</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 00:46:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346820451035-2</Id><Topic><Title>Another conspiracy theory ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1346792322524</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:58:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"they know who they are" or perhaps, he knows who he is. Back from a well deserved (I am not the judge here) or well needed vacation? I was thinking about you today, that perhaps the board, even or especially because of its new format, is just not the same, your, erstwhile, seemingly absent. But I can see that that was premature thinking on my part. Hooz is ever-ready, not missing beat - in the face of outstanding blather from the DNC conflagration. Even Fox News could not generate an acceptable filter. :-)</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1346820451035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 00:47:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346824108763-3</Id><Title>Fair Share - there you go again!</Title><Msg>You would think that this has become a worn-out message, but I suppose it plays well to the core "believers". Cory Booker tonight: "being asked to pay your fair share isn't class warfare, it's patriotism." OK, I conceptually get the need for more revenue as well as less spending – in order to balance the books. But "patriotism" equated with "paying your fair share"? If that is the case, and because the guilt-trip oriented comment is directed towards folks that have money, then the corollary is "if you don't pay any (federal) taxes you are not a patriot". Or do we simply assume that people that don't make a lot of money have no financial stake in our country? We are talking about the 50% of wage earners simply DO NOT PAY ANY FEDERAL TAXES. The fact that Obama's infamous 1% only makes 10% of all total income, the remaining and “untouchable” 99% actually have more leverage over the solution. I suppose that historically Democrats apparently do not understand the math. But they do get into all of that “touchy feely” stuff like, “Obama should be re-elected because he understands me.” No, we need someone who understands numbers and can make things happen. That is Romney, not Obama.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1346824108763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 01:48:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346834114862-4</Id><Topic><Title>Another conspiracy theory ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1346792322524</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:58:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris - And, since you brought it up, it occurred to me later that I should ask you a couple simple questions: If Jesus was not able to make forgiveness of sins possible, by His sacrifice alone, then what was the purpose of His sacrifice? And, if otherwise an amalgam of His sacrifice and our "good works" somehow constituted salvation (though Romans 3:23 is very clear that no one is "good enough") again how important would then be His sacrifice? How would "belief + works" be measured? There is zero foundation for salvation other than through His death and resurrection. The presumption that works somehow justifies a person before God makes what Jesus did null and void. Of course, works do not. We are justified ONLY by faith. - BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1346834114862</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 04:35:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346840068138-5</Id><Title>US Slips Down the Ranks of Global Competitiveness****</Title><Msg>The United States has slipped further down a global ranking of the world's most competitive economies, according to a World Economic Forum (WEF) survey released on Wednesday. The world's largest economy, which was placed 5th last year, fell two positions to the 7th spot - marking its fourth year of decline. A lack of macroeconomic stability, the business community’s continued mistrust of the government and concerns over its fiscal health were some of the reasons for the downgrade, according to the annual survey. "A number of weaknesses are chipping away at its competitiveness...the U.S. fiscal imbalances and continued political deadlock over resolving these challenges," said Jennifer Blanke, Economist at the Geneva-based WEF. Political deadlock over reducing the unsustainable federal government budget deficit – projected to hit $1.1 trillion this year – prompted Standard &amp; Poor’s to downgrade the country’s credit rating by one notch to AA+ from AAA last August. A mix of U.S. tax hikes and spending cuts – referred to as the "fiscal cliff" - are set to come into force in January unless lawmakers reach a compromise for avoiding them. The survey, which has been conducted annually for over three decades, ranks the competitiveness of 144 countries based on 12 key indicators including infrastructure, macroeconomic environment, labor market efficiency and innovation. “If you look at competitiveness, what we are talking about is productivity. It’s countries that are productive that can support the sorts of rising living standards and high wages that everyone is looking for,” Blanke told CNBC. Despite declining in the overall ranking, the forum highlighted that the U.S. remains one of the world’s top innovators – supported by an “excellent” university system - and continues to offer vast opportunities because of the sheer size of its domestic economy. Switzerland and Singapore retained their positions as the most competitive economies, coming in 1st and 2nd, respectively. Switzerland’s top spot was achieved as a result of its strong performance across the board, according to WEF, with notable labor market efficiency, sophistication of its business sector and its innovative capacity. The country has among the highest rates of patents per capita globally. “Switzerland’s productivity is further enhanced by a business sector that offers excellent on-the-job-training opportunities and labor markets that balance employee protection with the interests of employers,” the report said. China Tops the BRICs Among the large emerging economies, China was ranked highest at 26, thanks to favorable macroeconomic conditions. This was significantly higher than Brazil, India and Russia which came in at 53, 56 and 66, respectively. China runs a moderate budget deficit, boasts a low government debt-to-GDP ratio of 26 percent and its gross savings rate remains above 50 percent of GDP, the forum said. In addition, the rating of its sovereign debt (AA-) is significantly better than that of the other BRICs and of many advanced economies. However, the world’s second largest economy has slipped two notches from last year’s ranking, owing to a deterioration in the development of its financial markets and technological readiness. “Insufficient domestic and foreign competition is of particular concern, as the various barriers to entry appear to be more prevalent and more important than in previous years,” WEF report said.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1346840068138</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 06:14:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346847317440-6</Id><Title>Better watch the convention RWNJ's</Title><Msg>The speakers are burying the republican party with their own words. You are going to have to BUY this election with the money from the 28 fat white men giving unlimited cash to the PAC's. You better learn to grovel boys because these 28 fat white men are going to extract their pound of flesh from everyone, not just progressives.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346847317440</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:15:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346849168314-7</Id><Title>Ryan plan: Let American's starve.</Title><Msg>Food-stamp spending, which more than doubled in four years to a record $75.7 billion in the fiscal year ended Sept. 30, 2011 is the Department of Agriculture's (USDA) biggest annual expense. Republicans in Congress have criticized the cost of the program, and the House budget plan approved in April sponsored by Rep. Paul Ryan of Wisconsin, the party's vice-presidential nominee, would cut costs by $33 billion over 10 years.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346849168314</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346850548457-8</Id><Topic><Title>Better watch the convention RWNJ's</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346847317440</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:15:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well put</Msg><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1346850548457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:09:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346852365732-9</Id><Title>Attack dogs</Title><Msg>Were let loose last night at the DNC but were all bark and no bite.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1346852365732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:39:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346852738538-10</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan plan: Let American's starve.</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346849168314</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:46:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Geez Skunky, and when I thought you couldn't get any dumber you prove you can.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1346852738538</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346853745271-11</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing forcing it's Engineering workforce to make Striking Decisions</Title><Username>ev3044</Username><Timestamp>1346619149701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 16:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"IAM will not honor the strike". Maybe not - - but they should.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1346853745271</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:02:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346854017649-12</Id><Topic><Title>Attack dogs</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1346852365732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:39:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Scare tactics And divide and conquer will only embolden and unite more Americans and will backfire on them.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1346854017649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:06:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346855146640-13</Id><Title>Two ladies</Title><Msg>If Ann and Michelle are competing on the Apprentice and making a sale pitch who will the Donald fire?</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1346855146640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:25:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346855174685-14</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan plan: Let American's starve.</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346849168314</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:46:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it is on the record, Jack A** Google it if you don't believe me</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346855174685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346855232992-15</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan plan: Let American's starve.</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346849168314</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:46:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is an article in today's Seattle Times. If you can read, why don't you look it up. I will be coming to watch you golf some time soon.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346855232992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346855373946-16</Id><Title>Boeing stock price</Title><Msg>BONT is a stock suggested just last week, today it is up over 12%, since last week it is up 18% while Boeing is down, and Boeing is down over 3% for the year, another great stock that has beat Bowing for 15 years is apple AAPL Bont is up over 224% this year! You can list airplane orders for Boeing but you can't talk shareholder value about Boeing. Reason they make planes over budget and late and constantly delay the planes they need to develop, like the 737 delay and now the 777x delay. Each time Airbus grabs some more airplanes that Boeing should have been selling to their customer base.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1346855373946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:29:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346855450042-17</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing forcing it's Engineering workforce to make Striking Decisions</Title><Username>ev3044</Username><Timestamp>1346619149701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 16:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you typing with your elbows? You just don't make any sense.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346855450042</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:30:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346855671800-18</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan plan: Let American's starve.</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346849168314</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:46:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans in Congress have criticized the cost of the program, and the House budget plan approved in April sponsored by Rep. Paul Ryan of Wisconsin, the party's vice-presidential nominee, would cut costs by $33 billion over 10 years.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346855671800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346855948866-19</Id><Title>Boeing Raises China 20-Year Plane Demand Forecast 5.2</Title><Msg>Boeing(NYS:BA) on Wednesday forecast that China will need 5,260 new airliners valued at $670 billion over the next 20 years and expects the country to become the second largest market for new commercial airplanes. The U.S. planemaker said small and intermediate twin-aisles, such as the Boeing 787 Dreamliner and 777, will account for a significant part of future deliveries in China. ( see stoxlinecom website)</Msg><Username>opfment</Username><Timestamp>1346855948866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:39:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346856214141-20</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan plan: Let American's starve.</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346849168314</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:46:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you so dumb that you think that Ryan's plan is to starve Americans. BTW: Snohomish today at 9:15. Port Gardner's Men's Club (Legion Memorial) Monday 9th. Tee time TBA but approx. 8:30.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1346856214141</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:43:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346856864058-21</Id><Title>We “belong” to the government?</Title><Msg>We “belong” to the government? Did you happen to see the little video they ran at the convention last night? That video conveyed the message that while we may belong to different churches and such … we all belong to the government. The line was “The government is the only thing we ALL belong to.” Sorry .. no. We may be subject to different religions doctrines based on our choice of churches. We may be subject to different rules based on our choice of a club to join. But the government is not the only thing we all BELONG to … it is the only thing we are all SUBJECT to. In effect, the Democrats were celebrating the subjugation of the people to government. It’s interesting that the Democrats are now running like hell from this video. Everyone is trying to blame it on everyone else. Suddenly the Democrats have seen that their concept of everyone belonging to the government doesn’t look all that good in broad daylight. They won’t change, though. They’ll just run and hide.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346856864058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:54:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346857152778-22</Id><Title>Michelle Obama is Awesome!!!</Title><Msg>... such a beautiful and passionate first lady!!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346857152778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:59:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346857197777-23</Id><Title>Obama Saved the Auto Industry --- Bolshoi!</Title><Msg>No … he saved the United Auto Workers. The United Auto Workers are not, no matter how much they would like for you to believe that it is so, the auto industry. To expose this “Obama saved the auto industry lie” I’m going to have to go back to before there were automobiles. Back, in fact, to before there was a United States. We’re talking English Common Law. For the most part the legal structure of the United States and of 49 of the 50 states was derived from the laws in effect in England when our country was founded. The English Statute of Bankrupts was enacted in 1542. Even Genghis Kahn recognized bankruptcy … but if you went bankrupt three times you were executed. Let’s simplify this. An individual or a company has two basic types of creditors; secured and unsecured. If someone loans you money to buy a home or a car, that loan is secured by that property. If you don’t play, the lender can take the home (foreclosure) or the car (repossession) and either sell it or keep it as an asset to cover the money they lost when you defaulted on your loan. If you default on an unsecured loan the lender has little recourse but to sue you in court and attempt to get a judgment against you. The local sheriff can then seize some of your property – your bank accounts, for instance – to satisfy that judgment. But … what if you go bankrupt? The law is and the law always has been that if an individual or a corporation goes bankrupt the secured creditors get paid first – then the unsecured creditors can pick over what’s left. Sorry for the lengthy explanation here --- but this is necessary for you to understand what a crock of bat squeeze this “Obama saved the auto industry” line is. Now .. there are two basic types of bankruptcy, both named after a particular chapter or section of the Bankruptcy Code. You have Chapter 7 and Chapter 11. Under corporate or business Chapter 7 bankruptch you close down the business and the business assets are sold off to satisfy the creditors. Under a Chapter 11 you ask the court to hold off the creditors – to keep them from seizing your assets due to your inability to pay back their loans – while you work, under the court’s supervision, to reorganize your business. If you manage to successfully reorganize your business structure you come out of Chapter 11 and continue to do business as normal. Several airlines, including the world’s largest, Delta Airlines, have used Chapter 11 to reorganize their businesses in rough times. Now .. here’s the rub. And here is why Barack Obama stepped in and tossed the Bankruptcy laws aside with General Motors. Under a Chapter 11 bankruptcy the business can elect to void contracts which it deems to be injurious to the business or which the owners or managers believe would prevent a successful reorganization. Now one of the principal reasons the auto industry was in trouble was …unions. Over the years the unions had created an overwhelming array of benefits and wages that were killing the auto industry. Some of these auto workers were making the equivalent of $75 per hour or more in wages and benefits.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346857197777</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:59:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346857361366-24</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama is Awesome!!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346857152778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:59:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, she is.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346857361366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346857375801-25</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's War Against Facts..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346792606268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Truth Hurts...!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346857375801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:02:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346857611112-26</Id><Topic><Title>We “belong” to the government?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346856864058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:54:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't like the United States of America? Get the "blank" out. It is our country and we do have a government. You can't just pick those issues you like. The United States is our country and our country is run by our elected officials and that constitutes the government. Who do you think runs the country?????? Individuals? Corporations?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346857611112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:06:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346857671333-27</Id><Title>Chronicling the expanding catalogue of ObamaCare fables.</Title><Msg>Is there a health insurance horror story disseminated by the White House and its allies that ever turned out to be true? Obamacare advocates have exercised more artistic license than a convention of Photoshoppers. Now, a prominent sob story shilled by President Obama himself about his own mother is in doubt. It’s high past time to call their bluffs. The tall-tale-teller-in-chief cited mom Stanley Ann Dunham’s deathbed fight with her insurer several times over the years to support his successful push to ban pre-existing condition exclusions by insurers. In a typical recounting, Obama shared his personalized trauma during a 2008 debate: “For my mother to die of cancer at the age of 53 and have to spend the last months of her life in the hospital room arguing with insurance companies because they’re saying that this may be a pre-existing condition and they don’t have to pay her treatment, there’s something fundamentally wrong about that.” But there was something fundamentally wrong with Obama’s story. In a recently published biography of Obama’s mother, author and New York Times reporter Janny Scott discovered that Dunham’s health insurer had in fact reimbursed her medical expenses with nary an objection. The actual coverage dispute centered on a separate disability insurance policy. Channeling document forger Dan Rather’s “fake, but accurate” defense, a White House spokesman insisted to the Times that the anecdote somehow still “speaks powerfully to the impact of pre-existing condition limits on insurance protection from health care costs” — even though Dunham’s primary health insurer did everything it was supposed to do and met all its contractual obligations.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346857671333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346857763743-28</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle, ma belle</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney55</Username><Timestamp>1346797708694</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 18:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>she hit it out of the park!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346857763743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346857805017-29</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan plan: Let American's starve.</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346849168314</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:46:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You aren't very bright are you? What are the consequences of cutting 33 billion dollars out of a program that is requiring 77 billion. Some people will not get assistance. I am going to enjoy our time together. Really am</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346857805017</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:10:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346858114552-30</Id><Title>Obama acceptance speech moved indoors</Title><Msg>I guess that his support has eroded so much that, unlike 4 years ago when he filled Mile High stadium in Denver, he would have had to face thousands of empty seats -- and wouldn't that have been another disaster!</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1346858114552</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346858626567-31</Id><Topic><Title>We “belong” to the government?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346856864058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:54:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Who do you think runs the country?????? Individuals? Corporations?" The last time I checked, "We the People" were a bunch of individuals. I have to laugh my a** off when liberal says, if you do like it get out. They don't think Americans have a right to dissent. They seem to forget about that when the other side does something they don't like. What a bunch of collectivist hypocrites.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346858626567</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346858924125-32</Id><Title>The Rerun President</Title><Msg>Just go to youtube and search for "We've Heard It All Before" (Extended Cut).</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346858924125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:28:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346859399257-33</Id><Title>From Where Does Obama Get His Central Planning Ideas?</Title><Msg>Here’s a look at how Obama’s communist mentor Frank Marshall Davis realized the best way to champion his cause was to infiltrate the Democrat Party and change it from within. For Details just Google "Frank Marshall Davis and the Subversion of the Democratic Party."</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346859399257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:36:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346860060733-34</Id><Title>The real Obama</Title><Msg>Is he Lincoln,jFK,Reagan or Bill Clinton? or is he hiding behind them?</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1346860060733</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:47:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346860306319-35</Id><Title>jal has offering</Title><Msg>Japan Airlines Co., seeking to raise up to $8.5 billion in a listing later this month, has already received enough orders for the 175 million shares it plans to price Monday, suggesting the initial public offering will be well oversubscribed. However BONT as noticed a few days ago and posted on this board was a good day trade stock it is up 225 percent this year and up over 18 percent in the past few days or the new products from appleishious always beat the boring company</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1346860306319</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346860315325-36</Id><Topic><Title>From Where Does Obama Get His Central Planning Ideas?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346859399257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:36:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Swear you believe this on the lives of your children and your parents.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346860315325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:51:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346860355178-37</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Win Easily</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346858719154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:25:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you discussed your delusions with your psychiatrist?</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1346860355178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:52:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346860442549-38</Id><Title>Republicans seek God to influence Election..!!</Title><Msg>Vice Presidential candidate Paul Ryan says Democrats have "purged" God. “It’s not in keeping with our founding documents, our founding vision. I’d guess you’d have to ask the Obama administration why they purged all this language from their platform. There sure is a lot of mention of government. I guess I would just put the onus and the burden on them to explain why they did all this, these purges of God.” Is it necessary that a political platform specifically refer to God? For what purpose?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346860442549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346860534558-39</Id><Title>Blue State California has more debt than.......</Title><Msg>......Greece.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346860534558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:55:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346860689203-40</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Win Easily</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346858719154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:25:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, baby! The convention will lift him to a landslide victory! DON'T THINK SO....THE AMERICAN PUBLIC HAS FINALLY AWAKENED TO THE FACT THIS MAN IS A FRAUD LEADING US INTO BANKRUPTCY AND SOCIALISM.....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1346860689203</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346860869130-41</Id><Title>Obama Still Leading from Behind</Title><Msg>The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Wednesday shows Mitt Romney attracting support from 48% of voters nationwide, while President Obama earns 45% of the vote. Mitt Romney also holds a slight edge in 11 key states won by President Obama in 2008 and thought to be competitive in 2012. The states collectively hold 146 Electoral College votes and include Colorado, Florida, Iowa, Michigan, Nevada, New Hampshire, North Carolina, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Virginia and Wisconsin.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346860869130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346860917272-42</Id><Title>Ichelle Obama... Pathetic!</Title><Msg>Michelle Says “I” or “Me” 83 times by KEITH KOFFLER on SEPTEMBER 5, 2012, 10:51 AM In her address to the Democratic Convention Tuesday evening, First Lady Michelle Obama used the words “I” or “me” 83 times, an average of more than three self-references a minute during her 25 minute speech. The emphasis on herself is of note not only because of the strikingly personal nature of the speech, but because of the remarkable suggestion by the first lady that her political views and those of her husband arise much from their own experiences than a reasoned assessment of policies and facts. Time and again in her remarks, Michelle cites examples from her life and President Obama’s that lead to policies they have tried to implement during his presidency.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346860917272</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346861200344-43</Id><Title>DNC Glorifies Senator Who Left a Woman to Drown in His Car</Title><Msg>If you're going to wage a "war on women," there's no better way to do it than glorifying a guy who left a woman to drown in his car while he escaped to dry ground. The video they showed last night at the DNC convention in Charlotte. It documents Ted Kennedy's life, but for some reason skipped the time when he drove drunk off of a bridge and left Mary Jo Kopechne (who was on his side and worked for him as a young campaign assistant!) to die in his car, better known as the Chappaquiddick incident. The video also skips the part when Kennedy failed to tell police of the incident until nine hours after it happened and he had a chance to sober up..</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346861200344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:06:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346861516729-44</Id><Topic><Title>We “belong” to the government?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346856864058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:54:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Who do you think runs the country?????? On the afternoon of 1/20/13 it will be Mitt and the Republicans. I bet you won't say " It is our country and we do have a government. You can't just pick those issues you like. The United States is our country and our country is run by our elected officials and that constitutes the government." then. and "If you you don't like it, then get the "blank" out."</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1346861516729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:11:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346861579688-45</Id><Topic><Title>Two ladies</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1346855146640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:25:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? I thought the Donald will fire Ann to keep the ratings up.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1346861579688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346861615510-46</Id><Topic><Title>What Was In The OTHER Chair as Eastwood Spoke?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346861328445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:08:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What Was In The OTHER Chair as Eastwood Spoke?" Why it was the ghost of Obama future.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1346861615510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:13:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346861904925-47</Id><Topic><Title>From Where Does Obama Get His Central Planning Ideas?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346859399257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:36:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a fact. Read the article.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346861904925</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:18:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346862162884-48</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans seek God to influence Election..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346860442549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:54:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The same question might be asked about the declaration of Independence in which it says, "that all men are created equal, that they are endowed by their Creator with certain unalienable Rights, that among these are Life, Liberty and the pursuit of Happiness." If the Democrats feel that God does play a role either in their own lives or in recognition of a Higher Moral Authority to the function and purpose of government, by even a simple perfunctory acknowledgement, then what else do they think can go?</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1346862162884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346862361885-49</Id><Title>Dem circus comes to town peddling their Kool-Aid</Title><Msg>Marxist ideology is OK with them as long as it's wrapped up in helping the mediocre class by plundering the producers and high achievers. Remember class warfare and wealth distribution is straight from the Communist manifesto and is the foundation of what Karl Marx preached.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346862361885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346863238934-50</Id><Title>Navy f18 contract</Title><Msg>The Boeing Co. in Jacksonville has won a $27.8 million modification to a previously awarded contract for work on Boeing F/A-18 Hornet fighter jets. The modification provides for supplies and services for in-warranty and out-of-warranty depot-level modification installations and in-service repairs incident to modification kit installs including associated material and services. Work will be performed in Jacksonville, and is expected to be completed in September 2013.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346863238934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:40:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346863866914-51</Id><Topic><Title>Dem circus comes to town peddling their Kool-Aid</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346862361885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:26:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow,,,,compassionate conservatism at it;s finest</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346863866914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:51:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346865019966-52</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans seek God to influence Election..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346860442549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:54:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And then from a purely "moral" point of view, one might ask, how would it even be possible for the Democrats to both declare the right of unlimited abortion while in the same breath, or Party Platform, invoke the God of Heaven who hates abortion? While the Democrats pander to immorality, they are certainly not hypocritical about it. Bold and haughty are more apropos.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1346865019966</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:10:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346866004247-53</Id><Topic><Title>Navy f18 contract</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346863238934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:40:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, that sure is great that we're upgrading the F-18 to defend our country. Just think, if it weren't for our glorious military, Canada would invade us, and Mexico would . . . . oh never mind.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1346866004247</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:26:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346866110360-54</Id><Topic><Title>DNC Glorifies Senator Who Left a Woman to Drown in His Car</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346861200344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:06:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the darling of the democrats, champions of women's rights -- Slick Willie Clinton -- had a credible charge of rape lodged against him (Juanita Broderick), sexual harassment (Kathleen Willey), and settled a similar claim that led to his impeachment (Paula Jones) ya can't make this stuff up, what pathetic hypocrites</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1346866110360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346866114796-55</Id><Topic><Title>Ichelle Obama... Pathetic!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346860917272</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:01:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was pretty revealing when she said the Presidency doesn't change the man, it only reveals him. So I guess Barack was a thug and a murderer all along.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1346866114796</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346867877726-56</Id><Topic><Title>Obama acceptance speech moved indoors</Title><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1346858114552</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:15:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you lived in the east you would understand that the remnants of the Hurricane that hit New Orleans has reached the east coast. Obama's speech was moved indoors because of the rain.</Msg><Username>gpd8252</Username><Timestamp>1346867877726</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:57:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346868576381-57</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans seek God to influence Election..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346860442549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:54:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>save it bulky - of God and morality - Repubs speak of things they know not...!!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346868576381</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:09:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346868606178-58</Id><Topic><Title>Obama acceptance speech moved indoors</Title><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1346858114552</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:15:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean the same rain that caused the Republicans to cancel the first day of their convention -- the one that a bunch of democrats said "was sent by God" -- is that what you mean</Msg><Username>nostra.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346868606178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:10:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346868690419-59</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama is Awesome!!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346857152778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:59:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a class Act!!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346868690419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:11:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346868751160-60</Id><Topic><Title>I love Obama</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346721127841</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 21:12:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346868751160</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346868801379-61</Id><Topic><Title>DNC Glorifies Senator Who Left a Woman to Drown in His Car</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346861200344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:06:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's not surprising since they also praised their senator who also happened to be a sheet wearing, cross burning, Grand Wizard of the KKK.</Msg><Username>nostra.dumbass</Username><Timestamp>1346868801379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346868951443-62</Id><Topic><Title>jal has offering</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1346860306319</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is that interesting Boeing has a new suggested number of airplanes to build, mean time my Bont is up 23 per cent today and 225 per cent plus for this year and the apple-stock it continues to beat boering for 15 years straight seems like airplanes made and delivered late and overbudget don;t count much except if you want to losse 3 percent this year while appleshareholders make 66 percent and bont shareholders make 225 percent and only 23 percent today so lets hear it for those making airplanes and buying boreing stock the sound is silence , guess that is what borein is worth this stock will be delisted in 5 years and taken private. the McDonalds clown price took over fromt he conominium and price phillip left to do nothing more as he did enough.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1346868951443</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:15:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346870486602-63</Id><Title>Democrats worry over fundraising as Romney adds to campaign war chest</Title><Msg>Senior Democratic sources say that in closed-door meetings with campaign donors here at the convention, top Obama campaign officials like campaign manager Jim Messina are expressing increasing alarm over the fact that Republican Mitt Romney raised $100 million in the month of August alone, further expanding his cash edge. The Democratic sources say that the Obama team is privately saying they believe the final days of the presidential race are now shaping up as a dramatic battle between money and demographics, with President Obama's advisers fearful that Romney will use his war chest to unleash a bombardment of television ads and ground game to turn out more white, working-class voters. Bye, bye Barack.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1346870486602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346870641800-64</Id><Topic><Title>DNC Glorifies Senator Who Left a Woman to Drown in His Car</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346861200344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:06:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the reminder of how hypocritical the democrats are when it is convenient or necessary to make a point hoping their own past has been forgotten, really! As hypocrites, democrats can't get any bigger.</Msg><Username>old_crudmudgean</Username><Timestamp>1346870641800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:44:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346870981415-65</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama is Awesome!!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346857152778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:59:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"She hit the ball out of the park." Yes, she did. What you apparently did not see or chose to not see, however, was that it was a FOUL BALL!</Msg><Username>yb4itohitsfree</Username><Timestamp>1346870981415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346871012442-66</Id><Title>Graph</Title><Msg>Why does the chart on Yahoo start around 1:30?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1346871012442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:50:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346871929765-67</Id><Title>CNN Fact Check: About those 4.5 million jobs ...</Title><Msg>It's a big-sounding number, given the still-sputtering job market. So we're giving it a close eyeballing. The facts: The number Castro cites is an accurate description of the growth of private-sector jobs since January 2010, when the long, steep slide in employment finally hit bottom. But while a total of 4.5 million jobs sounds great, it's not the whole picture. Nonfarm private payrolls hit a post-recession low of 106.8 million that month, according to the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics. The figure currently stands at 111.3 million as of July. While that is indeed a gain of 4.5 million, it's only a net gain of 300,000 over the course of the Obama administration to date. The private jobs figure stood at 111 million in January 2009, the month Obama took office.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1346871929765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:05:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346871994506-68</Id><Topic><Title>CNN Fact Check: About those 4.5 million jobs ...</Title><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1346871929765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:05:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Meanwhile, the jobs that have come back aren't the same ones that were lost. According to a study released last week by the liberal-leaning National Employment Law Project, low-wage fields such as retail sales and food service are adding jobs nearly three times as fast as higher-paid occupations</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1346871994506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346873284374-69</Id><Topic><Title>CNN Fact Check: About those 4.5 million jobs ...</Title><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1346871929765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:05:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Join the Obama recovery -- and start your job flipping burgers at McDonalds! LOL! If our college grads keep doing that they'll still be living at their parents homes looking up at those faded Obama posters -- wondering -- "why did I vote for that #$%$"</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1346873284374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:28:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346873587630-70</Id><Title>Obama’s Popularity Dips Underwater</Title><Msg>"Barack Obama approaches his nomination for a second term with the lowest pre-convention personal popularity of an incumbent president in ABC News/Washington Post polls since the 1980s. He’s also at his lowest of the year among registered voters, with trouble among women. Just 47 percent of registered voters in the latest ABC News/Washington Post poll see Obama favorably overall, down 7 percentage points from his recent peak in April, while 49 percent rate him unfavorably. He’s numerically underwater in this group for the first time since February. The decline has occurred entirely among women registered voters – from 57-39 percent favorable-unfavorable in April to a numerically negative 46-50 percent now. That’s Obama’s lowest score among women voters – a focus of recent political positioning – in ABC/Post polls since he took office. " Looks like women are finally seeing O'Bummer for what he is: a fraud.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1346873587630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346873994112-71</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 332, Romney 206</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346871049824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>126 toss up according to real clear politics but go ahead and believe your delusions -- it'll be fun to hear you rant on 11/7/12.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1346873994112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:39:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346874093294-72</Id><Topic><Title>CNN Fact Check: About those 4.5 million jobs ...</Title><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1346871929765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:05:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Search this: "2011-06-03: Today 99.534 Million Americans Unemployed Uncounted Unreported" Overall workforce numbers are shrinking and our population is growing. This is a formula for disaster economically. Blame both parties. It's been happening since the end of WWII.</Msg><Username>old_crudmudgean</Username><Timestamp>1346874093294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346875180230-73</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Still Leading from Behind</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1346860869130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:01:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rasmussen is the "house" pollster for that bastion of accuracy and impartiality Fox News. Nothing to see here ... Everybody should just move on.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1346875180230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:59:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346875225609-74</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama is Awesome!!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346857152778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:59:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMG!!! seek help or better glasses.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1346875225609</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:00:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346878493983-75</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 332, Romney 206</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346871049824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to website's creator, Andrew S. Tanenbaum, an ex-patriot living in the Netherlands with his Dutch wife, his polls' "analysis" uses "only polls from neutral pollsters, who are generally hired by the media". While the living abroad and being married to a foreigner is no particular issue, it is also not mainstream American, and instead elitist. And he is apparently quite liberal. The fact that he depends almost exclusively upon the polls of the "media" is telling, as the media is clearly, in the majority, liberal and biased. If I integrate ten times the same answer of the polls of one bias and only one of the other bias, what does the math tell you? It is garbage.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1346878493983</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:54:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346879001102-76</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama is Awesome!!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346857152778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:59:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She was sincerely Incredible!</Msg><Username>stock.screener</Username><Timestamp>1346879001102</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346879343227-77</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 332, Romney 206</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346871049824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EVERYTHING.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1346879343227</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346879518828-78</Id><Topic><Title>About Michelle's Speech...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346877848936</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:44:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post. And she delivered many of the things Ann Romney didn’t in her own testament to her husband—notably, some genuine anecdotes about the man in her life.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1346879518828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346879675516-79</Id><Topic><Title>About Michelle's Speech...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346877848936</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:44:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hate this new board! I had added to that post, and it didn't appear: "Ann Rmoney and her husband Willtard are genuine plastic mannequins by comparison."</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1346879675516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:14:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346879891145-80</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama Blew The Doors Off Of The Democratic National Convention With This Speech</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346869703052</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:28:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More like blew the doors off their hinges as she squeezed her wide load through them. Fekin freaks each and everyone of you poor lost Dims are!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1346879891145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:18:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346880283372-81</Id><Title>Obama and Dems Chasing Romney...</Title><Msg>Capital of Israel and God Out of Dem Platform... Now both back In after Romney criticism... Romney has Obama reacting to him... Desperation is setting in!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346880283372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346880630032-82</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Dems Chasing Romney...</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346880283372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:24:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wishful thinking, eh?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1346880630032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:30:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346880662276-83</Id><Title>Obama Deploys 3 Aircraft Carrier Battle Groups off the Cost of IRAN</Title><Msg>October "IS" Looking like IT Just might be the Month "You Know WHO" decides that "Sanctions" Ain't Working!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Obama Deploys 3 Aircraft Carrier Battle Groups off the Cost of IRAN US Aircraft Carrier Stennis Is Now En Route To Join Enterprise And Eisenhower Off Iranian Coast READ All About IT Where "The REAL News Matters"!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1346880662276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:31:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346880674948-84</Id><Title>Obama not Popular Enough to Fill Stadium...</Title><Msg>... moves to an indoor venue with 50,000 less seats as not to embarrass the President Dems could Not find enough fools to pay and/or buss into the stadium! They know their gig is up. Pathetic... Heavy Drinking in Chicago!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346880674948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346880699449-85</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 332, Romney 206</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346871049824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sweet!!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346880699449</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346880704338-86</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama Blew The Doors Off Of The Democratic National Convention With This Speech</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346869703052</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:28:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a vulgar twit and low class troll and NOTHING MORE.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1346880704338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:31:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346880804487-87</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Dems Chasing Romney...</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346880283372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:24:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read and weep, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346880804487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:33:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346881180066-88</Id><Title>Dems Out of Control Ignore their Own Rules!</Title><Msg>Dem. Party Heads Ram Through Pro-Israel and 'God' Language, Steam Roll Opposition 5:19 PM, SEP 5, 2012 • BY DANIEL HALPERSingle PagePrintLarger TextSmaller TextAlerts Democratic party heads rammed through the revised platform, which includes updated pro-Israel language and the mention of God, against the clear wishes of those voting at the convention in Charlotte. Here's video of the chaos: The vote to adopt the new platform requires two-thirds. It's pretty clear that even after asking for multiple votes, two-thirds of the vote was not received. The revised platform was adopted anyway.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346881180066</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:39:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346881254309-89</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 332, Romney 206</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346871049824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, I am not disagreeing with you about the potential or likely bias of polls - liberal or conservative. I am simply saying that the website author's "trust" of media based polls is risky. With that already lack of firm foundation, he builds upon that by additional multiplicative error as the predominance of the media, thus number of polls, is by definition biased on the liberal side. - BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1346881254309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346881268400-90</Id><Topic><Title>Obama not Popular Enough to Fill Stadium...</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346880674948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep... keep dreaming little "man" They couldn't find enough Fools to attend!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346881268400</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:41:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346881290566-91</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Deploys 3 Aircraft Carrier Battle Groups off the Cost of IRAN</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1346880662276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:31:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ANOTHER!!! PEEDROOOOLLLLL!!! AAAAAIRRRRR!!! RAAAAAAIDDDD!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1346881290566</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346881575344-92</Id><Title>God and Jerusalem Boo'ed at Dem Convention</Title><Msg>The Socialist Dems are already out of Control ! So Much for Democracy within the Dem Party. Jerusalem And God Get Booed At Dem Convention Delegates and members of the Democratic party booed after former Gov. Ted Strickland (D-OH) discussed God and moved to recognize Jerusalem as the capital of Israel. Convention chairman Antonio Villaraigosa, mayor of Los Angeles, had to ask for the Yea and Nay vote several times before declaring the motion passed. C-SPAN cameras captured the dissatisfaction among members after the motion passed.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346881575344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:46:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346881903151-93</Id><Title>So Much for Hope and Change... Awaiting a Prison Term?</Title><Msg>Feds Seek Prison Time For Obama "Hope" Artist Prosecutors want Shepard Fairey sentencing to serve as a warning SEPTEMBER 5--Federal prosecutors want Shepard Fairey, the artist who created the Barack Obama “Hope” poster, to serve time in prison following his misdemeanor conviction for destroying and fabricating documents in connection with a civil lawsuit over the iconic campaign image. In advance of Friday’s scheduled sentencing of Fairey in U.S. District Court in Manhattan, the Department of Justice has filed a memorandum arguing that a prison term for the 42-year-old artist would be “appropriate.” However, prosecutors did not specify how long Fairey should be incarcerated (though, statutorily, his punishment would not exceed six months). Additionally, government lawyers have contended that Judge Frank Maas could fine Fairey up to $3.2 million. “A sentence without any term of imprisonment sends a terrible message to those who might commit the same sort of criminal conduct,” wrote prosecutor Daniel Levy in a September 2 memo. “Encouraging parties to game the civil litigation system…creates terrible incentives and subverts the truth-finding function of civil litigation</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346881903151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346882115425-94</Id><Title>Comical... Raul Emanuel, Obama "Makes the Sun Come Out" Pathetic!</Title><Msg>While introducing President Obama in June, Mayor Rahm Emanuel joked to Chicago Democrats that when Obama is in town the weather improves. “The president arrives, the rain stops, the sun comes out.” Emanuel said. “Coincidence? I think not.” Emanuel added that last time the president visited, the weather “was 71 degrees and beautiful.” “He arrives, the sun comes out, and things are beautiful again.” Emanuel concluded.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346882115425</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:55:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346882165256-95</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Deploys 3 Aircraft Carrier Battle Groups off the Cost of IRAN</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1346880662276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:31:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Laugh IT UP ALL You Want............But THIS "IS" Going to Happen and Much Sooner the YOU LIBERALS KNOW!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ""Massed US, UK, French navies for drill simulating breach of blocked Hormuz"" "U.S. sends aircraft carrier back to Gulf to face Iran, Syria" ""Iran must steer clear of US interests in Gulf"" Washington reportedly sends Tehran indirect message saying it will not back "You Know WHO's" strike on nuclear facilities as long as Iran refrains from attacking American facilities in Persian Gulf Read ALL About IT Where "The REAL News Matters"!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1346882165256</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:56:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346882436512-96</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama Blew The Doors Off Of The Democratic National Convention With This Speech</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346869703052</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:28:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's vulgar about my post little Dim one? Surely you didn't construe "Fekin" to be vulgar did you? No response needed as I know you are up to your eyeballs campaigning for "at will" taxpayer sponsored killing of babies!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1346882436512</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346882682939-97</Id><Title>Divided and Confused Democrats</Title><Msg>Shameful and Pathetic response by Leading Dem Senator... The Dems Do Not know if they are Afoot or HorseBack! Dems are in Total Disarray. Romney has Obama on the Defensive! Schumer Doesn't Know Obama's Position on Jerusalem 8:23 AM, SEP 5, 2012 • BY DANIEL HALPER Senator Chuck Schumer does not know President Obama's position on Jerusalem: Schumer is asked about Obama's position after Democrats removed this pro-Israel language from this year's party platform: "Jerusalem is and will remain the capital of Israel. The parties have agreed that Jerusalem is a matter for final status negotiations. It should remain an undivided city accessible to people of all faiths." Schumer is not able to say why that language has been removed, and where President Obama stands on the issue. CNN reported yesterday that the language was removed so that the platform would be aligned with the Obama administration's positions. The Democratic National Committee is "simply following what the Obama administration's policy is," CNN reported. "That the White House said several months ago that the status of Jerusalem is an issue that should be resolved in the final status negotiations between the Israelis and the Palestinians and that is why that is not in the platform as it was in 2008."</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346882682939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:04:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346882795162-98</Id><Title>BA expending S.C. facility</Title><Msg>Boeing is expanding its South Carolina aircraft manufacturing complex in an effort to operate more efficiently as the company pushes toward its goal of producing 10 model 787 Dreamliners by the end of 2013. The biggest project is a 63 percent expansion of the building where aft fuselage bodies are fabricated by adding 276,000 square feet of new capacity, Eslinger said. The second project will be a 54 percent expansion of the paint facility on the site by adding 37,000 square feet. Both projects start this month and will take about two years. Eslinger declined to share the cost. In addition to enlarging the buildings, Boeing also is bringing in new assembly equipment. It is replacing five mandrels, or tooling, that workers wind carbon fiber around to make an aft fuselage section, and is adding a sixth. On another note, three 737's were delivered today and there were five 737 and one 767 (DHL) test flights.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346882795162</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:06:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346882841666-99</Id><Title>the Further Adventures of a Lying Liar</Title><Msg>Here's the first exception. Ryan has told his hometown paper that he has climbed "about 40" of the famous "Fourteeners" in Colorado -- the 54 peaks more than 14,000 feet high. In fairness, he made this claim a few years ago, before he knew he would be under the scrutiny he is now. Still: this claim makes me even more suspicious than his marathon answer did. I know nothing about mountain climbing, so give my views appropriate weight. But to see what people who do have experience think, you might check out the current comments at the climbers' site SuperTopo. One explains the reason for his skepticism: The 54 peaks are scattered throughout remote parts of Colorado and you have to visit out-of-the-way little towns and valleys to tick the list, towns and valleys that you would never visit otherwise.... To have climbed forty and not be a resident means that you would have had to devote entire summers to climbing fourteeners, in essence becoming a "lifestyle" hiker/scrambler. I doubt Ryan had the time or dedication to fourteeners to take the required time out from his political career. Even if you did four a summer, that would be ten summers devoted to traveling to Colorado for the purpose of high altitude hiking. Even if you live here and can drive to the trail heads, forty is a huge commitment of time and energy.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1346882841666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346882975811-100</Id><Topic><Title>the Further Adventures of a Lying Liar</Title><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1346882841666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:07:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As I understand it, mountain-climbing is like marathon-running in this way: people pay enough attention to their achievements that they remember the details, and they know that they are written down somewhere. Lists of who has climbed which "Fourteener," like lists of finishers and their times for marathons, are part of the permanent record of each pursuit. As with his marathon time, this is so specifically impressive a claim that it should be very easy to back up and dismiss doubts about. If it is true.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1346882975811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:09:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346883138775-101</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama Blew The Doors Off Of The Democratic National Convention With This Speech</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346869703052</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:28:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did she say anything that was true? She said we can trust Obama. LMAO. She said they both grew up poor. Obama's stepfather was a leading general in the Indonesian government dictatorship, I'm sure he had servants. Now that's sure poor. LMAO. Then he went to high school in Hawaii. Pretty rough life allright. The Obamas just make stuff up and sell it to the fools.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1346883138775</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346883202128-102</Id><Topic><Title>Democraps are ashamed</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1346882975774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:09:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney is driving the Dem Convention... Making the Dems Change their Platform in mid Convention! Desperation is setting in around the Obama Campaign.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346883202128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346883425333-103</Id><Topic><Title>Divided and Confused Democrats</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346882682939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:04:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Dems are in Full Damage Control! God, No, err, God, Yes. Jesruslam, No, err, Jesruslam, Yes. Idiots!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346883425333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:17:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346884003507-104</Id><Title>Obama and Dems Flip Flopping on Party Platform</Title><Msg>Romney is driving the Dem Convention... Dems are Ashamed... Jerusalem As Capital Back In Platform President Obama Hands Republicans A Gift; Jewish, Palestinian Leaders Fume September 5, 2012 6:07 PM CHARLOTTE, N.C. (CBSNewYork) — A big flip flop by the Democratic Party has replaced what was perceived as a big snub to Israel. It was a stunning development. The party had dropped the assertion that Jerusalem was the capital of the Jewish state, but late word Wednesday evening was the Democrats had a change of heart. The vote went down just before 6 p.m. and it was quite contentious on the floor. It needed a two-thirds majority and it took three votes to get it, CBS 2’s Marcia Kramer reported. The Democrats caved, changing the platform language to reflect that they now regard Jerusalem as the capital of Israel. It came about as a result of intense political pressure,” CBS 2’s Kramer reported. “I think it is a mistake and I’m not happy about it,” Rep. Jerrold Nadler said. “I disagree with that platform,” Sen. Kirsten Gillibrand added. “We try to avoid this type of conflict by providing ammunition to the other side to exploit,” Rep. Nydia Velasquez said. President Barack Obama handed the Republicans a new avenue of attack on a silver platter when he supported a Democratic Party platform change that does not state that Jerusalem is the capital of Israel. It was a dramatic change from what the president said when he was running for office the first time. “Jerusalem will remain the capital of Israel and it must remain undivided,” he said back in 2008. The omission in a platform that does support strong security assurances for Israel left Democratic officials saying it was a mistake, but “I would very much have preferred that plank to be in there,” New York City Council Speaker Christine Quinn said. “That said, I think President Obama’s record on Israel is strong. It is a record of commitment to Israel.” Jewish leaders reacted swiftly. “The principle that Jerusalem should remain united and is the capital of Israel has been enshrined for a long time,” said Malcolm Hoenlein, the Executive Vice Chairman of the Conference of Presidents of Major American Jewish Organizations. “It concerns me. It concerns every Jew,” said Chanina Sperlin, Executive VP of the Crown Heights Council. “It’s a big mistake leaving that out of the party platform.” Many Palestinians were also annoyed. They want Jerusalem as the capital of a Palestinian state. “The debate surrounding this, it’s not so much about the peace process and a peaceful solution in the Middle East, but it’s more about scoring points, whether you’re a Democrat or Republican, and that’s unfortunate,” said Muneer Awad from the Council on American-Islamic Relations. The omission gave Republicans an opening. Presidential nominee Mitt Romney called it “shameful,” because Jewish voters in battleground states like Florida, Ohio, Pennsylvania and Nevada could be critical. “It’s mystifying that the Democrats would do this at a time when they are trying to repair relations with the Jewish community,” Hofstra University professor Larry Levy said. “Jewish voters have been concerned over whether the Obama administration has been playing fair in the Middle East The flip flop was explained away by campaign officials saying the change was done to “reflect the president’s personal point of view.”</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346884003507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346884683097-105</Id><Topic><Title>the Further Adventures of a Lying Liar</Title><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1346882841666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:07:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And, Joe Biden Does Not know what State nor what Decade he is in while Campaigning. Biden is a Buffoon and Obama knows it. Obama wanted to Replace Biden with Hillary, but she Gave Obama the Middle Finger!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346884683097</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:38:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346885171403-106</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Dems Flip Flopping on Party Platform</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346884003507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:26:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just donated to the Jewish state of Israel.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1346885171403</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346887254123-107</Id><Title>President Clinton Proved the Right Was Wrong</Title><Msg>Baggers believe more in republiwhoppers than in facts. For example, when President Clinton proposed raising taxes on the rich to reduce the projected deficits he was facing when he took office, repub politicians and their highly paid propaganda apparatus assured everybody that doing so would tank the economy and lead to massive job losses. His plan was passed without a single GOP vote. As it turns out he was right and they were 100% wrong because we all know now that his economy was great and that unemployment quickly dropped from 7.3% to 5.5% just in his first two years and continued to drop until it reached about 4%. and led to a federal balanced budget with a budget surplus. Now it is 19 years later and even though the right wing ignorati was proven wrong, they are still spreading their zombie republiwhoppers about what would happen if we went back to those tax rates.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346887254123</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:20:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346887612862-108</Id><Topic><Title>the Further Adventures of a Lying Liar</Title><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1346882841666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:07:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He fabricates a tad is all.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346887612862</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:26:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346887688253-109</Id><Topic><Title>the Further Adventures of a Lying Liar</Title><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1346882841666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:07:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He gets caught up in the moment. Probably a pretty blond he was trying to impress some where around.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346887688253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346888524867-110</Id><Topic><Title>President Clinton Proved the Right Was Wrong</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346887254123</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:20:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 1993, Clint0n's first year in office. the median household income was $46,419. When he left office and Bush took over it was $53,164. The Bush Repubs implemented their economic plan and when Bush left the median household income was $50,939. But the rich were hugely richer.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346888524867</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346888793862-111</Id><Topic><Title>President Clinton Proved the Right Was Wrong</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346887254123</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:20:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dokeycom, I'd recommend you watch President Clinton tonight but I know that exposure to the truth would be like daylight to a vampire. You would curl up like a burning bagger in the morning.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346888793862</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:46:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346889257869-112</Id><Topic><Title>the Further Adventures of a Lying Liar</Title><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1346882841666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:07:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All of these damning revelations are nothing more than a slow death by a thousand political cuts.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346889257869</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:54:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346891814386-113</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans seek God to influence Election..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346860442549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:54:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spoke too soon AGAIN sticky apparently your party thinks so ... ROTFLMAO, were you born dumb or are you a self made man ? "CHARLOTTE, N.C.—Facing unhappy pro-Israel groups amid a Republican-led outcry, Democrats gathered Wednesday at their presidential nominating convention made 11th-hour changes to the party platform to reinstate a reference to God and a declaration that "undivided" Jerusalem is Israel's capital."</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1346891814386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:36:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346892017682-114</Id><Topic><Title>Obama not Popular Enough to Fill Stadium...</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346880674948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The other consideration is Bank of America paid a lot of money for the name on the outdoor stadium, BOA received mondo taxpayer bucks in the bailout and now BOA is laying off and offloading many of their employees. So obama would be standing in a stadium, paid for by a bank that he bailed out with tax money, which is now off loading employees. In some ways this is his legacy.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1346892017682</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:40:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346892543432-115</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans seek God to influence Election..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346860442549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:54:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does welfare and food stamp script have the word In God We Trust printed on it? It could be that most libs having received only gov handouts through out their deadbeat lives don't know that it is on US currency.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1346892543432</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346893526989-116</Id><Title>Democratic Convention in Total Disaray... Flip Flopping on Basics</Title><Msg>Delegates Yelling and Snearing at Each Other over God and The Capital of Israel In or Out of the Party Platform They are Starting to Eat Each Other! Pathetic.... The Dems are Scared, very Scared about November.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346893526989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346893773956-117</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans seek God to influence Election..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346860442549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:54:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are behind the Times as the Democrats have Flip Flopped and Put God back in their Platform Romney is Running the Dem Convention in more ways than you Little Libs can Understand.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346893773956</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:09:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346894199885-118</Id><Title>Democrats Are Prepared to Strike</Title><Msg>Should President Obama lose in the November elections the Democrat party is prepared to go on strike and shut down the country. Since all the unions are well represented in the party, they have strike captains ready to organize the picket lines in every state. Nancy Pelosi and Debbie Wasserman Schultz will be in charge to see that President Obama remains in the White House as a non-negotiable demand.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1346894199885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:16:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346894604474-119</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Are Prepared to Strike</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1346894199885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:16:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fortunately, the Socialist Dems are too Fractured to Organize anything Significant. Too many Flip Floppers. Just look at their Convention... Totally Disfunctional.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346894604474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346895154061-120</Id><Topic><Title>BA expending S.C. facility</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346882795162</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they also delivered a 777.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346895154061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:32:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346896417698-121</Id><Title>Mitt Romney Totally Controlling the Presidential Campaign Narrative</Title><Msg>Obama is on the Defensive and is having to Respond to Romney... The Flip Flop over God and the location of the Israeli Capital is only a few examples. Who is Running Obama's Campaign? Mitt is making Obama look Foolish and Sad! Pathetic!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346896417698</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346897395253-122</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney Totally Controlling the Presidential Campaign Narrative</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346896417698</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:53:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's no bummer like O'bummer . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1346897395253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:09:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346897730678-123</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's hypocracy seeking the Grahams twice and doing the opposite. Why go there</Title><Username>tommaxgreg</Username><Timestamp>1346897393911</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:09:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Moslems in Africa are slaughtering everyone who won't bow down to them, and they would do it here too, if they could . Why lie, they are a menace to modern civilization, but just another voting block for dims to kiss up to . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1346897730678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346898093799-124</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Are Prepared to Strike</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1346894199885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:16:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ooooo, they'll boycott the welfare office, and stop giving good service at the DMV . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1346898093799</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:21:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346898094403-125</Id><Topic><Title>BA expending S.C. facility</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346882795162</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SC will soon be, if not already, more Productive and Assemble Higher Quality Aircraft than Seatle. Unions have decayed Seatle productivity... Headquarters now on Chicago and Production in South Carolina!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346898094403</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:21:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346898631803-126</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Are Prepared to Strike</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1346894199885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:16:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: Employee Speaks Out 2-Aug-12 08:15 pm " Maybe Liberals should start their own business instead of criticizing someone else’s, they could call it dik-fil-A, and you could be the waitress . Y.T. Jumbojetski"</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1346898631803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:30:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346898701058-127</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney Totally Controlling the Presidential Campaign Narrative</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346896417698</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:53:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: What caused Out sourcing July 27, 2012 "Liberals caused "outsourcing" when they bought their first jap car . Y.T. Jumbojetski"</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1346898701058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:31:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346898771895-128</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Are Prepared to Strike</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1346894199885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:16:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: 4th of July 3-Jul-12 07:33 pm "If it weren't for A.I.D.S., most Liberals would not need condoms . Y.T. Jumbojetski"</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1346898771895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:32:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346899394038-129</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney Totally Controlling the Presidential Campaign Narrative</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346896417698</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:53:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is foolish and sad. He has nothing to say except to shout nonsence.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1346899394038</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:43:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346903462524-130</Id><Title>Clinton speech @ the DNC - record book home run</Title><Msg>Laid out the case for Obama/Biden and against the republicon Rmoney/lyin' Ryan Printing the speech now!!! It will be one that all of our grandkids will be repeating in the future!!!</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1346903462524</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>