<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-04"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349323423560-1</Id><Title>Cutting sesame street is the key to a balaniced budget</Title><Msg>don't say mitt did not give specifics</Msg><Username>ca.andse</Username><Timestamp>1349323423560</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 00:03:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349324757557-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Must Now Be Considered For Inclusion On Mount Rushmore</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney55</Username><Timestamp>1349224719395</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 20:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey look , sir paul's got jokes! just like his president is!</Msg><Username>duffymagoo</Username><Timestamp>1349324757557</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 00:25:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349325579674-3</Id><Title>Obama is clueless on the economy</Title><Msg>and just about everything.</Msg><Username>weightbayou</Username><Timestamp>1349325579674</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 00:39:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349327333032-4</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1349324103921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 00:15:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eventually one reruns the debate to examine what each candidate said......no matter how it's explained I don't see how you cut the income taxes 20% from where the "Bush" cuts already are AND maintain current levels of defense spending and seriously say that the deficit will be seriously addressed. To do that - I suspect not only full employment (millions of people working &amp; Paying taxes) but probably will require people already retired to go back to work full time so they can be pumping income tax revenues into the government coffers. Everybody will be employed even if you're 78 years old and half blind.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1349327333032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 01:08:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349330423014-5</Id><Topic><Title>The foul message is more junk about SPEEA and non union threats</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1349291404010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:10:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. skunked again man aka pepe le pew, , you said" that I "know little or nothing about the Dreamliner" but stop short of listing anything that I do not know about the dreamliner or anything that you might know. Since I did say that the 777 was the last airplane that SPEEA designed and it was built on time and on budget and works great, then I pointed out that in spite of you wanting me to "shut up" that the 787 was not designed by SPEEA and is a complete failure to be built on time and on Budget and is still 4 years late having problems all the time like the last week PR disaster with the customers first flight to Seattle being grounded because the 787 new plane broke down. So let’s see what I know and this is actually available for outsiders to Boeing like yourself, since you do not know squat and are not qualified to work for the IAM or SPEEA as you do not meet the minimum credentials and cannot pass the various tests and pre employment interviews,, here it is in the Seattle times newspaper about who engineered the 787, and like I told you it was not SPEEA and I guess you are just too ignorant to actually learn this fact for yourself. So Mr Skunked again man, (real good name for yourself too) A little special education for you then "Boeing's major partners did the design of the Dreamliner sections that they build. All this is entirely new. Previous Boeing jets had pieces made around the globe, but they were designed solely by Boeing and assembled wholly in its Puget Sound-area factories. Yet with all the global resources thrown at it, the vision of a quick, snap-together jet hasn't materialized, it is 4 years late so far.. Boeing belatedly pulled back in-house some of the engineering design work when its partners proved incapable. And the partners failed to finish their pieces of the first planes on time. Hundreds of Boeing SPEEA staff flew out on months-long assignments to help overcome manufacturing paralysis caused by inexperienced Engineers, assembly mechanics, parts shortages and work done out of sequence." So Pepe', sure in order for you to be a successful liar I do need to “shut up” , but so sorry, that is not going to happen Mr Skunked again man – did I mention you have a real great and appropriate name, exlax might work too</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1349330423014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 02:00:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349331012417-6</Id><Topic><Title>Etch-a-sketch Rmoney - the myth candi-date</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349320471487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:14:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go ahead and blame Bush, it will make you feel better. I'll help - Obama looked completely clueless because George Bush...bla bla bla</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1349331012417</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 02:10:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349341457535-7</Id><Title>Barry looked very funny and very lost</Title><Msg>without his teleprompter.................Romney is way smarter than Barry, proved it last night BIG TIME!!!! Libtards are all very nervous and in FULL PANIC MODE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1349341457535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 05:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349341589115-8</Id><Title>Liberals need a teleprompter</Title><Msg>otherwise they sound like stuttering and shuffling idiots.......</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1349341589115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 05:06:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349344565468-9</Id><Title>Romney Crushed Obama Last Night!</Title><Msg>Obama Looked Lost and Helplessness without his Pacifier... But what Else would One Expect from an Affirmation Action President, eh? Obama's Campaign Definitely Smells Smoldering Peanuts!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349344565468</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 05:56:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349345985828-10</Id><Title>CNN Poll Romney 67% Obamer 25%</Title><Msg>The CNN Poll shows that 25% of Americans are watching presidential debates while on hallucinogens.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349345985828</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 06:19:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349346881279-11</Id><Title>"Crouching Tiger Hidden Drag Queen"</Title><Msg>This would be the movie title of the debate. Barry's buddies at "Man Country" are ROTF, literally. :-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349346881279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 06:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349348944778-12</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Crushed Obama Last Night!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349344565468</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 05:56:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>imaccomunist - Touting a Romney victory in last night's debate ... Shocking. If Romney had unzipped his pants, whipped out his dong, whirled it around for everybody to see and asked Lehrer to kiss it you'd still be claiming that. Sadly for you, Obama still enjoys significant leads in the polls of almost all of the swing states. : ) Too bad. So sad. Question - Come November 7th, if Obama has won the election will you acknowledge that he's president for another four years? Bet not. You'll no doubt be taking hits off that crack pipe of yours and denying that it's so.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1349348944778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 07:09:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349349136422-13</Id><Topic><Title>Libturd are sore, not on the board tonight Obama is out of the race, he just hung his head now cnn, msnbc</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349319630536</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Out of the race? Apparently you haven't seen the latest polls. BWAA! HA! HA! HA! HA! HA! HA!</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1349349136422</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 07:12:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349350672241-14</Id><Title>hustling businessman</Title><Msg>only saw bits..things are not always as they seem....governor is a pathological liar...he was cute...there will be waves of energy reminding the public he is a corporate vulture ......a slick liar......out for his class, the very rich...wait for the response</Msg><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1349350672241</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 07:37:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349350753163-15</Id><Title>MSNBC Says Romney Crushed Obama!</Title><Msg>Chris Mathews says "What is He Doing?" Obama is Lost and Confused without his Pacifier and Handlers. America saw Intellect in Romney Tonight and an Affirmation Queen in Obama... no Wonder he Won't Release his College Grades. Un-Employment over 8% for Almost Four Years is Killing Obama as Americans are Worse Off Under Obama than Before!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349350753163</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 07:39:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349351031467-16</Id><Title>Romney Will Win Says 100% Historically Accurate Model</Title><Msg>DENVER—Two University of Colorado professors have devised a model to predict who will win the presidential election under current economic circumstances. The victor, they say, will be Republican Mitt Romney. The model uses economic indicators from all 50 states to predict the race's outcome. The forecast calls for Romney to win 320 electoral votes out of 538. It says Romney will also win virtually every state currently considered a swing state, including Colorado. The professors who created the model, Ken Bickers from CU-Boulder and Michael Berry from CU-Denver, say it correctly forecast every winner of the electoral since 1980. Read more: CU forecasters predict a Romney presidency - The Denver Post</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349351031467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 07:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349351127648-17</Id><Topic><Title>Libturd are sore, not on the board tonight Obama is out of the race, he just hung his head now cnn, msnbc</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349319630536</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most Obama supporters don't get up until noon.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349351127648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 07:45:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349351280613-18</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Will Win Says 100% Historically Accurate Model</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349351031467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 07:43:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>my sources tell me this poll is 200% correct..dating back to when marco polo ran for mayor of venice....absolutely right on!!</Msg><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1349351280613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 07:48:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349351317618-19</Id><Topic><Title>Libturd are sore, not on the board tonight Obama is out of the race, he just hung his head now cnn, msnbc</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349319630536</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a very funny liberalnazi. HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1349351317618</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 07:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349351879157-20</Id><Title>Planned Layoffs Up in September</Title><Msg>The number of planned layoffs at U.S. firms in September rose 4.9 percent after hitting a 20-month low in August, a report on Thursday showed. Employers announced planned job cuts of 33,816 last month, up from 32,239 in August, according to the report from consultants Challenger, Gray &amp; Christmas, Inc. Despite this relative increase, the latest data marks a 15-year low in planned job cuts announced for the month of September. Last month's planned cuts were 71 percent lower than they were this time last year, when 115,730 expected job cuts were announced. Employers have announced 386,001 j o b cuts so far in 2012, down 19 percent from the 479,064 jobs cut during the first nine months of 2011. "Layoffs are definitely at pre-recession levels. Unfortunately, hiring has not returned to those levels. A combination of factors, including the upcoming election, ongoing instability in Europe, growing signs of weakness in Asia and a host of other issues, are keeping companies from making any major expansion or hiring moves," John Challenger, chief executive officer of Challenger, Gray &amp; Christmas, said in a statement. Cuts in the government sector fell significantly this year to 14,186 through September, compared to 119,027 at this point in 2011. The hiring forecast was also positive, with 425,683 planned hires announced last month, of which 413,700 will be in the seasonal retail and food industry. The Challenger report comes a day ahead of the key U.S. jobs report on Friday, which is forecast to add 113,000 jobs to nonfarm payrolls in September — up from 96,000 jobs added in August. Private payrolls are forecast to add 130,000 jobs, Reuters poll data shows</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1349351879157</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 07:57:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349352496893-21</Id><Title>I will only say this once,</Title><Msg>Romney clearly won the debate, without once telling the truth or explaining any details of his plan.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349352496893</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:08:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349353355637-22</Id><Title>Obama had much more detail for his plan</Title><Msg>Unfortunately, the details were higher unemployment, higher deficits more rules, more regulations, higher taxes, more government and worse foreign policies with more governments hating us.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349353355637</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:22:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349353561279-23</Id><Title>Without the Main Street Media to Shield and Protect Him......</Title><Msg>......the emperor clearly had no clothes.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349353561279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349354699375-24</Id><Title>Romney Wins!!</Title><Msg>Incidentally, the topic title is what everybody will see on November 7, 2012. "The CNN/ORC International poll of 430 people who watched the debate showed 67% thought Romney won, compared to 25% for Obama." Story on CNN.</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349354699375</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349354782337-25</Id><Title>Romney wins debate -- on Intrade!!</Title><Msg>There ya go Intrade junkies. Story on CNN.</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349354782337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:46:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349354990893-26</Id><Topic><Title>I will only say this once,</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349352496893</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:08:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to repeat your lies a bunch of times, like the MSM, for you to have any chance of being believed.</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349354990893</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:49:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349355101577-27</Id><Title>Left Wing Turns on Obama</Title><Msg>“I don’t think he explained himself very well on the economy. I think he was off his game. I was absolutely stunned tonight,” Ed Schultz said. “Where was Obama tonight?” Chris Matthews asked. “It does remind you that the last debate Mitt Romney had was seven months ago and the last debate that Barack Obama had was four years ago,” said Maddow. The Daily Beast’s Andrew Sullivan called Obama “tired,” “bored” and wrote that he might have even lost the election. “He choked. He lost. He may even have lost the election tonight,” Sullivan wrote, later adding, “Obama looked tired, even bored; he kept looking down; he had no crisp statements of passion or argument; he wasn’t there. He was entirely defensive, which may have been the strategy. But it was the wrong strategy. At the wrong moment.” Sullivan, an Obama supporter, was even more vicious on Twitter, calling Obama’s performance “terrible” and “political malpractice.” Another Obama supporter, liberal comedian Bill Maher, went on a similar Twitter rant, firing off such comments as, “Obama made a lot of great points tonight. Unfortunately, most of them were for Romney.” Michael Moore: 'This is what happens when u pick John Kerry as your debate coach'...</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349355101577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:51:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349355542956-28</Id><Topic><Title>Etch-a-sketch Rmoney - the myth candi-date</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349320471487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:14:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Great Recession came crashing down in 2007 due to the failed policies of the Boosh Administration, be in denial if you want. Myth Rmoney has most of the same advisors as Boosh. Try dealing with facts instead of Myths. The only cluelessness would be the continued flip-flopping and lack of specifics by Myth Rmoney. Can't really tell what Rmoney stands for, is he the liberal former governor or the right-wing extremist. Bet on the latter, and be afraid for that. Surely America will be doomed should the republicon fascists take control.</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349355542956</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:59:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349355801762-29</Id><Title>Who Are the Undecided</Title><Msg>Let’s face it … last night -- and all of these “debates,” for that matter -- are really for two purposes: To generate enthusiasm among your base and appeal to those who are still undecided. First, the base … If you HAVE already decided you are going to vote for Obama, I can recognize (though don’t understand) the reasons: You’re black, you’ve always voted for Democrats, you rely on the government and security is more important to you than freedom, you hate the rich. Like I said, I don’t understand it but at least you have a reason (albeit asinine). But the undecided voters have neither reason nor understanding. What is their problem? The painful truth is this: The difference between Obama and Romney is so stark that if you haven’t yet made up your mind, you’re either not very bright or not very informed. I’m sorry … you haven’t been paying attention or you are dumb as a sack of oysters. Let’s just take one example: The national debt. The national debt is an enormous $16 trillion, up from $10.7 trillion when Obama took office. For those of you who are government educated, that is an increase of about 50% in less than four years. But it gets worse. If Obama is re-elected (God help us), his own budget projections predict that our national debt will be over $20 trillion in 2016. If this is allowed to happen, Barack Obama will have managed to increase our debt by 87%. That’s just one president. He will have managed to increase the debt more than all of the presidents from George Washington all the way through (probably) Bill Clinton at that point. Here’s another way to look at the enormous amount of money (that we don’t have!) being spent by the Obama administration. From CNSNews: The federal government added $93,245,605,914.16 to its debt on Oct. 1, the first day of fiscal 2013. That was more than all the debt the federal government accumulated between July 4, 1776 when the United States declared independence from England and sometime in October 1942, which was ten months after the Japanese attacked Pearl Harbor and the United States entered World War II. Ok, those numbers are hard to grasp. They are large. What does that really mean for my family? Fine, we can do that too. Our total national debt is now equivalent to $136,690 for each American household. Just last year, your share of the national debt increased by $10,855 for each household … just last year! And Barack Obama’s budget plan says that by the end of his second term, our national debt will be $20 trillion. What will your share look like then? And you’re undecided? At this point it is because you are ignorant (you haven’t learned), or you are stupid (you can’t learn) or you are leach, a parasite, a moocher and you don’t give a flying fornication what the national debt is, so long as you keep getting your checks.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349355801762</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349355950656-30</Id><Topic><Title>Left Wing Turns on Obama</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349355101577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:51:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now America will Turn on Obama! Obama is Totally Exposed and Helpless without his Pacifier and Handlers. Can't wait for the Foreign Policy Segment Debate... Ambassador and Three Others Killed, including Former SEALs, Killed even After Asking Repeatedly for More Security... Obama Said NO! And Obama's Ambassador Rice Repeatedly Lying to the American People and the World... Denying the Obvious Days After the Truth was Known. As Paul Ryan said, "Obama's Foreign Policy is Unraveling Right in Front of our Eyes"</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349355950656</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:05:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349356359000-31</Id><Title>Liberal Washington Post... Obama Made Jimmy Carter Look Awesome</Title><Msg>HURT: Obama the debater: Making Jimmy Carter look awesome By Charles Hurt Wednesday, October 3, 2012 Party like it’s 1980! Bewildered and lost without his teleprompter, President Obama flailed all around the debate stage last night. He was stuttering, nervous and petulant. It was like he had been called in front of the principal after goofing around for four years and blowing off all his homework. Not since Jimmy Carter faced Ronald Reagan has the U.S. presidency been so embarrassingly represented in public. Actually, that’s an insult to Jimmy Carter. The split screen was most devastating. Mitt Romney spoke forthrightly, with carefully studied facts and details at the ready. He looked right at the president and accused him of being miles out of his depth. Mr. Obama? His eyes were glued to his lectern, looking guilty and angry and impatient with all the vagaries of Democracy. This debate was seriously chafing him. What exactly was Mr. Obama’s strategy here? Did he figure with so many people unemployed in this abomination of an economy he should go for the sympathy vote? Like voters could relate to a guy who is just scared pantsless that he is about to lose his job? In the middle of the blood-letting segment about jobs, Mr. Romney said good-naturedly: “This is fun.” Almost pleading, Mr. Obama reached out to the moderator for a lifeline: “You may want to move onto another topic.” When an unexpected noise went off behind him, Mr. Obama wheeled around to look as if to ask, “Time to go?” Hopefully. Turns out, it was the first honest thing we have heard from Mr. Obama’s campaign: The president really was absolutely terrible on the debate stage. Maybe the next debate will be on something other than the economy that won’t be so bad for Mr. Obama. Perhaps they could hold a debate on street organizing. Who knew anyone on the planet could make Mitt Romney look easy, relaxed, smooth and human? But Mr. Romney was absolutely on fire Wednesday night. He had command of countless specifics from voters and business owners from all across country. Read more: HURT: Obama the debater: Making Jimmy Carter look awesome - Washington Times http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/oct/3/hurt-obama-debater-making-jimmy-carter-look-awesom/#ixzz28Kr8HgUo Follow us: @washtimes on Twitter</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349356359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349356504102-32</Id><Title>Obama's World Class Arrogance</Title><Msg>When President Obama came to the U.N. General Assembly on September 25, his arrogance was on full display. He skipped meeting any world leaders, but did find time to sit down and talk about his lover moves on ABC’s “The View.” Topics included how he’s a “romantic husband,” how he “tucks in” his wife at night, and how his first kiss with Michelle is now memorialized by a monument in Chicago. Meanwhile, Israel is preparing for war against a soon-to-be-nuclear Iran. Yawn. Obama also skipped the traditional luncheon, leaving UN secretary general Ban-Ki Moon looking like “a jilted prom date,” reported CNN’s Anderson Cooper. “I think he must be busy with something at this moment,” Moon said at the lunch, drawing laughs. “Or perhaps he must be stuck somewhere in traffic.” But the arrogance was also there in Obama’s UN speech. In one passage, he flagrantly drew a straight line from blasphemers of Jesus Christ to his own critics, as if those two groups are similar in their willingness to offend messianic figures. “Like me, the majority of Americans are Christian, and yet we do not ban blasphemy against our most sacred beliefs,” he declared. Then it was all about him: “As president of our country, and commander in chief of our military, I accept that people are going to call me awful things every day, and I will always defend their right to do so.” Anyone who’s heard him diss the Supreme Court for the Citizens United verdict, affirming political free speech, knows that’s baloney.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349356504102</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:15:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349357013606-33</Id><Title>Big Bird a Threat to Republicans..!!</Title><Msg>the big yellow fluffiness is getting the axe if pukes get their way...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349357013606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:23:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349357072948-34</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins debate -- on Intrade!!</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349354782337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:46:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like you don't understand how intrade works. Obama has taken a hit there of course, but is still ahead by 32.9 percent points. There would not have been a market for "Obama/Romney wins the debate" because the answer is subjective and not a clearcut yes/no case; whereas winning the election is. It helps to think before you post, at least that's the case for most people with a room-temp IQ or better.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349357072948</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349357132669-35</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's World Class Arrogance</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349356504102</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:15:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's "World Class Arrogance" Came Tumbling Down Last Night... Obama is an Idiot without his Pacifier. Obama was Utterly Defeated Last Night for Millions of Americans to See. For some Odd Reason, Obama Seemed more Interested in his Shoes than the Debate... Perhaps, Crib Notes were Written on Top his Shoes, eh? Heavy Drinking Last Night in Chicago and Probably this AM as Well!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349357132669</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:25:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349357207526-36</Id><Topic><Title>Libturd are sore, not on the board tonight Obama is out of the race, he just hung his head now cnn, msnbc</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349319630536</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a very funny feminazi, Analgonqueer.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1349357207526</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:26:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349357211191-37</Id><Title>Obama officials ‘clearly involved’ in decision to terminate non-union Delphi retirees’ pensions</Title><Msg>House investigation: Treasury, Obama officials ‘clearly involved’ in decision to terminate non-union Delphi retirees’ pensions Powerful House Ways and Means Committee chairman Rep. Dave Camp announced Wednesday morning that documents his committee obtained prove political appointees in President Barack Obama’s administration were “clearly involved” in the decision to terminate 20,000 non-union Delphi salaried retirees’ pensions during the 2009 auto bailout. “Treasury was clearly in the center of the decision to terminate the pensions of Delphi’s salaried workers,” Camp said in a release. “Instead of withholding important documents, Treasury should release all documents without further delay and give these hardworking Americans answers as to why Treasury believed they were not entitled to their full pensions. I have serious concerns about this Administration picking winners and losers in Delphi’s bankruptcy.” The finding directly contradicts the testimonies of several Obama administration and White House officials, and means several communications the Treasury Department sent to Congress may have been false. In a press release, Camp’s committee said that the Pension Benefit Guaranty Corporation (PBGC) provided “what appears to be a nearly complete response” to his document request but Treasury “provided an incomplete response” and the White House provided nothing but “claimed Treasury was responding on its behalf.” During the auto bailout, a decision was made to terminate the pension plans for 20,000 non-union autoworker retirees from auto parts manufacturer Delphi. While those non-union retirees lost significant portions of their pensions, healthcare and life insurance benefits from this deal, their union brethren saw their benefits completely topped up. For years since, the Obama administration has claimed the PBGC made the decision and it was in no way involved in it at all. Email evidence TheDC obtained and published in early August shows that’s not the case.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349357211191</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:26:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349357435267-38</Id><Topic><Title>Getting Ready For The Debate</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney55</Username><Timestamp>1349307662200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:41:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dik/Paul: I Bet it wasn't Ten Minutes into the Debate that Your Popcorn went Stale and your Beer went Flat, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349357435267</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:30:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349357612329-39</Id><Title>Whatever Happened to Truth?</Title><Msg>Perhaps the most frustrating part of this campaign is the great lengths the ObamaMedia will go to in order to ignore the facts of Obama’s failures. Did you know that one-third of children in Ohio are enrolled in Medicaid? Neither did I, until last week when I picked up a copy of the Bucyrus (Ohio) Telegraph-Forum and read down to the seventh paragraph of a story headlined, "Study says more children have health insurance." The positive spin in the headline was undercut by the statistical facts of the story: "The increase in children on insurance comes as median incomes across the state were relatively flat, and the percentage of families in poverty -- especially those with children -- rose slightly." An increase in poverty, in other words, actually reduced the number of uninsured children by qualifying them for coverage under a government program for the poor. Such was the substance of the explanation by Angela Krile, spokeswoman for the Ohio Children's Hospital Association, who said: "Really, this just shows the importance of Medicaid in our state for children." Americans have become accustomed to this sort of "good news" in the Obama era, and there was more of it in that small-town Ohio paper. "Unemployment remains the same," declared the headline across the top of the front page. The story explained that, although the official unemployment rate in Crawford County, Ohio (population 43,389) declined from 9 percent in July to 8 percent in August, it wasn't because more people were working. "Since the number of employed stayed the same, 200 people went off of unemployment because their time limit is up and they have not found work yet," Dave Williamson, director of the Crawford County Economic Development Partnership, told the Bucyrus paper. "We have no more people working than we did last month." Extrapolate such statistical hocus-pocus at the local level across the entire state of Ohio, or nationwide, and you understand how some people might be deceived into believing that the Obama administration has actually produced an economic recovery. Yet it doesn't take much effort to discover how grim the situation really is.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349357612329</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:33:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349357827496-40</Id><Title>Repugs in a tizzy over Willtards 5-hour energy performance</Title><Msg>But there was not a single memorable Rmoney moment, was there... Guess which debate voters will remember most...most likely, the last one... Obviously, Repugs prefer lies, empty promises, and lack of specifics compared to facts and the cold hard truth, and want corporations to rule their lives and ration their healthcare</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349357827496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:37:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349357924262-41</Id><Topic><Title>Big Bird a Threat to Republicans..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349357013606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:23:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama was a big bird last night. He was a turkey at a turkey shoot. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349357924262</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:38:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349358032512-42</Id><Topic><Title>Whatever Happened to Truth?</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349357612329</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:33:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whatever happened to the truth? it went out the window when Willard started speaking last night, denying his across the board 20% tax cuts primarily benefitting the most wealthy...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349358032512</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349358166185-43</Id><Title>so romeny will end charitable and mortgage deductions</Title><Msg>I would vote for him if I knew he was not lieing</Msg><Username>ca.andse</Username><Timestamp>1349358166185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:42:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349358183057-44</Id><Title>Four More Years? Of This?</Title><Msg>Why was there little protection for our consulate in Benghazi before the September 11th attack? According to Princess Pelosi, we have the Republicans to blame because of their budget cuts. What? Wait a minute.....we have a budget? Is Pelosi just brain-dead?</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349358183057</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:43:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349358217110-45</Id><Topic><Title>Big Bird a Threat to Republicans..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349357013606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:23:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually it is About Public Funding to a Liberal Network... You Missed the Joke!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349358217110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:43:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349358246715-46</Id><Topic><Title>Big Bird a Threat to Republicans..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349357013606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:23:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is impossible for Willtard to repeal 'Obmacare' on his first day, even in the remote chance if he were to be elected. Chow down on that piece of gizzard!</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349358246715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349358279854-47</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins debate -- on Intrade!!</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349354782337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:46:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, I know how Intrade works. I also laugh at it's proponents because it's been wrong in BIG issues in the past. For example, Intrade odds were 80% that the SCOTUS would overturn Obamacare. LOL! Nonetheless, Intrade odds on Obummer fell from almost 80% yesterday afternoon to about 65% now - the first of many big drops to come.</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349358279854</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:44:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349358295947-48</Id><Topic><Title>Whatever Happened to Truth?</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349357612329</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:33:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" By double-digit advantages, the registered voters in CNN's poll said he (Romney) came across as the better leader and better on the economy." He laid it out for you last night....you must have missed the part where he suggested capping itemized deductions at a specific amount.....a tax change that in no way benefits the wealthy.</Msg><Username>commishfree1</Username><Timestamp>1349358295947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:44:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349358396613-49</Id><Topic><Title>Four More Years? Of This?</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349358183057</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:43:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America Does Not want Four More Years of Un-Employment Above 8% nor a Pathological Lier for a President</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349358396613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349358574872-50</Id><Topic><Title>so romeny will end charitable and mortgage deductions</Title><Username>ca.andse</Username><Timestamp>1349358166185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:42:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney is Considering a Cap on the Deductions... That will Affect the Rich and Never the Free Loading 47%ers.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349358574872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:49:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349358682858-51</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs in a tizzy over Willtards 5-hour energy performance</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349357827496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, it is Obama and His Campaign that are Hugely Depressed this AM.... Obama Can't Run on his Record and He Knows it!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349358682858</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:51:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349358711968-52</Id><Title>Even Van Jones the Communist Says Romney Humiliated Obama Last Night.</Title><Msg>When even your Left-as-can-be former green jobs czar thinks you lost...you lost. Mitt Romney delivered the debate of his life last night, and this telling soundbite from Van Jones illustrates why: Romney did a better of job connecting with, and dare we suggest, empathizing with, his audience. President Obama’s former environmental jobs czar believes his former boss lost the debate. Van Jones, President Obama’s former special adviser for green jobs, said on CNN that the president was not ready for Wednesday night’s debate against Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney. “I think he took Romney too lightly. I think he did not expect Romney to throw that kind of heat,” Jones explained. Jones added: “Romney was able to ‘out-Obama’ Obama. On the connection piece, on the authenticity piece, on the being able to tell the story.” Jones said Obama’s game-plan set him up for failure.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349358711968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349358713002-53</Id><Title>CBS Poll: Romney WON!</Title><Msg>Sorry, dumbocrats. I guess that Barry really does need a teleprompter. Story on MSNBC video.</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349358713002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:51:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349358831090-54</Id><Topic><Title>CBS Poll: Romney WON!</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349358713002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All Polls Show Romney Crushed Obama ... Can't Wait for the Foreign Policy Debate Segment</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349358831090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349359034759-55</Id><Title>The Ghost of Jimmy Carter has Arrived Right on Time</Title><Msg>After the Next Two Debates, Obama will Make Jimmy Carter Look Awesome as the WaPo Wrote!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349359034759</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:57:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349359157080-56</Id><Topic><Title>Whatever Happened to Truth?</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349357612329</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:33:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except for one thing, Rmoney failed to mention a single one. Rmoney was just 5-hour energy fluff for the mentally impaired RWNJ's. 20% of $2M = $400k 20% of $50k = $10k so who benefits more? And how is Rmoney gonna pay for all these tax cuts benefitting mostly the wealthy? Wave his magic wand and sprinkle some faerie dust? Get real! Any grown man who believes that an angel called Moroni from the planet Bolock gave Joseph Smith some golden plates, has to be considered suspect mentally</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349359157080</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349359283226-57</Id><Topic><Title>Four More Years? Of This?</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1349358183057</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:43:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is Pelosi just brain-dead? When stretch had her face lifted??? Was her face the only thing which got lifted? I guess not, because before something can be stolen or lost, doesn't it have it have to have existed in the first place? Too have a brain, we have to vote for it first to find out what is in it. I can only conclude Pelosi's constituents, those who voted for her, have no brains.</Msg><Username>mcfool_chuckles</Username><Timestamp>1349359283226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:01:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349359391850-58</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs in a tizzy over Willtards 5-hour energy performance</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349357827496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why can't Obama run on his record,,, it is far better than repugs Boosh record,,,by leaps and bounds, and Rmoney only offers more failed Boosh policies! In his 5-hour energy tizzy, Rmoney even contradicted what he said days earlier and denied his own 20% tax cut plan. Ignore the facts, if you want. Better yet, put your (r) money where your mouth is!!!</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349359391850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349359584518-59</Id><Topic><Title>Big Bird a Threat to Republicans..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349357013606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:23:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you OK or are you having a stroke? What is Obmacare? Did you mean to write Mobacare to signify a new union health plan? What does Obmacare have to do with big bird and PBS which is the subject of this thread? I don't think the voters are going to pardon the big turkey in the White House this year when there are so many unemployed with little to be thankful for this Thanksgiving. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349359584518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:06:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349360312245-60</Id><Topic><Title>Big Bird a Threat to Republicans..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349357013606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:23:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take your meds. You are quite delusional. All the homeless and out of work like yourself will have plenty of turkey at Thanksgiving as usual due to the hard work of volunteers, the charity of the average person/the 47% and non-profit organizations... Especially after voters REJECT the Myth Rmoney!!! Hey here's an idea, why don't the myth rmoney sit down with party leaders today and wave his magic wand/spread his faeire dust since you and he believe in that sorta stuff...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349360312245</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349360578672-61</Id><Topic><Title>Big Bird a Threat to Republicans..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349357013606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:23:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just wait until PBS is wholly corporate owned and big bird says to all the kids like you mmm, high fructose corn syrup is just a yummy as sugar, fracking water is tasty, and bp oil is really really really cleaning up the gulf coast due to the kindness of their hearts</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349360578672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:22:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349360839721-62</Id><Topic><Title>Big Bird a Threat to Republicans..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349357013606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:23:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamer is the only expert on fairy dust and all things fairy for that matter as he was a member of 'Man Country', in Chicago. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349360839721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:27:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349361024384-63</Id><Topic><Title>Big Bird a Threat to Republicans..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349357013606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:23:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you think sitcky's Mom knows he is using the computer so much -- that can be very damaging for a 9 year old</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1349361024384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:30:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349361195072-64</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins debate -- on Intrade!!</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349354782337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:46:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, you could always put your money where your mouth is; try it, you might win some spare change. BTW, can you document "Intrade odds were 80% that the SCOTUS would overturn Obamacare"? I've followed the site quite closely and don't remember seeing that one. I don't think anyvody could anticipate Roberts going the way he did. FYI: Although I voted for Obama 4 years ago and this time as well, I do think his perfornance yesterday was very disappointing. .</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349361195072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:33:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349361245331-65</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Will Win Says 100% Historically Accurate Model</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349351031467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 07:43:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those 2 professors - one of them was assisting Donald Trump dig up some scoop about Obama's birth place the other was released from New Mexico state pen for fraud &amp; impersonating a college professor</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1349361245331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349361367870-66</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins debate -- on Intrade!!</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349354782337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 08:46:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"BTW, can you document "Intrade odds were 80% that the SCOTUS would overturn Obamacare"? I've followed the site quite closely and don't remember seeing that one. " typical dumbocrat -- never does see the truth. LOL!</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349361367870</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:36:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349361446578-67</Id><Title>CBS Poll Says Independents thought that Romney won</Title><Msg>.. by better than a 2 to 1 rate!!</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349361446578</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:37:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349361456327-68</Id><Topic><Title>Big Bird a Threat to Republicans..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349357013606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:23:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no worries sparty i think the village, err hood, has warped the message, if you and your dumbo/mobro village friends value value the bird, you can fund him.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1349361456327</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:37:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349361645730-69</Id><Topic><Title>NYT: 'President Xanax'...</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1349360031114</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Police in Chicago became farmers for a day Wednesday as they began to chop down a marijuana farm as big as two football fields found in the city. The farm, which contains about 1,500 plants and could have netted $7-10 million, was spotted by a police officer and county sheriff's deputy in a helicopter as they headed back to their hangar." Cops still trying to find out who owns the plot...........just sayin'.</Msg><Username>commishfree1</Username><Timestamp>1349361645730</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:40:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349361712298-70</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Will Win Says 100% Historically Accurate Model</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349351031467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 07:43:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't make any difference whio the profs comsult with -- what does matter is that the MODEL HAS NEVER BEEN WRONG!</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349361712298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:41:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349361817963-71</Id><Topic><Title>NYT: 'President Xanax'...</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1349360031114</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe O'Bummer needs to join Illinois Representative Jackson at the Mayo Clinic - something about being bipolar.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349361817963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:43:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349362157414-72</Id><Title>Even on the most basic political points, Jeff Greenfield says, Obama seemed clueless.</Title><Msg>Why yes, he was clueless!! Story on Yahoo News.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349362157414</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:49:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349362272452-73</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs in a tizzy over Willtards 5-hour energy performance</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349357827496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You poor insane leftys! You have to spin the obama administration's total failures into some sort of fantastic success story. Not an easy job even for you experienced and expert liars.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1349362272452</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:51:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349362398007-74</Id><Topic><Title>Even on the most basic political points, Jeff Greenfield says, Obama seemed clueless.</Title><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349362157414</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:49:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>O'Bummer seems to be clueless about lots of things: clueless about getting the economy to grow clueless about reducing unemplyment clueless about how to keep China from stealing our jobs cluesless about building bipartisan support for anything cluess about transparent goverment clueless about stopping Iran from getting the bomb clueless about insuring that our ambassadors don't get killed</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349362398007</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:53:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349362620534-75</Id><Title>No matter how much you shake, kick or dance.......</Title><Msg>Democrats are shaking, Obama got his #$%$ kicked and Freedom lovers are dancing. Dik Hertz has sand in his head, his toes stink, and I'm drinking his beer. Life is good.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1349362620534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349362652878-76</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs in a tizzy over Willtards 5-hour energy performance</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349357827496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But there was not a single memorable Rmoney moment" You must not have seen Mitt school the president by saying "Mr President, you are entitled to your own house. You are entitled to your own plane , but Mr President, you are not entitled to your own facts." As they used to say on the old Batman TV series: BLAM! SMASH!! BOFF!! OOOOOFFFF!</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349362652878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:57:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349362687701-77</Id><Topic><Title>Even on the most basic political points, Jeff Greenfield says, Obama seemed clueless.</Title><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349362157414</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:49:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor O, he's never had to face any hard questions before. I guess the only thing left for him to do is play the race card very very hard, but that act isn't working as well as it used to with most people. We just don't care about that any more.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1349362687701</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:58:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349362706256-78</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs in a tizzy over Willtards 5-hour energy performance</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349357827496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:37:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know, getting bin laden et al, and keeping America safe for four years, stopping the loss of 700,000 jobs per month, reestablishing the auto industry, taking the GDP from -7% to +3 %, unemployment from 105 to 8% these are all bad things to the brainwashed RWNJ's/repigs losers now where are those WMD's in iraq the duh-bya is still looking for after they attacked us 9/11, ha-ha</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349362706256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349362843860-79</Id><Title>Did Romney mislead or did he outright lie?</Title><Msg>He said he will not raise the tax on the middle class! Perhaps he will not raise the middle income tax rate however he will kill all deductions that help the middle class and for sure will shift much much more taxation burden to the state and municipal levels! In essence if you delve into the fine print of his plan he will slash the tiny top income tax the elites now enjoy and wage workers will end up picking up the burden and suffer painful austerity! Just Google--- Study: Romney’s Tax Plan Crushes the Middle Class</Msg><Username>sallykohles</Username><Timestamp>1349362843860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:00:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349362923152-80</Id><Title>Repugs in a tizzy over the Donny and Marie Osmond candi-date</Title><Msg>all fluff, no substance</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349362923152</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:02:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349362945451-81</Id><Topic><Title>Did Romney mislead or did he outright lie?</Title><Username>sallykohles</Username><Timestamp>1349362843860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why on earth would I want to Google your lies?</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349362945451</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:02:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349363008408-82</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs in a tizzy over the Donny and Marie Osmond candi-date</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349362923152</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haaaaaaa ha ha ha ha! Is that the best you can do?</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349363008408</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:03:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349363196535-83</Id><Topic><Title>No matter how much you shake, kick or dance.......</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1349362620534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:57:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was funny. You deserve 100 thumbs up or at least a free Obamer cell phone for your brilliance. :-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349363196535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349363213384-84</Id><Topic><Title>Did Romney mislead or did he outright lie?</Title><Username>sallykohles</Username><Timestamp>1349362843860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Did Romney mislead or did he outright lie?" No, but he did kick the president's posterior last night. I wonder how well O'bummer slept last night with his sore posterior nestled next to Michelle?</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349363213384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:06:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349363364929-85</Id><Topic><Title>Spin it libs!</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1349359692616</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:08:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libs Like Obama have Nowhere to Hide! Obama Can't run on his Poor Economic Record and Now his Foreign Policy is Crumbling in Front all American Eyes... "ain't" Pretty for the Obama Camp! Obama is and has Been a Total Failure!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349363364929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:09:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349363453987-86</Id><Title>Who is fighting for middle class tax cuts?</Title><Msg>Just Google--- Who is fighting for middle class tax cuts? You should than click onto a online calculator that shows the tax you will pay under Obama or Romney! This is my result! Under President Obama saved $3,600 over the last 4 years Under the President’s plan will continue to save $2,200 next year Under Romney would pay over $2,000 more</Msg><Username>sallykohles</Username><Timestamp>1349363453987</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:10:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349363503580-87</Id><Topic><Title>Did Romney mislead or did he outright lie?</Title><Username>sallykohles</Username><Timestamp>1349362843860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even MSNBC Could Not Find any Fact to Support Obama or Reason to Attack Romney! Obama Cooked his Goose last Night!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349363503580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349363780065-88</Id><Title>Ann Romney Spends Day picking out New Drapes for Whaite House</Title><Msg>Old ones going to Chicago</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1349363780065</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:16:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349364029483-89</Id><Topic><Title>Who is fighting for middle class tax cuts?</Title><Username>sallykohles</Username><Timestamp>1349363453987</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:10:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Under Obama, Middle Class Americans Have Already Lost over $4,000 in Income... Even Joe Biden says the Middle Class has been Hammered the Last Four Years under Obama! Is Joe a Buffoon or just Telling the Truth, eh? Ryan will Crush the Buffoon in the VP Debates. Un-Employment over 8% for More than Four Years... Mainly Hit are the Middle Class and African Americans (18+%)... no Wonder the Later Plans to Stay Home in November!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349364029483</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349364093033-90</Id><Topic><Title>Did Romney mislead or did he outright lie?</Title><Username>sallykohles</Username><Timestamp>1349362843860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>which multi-id cross dresser, sparty or chrissie? please step forward and claim your new ID</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1349364093033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:21:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349364334124-91</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs in a tizzy over the Donny and Marie Osmond candi-date</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349362923152</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Teleprompter-less Troubadour Takes a Tumble The "O" in OH Bummer Officially is a "ZERO" Without the Lame Stream Media there to prop up and filter what the DumbSter had to say, America got to see the Lacking Lackey as the fumbling, bumbling Community Organizer -In-Chief he is. On the up side, Uh-Oh-Bumbler did stare a hole through one of his shoes and set some of his notes on fire!!!!</Msg><Username>tminusten</Username><Timestamp>1349364334124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:25:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349364577124-92</Id><Topic><Title>At Last Night’s Debate: Romney Told 27 Myths In 38 Minutes</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349364448347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dik-hed obviously has his Bigot colored glasses on!</Msg><Username>tminusten</Username><Timestamp>1349364577124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:29:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349364586795-93</Id><Topic><Title>At Last Night’s Debate: Romney Told 27 Myths In 38 Minutes</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349364448347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haaaa hahahahha! Did you come up with those all by yourself, or did you steal them from someone else, plagerize, and not give full credit to the author?</Msg><Username>parkplacebob</Username><Timestamp>1349364586795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:29:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349364830379-94</Id><Title>Now AARP Gives Obama the Middle Finger!</Title><Msg>AARP objects to Obama invoking group's support during debate Published October 04, 2012 The AARP, which put itself in the middle of the health care debate by endorsing ObamaCare, now is telling President Obama to keep the group out of his political talking points. The nation's leading senior advocacy organization objected after the president during Wednesday's debate twice mentioned the AARP while defending his health care plan and attacking Mitt Romney's plans for Medicare. The AARP posted a blog saying that while the group is "grateful" the candidates had a "robust" debate on health care, the organization is not aligned with either candidate. "While we respect the rights of each campaign to make its case to voters, AARP has never consented to the use of its name by any candidate or political campaign. AARP is a nonpartisan organization and we do not endorse political candidates nor coordinate with any candidate or political party," the group said. Obama invoked the AARP during the Denver debate because the group had endorsed his health care overhaul earlier in his term. He used that endorsement to challenge Romney's claims that the law's cuts to Medicare would weaken the health care system. "And this is not my own -- only my opinion. AARP thinks that the savings that we obtained from Medicare bolster the system, lengthen the Medicare trust fund by eight years. Benefits were not affected at all," Obama said. He went on to say that Romney's plan, which he describes as a "voucher system," would put seniors "at the mercy" of insurance companies. "And this is the reason why AARP has said that your plan would weaken Medicare substantially. And that's why they were supportive of the approach that we took," Obama said. The AARP, while having gotten involved in the health care debate, stressed that it is trying not to take sides in the presidential race itself. Some, though, have questioned the AARP's objectivity. Sen. Jim DeMint, R-S.C., in a recent op-ed in Politico, said the group "poses as a disinterested senior advocate" while taking positions that "just happen to coincide with its financial interests." He claimed that group's support of the health care law could yield "windfall profits" by forcing seniors off Medicare Advantage and into a separate supplemental coverage program. "AARP knows it can protect its financial interests by aligning with Democrats, no matter what its members think," DeMint wrote. Romney said during Wednesday's debate that his plan for overhauling Medicare would give seniors a decade from now a choice between traditional Medicare and private insurance. "And by the way, if the government can be as efficient as the private sector and offer premiums that are as low as the private sector, people will be happy to get traditional Medicare or they'll be able to get a private plan," Romney said.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349364830379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:33:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349365414287-95</Id><Topic><Title>Ann Romney Spends Day picking out New Drapes for Whaite House</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1349363780065</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:16:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And everything else DimBummer can sneak out in the middle of the night!</Msg><Username>tminusten</Username><Timestamp>1349365414287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:43:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349365421422-96</Id><Title>The man with a Midas touch</Title><Msg>Has a Golden tongue too. What a surprise!</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349365421422</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:43:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349365421531-97</Id><Title>Dem Insider: "We got our clock cleaned"</Title><Msg>Who was that man, and what has he done with Mitt Romney? The Republican presidential nominee was more cheerful, more prepared, more specific, more informed and more energetic than President Obama tonight, resulting in a genuine rout. Romney seemed eager to answer every question, Obama looked peeved and sluggish. For every straw man argument the president raised, his challenger offered a lengthy and detailed rebuttal, in full command of the facts. Romney won virtually every single exchange throughout the night -- on jobs, on deficits, on energy, on Medicare, on health care, and especially on the role of government. Obama's strongest moment may have been wishing his wife a happy wedding anniversary. According to polls, a large majority of Americans expected the president to skate in these debates. What a different reality viewers encountered tonight. I'm not sure how others felt, but I actually found myself looking forward to Romney's next answer, every time. I'll have a few more specific thoughts as the night unfolds, but this was an exceptional evening for Governor Romney.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349365421531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:43:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349365613409-98</Id><Topic><Title>The man with a Midas touch</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349365421422</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:43:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When DimmBumma gets his VACATE THE PROPERTY notice in November, DOG will be showing up more and more on his daily menu!</Msg><Username>tminusten</Username><Timestamp>1349365613409</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:46:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349365646687-99</Id><Topic><Title>Dem Insider: "We got our clock cleaned"</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349365421531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:43:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Cleaned Very Well... Jimmy Carter all Over Again!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349365646687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349365660044-100</Id><Title>(CNN) -- The Etch a Sketch was in full effect at the first presidential debate in Denver on Wednesday night.</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney put forward a strong performance, transforming back into his 2002 Massachusetts moderate mold, a belated advocate of bipartisan leadership. It would have had a lot more impact if it hadn't contradicted almost every policy statement Romney has made on the campaign trail since he started running for president. This flip-flopping is a force of habit, but it was used to great effect, reflecting a campaign and a candidate finally focused on the general electorate The trick of communicating policy is to distill it to memorable concise concepts. That happened far too rarely, and when it did, it seemed to be off the cuff, winning Obama points for authenticity but few for debate prep. Opinion: Romney shakes up the race The audacity of the Etch a Sketch was evident in the first 15 minutes of the debate, when Mitt Romney said, "I will not reduce the taxes paid by high-income Americans." It was an eye-popping assertion, almost as if the candidate hadn't been listening to his own campaign rhetoric -- especially if you'd been following Romney's campaign rhetoric for the past 18 months or more. (Remember that "Etch A Sketch" entered the campaign lexicon in March, when Romney adviser Eric Fehrnstrom signaled on CNN that Romney could transform his primary campaign message for the general election.) The pattern continued with Romney asserting that after repealing Obamacare, he would advocate the implementation of his own individual mandate plan -- "And the best course for health care is to do what we did in my state" -- but it would be state by state, along a federalist model. President Barack Obama and Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney finish their debate in Denver on Wednesday, October 3. View behind-the-scene photos of debate preparations. Romney stands with his wife, Ann, and family following the first presidential debate. President Obama kisses first lady Michelle Obama after the debate Wednesday. It took place on their 20th wedding anniversary. Jim Leher of PBS moderates the 90-minute debate on Wednesday. It was the candidates' first time debating face to face. Obama defended his record and challenged his rival's proposals. Romney was more aggressive Wednesday in criticizing Obama's vision. People watch the debate at Galapagos Art Space in Brooklyn, New York. The event was expected to draw the candidates' largest nationwide audience to date. Romney answers a question from the moderator. Obama argues his view. Both candidates said the other's proposals won't work. Michelle Obama listens to the debate. Romney said Obama has failed to bring down high unemployment and get the economy surging again. Obama reacts to Romney's remarks on Wednesday. Obama listens during the debate in Denver. Romney, who has been unable to catch the president in most polls to date, sought to generate enthusiasm for a change in the White House. Romney's shadow is projected beneath text from the Declaration of Independence at the University of Denver's Magness Arena. The first of three presidential debates focused on domestic issues: the economy, health care and the role of government. Obama and Mitt Romney clashed over the economy on Wednesday. Romney speaks during Wednesday night's debate. The candidate called for a new economic path. Obama called for "economic patriotism" and said Romney's plan of tax cuts for the rich failed before. Romney and Obama wave to the crowd at the start of the presidential debate. Obama greets Romney on Wednesday. The candidates meet on stage less than five weeks before Election Day. Obama and Romney shake hands Wednesday night. The presidential race has been dominated so far by negative advertising as both camps try to frame the election to their advantage. Leher takes the stage Wednesday. It's his 12th time moderating a presidential debate. Michelle Obama points to Lehrer before the start of the debate. Ann Romney and first lady Michelle Obama hug on Wednesday. The candidates wives were in attendance for the most highly anticipated campaign event to date. Michelle Obama sits with White House Senior Advisor Valerie Jarrett, right. Rapper Will.i.am, left, speaks with Jarrett before the debate on Wednesday. View behind-the-scenes photos of debate preparations. The first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateThe first presidential debateHIDE CAPTION Photos: The first presidential debate Separating truth from fiction at debate U.S. voters overseas discuss Obama-Romney Granholm 'high on democracy' Romney did not hesitate to play the MediScare card -- the most discredited Democrat tactic against entitlement reform, but apparently acceptable if it is done by a Republican trying to win Florida. Happily, for hypocrisy watchers, this move also scored worst with the focus group of undecided voters conducted by CNN's Erin Burnett in Denver during the debate. The litany of flip-flops increased when the candidates' policy positions were pushed for specifics. It was a necessary goal that wasn't aided by the too often unfocused moderation of veteran newsman Jim Lehrer, who did not need a 12th presidential debate under his belt. Among the gaps was the question of whether Romney supports ending "too big to fail" -- which might mean breaking up the big banks, and/or restoring safeguards from the 1933 Glass-Steagall banking reform act, repealed in 1999 -- or simply repealing the 2010 Dodd-Frank law, which regulates Wall Street. On that issue, as well as on Obamacare, it was not clear what Romney would put in place of the laws he plans to repeal. Romney seemed to indicate he would end oil company subsidies if corporate rates were lowered enough -- that's news to Exxon, I'm guessing. Romney said Obama should have backed the Bowles-Simpson Commission's deficit reduction proposals (I agree), but did not back the recommendations of that panel himself. Opinion: Romney wasn't stellar, but Obama fell short He advocated a balanced deficit reduction plan but refused to raise any revenue -- and perhaps unwisely said he'd kill "Sesame Street" icon Big Bird in the process. His enthusiasm for budget cutting does not square with his commitment to increasing military spending to 4% of GDP. Likewise, he wasn't pressed -- by Obama or Lehrer -- to specify the loophole closures which Romney said would make his 20% tax cuts revenue-neutral for top income earners. Whenever Lehrer did try to assert himself as a moderator, Romney reflexively bristled -- he is not a man who likes being told he has to conform to other people's rules. The president's strategic decision to try to find rhetorical common ground on policy at the outset came across as passive rather than conciliatory. His correct pressing on the fact that many of Romney's stated economic plans "do not add up" got lost in paragraphs rather than topic sentences. To be fair, Obama had a few good lines -- dismissing Romney's economic plan by saying "math, common sense, and our history shows us that's not a recipe for job growth." His pushback on Wall Street reform was also memorable: "Does anybody out there think that the big problem we had is that there was too much oversight and regulation of Wall Street? Because if you do, then Gov. Romney is your candidate. But that's not what I believe." But Romney exceeded expectations and put forward a confident debate performance that was especially impressive given its disregard for his own past policy positions. Romney shone in the moments he discussed the generational theft of deficits and debt. In contrast, Obama did not come ready for combat, even in a Jed Bartlett egghead way. Assessments of presidential debate performances tend to evolve over the next day, reflecting a combination of spin, fact-checking and conventional wisdom. This first debate will be subject to the same evolution, as partisans on both sides try furiously to spin the debate in their direction. A flip-flop ad, contrasting past statements with debate statements, could be effective for either campaign. It's worth remembering that many swing voters who have lives were watching the high-stakes season-ending baseball games, instead of obsessively trolling Twitter for debate commentary. Opinion: It wasn't just Romney who won In the search for honest brokers -- patriots, not partisans -- we can only hope that the truth, ever elusive, will win out in the end, because we ultimately get the government we deserve.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349365660044</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:47:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349365744139-101</Id><Topic><Title>At Last Night’s Debate: Romney Told 27 Myths In 38 Minutes</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349364448347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many women and children did Obama murder while Romney was lying on TV?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1349365744139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:49:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349365891957-102</Id><Topic><Title>At Last Night’s Debate: Romney Told 27 Myths In 38 Minutes</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349364448347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, Romney was Not Lying Last Night. Obama is the Pathological Lier in Chief! Obama Could Not Defend his Un-Defendable Record Last Night and it Showed!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349365891957</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:51:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349366192338-103</Id><Title>CNN Poll... Romney Crushed Obama by Large Margin! Historic Numbers.</Title><Msg>CNN Poll: Most watchers say Romney debate winner Posted by CNN Political Unit Denver, Colorado (CNN) – Two-thirds of people who watched the first presidential debate think that Republican nominee Mitt Romney won the showdown, according to a nationwide poll conducted Wednesday night. According to a CNN/ORC International survey conducted right after the debate, 67% of debate watchers questioned said that the Republican nominee won the faceoff, with one in four saying that President Barack Obama was victorious. "No presidential candidate has topped 60% in that question since it was first asked in 1984," says CNN Polling Director Keating Holland.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349366192338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:56:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349366328455-104</Id><Topic><Title>At Last Night’s Debate: Romney Told 27 Myths In 38 Minutes</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349364448347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He got it from CPUSA aka Think Progress. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349366328455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:58:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349366753950-105</Id><Topic><Title>Presidential Debate Won't Change Anyone's Mind</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349366504584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:01:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are You Drinking? Debates Killed Nixon and Killed Carter.... Looks Like You are Only Left with Only Hopeful Thinking, eh? Need to Better, Dik/Paul/Chrissie!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349366753950</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:05:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349366881816-106</Id><Topic><Title>Presidential Debate Won't Change Anyone's Mind</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349366504584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:01:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but, but ,but, the debates already changed odds on intrade 15% of the people that voted for O'Bummer yesterday afternoon, aren't voting for him anymore ...</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349366881816</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:08:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349366997368-107</Id><Title>Manufacturing Plunges Under Obama... Again! Thanks Obama!</Title><Msg>Orders to U.S. Factories Plunge on Airplanes, Computers By Lorraine Woellert - Oct 4, 2012 11:17 AM ET Orders placed with U.S. factories fell in August by the most in more than three years, signaling that slowdowns in business investment and exports restrained the economic expansion. The 5.2 percent decrease in bookings was the biggest since January 2009 and followed a revised 2.6 percent increase in July, the Commerce Department said today in Washington. The median forecast of economists in a Bloomberg News survey called for a decline of 5.9 percent. Demand for durable goods dropped 13.2 percent, the same as reported last week, while shipments of non-durables, which includes such things as petroleum and chemicals and often reflect swings in price, climbed 2.2 percent. Enlarge image In the U.S., concerns about a fiscal cliff of tax increases and government spending cuts set for January also are putting the brakes on business investment, which has been a mainstay of the expansion. Photographer: Ty Wright/Bloomberg Factories are feeling the effects of Europe’s debt crisis and a slowdown in China and other Asian markets. In the U.S., concerns about a fiscal cliff of tax increases and government spending cuts set for January also are putting the brakes on business investment, which has been a mainstay of the expansion. “These data indicate that the recent softness in manufacturing activity and capital spending is likely to continue, at least for several more months,” Steven Wood, president of Insight Economics LLC in Danville, California, said in a note to clients. Economists’ forecasts in the Bloomberg survey ranged from declines of 1.2 percent to 8 percent.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349366997368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:09:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349367082827-108</Id><Topic><Title>Presidential Debate Won't Change Anyone's Mind</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349366504584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:01:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dik is in Denial... let the Little Fool go Through the Steps to Reality!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349367082827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:11:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349367162643-109</Id><Topic><Title>A Skewed CNN Snap Poll?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349367012342</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:10:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dik, You are Really in Denial.... Did you Drink you Flat Beer last Night, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349367162643</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349367165890-110</Id><Topic><Title>A Skewed CNN Snap Poll?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349367012342</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:10:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean that the CBS poll said by more than 2 to 1 that Romney beat O'Bummer last night -- it must be skewed, too. ROTFLMBFAO!!</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349367165890</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349367290489-111</Id><Title>Social media results of last night's debate:</Title><Msg>Romney crushed Obama -- according to twitter and facebook look for the story on AP</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349367290489</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:14:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349367423525-112</Id><Topic><Title>A Skewed CNN Snap Poll?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349367012342</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:10:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Corporate media need to make even the most boring of political events seem exciting;" the only thing boring last night was your president.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349367423525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:17:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349367574991-113</Id><Title>Chris Christie's Prediction was Right... Romney Did Indeed Crush Obama</Title><Msg>Poor, Dik, he was Wrong again... Dik, did you Eat your Stale Popcorn?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349367574991</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:19:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349367868395-114</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie's Prediction was Right... Romney Did Indeed Crush Obama</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349367574991</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:19:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The dik is choking on the kernel.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1349367868395</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:24:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349367999563-115</Id><Title>Romney: 5 Obama: 0</Title><Msg>NO Teleprompter NO Lame Stream Media NO Clue NO Bamma 2013 When the going gets tough, DumBummer gets going. THE OTHER WAY! The Lame One Aptly demonstrated just how inept he is and why America must vote R/R. Our friends and enemies all over the world got a eyeful of a lacking, shallow and ill prepared Demander-N-Thief. A real low light for the prestige of the Presidency of The United States. Talk about aid and comfort to our enemies! For you Union types: WHO do we want to DUMP: OH BOMMER WHEN do we want to DUMP HIM: NOW WHO do we want to DUMP: OH BOMMER WHEN do we want to DUMP HIM: NOW Advanced Union Types: HAY, HEE, HYE D, HO, DAT Dum Bammer GATS TO GO. BACK UP DA KAR, BACK UP DA TRUCK, KICK IZ ADZE OUT, HE AINT WURF AH DUCK ENNIE, MEENIE, MINEY, MO, DAT Dum Bammer GATS TO GO. (Repeat until the Burn Barrel go out or the Colt 45 is gone)</Msg><Username>tminusten</Username><Timestamp>1349367999563</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:26:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349368067820-116</Id><Topic><Title>The man with a Midas touch</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349365421422</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:43:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cannot even convince my kids to eat vegetables at that age.Good thing there was no Child Services in Indonesia at that time.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349368067820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349368417709-117</Id><Title>Business Insider Assessment of last night's O'Bummer performance:</Title><Msg>Both campaigns set low expectations, but only Obama met them. Read more: http://www.businessinsider.com/why-romney-clobbered-obama-2012-10#ixzz28LgU6yRV</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349368417709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:33:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349368696571-118</Id><Topic><Title>Business Insider Assessment of last night's O'Bummer performance:</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349368417709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:33:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent Post... That is the Only Thing Obama has Met!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349368696571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:38:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349368995795-119</Id><Title>Michael Moore to Obama - 'This is what happens when u pick John Kerry as your debate coach'</Title><Msg>tweeted the fat socialist during last night's debate-- he also tweeted" "If Romney keeps this up...Obama is going to vote for him!" how funny!! story at the Washington Times</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349368995795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:43:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349369175052-120</Id><Topic><Title>Even on the most basic political points, Jeff Greenfield says, Obama seemed clueless.</Title><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349362157414</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:49:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's What Happens When America Votes for an Affirmative Action Queen over Competence! This Time America will Not be Fooled.... Romney will Expose Obama for Who he Truly is... an Incompetent Fool! Should we Mention the Buffoon Biden as well? What a Ticket, eh? PS. Obama is Crying Like a Baby to Get his Pacifier/TelePrompter Back! Can't Think on his Feet!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349369175052</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:46:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349369414259-121</Id><Topic><Title>Even on the most basic political points, Jeff Greenfield says, Obama seemed clueless.</Title><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349362157414</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:49:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Tired and No Longer Effective Race Card is all Obama has Left as Obama can't Run on his Failed Economic and Foreign Policies Obama Looks Tired and Ready to Give Up!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349369414259</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:50:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349369521187-122</Id><Title>Last Night's Debate's most Memorable Moment</Title><Msg>It had to be when Mr. Obama began talking about some tax incentive for sending jobs overseas. I remember staring at my TV set and thinking that I had absolutely no idea what he was talking about. When the moderator panned over to Mr. Romney, Mr. Romney said: "I've been in business for 25 years, and I have no idea what you're talking about". This morning, I woke up to an ABC "hard" news broadcast... and the news guy proceeded to tell me what I thought about last night's debate. I guess they didn't fully realize that I WATCHED the debate. The "hard" news went on to tell me about how Mr. Romney was playing fast and loose with the facts... ... maybe THEY had some idea about where the hell Obama was getting his figures... but I've been an economist, a financier, and and educator for more than 30 years, and I STILL had no idea where Mr. Obama was getting some of those numbers... particularly the ones he was coming up with about Mitt Romney. S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349369521187</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:52:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349369739223-123</Id><Title>Remember Voters Are Fickle</Title><Msg>And Winning is Contagious. Nobody wants to be associated with a Loser.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349369739223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:55:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349369746326-124</Id><Title>Bully Pulpit</Title><Msg>Obuma got another shellacking last night.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1349369746326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:55:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349370099364-125</Id><Topic><Title>Last Night's Debate's most Memorable Moment</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349369521187</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the most memorable line was ..."most people pick winners and losers ... you just pick losers" Mitt Romney</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1349370099364</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:01:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349370285120-126</Id><Topic><Title>Bully Pulpit</Title><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1349369746326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:55:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama will Always get a Shellacking when Speaking or Thinking without His Pacifier... Obama is an Affirmative Action Fool! Release you College Transcripts! Obama, What are you Hiding?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349370285120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:04:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349370368525-127</Id><Topic><Title>Remember Voters Are Fickle</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349369739223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:55:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Loser Like Obama, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349370368525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:06:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349370744721-128</Id><Topic><Title>Did Romney mislead or did he outright lie?</Title><Username>sallykohles</Username><Timestamp>1349362843860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A sample of Romneywhoppers: : When he claimed that "pre-existing conditions are covered under my plan." They're not. When he said that President Obama had "cut Medicare by $716 billion to pay for Obamacare." Obama didn't. When he denied proposing a $5 trillion tax cut. He did. When he said President Obama had "added almost as much to the federal debt as all the prior presidents combined." Not even close. When he resurrected "death panels." That was called "one of the biggest whoppers of the night." When he stated that half the green energy companies given stimulus funds had failed. Only if three out of nearly three dozen is half.?</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1349370744721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:12:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349370905516-129</Id><Topic><Title>Did Romney mislead or did he outright lie?</Title><Username>sallykohles</Username><Timestamp>1349362843860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are "Shocked" that you are Still in Denial... you will go through the phases and come back to normal tomorrow... Everyone needs to take it easy on Shocked... he is Hurting and Hurting bad!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349370905516</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:15:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349371089482-130</Id><Topic><Title>Did Romney mislead or did he outright lie?</Title><Username>sallykohles</Username><Timestamp>1349362843860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney whopper: "Up to 20 million people will lose their insurance as Obamacare goes into effect next year." Truth "Some workers may switch from their employer-provided health plans, according to the Congressional Budget Office, but that number is more likely to be closer to between 3 and 5 million per year between 2019 and 2022"</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1349371089482</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349371136371-131</Id><Topic><Title>Presidential Debate Won't Change Anyone's Mind</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349366504584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:01:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The OP is an idiot. Carter was way, way, way ahead of Reagan before the debates, and he didn't even do as bad as OVomit did and he got destroyed in 1980. Does anyone really want that empty suit who was about to throw up representing this country 4 more years?</Msg><Username>jjacksgeo</Username><Timestamp>1349371136371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:18:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349371165931-132</Id><Topic><Title>Last Night's Debate's most Memorable Moment</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349369521187</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you send jobs overseas you now have less or don`t have any taxes to pay, I would say that`s a pretty good break no matter how you spin it.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1349371165931</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:19:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349371207199-133</Id><Title>Obama the Old Jimmy Carter... Obama Makes Carter Look Awesome, per WaPo!</Title><Msg>... Romney, the New Reagan! Reagan was Trailing Peanuts before the First Debate!!!!!!!! And, we all Know How that Turned Out, eh? Heavy Drinking in Chicago!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349371207199</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:20:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349371252122-134</Id><Topic><Title>Did Romney mislead or did he outright lie?</Title><Username>sallykohles</Username><Timestamp>1349362843860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>iamaccom, speaking from experience? It took you four years to recover?</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1349371252122</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:20:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349371402131-135</Id><Topic><Title>Remember Voters Are Fickle</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349369739223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:55:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BHO Capital stock was downgraded by a host of analysts today from buy to sell!</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349371402131</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:23:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349371491208-136</Id><Title>Oh My: The Brutal Post-Debate Focus Group</Title><Msg>The only focus group you really needed to get the gist of how this debate turned out was the circus on MSNBC after it ended. The anchors ranged from morose to unhinged. But what about the rest of America? I flagged a few nuggets from the network's insta-polls last night, but let's circle back, shall we? First up is CNN, which polled 430 American adults (not likely, or even registered, voters) with a D+4 sample. So the deck was somewhat stacked to begin with. And yet: - 67 percent said Romney won the debate, 25 percent said the same of Obama; among independents it was 75-17 (!) - 82 percent said Romney performed better than they'd expected, 61 percent said Obama fell short of expectations. - Mitt Romney's favorable rating jumped to 56 percent. - Romney led on every issue polled: The economy by 12 points, healthcare by five, taxes by nine, and the deficit by 16. - Asked who would be the stronger leader, Mitt won 58-37; that's a 21-point lead over the sitting president. - Romney even won the "likeability" head-to-head, albeit by a single point. - By a 2-to-1 margin, voters said the debate made them more likely to vote for Romney than vice versa. Next we have CBS News, which only polled undecided voters -- 523 of them, to be precise: - Romney won, and it wasn't close: 46/22. - Asked if the debate improved respondents' impressions of the candidates, 56 percent said this was true of Romney. Just 13 percent said the same of Obama. - On issues: Romney +21 on the economy, +37 (!) on the deficit, +5 on taxes, +1 on energy. Obama maintained a small lead on Medicare, though Romney gained ten points on that issue overnight. - The percentage of undecideds who said they were now voting for Romney increased by 12 percent. Obama flat-lined. - Prior to the debate, these undecideds were asked if Romney (1) understands the needs of people like you, (2) has strong leadership qualities, (3) has made clear what he'd do if elected. They were asked the exact same questions after the debate. Here are the percentages of undecided voters answering "yes," pre/post debate: (1) 30/63. (2) 59/78. (3) 22/54. That first one is huge.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349371491208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:24:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349371781498-137</Id><Topic><Title>(CNN) -- The Etch a Sketch was in full effect at the first presidential debate in Denver on Wednesday night.</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349365660044</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:47:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The low-information, mostly stupid, baggers go for Romney's etch-a-sketch routine without fact checking his statements. But then facts and truth mean nothing to them..</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1349371781498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349372076576-138</Id><Topic><Title>Did Romney mislead or did he outright lie?</Title><Username>sallykohles</Username><Timestamp>1349362843860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Answer: Outright lie!</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1349372076576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:34:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349372278848-139</Id><Title>September defense deliveries</Title><Msg>one 373 P-8. Two Apache. Six Apache remanufactured. Two C-17's. Four Chinook. One chinook remanufactured. Four F18's. Eight Harpoons. One satellite. Three Ospray V22's.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1349372278848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349372448139-140</Id><Title>pathological liar</Title><Msg>like the business deals..you lie when you need to...you lie to get the deal to go thru..but this time it's the voters he's lying to..the lying governor......no one i know changes their vote based on a debate...obama serves the whole country and surely the working class..gov is there to keep a system where the super-rich remain so..and the racists can vote against the black community..against the guy who prevented a world economic depression and caught bin laden</Msg><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1349372448139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:40:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349372606868-141</Id><Title>5Deferment Dick Endorses Willard Mittford</Title><Msg>Romney cites an "independent" and "non-partisan" analysis validating his tax cuts for the rich.. And who might that source be? "New Romney/RNC TV ad cites as its source "independent, non-partisan" study ... from the American Enterprise Institute " Yeah, the same AEI that has Dick Cheney as boss. How very independent and non-partisan of them.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1349372606868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:43:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349372723725-142</Id><Topic><Title>5Deferment Dick Endorses Willard Mittford</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1349372606868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:43:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Willard only had four deferments. Nine deferments between these two super patriots.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1349372723725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:45:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349373353929-143</Id><Title>Rassmussen poll has it right</Title><Msg>Rasmussen Reports presidential tracking poll has President Obama up by 2% over Mitt Romney. Obama was at 49% compared to 47% for Romney. Third party candidates were at 1% while 3% of voters remain undecided. Rasmussen Reports released their presidential tracking poll this morning, Thursday, October 4, 2012.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349373353929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349373410317-144</Id><Title>Obama Supporters are Going Berserk</Title><Msg>.....the feel their food stamps slipping away.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349373410317</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:56:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349373590749-145</Id><Topic><Title>Rassmussen poll has it right</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349373353929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:55:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot to mention Rasmussen took most of the poll before the debate and the daily poll is a rolling 3 day average.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349373590749</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349373749844-146</Id><Topic><Title>Rassmussen poll has it right</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349373353929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:55:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope Taken after debate.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349373749844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:02:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349374203999-147</Id><Topic><Title>Rassmussen poll has it right</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349373353929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:55:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thursday, October 04, 2012 "The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Thursday shows President Obama attracting support from 49% of voters nationwide, while Mitt Romney earns the vote from 47%. One percent (1%) prefers some other candidate, and three percent (3%) are undecided. See daily tracking history. It is important to note, however, that most of the interviews for this survey were conducted before last night’s first presidential debate between Obama and Romney. The daily Presidential Trackng Poll is based on telephone interviews of 500 likely voters per night and reported on a three-day rolling average basis."</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349374203999</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:10:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349374541437-148</Id><Topic><Title>Rassmussen poll has it right</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349373353929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:55:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously a different article than I quoted. That information is not in the one I posted from. My profound apology</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349374541437</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:15:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349374864679-149</Id><Topic><Title>Rassmussen poll has it right</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349373353929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:55:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DIFFERENT ARTICLE Two national presidential polls and two statewide presidential polls are out today. In the Gallup presidential tracking poll President Obama leads by 4% over Mitt Romney. Obama was at 49% compared to 45% for Romney. Obama had a 1% decrease in support from the previous poll and Romney had a 1% increase in support from the previous poll. Third party candidates and undecided voters combined were at 6% nationally. The Gallup presidential tracking poll was released yesterday afternoon, Wednesday, October 3, 2012. Rasmussen Reports presidential tracking poll has President Obama up by 2% over Mitt Romney. Obama was at 49% compared to 47% for Romney. Third party candidates were at 1% while 3% of voters remain undecided. Rasmussen Reports released their presidential tracking poll this morning, Thursday, October 4, 2012. Rasmussen Reports also released a statewide presidential poll that has Mitt Romney up by 3% in the state of Missouri. Romney was at 49% compared to 46% for Obama. Third party candidates were at 2% and undecided voters were at 3% in Missouri. Rasmussen released the Missouri presidential poll this morning, Thursday, October 4, 2012. Quinnipiac conducted a presidential poll in the state of Connecticut that has President Obama ahead with a 12% lead. Obama was at 54% compared to 42% for Romney. Undecided voters were at 4% in Connecticut and Third party candidates were not mentioned by name in the Quinnipiac poll. Quinnipiac finished the Connecticut presidential poll on October 2, 2012. ..</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349374864679</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:21:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349374867791-150</Id><Topic><Title>CNN Poll... Romney Crushed Obama by Large Margin! Historic Numbers.</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349366192338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He Looked and Sounded like he could be a great president.</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349374867791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:21:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349375876632-151</Id><Topic><Title>Rassmussen poll has it right</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349373353929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:55:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liar "It is important to note, however, that most of the interviews for this survey were conducted before last night’s first presidential debate between Obama and Romney. The daily Presidential Trackng Poll is based on telephone interviews of 500 likely voters per night and reported on a three-day rolling average basis."</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349375876632</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:37:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349376134395-152</Id><Topic><Title>(CNN) -- The Etch a Sketch was in full effect at the first presidential debate in Denver on Wednesday night.</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349365660044</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:47:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Romney clearly won this debate. He was articulate, detailed, passionate, presidential. He clearly had full command of his material. And I didn't believe a single fracking word that came out of Flip's mouth!</Msg><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1349376134395</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349376404213-153</Id><Topic><Title>Rassmussen poll has it right</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349373353929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:55:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But, but, but, Rasmusson itself said that it has not polled since the debate -- so who am I to believe Rasmusson or you?? Let's see what Rasmusson says on Sunday when we have a full three days of post debate data from the company.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349376404213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:46:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349376667654-154</Id><Topic><Title>pathological liar</Title><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1349372448139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:40:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(obummer) caught bin laden?? You mean that he was in that helicopter in Pakistan??? Wow, I didn't know that! That must mean that O'Bummer is a closet navy seal -- like the other seals that were in the helicopter.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349376667654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:51:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349376829735-155</Id><Topic><Title>Michael Moore to Obama - 'This is what happens when u pick John Kerry as your debate coach'</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1349368995795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:43:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""If Romney keeps this up...Obama is going to vote for him!" Now that something about Barry's performance, doesn't it?</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349376829735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:53:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349377352315-156</Id><Topic><Title>Bring it on!</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1349375279540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 14:27:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is startinbg to make Joe look half way intelligent and Jimmah Kaatah look like a winner.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349377352315</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:02:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349377565756-157</Id><Title>As president Romney will work to lower the number of poor people......</Title><Msg>.....not the number of rich people. This will surely anger Democrats.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349377565756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:06:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349377746669-158</Id><Topic><Title>pathological liar</Title><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1349372448139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:40:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama lies almost every time he opens his mouth. Now he's lying about the Ambassador and other Americans killed because he denied them the security they requested.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349377746669</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:09:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349377822778-159</Id><Topic><Title>As president Romney will work to lower the number of poor people......</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349377565756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:06:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he could just be lying too which is most likely and more folks will get poor while the already rich get richer, last time we tried the approach Romney is talking we had the largest amount of wealth ever go from the middle class into the hands of the super rich.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1349377822778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:10:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349377933485-160</Id><Title>Obama Lied After People Died</Title><Msg>Suddenly, the President's new clothes seem embarrassingly transparent. The contention relentlessly promoted by Team Obama, to the effect that the Commander-in-Chief's performance with respect to foreign policy and national security was simply unassailable, is being seen for what it is: an utter fraud.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349377933485</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:12:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349378154473-161</Id><Title>AARP to Obama: Don’t mention us again</Title><Msg>Search the subject title for the article. While a health insurance who wants always more clients, it is wanting to appear neutral. In truth its a left wing bunch that uses the profits to that end. Definitely misleads it elderly subscribers.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1349378154473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:15:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349378285408-162</Id><Topic><Title>As president Romney will work to lower the number of poor people......</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349377565756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:06:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>last time we tried the approach Romney is talking we had the largest amount of wealth ever go from the middle class into the hands of the super rich.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349378285408</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:18:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349378389250-163</Id><Topic><Title>As president Romney will work to lower the number of poor people......</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349377565756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:06:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that happened under Clinton u #$%$</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349378389250</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:19:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349378490940-164</Id><Title>Gas prices in CA hit record highs...</Title><Msg>.....You can think of it as a tax Obama has put on the mediocre class.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349378490940</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:21:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349378753505-165</Id><Topic><Title>AARP to Obama: Don’t mention us again</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1349378154473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:15:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THAT ISN'T EXACTLY WHAT THEY SAID Below is the statement AARP released on this evening’s Presidential debate: Denver, CO—Earlier this evening the Presidential candidates discussed AARP, Social Security and Medicare during the first Presidential debate of the 2012 general election. AARP, a sponsor of activities at all four of the 2012 Presidential and Vice Presidential debates, released the following statement in response. AARP Senior Vice President John Hishta said: “We’re grateful that this evening the candidates engaged in a more robust conversation with regard to Medicare. We’re also pleased Social Security was included in tonight’s debate. But America’s voters deserve more than talking points and 30-second sound bites. Our members and older Americans want to hear how the candidates would strengthen Social Security, Medicare, and financial security, and we encourage the candidates to offer more specifics about their plans before Election Day. “Across party lines, older voters say that getting more information on the candidates’ plans on these crucial economic security programs will help them determine their vote. We know that our members vote, and they want the candidates to tell them how they’ll fix Medicare and Social Security for them, their kids and their grandkids. “Earlier this year, we launched You’ve Earned a Say, a national conversation on the future of Social Security and Medicare, to engage people in communities across the country so they have the pros and cons of proposals currently on the table in Washington and on the campaign trail. “While we respect the rights of each campaign to make its case to voters, AARP has never consented to the use of its name by any candidate or political campaign. AARP is a nonpartisan organization and we do not endorse political candidates nor coordinate with any candidate or political party. “We remain focused on providing voters with balanced information on where candidates stand on the key issues, so they can make their own decisions on Election Day. For more information on where the candidates stand on premium support and other Medicare topics discussed tonight, see AARP’s Voters’ Guides at</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349378753505</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349379128563-166</Id><Title>747 GE engine failure due to factory engine assembly error</Title><Msg>From WSJ: General Electric Co. said the failure of an aircraft engine on a Boeing Co. 747-8 in Shanghai was caused by an error in the assembly of the lower pressure turbine and the company plans a one-time, hour-long round of inspections on the engine fleet.GE's so-called service bulletin calls for inspections of the low pressure turbines to check that the stage-one nozzles are properly installed. The nozzle directs air into the rotating blades of the turbine. "The initial findings indicate that a (low pressure turbine) stage-one nozzle may have been improperly assembled and became dislodged," a spokeswoman for the National Transportation Safety Board said. "Efforts are continuing to determine the reason for these observations."</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1349379128563</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:32:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349379295095-167</Id><Topic><Title>Bully Pulpit</Title><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1349369746326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:55:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spot on, spot on..</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1349379295095</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349379751956-168</Id><Topic><Title>AARP to Obama: Don’t mention us again</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1349378154473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:15:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Search this for the real story on BO and AARP. ( Strassel: The Love Song of AARP and Obama). If Obama had done real well, AARP would have thought it was all okay.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1349379751956</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:42:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349380140251-169</Id><Title>Lib Roaches</Title><Msg>and the President were crushed beyond recognition after Romney took the President to the cleaners. Heard Rosie O'Donnell locked herself in the toilet last night after the debates and wouldn't come out.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1349380140251</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349380259326-170</Id><Topic><Title>Bully Pulpit</Title><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1349369746326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 12:55:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney, release your taxes for more than 2 years what are you hiding? you are the spoiled son of a millionaire that has been running for office for 20 years. doofus</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349380259326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:50:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349381587471-171</Id><Topic><Title>Lib Roaches</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1349380140251</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:49:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is all made for TV drama, they will have Obama as the big winner of the next debate, they have commercials to sell and this stuff sells lots of commercials. could you imagine if it was lop sided one way or the other that would not sell too much commercial time.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1349381587471</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:13:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349383055976-172</Id><Title>Eastwood was Right.......</Title><Msg>.....Romney was debating an empty chair last night.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349383055976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:37:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349383195225-173</Id><Topic><Title>747 GE engine failure due to factory engine assembly error</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1349379128563</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 15:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for all the updates....</Msg><Username>goddlo</Username><Timestamp>1349383195225</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:39:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349383262866-174</Id><Title>Rmoney May Get a 2 point Bump</Title><Msg>Unfortunately for him he needs five to pull ahead.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1349383262866</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:41:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349383502687-175</Id><Topic><Title>Eastwood was Right.......</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349383055976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly... that is What the American People saw Last Night! Incompetence without a Pacifier.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349383502687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:45:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349383764300-176</Id><Title>Obama Doesn't Need this Kind of Help from Algore</Title><Msg>Gore, the True Air Head Speaks and People Laugh at Him! Gore Blames Altitude for Obama's Debate Woes 11:20 AM, OCT 4, 2012 • BY DANIEL HALPERSingle PagePrintLarger TextSmaller TextAlerts Former Vice President Al Gore, reacting to the debate: "Obama arrived in Denver at 2 p.m. today — just a few hours before the debate started," Gore said on his network, Current. "Romney did his debate prep in Denver. When you go to 5,000 feet, and you only have a few hours to adjust, I don't know..." "The president had an off night," a pundit on the liberal network said. No #$%$@</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349383764300</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:49:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349383787274-177</Id><Title>Did hubris catch up with Team Obama?</Title><Msg>As the Republican primary process wound down and Mitt Romney emerged as the likely candidate in spring of 2012, President Obama was itching to take him on, according to Glenn Thrush’s inside look at the Obama campaign, “Obama’s Last Stand.” How to take Romney on was another story, as the campaign waffled between pegging Romney as a man with “no core” or a “rotten core.” But the issue wasn’t just one of a strategy disagreement, as Thrush explained: “Inside the White House, Romney was such an object of ridicule that it was hard to take him seriously, difficult to narrow the mass of contempt into a single, coherent narrative for not electing the presumptive GOP nominee.” Was that the attitude President Obama brought to his three days of debate prep in Nevada? Obama certainly seemed to have trouble Wednesday “narrowing the mass of contempt into a single, coherent narrative for not electing the presumptive GOP nominee.” He meandered and stuttered in lengthy answers the media is generous in calling “professorial.” He sounded unprepared, pulling the same lines from his stump speeches again and again. He reached for straw men Mitt Romney had already dismantled.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349383787274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:49:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349383889404-178</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney May Get a 2 point Bump</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1349383262866</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:41:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to forget that this IS a zero sum game -- when Romney gains two points, Obama loses two points -- a swing of four points for you mathematically impaired dumbocrats.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349383889404</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:51:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349384377594-179</Id><Topic><Title>Did hubris catch up with Team Obama?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349383787274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:49:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Looks Like Jimmy Carter... Carter was ahead Before the Debates... That is What has Obama and his Followers Scared to Death! They See it Slipping Sliding Away. Poor Dik is Beside Himself! Stale Popcorn and Flat Beer......</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349384377594</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:59:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349384420970-180</Id><Topic><Title>Nate Silver's Five Thirty-Eight Forecast: Obama 320, Romney 218</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349384222217</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep Digging... Still in Denial, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349384420970</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:00:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349384550877-181</Id><Title>Biden Says Obama Wants to Raise Taxes by a Trillion Dollars... Great!</Title><Msg>Biden: 'Yes, We Do' Want to Raise Taxes By a Trillion Dollars 3:53 PM, OCT 4, 2012 • BY DANIEL HALPERSingle PagePrintLarger TextSmaller TextAlerts Vice President Joe Biden, speaking earlier today in Iowa said, "Yes, we do" want to raise taxes by a trillion dollars: "On top of the trillions of dollars of spending that we have already cut, we’re gonna ask – yes – we’re gonna ask the wealthy to pay more," said Biden. "My heart breaks, come on man. You know the phrase they always use? Obama and Biden want to raise taxes by a trillion dollars. Guess what? Yes we do in one regard. We want to let that trillion dollar tax cut expire so the middle class doesn’t have to bear the burden of all that money going to the super wealthy. That’s not a tax raise, that’s called fairness where I come from."</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349384550877</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:02:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349384738538-182</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney May Get a 2 point Bump</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1349383262866</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:41:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh! So there was a 100% decideds? The only zero sum is in your feeble GOP propaganda mindless fantasy.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1349384738538</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349384917141-183</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney May Get a 2 point Bump</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1349383262866</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:41:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch the polls by Sunday -- Romney up, and O'Bummer down that is unless you are telling me that ALL of the undecideds went for Romney last night.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349384917141</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:08:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349385053793-184</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Will Win Says 100% Historically Accurate Model</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349351031467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 07:43:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>-bump-</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349385053793</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:10:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349385226240-185</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney May Get a 2 point Bump</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1349383262866</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:41:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to offshore gambling site, Pinnacle Sports, Obama’s odds of winning the election declined to about 73 percent after the debate from around 80 percent beforehand.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1349385226240</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349385677620-186</Id><Topic><Title>(CNN) -- The Etch a Sketch was in full effect at the first presidential debate in Denver on Wednesday night.</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349365660044</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:47:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Last night was confirmation of the comment made last summer by Romney's campaign manager - "Etch a Sketch." Shake it up and change your positions after having taking a hard right line throughout the primaries. .</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1349385677620</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:21:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349385696906-187</Id><Topic><Title>Eastwood was Right.......</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349383055976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without a telepromter he is screwed...................ks</Msg><Username>kingslmon6</Username><Timestamp>1349385696906</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:21:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349385963478-188</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney May Get a 2 point Bump</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1349383262866</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:41:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to Intrade, Obama's odds declined from about 80% yesterday afternoon to about 65% this morning.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349385963478</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:26:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349386012918-189</Id><Topic><Title>Eastwood was Right.......</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349383055976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And with a teleprompter America is skrewed</Msg><Username>tminusten</Username><Timestamp>1349386012918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:26:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349386037736-190</Id><Topic><Title>pathological liar</Title><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1349372448139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:40:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney campaigned in the primaries as a "severe conservative." Last night he was a Rockefeller Republican. By the last debate he' ll be a Democrat. Mitt Romney lied. And when his lies were corrected, he denied they were lies.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1349386037736</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349386065444-191</Id><Title>Obama: ‘Social Security is Structurally Sound;’ Trustees: ‘Unfunded Obligation … Is $8.6T'</Title><Msg>Now you know why the economy is in the shape it's in......Obama doesn't have a clue how much a $trillion dollars is.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349386065444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:27:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349386129355-192</Id><Title>The "prevent defense"--a popular President playing not to lose--is a lousy debate strategy</Title><Msg>In the first debate, Obama's strategy seems to have been designed around the theory that the debate could only hurt him, not help him. As a result, it hurt him badly. What Americans saw on stage was not a "President" and a "Challenger." What they were two men, one of whom was speaking much more confidently, passionately, and compellingly than the other. If being President was supposed to confer some special aura on Obama, that aura evaporated as soon as Romney won the first question. And for the rest of the night, what Americans saw was a man they normally think of as being a super-inspiring orator and leader seeming hesitant, inarticulate, and mystifyingly rattled by a good salesman. story on Yahoo...</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349386129355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349386158077-193</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney May Get a 2 point Bump</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1349383262866</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:41:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...and Rmoney's odds of winning?</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1349386158077</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:29:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349386245516-194</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney May Get a 2 point Bump</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1349383262866</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:41:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why they imporved by he same 15% -- as I said earlier IT IS a zero sum game.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349386245516</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:30:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349386322162-195</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: ‘Social Security is Structurally Sound;’ Trustees: ‘Unfunded Obligation … Is $8.6T'</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349386065444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but he does seem to know what 6 tillion dollars is -- since that is how much he has added to the deficit.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349386322162</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:32:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349386514330-196</Id><Title>Obama Lost the debate because</Title><Msg>It was his wedding anniversary and he couldn't get Moo-Shell's caboose out of his mind. He had other plans but Moo-Shell grounded him for the evening.</Msg><Username>tminusten</Username><Timestamp>1349386514330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:35:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349386678040-197</Id><Topic><Title>Did hubris catch up with Team Obama?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349383787274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 16:49:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In other words: Bum Bummer brought his teddy bear to a gun fight!</Msg><Username>tminusten</Username><Timestamp>1349386678040</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349386685588-198</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Will Win Says 100% Historically Accurate Model</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349351031467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 07:43:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NEVER??? It picked Lincoln over Douglas? Wilson over Roosevelt? Or just Obama over McClain?? In any event - just because it's been accurate so far doesn't mean it's a for sure lock going forward.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1349386685588</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 17:38:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349390809938-199</Id><Title>Romney had the edge in the debate last night.</Title><Msg>Romney was well prepared with facts and proposals. President Obama's responses seemed to come from an automated menu. President Obama seemed to lack energy and enthusiasm for the debate. He seemed preoccupied. Maybe President Obama would rather be someplace else celebrating his 20th wedding anniversary with Michelle rather than debating Romney. In my opinion, the Obama Administration's handling of the tragedy in Bengazy is a real failure. Congressman Peter King is working day and night with the FBI and NYPD to keep America, and especially New York City, safe from another deadly terrorist attack. It's time the Obama Administration accepted responsibility for protecting Americans at home and abroad. The recent 9/11 attacks were well planned, and not the reaction to a video. Finally Mrs. Clinton, Ms. Rice and President Obama admitted that the 9/11 attacks on U.S. Embassies were well planned. President Obama shouldn't treat the American people like dupes! Not very nice presidential conduct!</Msg><Username>maramwp</Username><Timestamp>1349390809938</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 18:46:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349391454640-200</Id><Topic><Title>Romney had the edge in the debate last night.</Title><Username>maramwp</Username><Timestamp>1349390809938</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 18:46:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Willard's already starting to walk back a bunch of what he said. Nothing surprising there, as he has taken both sides of most major issues already.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1349391454640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 18:57:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349392875324-201</Id><Title>Europeans and bankers shaking in their boots</Title><Msg>Romney would let 5 big banks fail!, and he would return the world to free market capitalism. The EU would be content to leave bank rates at 0% for the century. The EU is salivating for Obama to win and impose socialism on America. Prime Minister Cameron ridiculed Mitt Romney about the Utah Winter Olympics saying that Romney managed the Olympics in the "middle of nowhere", but the UK is managing the Olympics in London, a world-class city. Well, it turns out that British Prime Minister Cameron got stumped by the meaning of Magna Carta. On his visit to the "Dave Letterman Show" he was asked the question: "What does Magna Carta mean?" Cameron was stumped. He couldn't even make a crude translation like any 4th grader might have made, "Big Letter". Europeans aren't so smart, and they shouldn't look down on Americans. By the way, Magna Carta means Great Charter.</Msg><Username>maramwp</Username><Timestamp>1349392875324</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:21:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349394714110-202</Id><Title>Obama's Excuse for losing the debate</Title><Msg>That the "other" Mitt Romney showed up last night. Or was it that the "real" Obama showed up last night?</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349394714110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:51:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349394962121-203</Id><Title>Progress on Boeing laser</Title><Msg>Boeing will continue development and testing of a truck-mounted laser weapon system on the heels of a three-year $16.18 million follow-on contract agreement with U.S. Army Space and Missile Defense Command, company officials announced. The truck-mounted system is designed to provide increased ability to counter rockets, artillery, mortars and threats from unmanned aircraft. Boeing has been working with ASMDC to integrate its High Energy Laser Mobile Demonstrator system onto a tactical truck, with the work done at the company's Huntsville facility. The truck is currently in Albuquerque, NM, for installation of a 10-kilowatt solid-state laser, system checks and field testing.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1349394962121</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:56:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349395653556-204</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Excuse for losing the debate</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349394714110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:51:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do these people have doubles?</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349395653556</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 20:07:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349396159811-205</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama has done it again</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1349394039104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:40:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You guys are sick,this cat is a looser ....by by Obama, thats how it must be or this country is up a creek................ks</Msg><Username>kingslmon6</Username><Timestamp>1349396159811</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 20:15:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349404391254-206</Id><Topic><Title>Romney had the edge in the debate last night.</Title><Username>maramwp</Username><Timestamp>1349390809938</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 18:46:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DimBummer had great eye contact with the cockroaches scurrying around his feet last night. But then he has great eye contact with the cockroaches in his cabinet and his all the czar cockroaches he has appointed.</Msg><Username>sevencarco</Username><Timestamp>1349404391254</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 22:33:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349407628363-207</Id><Title>Time to Put Libs on Suicide Watch</Title><Msg>I almost feel sorry for them -- not really -- you elected an empty suit whose brain doesn't work at high altitude according to ALGORE</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1349407628363</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 23:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349408424254-208</Id><Topic><Title>Time to Put Libs on Suicide Watch</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1349407628363</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 23:27:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are the ones they are waiting for.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1349408424254</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 23:40:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>