<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348290389796-1</Id><Topic><Title>CNN is now reporting that Amb. Stevens was specifically targeted for death by Al Qaeda</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1348239407819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:56:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holder probably was the one giving them the RPGs, more Fast &amp; Furious hardware</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1348290389796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 01:06:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348292343920-2</Id><Topic><Title>Ambassador Chris Stevens was killed because he was gay</Title><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1348207516131</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 02:05:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No I'm not publishing it but others are including The Libyan Free Press - check it out. The youtube excuse just doesn't pass the laugh test, it was added back on July 2nd. Be he straight, gay or in between, the guy was a US ambassador and obama should be dusting off the waterboard as opposed to saying we are sorry.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1348292343920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 01:39:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348308831637-3</Id><Topic><Title>CNN is now reporting that Amb. Stevens was specifically targeted for death by Al Qaeda</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1348239407819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:56:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahhhhhhh --------- But why is Obama and NATO arming and working with AlQaeda in the first place ? google it</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1348308831637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 06:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348323226664-4</Id><Title>Likes the job, hates the work that comes with it</Title><Msg>Obama exposed his weakness when he said that you cannot change Washington from the inside. It showed t hat when the going gets rough, he is not tough enough to work with t he legislatures on both sides of the aisle. Assuming he gets the post once more but his party remains deadlock,will he be able to move the country forward like he is promising to do or will it be déjà vu all over again?</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1348323226664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348324122934-5</Id><Title>1.9 B P-8 contract</Title><Msg>Boeing Co (BA.N) has won a $1.9 billion contract to build 11 more P-8 maritime surveillance planes for the U.S. Navy, the U.S. Defense Department said Friday. About three-quarters of the work on the P-8A Poseidon multi-mission maritime aircraft will be performed in Seattle, Washington under the U.S. Navy contract, the Pentagon said in its daily contract digest. This is the third batch of low-rate, production planes bought by the Navy, bringing the total number of P-8 planes under contract to 24, out of a total of 117 that the Navy plans to buy overall</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348324122934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:28:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348326243160-6</Id><Topic><Title>Likes the job, hates the work that comes with it</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1348323226664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"According to the 2011 and 2012 digests of Obama’s public schedule from the U.S. Government Printing Office, he attended 198 of his daily intelligence briefings between April 14, 2011 (the day he hosted the first fundraiser of his reelection campaign) and August 24, 2012 (the last day included in the latest GPO digest). By August 14, 2012, Obama had already reached 203 fundraising events since launching his reelection campaign, slightly more than the number of intelligence briefings he had attended during that time period."" More fundraising than doing the job......telling.</Msg><Username>commishfree1</Username><Timestamp>1348326243160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:04:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348330737888-7</Id><Topic><Title>Republicon fascists have moved to the right of Adolf</Title><Username>republicanfascists</Username><Timestamp>1348254839715</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:13:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe Satan and Beelzebub are certainly leftists. You're right though, O is no liberal. He's just a political operative who enjoys the power and perks. He believes in nothing. His formative years were spent in the home of a general working in the dictatorship running Indonesia, until it was overthrown by the people. Then he moved to Hawaii to live with his grandparents. No more servants for him after that. A background like that is probably not going to make a person into a liberal, but it's good training for a political operative.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1348330737888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 12:18:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348332075843-8</Id><Topic><Title>Likes the job, hates the work that comes with it</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1348323226664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Running the country on auto pilot with no budget in sight for past three years,no credible energy and economic policy,believes in the role of government as a redistrutor of wealth,soft foreign policy leading from behind playing the role of psychologist instead of the leader of the most powerful country in the world,spending money without regard to the printing press non-stop,trapping able bodied and able minded Americans into the welfare system permanently by removing work requirement making them unproductive.This is when little knowledge gets dangerous.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1348332075843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 12:41:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348332892883-9</Id><Title>Direction this country is heading</Title><Msg>Into the fiscal cliff. A smart car with a dumb driver.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1348332892883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 12:54:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348335188258-10</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing races to the bottom !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1347979750530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:49:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zosimomaximo, must be forgetting to put me on egnor there, I see you message , would it show up if you really put me on ignor. I am so sorry you can ot make 75% yar to date on apple and lost almost 5% on your Boeing stock, but i told you many years ago to buy apple and I am suggesting that you reconsider your opinion on boeing, get out now at a loss and move to a stock that makes 26% net compared to Boeing which claims 5.7% net but the killer for boeing is massive development costs ont he 747-8 , 8 billion, 787 20-30 billion, and pensions owe 2 billion,with more costs to come on the delayed 777X, the 767tanker fixed cost the delayed "customer will wait" 737MAX while apple has zero debt and has billions inthe bank , it is real simple your simple if you can not figure out that apple is the palce to be and Boeing is the place to be away from , now go out and buy some apple and stop trying to kill the messenger your unable to do that</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348335188258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:33:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348338965835-11</Id><Title>AMERICA WAKE UP BEFORE IT"S TOO LATE</Title><Msg>AND VOTE BIG EARS OUT IN NOV.....</Msg><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1348338965835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 14:36:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348348043538-12</Id><Topic><Title>NEW POLL : ROMNEY % 53, OBAMA % 41</Title><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1348259423501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:30:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As hard as they try the Liberal Poll Takers can't make the American People believe that Obama is actually leading Romney considering all the harm that Obama has brought to America in 4 short years! Incentive for Republicans AND Independents to vote this horrible person out of office is extremely urgent! The American People will have NO MORE of this lying traitorous evil man! May God strike this traitor down in his footsteps before unimaginable harm is brought to our cherished nation!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1348348043538</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 17:07:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348354389164-13</Id><Title>AMBASSADOR OR CIA OPERATIVE UR GVT AT WORK</Title><Msg>Nice to know that should you be either- UR gubbermint will always stand behind you - WAY behind Former CIA operative Edwin Wilson dies at 84 Edwin P. Wilson, a former CIA operative who was branded a traitor and convicted of shipping arms to Libya but whose conviction was overturned after he served 22 years in prison, has died. He was 84. The Associated Press SEATTLE — Edwin P. Wilson, a former CIA operative who was branded a traitor and convicted of shipping arms to Libya but whose conviction was overturned after he served 22 years in prison, has died. He was 84. Wilson died Sept. 10 in Seattle from complications from a heart valve replacement surgery, said Craig Emmick, a director at Columbia Funeral Home in Seattle. Wilson who set up front companies abroad for the CIA and posed as a rich American businessman was convicted in 1983 for shipping 20 tons of C-4 plastic explosives to Libya. At trial, he said he did it to ingratiate himself with the Libyan government at the CIA's request. A federal judge threw out that conviction in 2003, saying the government failed to correct information about Wilson's service to the CIA that it admitted internally was false. Wilson had been sentenced to 52 years in prison for selling arms and explosives to Libya in the late 1970s and early 1980s, and for other crimes. He served 22 years in prison, mostly in solitary confinement, until he was released in 2004. He then moved to Edmonds, Wash., north of Seattle, to live with his brother. While in prison, he sought to prove his innocence by using the Freedom of Information Act to request government documents. . . . goes on.. ..</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1348354389164</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:53:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348356316754-14</Id><Title>Dreamliner engine inspections ordered after cracks found</Title><Msg>FAA orders immediate inspection before next flight all 787 GE engines. Search with post title for the KOMO article.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1348356316754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:25:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348366002817-15</Id><Topic><Title>NEW POLL : ROMNEY % 53, OBAMA % 41</Title><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1348259423501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:30:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of a true evil, here's sdmiller4747's take on things from earlier: 20-Aug-2012 "What will it take to get blacks not to vote for Obama? . . . Is there anything that blacks cherish more than money, drugs, and white women? Maybe tickets to next year's Superbowl! sdmiller4747"</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1348366002817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 22:06:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348366594994-16</Id><Topic><Title>NEW POLL : ROMNEY % 53, OBAMA % 41</Title><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1348259423501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:30:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As citizens, we should actually worry about sdmiller, or more specifically, his family. Many thousands of Americans will commit suicide when the black guy is re-elected.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1348366594994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 22:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348370020900-17</Id><Topic><Title>NEW POLL : ROMNEY % 53, OBAMA % 41</Title><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1348259423501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:30:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MAOBANANA TO WIN reelection 33%</Msg><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1348370020900</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>