<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-18"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355807153905-1</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Raises Dividend 10 Percent and Resumes $3.6 Billion Share Repurchase Program</Title><Username>retiredbill</Username><Timestamp>1355799156984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 21:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill, go Boeing? Boeing shareholders are buying the stock , so that means if you are a stakeholder , your money is being wasted to buy back failed Boeing stock, so executives can take a bonus on earnings per share which is how executive pay is determined. You sir, are paying for excessive executive pay, while the 787 is 3 years late and 30 billion over budget and your share value has been flat for 3 years and is predicted to stay flat for 9 more years until 2021. Bill, until the 787 makes a profit, you are Better off with a nasdaq ETF. if this is your best stock, BA is up about 1% for the year and nasdaq is up over 15% year to date. As t the 10% dividend increase well the tax now is 15% on dividends and scheduled to go to about 50% next year so subtract the increase in dividend tax and the 15% loss to stock price appreciation for the year to a nasdaq average or just go with BAC up 98% this year.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355807153905</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 00:05:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355809919816-2</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Raises Dividend 10 Percent and Resumes $3.6 Billion Share Repurchase Program</Title><Username>retiredbill</Username><Timestamp>1355799156984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 21:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing management has made some mistakes, but they are not the only ones to blame for the delay of the 787. Just like every other company in the world, Boeing had to endure the economic crisis starting in 2008, which really hurt a lot of their contractors and customers. Boeing came through the crisis better than a lot of other companies and has been able to work with a lot of their customers while they get back on their feet. Boeing has a surplus of cash, with which they are rewarding shareholders who have invested in them. It sounds like the buyback will really help you disgruntled people.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1355809919816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 00:51:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355812431722-3</Id><Topic><Title>Newtown Is A Game Changer</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355771067496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 14:04:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>=You are definitely sick at your core! = badolt is truly as a master of irony.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1355812431722</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 01:33:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355813017007-4</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Raises Dividend 10 Percent and Resumes $3.6 Billion Share Repurchase Program</Title><Username>retiredbill</Username><Timestamp>1355799156984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 21:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>albucucu, you just painted me with a "disgruntled people" smear , What I said was a stock buy back is done due to failure, when SteveJobs ran Apple the second time Apple did not have to buy back stock because it went up over 600% in 10 years until cancer forced his retirement. You did say Boeing managment made mistakes, one huge mistake and many smaller ones. outsourcing work was the major mistake, going with Condit,Stonecipher,McNerney, Mike Sears were other mistakes. In 2008 Apple made a lot of money in 2012 Bank of America did much better than Boeing, I am a stock market investor , not a disgruntled person. You are a Boeing enthusiast on a advertisement effort to sell the sizzle of the steak not the steak. Boeing stock price will have problems for 9 more years on what I posted go read it. The shareholder will not get a 98% increaselike going with BAC,this year. BTW I posted about BAC a few weeks ago when the cup and handle formed and said if you knew how to read a stock chart you could make money.Same thing with JRCC when Romney was in the run up and a dirty energy guy, JRCC made any investor who followed me in 4 weeks over 100%. substitue your name calling for stock investor. Next point with all that free money I am guessing SPEEA will not miss this point you just posted, with all that shareholder money going to pump up the earnings, if not the stock price then the Union will be striking for their share of the excessive money that Boeing managment has to spend on their bonus plan.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355813017007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 01:43:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355826270537-5</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Shuts Down</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355790195449</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 19:23:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"party line" Are you a drug addict?</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1355826270537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 05:24:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355828351504-6</Id><Topic><Title>Do you get bounus miles when a the 787 makes an emergency landing?</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1355745119808</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 06:51:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>falmouthharbor, you said," since the Engineers inspect every plane" ? and once more foulmouthharbor your wrong, par for the coarse. Engineers design the plane and contractor engineers design the parts, but the engineers seldom inspect every plane, production procedures review is not done by design engineers. Your grasp of Boeing procedures, engineering, and the function of parts contractors iand how Boeing works is flawed.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355828351504</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 05:59:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355829785805-7</Id><Title>This board is like watching The View</Title><Msg>Every day it's the same #$%$ running their mouths about things they know nothing about. The only question is which one is little Chrissy, Whoopi or Barbara?</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1355829785805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 06:23:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355829956931-8</Id><Title>Liberal control freaks get all emotional and then</Title><Msg>try to come up with solutions that mirror the policies of Stalin, Hitler and Mao.</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1355829956931</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 06:25:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355830367812-9</Id><Topic><Title>On ROOT CAUSEs</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1355781417163</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 16:56:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you know the root cause of your issues and are you treating it anyway?</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1355830367812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 06:32:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355830503463-10</Id><Topic><Title>Ban Assault Weapons</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1355757368954</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 10:16:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like you could be either a very uniformed person or a Nazi.</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1355830503463</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 06:35:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355830672626-11</Id><Topic><Title>This board is like watching The View</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1355829785805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 06:23:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He looks like Whoopi but sounds like Barbara or is it the other way around.</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1355830672626</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 06:37:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355834750153-12</Id><Topic><Title>26 children were killed........AT WACO ...by our own Government !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355792236179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 19:57:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, the early CNN video (before it was scrubbed) does show flame throwers. ... Investigation by Congress of WACO shows incendiaries were used. Sonny Bono (before he was mysteriously murdered) stated the same thing while questioning Janet Reno. What we also know for sure is FBI Agents machine gunned women and children while they were trying to escape. Americans better WAKEUP...or WACO !!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355834750153</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 07:45:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355835778333-13</Id><Topic><Title>26 children were killed........AT WACO ...by our own Government !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355792236179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 19:57:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you have any proof that Bono was murdered?</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1355835778333</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 08:02:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355835914322-14</Id><Topic><Title>26 children were killed........AT WACO ...by our own Government !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355792236179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 19:57:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...Sonny Bono (before he was mysteriously murdered)" Oh really? "Bono died on January 5, 1998 of injuries sustained when he hit a tree while skiing on the Nevada side of Heavenly Ski Resort near South Lake Tahoe, California.[16] [...] Great place to ski by the way.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1355835914322</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 08:05:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355836416198-15</Id><Topic><Title>26 children were killed........AT WACO ...by our own Government !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355792236179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 19:57:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can google it yourself but this is one of many people who believe the same thing....Also note the last paragraph "Fletcher also got his hands on Bono's autopsy, which until that time, had been basically secreted away. The autopsy report, as was discussed in the Globe article, apparently revealed that the damage to Bono was caused by something much worse than simply skiing into a tree. According to the report, Bono had "a black eye, swollen lips, bloody nose, bruised jaw, and two upper teeth knocked out, all on the right side of the head," as well as several "fractures in a 'central depressed region' on the right side of Bono's skull and found 'some of the fractured bone pieces have a curved configuration.'" Fletcher believed these fractures were the result of being beaten with a gun. He was so convinced that he convened a panel to investigate the fractures. Fletcher believes the wounds indicate that Bono was held from behind by one man while another wailed on his face with a pistol. Fletcher also noted that Bono suffered minimal brain damage, which goes against the concept of running into a tree. He also noted that "Bono had no smashed ribs, broken knees, neck trauma - or hand injuries that would have come from trying to ward off a collision with a tree." In addition, the tell-tale signs that he would have run into a tree were not present, such as "bark impressions on his face and plant debris on his clothes." Furthermore, Bono's ski goggles were not smashed in as would have been expected. Finally, the investigator added that "the back of Bono's clothes were soaked with blood - but he had no back wounds." His assessment was that "the blood must have come from someone else, perhaps when Sonny valiantly fought back and hit one of his assailants." Kenny's Sideshow blogger David Martin postulates that Bono's possible murder may have resulted from the Branch Davidian-ATF conflict led by then-Attorney General Janet Reno. He believes that Bono's tough criticism of Reno during federal hearings about her approval to use CS gas on children at the Davidian compound was excessive and irresponsible at best, and may have led to retaliation by the United States government."</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355836416198</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 08:13:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355841066288-16</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal control freaks get all emotional and then</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1355829956931</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 06:25:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do we have to put up with the psychotic ravings of a gun nutt like analgonqueer? especially since he is an illegal alien</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1355841066288</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:31:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355841478074-17</Id><Topic><Title>How come S.W.I.T.Z.E.R.L.A.N.D doesnt have any gun problems ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355787473799</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 18:37:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>keep it up sonney- you are eventually going to find yourself in the insane asylum- but cheer up your paranoid schizophrenia is treatable-</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1355841478074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:37:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355841823195-18</Id><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Msg>This won't get much coverage in liberal media. With one shot, an off-duty sheriff’s deputy took down a gunman who attempted to opened fire at a crowded movie theater lobby during a late night showing of “The Hobbit” in San Antonio, WOAI reports. Police say a gunman, identified as Jesus Manuel Garcia, chased patrons from the nearby China Garden Restaurant into the lobby of the Santikos Mayan 14 movie theater at around 9 p.m. on Sunday. Garcia, an employee of the restaurant, reportedly walked in the establishment looking for a woman.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355842779118-19</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Raises Dividend 10 Percent and Resumes $3.6 Billion Share Repurchase Program</Title><Username>retiredbill</Username><Timestamp>1355799156984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 21:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know of any credible source who is predicting flat for 9 years....last 9 years boeing is up 100%.</Msg><Username>wredde</Username><Timestamp>1355842779118</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355842781406-20</Id><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Msg>And yet those who study mass shootings say they are not becoming more common. "There is no pattern, there is no increase," says criminologist James Allen Fox of Boston's Northeastern University, who has been studying the subject since the 1980s, spurred by a rash of mass shootings in post offices. The random mass shootings that get the most media attention are the rarest, Fox says. Most people who die of bullet wounds knew the identity of their killer. Society moves on, he says, because of our ability to distance ourselves from the horror of the day, and because people believe that these tragedies are "one of the unfortunate prices we pay for our freedoms." Grant Duwe, a criminologist with the Minnesota Department of Corrections who has written a history of mass murders in America, said that while mass shootings rose between the 1960s and the 1990s, they actually dropped in the 2000s. And mass killings actually reached their peak in 1929, according to his data. He estimates that there were 32 in the 1980s, 42 in the 1990s and 26 in the first decade of the century.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355843065382-21</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did the people who are giving my post the "thumbs down" wish this guy had been successful in killing a bunch of people? I thought people would be happy to know that armed citizens can prevent mass murder.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355843065382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 10:04:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355843534857-22</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Raises Dividend 10 Percent and Resumes $3.6 Billion Share Repurchase Program</Title><Username>retiredbill</Username><Timestamp>1355799156984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 21:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill we will be flying soon$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1355843534857</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 10:12:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355843598113-23</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you think it should be legal for private citizens to own assault rifles and if your answer is yes - then the question is why?</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1355843598113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 10:13:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355844594672-24</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IMO the left contributes greatly to the problem. Their notion that "accept the fact you are stupid", and you need big govt to take care of you. Forget all of those responsibilities to family and community, you are not capable of accepting that responsiblity, and need some freedoms taken away, and bigger and bigger govt. Govt officials increase in numbers all of them getting rich at the expense of the tax payer whose taxes continue to rise. Presently the workin stiff works about 4 mo. a year for the govt. And when finincial crisis' occur because of big govt?...divorce, job loss, financial ruin all contribute to acts of violence.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355844594672</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 10:29:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355844796017-25</Id><Topic><Title>This board is like watching The View</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1355829785805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 06:23:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Q; what kinda man watches The View A; an alan girly man</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355844796017</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 10:33:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355845627973-26</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As usual, you RWNJs have no arguments that are not lies and/or the product of over-active fantasies.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1355845627973</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 10:47:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355846240810-27</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmm... the post I replied to has already been deleted.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1355846240810</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 10:57:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355846325589-28</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Something that is fact, not fantacy. TEN POOREST CITIES City, State, % of People Below the Poverty Level 1. Detroit , MI 32.5% 2. Buffalo , NY 29.9% 3. Cincinnati , OH 27.8% 4. Cleveland , OH 27.0% 5. Miami , FL 26.9% 5. St. Louis , MO 26.8% 7. El Paso , TX 26.4% 8. Milwaukee , WI 26.2% 9. Philadelphia , PA 25.1% 10. Newark , NJ 24.2% What do the top ten cities(over 250,000 population) with the highest poverty rate all have in common? Detroit, MI (1st) hasn't elected a Republican mayor since 1961. Buffalo , NY (2nd) hasn't elected a Republican mayor since 1954. Cincinnati , OH (3rd) hasn't elected a Republican mayor since 1984. Cleveland , OH (4th) hasn't elected a Republican mayor since 1989. Miami , FL (5th) has never had a Republican mayor. St. Louis , MO (6th) hasn't elected a Republican mayor since 1949. El Paso , TX (7th) has never had a Republican mayor. Milwaukee , WI (8th) hasn't elected a Republican mayor since 1908. Philadelphia , PA (9th) hasn't elected a Republican mayor since 1952. Newark , NJ (10th) hasn't elected a Republican mayor since 1907.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355846325589</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 10:58:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355846605027-29</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now, Given the fact that libs have overwhelmingly implimented liberal policy in these degenerating cities what levels of crime involving firearms would you expect there to be?</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355846605027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 11:03:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355846701116-30</Id><Topic><Title>Do you get bounus miles when a the 787 makes an emergency landing?</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1355745119808</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 06:51:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When the plane is being assembled an engineer has to sign off on EVERYTHING. That is why something wrong with this bird. Looks like a Ford Pinto with wings.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1355846701116</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 11:05:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355848127649-31</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>t's being reported by a number of sources that the mind of Nancy Lanza, the mother of the mass killer, was convinced that the world would end soon and that she and her son could survive (fend, hunt, collect wood) in the ruins of this civilization...Last night it also emerged Nancy was a member of the Doomsday Preppers movement, which believes people should prepare for end of the world.Her former sister-in-law Marsha said she had turned her home ‘into a fortress’. She added: ‘Nancy had a survivalist philosophy which is why she was stockpiling guns. She had them for defense. ‘She was stockpiling food. She grew up on a farm in New Hampshire. She was skilled with guns. We talked about preppers and preparing for the economy collapsing.’ It's now beginning to look like the mother was also not mentally stable. If she was indeed a "prepper," she was indeed in need of help herself. You know neoliberal ideology has reached a state of perfection/insanity when some of its subjects see the collapse of the economy as a natural disaster (volcanoes erupting, an astroid slamming into the planet, a towering tsunami). But the closest thing to an apocalypse did not come to her but came from her distorted mind.</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355848127649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 11:28:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355848540127-32</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I looked at the data nd the charts to form my opinion rather than rely on one horrific incident and responding in an emotional manner. So I am very much open to any data that you can offer.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355848540127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 11:35:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355849075104-33</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget Al Gore's "we're all going to die from global warming" end of the world preaching that is filling the heads of children, childlike adults and "preppers".</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355849075104</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 11:44:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355849200960-34</Id><Topic><Title>B.O. Sheds Crocodile Tears, Prepares Ground For Assault On 2nd Amendment</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1355715506104</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 22:38:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, It's hard for me to understand how anyone can take prez O seriously. The guy is just a pure weasel in every way. A war criminal who won the Nobel Peace Prize, very nicely done! A man with a very questionable past, adopted son of a general in a third world military dictatorship, elected to 2 terms as prez of the united states, incredible! I admit he is very, very good at hearding the sheep.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1355849200960</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 11:46:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355849468726-35</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Raises Dividend 10 Percent and Resumes $3.6 Billion Share Repurchase Program</Title><Username>retiredbill</Username><Timestamp>1355799156984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 21:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not all companies reach high points at the same time. Boeing often has upturns while much of the economy is struggling. Just because aapl had a couple strong qtrs at a certain point in time doesn't mean other companies are failures because they didn't mimic that. As far as my blurting out for all to know about the cash surplus, that has been public knowledge for a year or so. Certainly some of the first to realize it would have been SPEEA. At best, that knowledge will only gain them a fair contract, not a bloated one. Some of the unions had been working with the company in acknowledgement of poor economic times and are now due for some reward. How about aapl now? Down about $200 from the high.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1355849468726</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 11:51:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355849550002-36</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just try to imagine a young man -- say 20 -- who is already maybe half a bubble off, being forced to listen to someone 24 hours a day, 7 days a week spouting stuff like "our president isn't an American," "FEMA will slap us all in concentration camps," "it doesn't matter who you vote for because the game is rigged," and "we need to stockpile ammo and food and water putifiers for the day the revolution comes." It would be like having Spartacus trying to drive us all over the edge on this board. Except we don't have to HEAR it.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1355849550002</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 11:52:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355849687947-37</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like a female version of spartakook.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1355849687947</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 11:54:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355849719147-38</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh great, mass shootings aren't becoming more common. Fantastic. Then I guess we don't have to do anything to make them less common.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1355849719147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 11:55:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355849908397-39</Id><Topic><Title>Real Minutemen, Rise Up!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355840253133</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for posting that, hooz. (I apologize but I can't bring myself to say "he shoots ... " in response to anything in these threads.)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1355849908397</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 11:58:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355850457542-40</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Infestor, I can agree with you that armed citizens with legal carry weapons could have stopped several shootings from allowing an unhindered attack on the unarmed patrons. Throwing popcorn and Pepsi cups at an ambush / attack is usually not a successful tactic.</Msg><Username>manferfish</Username><Timestamp>1355850457542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:07:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355850596728-41</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually they have been becoming less common according to the data and there is no correlation between automatic weapons and mass shootings. So there is no rational argument for banning automatic weapons as that will not do anything to make these shootings less common. Why don't we try to look at what can make these incidences less common?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355850596728</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:09:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355850710084-42</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Infestor doesn't seem to want to answer my question, so I'll ask it of you. Do you think it should be legal for private citizens to own assault rifles and if your answer is yes - then the question is why?</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1355850710084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:11:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355851583798-43</Id><Title>Obama Makes Third Fiscal Cliff Offer</Title><Msg>and the republicons reject it? WASHINGTON -- The White House made a new offer to House Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio) on Monday to avoid the so-called fiscal cliff. The proposal matches the amount of spending cuts with revenue-raisers, calls for two stimulus measures and seeks an avoidance of a debt limit fight for the next two years. The White House has moved off of its initial and second revenue demands of $1.6 trillion and $1.4 trillion respectively. As of now, the president would be fine raising $1.2 trillion in revenue. He also is no longer insisting that taxes increase on families with income above $250,000. Instead, he is calling for a permanent extension of the Bush tax cuts for incomes of less than $400,000. To meet the $1.2 trillion revenue goals, the White House proposal calls for limiting the tax benefit of itemized deductions to 28 percent for taxpayers. It would return the estate tax to 2009 parameters, which would mean that estates worth more than $3.5 million would be taxed at a 45 percent rate. The compromise on revenue may be difficult for some in the president's own party to swallow, though few would have imagined the White House scoring such a victory just one year ago. The spending cuts in the new proposal could be a harder sale. In his latest offer to Boehner, the president proposes $800 billion in savings, including $290 billion in interest savings, $100 billion in defense cuts, and $130 billion in savings that would come from an adjustment to the inflation index for Social Security benefits. The administration insisted that there would be "protections for most-vulnerable populations" perhaps by indexing the changes so that they don't affect those with low-income. The president has refused to give in on another Republican demand: that he gradually raise the eligibility age for Medicare from 65 to 67. There is, however, $400 billion in health care savings included in his offer. Additional components of the proposal include language that would call for the fast track pursuit of corporate and individual tax reform as well as "spending reform." The White House proposal calls for a permanent extension of certain tax extenders (which ones weren't made entirely clear) and the alternative minimum tax. The payroll tax cut passed two years ago would, under this proposal, be allowed to lapse without an apparent replacement -– a major blow for progressive economists, who argue that the economy is too fragile to take such a hit. The president is, however, pursuing some provisions that would make his base pleased. His plan calls for an extension of unemployment benefits -- set to expire at the end of this year -– and money for infrastructure spending. How much money is unclear, though the president's first offer asked for $50 billion. Finally, he is demanding that the nation's debt limit be increased for two years. He will continue to allow Congress the right to periodically vote not to raise the ceiling, but he would grant himself veto power over those votes. That may be too much for Boehner to swallow. In his last offer, the speaker signaled comfort with a yearlong extension of the debt ceiling, but nothing more. An administration official said that this was not the president's "final offer," but one that the White House viewed as a legitimate halfway point between the two sides. The official noted that the president already agreed to a trillion dollars in spending cuts as part of the first debt-ceiling standoff. When adding those figures to this plan, one gets to $3.4 trillion in deficit reduction. When considering war savings, that number goes up to well over $4 trillion over a 10-year period. Boehner's spokesman Michael Steel emailed this response: Any movement away from the unrealistic offers the President has made previously is a step in the right direction, but a proposal that includes $1.3 trillion in revenue for only $930 billion in spending cuts cannot be considered balanced. We hope to continue discussions with the President so we can reach an agreement that is truly balanced and begins to solve our spending problem.</Msg><Username>ordinarybob25x18</Username><Timestamp>1355851583798</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:26:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355851680055-44</Id><Topic><Title>BA is too beneficial to miss right now. Discover why!</Title><Username>mannpeter35</Username><Timestamp>1355831097680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 06:44:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In hopes that it is as consistent as it looks.</Msg><Username>bleroy70</Username><Timestamp>1355851680055</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:28:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355851980112-45</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody has said we are all going to die from man-made global climate change, rather it's effects are evident and continuing, and future generations are in for drmatic changes if not checked. Pales in compoarison to Dr. Strangelove: Or How I Learned To Love The Bomb duck and cover drills in the first grade</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355851980112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:33:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355852041511-46</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I get the feeling that this needs to be Fact Checked adding number of victims and/or child victims</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355852041511</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:34:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355852502821-47</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Precisely. Why not do things to make them less common. I agree that banning SEMIautomatic weapons is not the answer. (I am a little wary of your statement about "automatic weapons" because fully automatic weapons SHOULD be kept out of civilain hands -- as well as the parts that can convert a semiautomatic weapon to fully automatic. (However, I told my liberal newsroom colleagues at the time of the Stockton shooting many years ago that a firm five-round mag limit would make even fully automatic weapons less dangerous -- you'd have to reload after a second or two.) I am not enough of a firearms devotee to be terribly specific (I originally asked that we start an open-minded discussion rather than suggest specific rules) but I would say: * we could limit magazine capacity to 5-10 rounds. It could be done without grandfathering in the existing hi-caps by requiring that those be blocked to 5-10 rounds. I've heard it said that magazines are eayt to fabricate, but if deranged 20-year-olds wanted to try it, it seems like possession of one could be made illegal, subjecting the ownerf to fine and confiscation. (In Oregon, if you violated certain hunting regulations, your hunting firearm could be confiscated, so there IS precendent for such a limit to the 2nd Amendment Yes, there would be a bootleg after-market set up by some talented metal workers, but we could fine them heavilly when we tracked them down and we ARE talking about making mass shootings LESS COMMON, right. * we could ban armor-piercing and frangible bullets, which would protect first-responders some. * we could require psychological testing before purchasing a firearm. (Bring a note from your doctor. :-) * we could institute a WORKING background-check apparatus. The govt, has a no-fly list, why not a no-buy list? * we should figure out a way to more tightly control firearms dealers, including those at gun shows and after-market dealers (as in "used" guns, if you will) A BAN on so-called "assault rifles" would be problematic -- including defining precisely what an "assault rifle" is. But such a law has a certain appeal. The last time we had an assault rifle ban, it included a list of specific firearms, which only resulted in a lot of weapons getting new model numbers by their manufacturers. But I'm open-minded about considering a ban if some bright person can figure out a reasonable way to draft one.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1355852502821</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:41:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355852733862-48</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Makes Third Fiscal Cliff Offer</Title><Username>ordinarybob25x18</Username><Timestamp>1355851583798</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:26:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fiscal cliff fiscal cliff fiscal cliff talks (to the tune of jingle bells rock) showing and blowing tons of hot air the fiscal cliff hop has got to stop it's the right time to talk the night away fiscal cliff talk is a swell time to talk the night away in a partisan way Giddy-up fiscal cliff horse lift up your head and talk around the clock Mix and a-mingle your fiscal cliff mouth That's the fiscal cliff That's the fiscal cliff That's the fiscal cliff talk</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355852733862</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:45:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355853355024-49</Id><Topic><Title>The NYT couldn't bury this one</Title><Username>cws2012wc</Username><Timestamp>1355772557053</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 14:29:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hoozik, you dik, tell me what it is you do not understand about wanting people to be hard working, self-sufficient, and less dependent on the govt do. You are just another libdem that ignores the damage (virtually destruction in reality) the democrat-liberal programs have inflicted on the black community. When over 70% of black children are born without an identified father because big govt programs have replaced the father, there is a problem. You call this remark “racism” -- I call it common sense reality. If the blacks and others want what the democrats are offering they will remain in the underclass for eternity. Of course the democrats have to have this voting underclass to maintain power. Don't forget that. Republican-conservative principles will eliminate this problem and all people that desire to be prosperous will have the opportunity to throw off the shackles of govt and become self-sufficient, independent, and feel good about themselves. But the libdems won’t feel good about THEMSELVES because they aren’t sincerely interested in solving problems in poor minority communities, and will certainly block any attempts to vote on any programs that are aimed at avoiding the dilemma faced by the minority community. VOTES are the only thing that really counts and to insist otherwise makes libdems look like bigger hypocrites than they already are.</Msg><Username>db0865</Username><Timestamp>1355853355024</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:55:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355853401580-50</Id><Title>#$%$ and his nutjob caucus propose to tax millionaires</Title><Msg>#$%$ and his nutjob caucus are in the process of throwing Grover under the bus. Their latest proposal is to raise taxes on millionaires. Willard is busy moving more cash to Switzerland.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1355853401580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:56:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355853612679-51</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$ and his nutjob caucus propose to tax millionaires</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1355853401580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:56:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Nutjob repub caucus say they will go along only if they can kill Social Security and Medicare.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1355853612679</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:00:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355854154416-52</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ah, the first grade duck and cover drills (same for nuclear attack and earthquakes) 1962, especially when jfk is on the tube in B&amp;W about soviet missiles going to cuba you live a couple of miles from a primary target, some neighbors are installing bomb shelters other neighbors including the metalugists family are prepping to 'bug-out' just in case a year later he will be dead and oswald (the patsy) will be shot on live t.v. and the Morris brothers busted outta Alcatraz with a spoon... and The beatles</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355854154416</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:09:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355854344011-53</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The morning after his debut as leading man, Gore pronounces this whole Sundance thing "a most excellent time." He is wearing earth tones again. He seems jolly . He brought Tipper and the kids. He is attending parties and posing for pictures with his fans and enjoying macaroni and cheese at the Discovery Channel soiree. He's palling around with Larry David of "Curb Your Enthusiasm," who says, "Al is a funny guy." But he is also a very serious guy who believes humans may have only 10 years left to save the planet from turning into a total frying pan. " "The heart of Gore’s message is that the way to prevent the potential catastrophe global warming represents is for each of us to make a personal commitment to bring about lasting change—in our own lives, our communities and the world. According to the science Gore presents so expertly, the world has 10 years or less to turn things around before it is too late. But Gore sees that as a reason for urgency, not despair." I can go on and on and on........................................................</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355854344011</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:12:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355854604093-54</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Man attempts to rob a bank and off-duty cop tackled him, the offender had a bag, and pocket knife the size of a nail-clipper probably won't get much RWNJ attention Zimmerman killed a youth with a gun about an iced-tea and bag of Skittles...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355854604093</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:16:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355854698246-55</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>armed citizens at elementary schools = naziism/fascism</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355854698246</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:18:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355854919600-56</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have no opinion and would have to research the issue further. This post was intended to show that armed citizens can be an effective deterent to mass murder attempts. Do you think that armed citizens can be an effective deterent to mass murder attempts?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355854919600</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:21:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355855183626-57</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Makes Third Fiscal Cliff Offer</Title><Username>ordinarybob25x18</Username><Timestamp>1355851583798</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 12:26:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The old adage buy on Dec. 31st when the big-boys lock-in thier profits and their lower tax rate might just apply this year</Msg><Username>green.onions23</Username><Timestamp>1355855183626</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:26:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355855321462-58</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A complex and often divisive (mostly from the uber right-wing) issue which needs some serious discussion.</Msg><Username>ordinarybob25x18</Username><Timestamp>1355855321462</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:28:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355855637331-59</Id><Title>ali_infesto, I can go on and on and on........................................................</Title><Msg>Re: Re: Re: Re: Re: Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say by ali_infesto.16 minutes ago.Permalink . "The morning after his debut as leading man, Gore pronounces this whole Sundance thing "a most excellent time." He is wearing earth tones again. He seems jolly . He brought Tipper and the kids. He is attending parties and posing for pictures with his fans and enjoying macaroni and cheese at the Discovery Channel soiree. He's palling around with Larry David of "Curb Your Enthusiasm," who says, "Al is a funny guy." But he is also a very serious guy who believes humans may have only 10 years left to save the planet from turning into a total frying pan. " "The heart of Gore’s message is that the way to prevent the potential catastrophe global warming represents is for each of us to make a personal commitment to bring about lasting change—in our own lives, our communities and the world. According to the science Gore presents so expertly, the world has 10 years or less to turn things around before it is too late. But Gore sees that as a reason for urgency, not despair." I can go on and on and on........................................................ _-_ ali_infesto is against personal responsibility and rational thought = no guns or ammo for him....</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355855637331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:33:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355855739922-60</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear Ali_infesto: Now you understand what I have to deal with on this demented BA message board each day. Socialists Liberals are such a confused group of individuals. Very pious and arrogant baloneyness. How can you reason with these individuals when they give Madonna 'woman of the year' status?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1355855739922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:35:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355855852994-61</Id><Title>Boehner’s ‘fiscal cliff’ ‘Plan B’</Title><Msg>REJECTED by The White House it should read: White House rejects Boehner’s ‘fiscal cliff’ ‘Plan B’</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355855852994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:37:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355856322239-62</Id><Topic><Title>26 children were killed........AT WACO ...by our own Government !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355792236179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 19:57:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty is finally getting to the bottom of this. The New World Order Trilateral Commission Armand Hammer Arm And Hammer Rothschild Ruby Orly Taitz Ridge Republicans secretly stored Obama's Hawaiian Martian Kenyan birth certificate at David Koresh's compound in Waco. (Along with their world domination plan on how to make everybody buy Mars bars.)</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1355856322239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:45:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355856704045-63</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have no opinion yet on fully automatic arms as I have not researched it enough. In the case of CT, magazine capacity limits would not have changed the outcome so I'm not sold on it. Most of your suggestions have merit and should all be considered in looking for ways to reduce mass murder as well as murder and gun violence in general. What about the culture of violence being presented to young adults via music, games movies, etc? What about being more proactive in educating teens and adults to be more aware of traits we can already see in the youth that have already been involved in mass murders so that as a community we are better at identifying those who might be at higher risk for becoming a shooter and getting them counseling? These are just a few of the ideas being presented by people in my community where this is being discussed.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355856704045</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:51:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355857080690-64</Id><Topic><Title>Mass shootings are not growing in frequency, experts say</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355842781406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:59:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I have no opinion yet on fully automatic arms as I have not researched it enough. In the case of CT, magazine capacity limits would not have changed the outcome..." Of course the parameter of magazine capacity would have changed the outcome... in this case see Anakin Skywalker and the slaughtering(s) first of his mothers killers and then of all the younguns/young'uns just guessing</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355857080690</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:58:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355858107728-65</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...Jesus Garcia, 19, was at the Santikos Mayan Palace 14 at SW Military and I-35 on Sunday night. According to San Antonio police, he was upset over a recent breakup with his girlfriend. According to both police and deputies, Garcia called into his girlfriend's work at The China Garden restaurant and said he was going to shoot somebody. The restaurant is located outside the theater. At 9:30 p.m., Garcia walked in and chased all employees and patrons out of the restaurant before firing at an employee as he or she tried to flee, police said. It was not immediately known if the targeted employee was his girlfriend. Garcia continued to chase the employee from the restaurant to the parking lot outside the theater, firing his weapon along the way. San Antonio police said Garcia also took aim at an officer who pulled up in a marked cruiser. He missed the officer but shattered the officer's windshield. The chase went into the lobby of the Mayan 14 Theater, where off-duty Sheriff's Sgt. Lisa Castellano immediately sprang into action. The 13-year veteran quickly moved all patrons out of the lobby and into a secure location, deputies said. She then chased Garcia into the men's restroom, where she and another off-duty police officer cornered the suspect. Castellano then shot the suspect. “The actions she took prevented a lot more people from getting hurt or even worse, killed.” said Deputy Chief Manuel Longoria of the Bexar County Sheriff's Office. Garcia was taken to San Antonio Military Medical Center, where he underwent surgery on Monday. He was listed in critical condition. He faces charges of capital murder, aggravated assault with a deadly weapon on a police officer and aggravated assault with a deadly weapon. Investigators said there could be more charges once officers finish looking into all the details of what happened.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1355858107728</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 14:15:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355858153425-66</Id><Title>ATF..</Title><Msg>Firearms are classified with alcohol and tobacco. Is shooting a gun as addictive as drinking and smoking or because it is as deadly.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1355858153425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 14:15:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355858506543-67</Id><Topic><Title>Turning Medicare into a Voucher Program</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349796717254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" can make it up to $50,000 most days on Who Wants To Be A Billionaire without using a lifeline. ...those were the days, my friend</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355858506543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 14:21:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355859875759-68</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Raises Dividend 10 Percent and Resumes $3.6 Billion Share Repurchase Program</Title><Username>retiredbill</Username><Timestamp>1355799156984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 21:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing makes huge profits, give execs bonuses, boeing increases cost of medical to the workforce (boeing is self funded) boeing pockets the money - gives execs more bonuses. Now we have boeing buying back stock - which causes the price to go up so their money becomes more valued and thus gives execs more bonuses. All of this above goes on while the Engineering groups at Boeing whom have only been on strike twice in all the years of existence (once for a day, once for 40 days) are finally fed up with all the costs being implemented and lowering of salaries while the company is reaping all these huge profits. It makes no sense for Boeing to put up a wall for their own self greed. Customers want their planes, people are entitled to prosper and not have their ability to take care of their family reduced. Boeing is playing games and it doesn't matter if you're union or not. What matters is this is typical of business these days. Take back what you can, give nothing back - they're business pirates and if you don't like it you can walk the plank and take your chances. How much money does a exec need to live on? Do we not need the same?</Msg><Username>ev3044</Username><Timestamp>1355859875759</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 14:44:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355860448004-69</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see things differently. For me this board is entertainment and I'm not here for politics or to influence anyone, at least not intentionally. Once in awhile I'll get serious but I don't pretend to imagine that this is a forum for a meaningful exchange of ideas although once in awhile it can happen. I spend about 1/10 the time here as I used to as not much has evolved on the board and it is mostly boring. I try to avoid the bias of lumping all liberals into one group which keeps me from fitting in here as most everything is polarized, insult based and reduced to binary breakdown. Not much new thought or ideas can come from exchange bound by binary thinking. While I still hurl an insult or two, for me it is a sign of my own weakness in programming. I would suggest you take advantage of the beautiful area where you live and the wonderful generous people there and not take any of this BA board stuff seriously. also think about how much luckier you are than those that live in a #$%$ hole like New York or some other big ugly city. ;-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355860448004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 14:54:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355861021969-70</Id><Topic><Title>This board is like watching The View</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1355829785805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 06:23:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The View is Chrissy's favorite show.</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1355861021969</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:03:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355861066672-71</Id><Title>A DOWNGRADE IS COMING,</Title><Msg>BEWARE</Msg><Username>billionare_tk</Username><Timestamp>1355861066672</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:04:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355861233728-72</Id><Topic><Title>Real Minutemen, Rise Up!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355840253133</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and Chrissy should get a room, in Cuba or NK.</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1355861233728</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:07:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355861377639-73</Id><Topic><Title>Real Minutemen, Rise Up!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355840253133</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ooooooooooh, such drama from the BA board "Drama Queen"...........go cry yourself a river pantywaistboy.</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1355861377639</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:09:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355861581182-74</Id><Topic><Title>Wal-Mart pulls ad, #$%$ halts assault rifle sales</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355859613002</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 14:40:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i didnt know walmart sold assault rifles... must be made in china... !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355861581182</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:13:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355861676277-75</Id><Title>Hope this stays above thatball buster $75.00</Title><Msg>Lets get this over that $75 then we will go to $80.00!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1355861676277</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:14:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355861757978-76</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner’s ‘fiscal cliff’ ‘Plan B’</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355855852994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:37:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>White House rejects Boneheads ‘fiscal cliff’ ‘Plan B’ !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355861757978</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:15:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355861773511-77</Id><Topic><Title>A DOWNGRADE IS COMING,</Title><Username>billionare_tk</Username><Timestamp>1355861066672</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:04:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No way$$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1355861773511</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:16:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355861928768-78</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner’s ‘fiscal cliff’ ‘Plan B’</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355855852994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:37:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BOEHNER Plan "C" also REJECTED PLAN "D"</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355861928768</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:18:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355862006877-79</Id><Title>Obama to Reinstate Assault Weapons Ban</Title><Msg>The White House today indicated President Obama would support legislation that would reinstate the ban on certain types of semi-automatic rifles – known as “the assault weapons ban” — and may support other efforts, such as a proposal to ban high-capacity magazines, in the wake of the deadly massacre in Newtown, Conn. “He is actively supportive of, for example, Senator Feinstein’s stated intent to revive a piece of legislation that would reinstate the assault weapons ban,” White House press secretary Jay Carney told reporters, publicly backing for the first time legislation Feinstein plans to introduce. The White House had previously been reluctant to publicly named any specific action it might support in an effort to prevent future massacres.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355862006877</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:20:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355862034002-80</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to Reinstate Assault Weapons Ban</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355862006877</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:20:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its a good start !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355862034002</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:20:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355862232769-81</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to Reinstate Assault Weapons Ban</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355862006877</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:20:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>between 'private sellers' ? It is about as complex as the fiscal cliff talk...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355862232769</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:23:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355862290090-82</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to Reinstate Assault Weapons Ban</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355862006877</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:20:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you a real Nazi?</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1355862290090</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:24:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355862845434-83</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>= when they give Madonna 'woman of the year' status? = Fantasizing again, are we?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1355862845434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:34:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355862888646-84</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner’s ‘fiscal cliff’ ‘Plan B’</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355855852994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:37:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama';s/the White House offer was 'very generous' and included most of those in Congress except for...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355862888646</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:34:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355862979481-85</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I supported the ban on assault weapons and large capacity magazines and was against the repeal in 2004. Having said that I can not see that reimplementing the ban will accomplish anything and if these weapons are made illegal I cant see how it will be enforced and I wont cooperate (I own several pistols, hunting rifles and shotguns but no assault weapons.). This genie is out of the bottle and criminalizing mags or weapons will ensure that only criminals have them and cause huge problems trying to take them away from many Americans... A main issue about these shootings is that the weapons were not secured and were stolen to use in these attacks. Holding owners accountable for proper storage would be fair IMO... I would suggest that owning these weapons and the large capacity mags for home defense on private property and for use at proper events on ranges could be managed and still allow enforcement to regulate their carrying anywhere else. Displaying a concealed weapon is illegal, having more than three rounds for shotgun hunting is illegal, having more than 5 rounds for game hunting is illegal. Possesing a loaded weapon in a vehicle w/o a carry license or in a hunting area is illegal. My largest capacity .45 can hold 12 rounds so I would only need to give up two rounds if I wanted to carry it. For me that is reasonable for carry and my normal carry is a 1911 commander anyway (7+1). I believe that fast is fine but accuracy is Final . Like I said before, throwing popcorn at an attacker is a bad tactic. But overall I agree with you,Oldbuck, that there is little or no need for most to have a large capacity weapon.</Msg><Username>manferfish</Username><Timestamp>1355862979481</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:36:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355863375530-86</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to Reinstate Assault Weapons Ban</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355862006877</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:20:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i could be... but im certainly not a girly man watching the View !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355863375530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:42:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355863554427-87</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I dropped two hungarian Partridge this morning hunting with my bird dogs. Always envisioned being around when one of those chicken schit mass murders was about to open fire. Let me be within 15 yrds. and both barrels with my over/under would do the trick, and not hard hitting them.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355863554427</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:45:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355863833534-88</Id><Title>The Pumpmaster 760 bought at Walmart</Title><Msg>didn;t make into the car... "THEY SAID": IT WAS FOUND IN THE PARKING LOT the next day so I I went there 4 days later and it was true bought it for a grandchild, ya, know, for the skunk run away... we have no use for your kind around here... uh, YEAH....</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355863833534</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:50:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355864065912-89</Id><Topic><Title>The Pumpmaster 760 bought at Walmart</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355863833534</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:50:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>power source: pneumatic pump mechanism: bolt action caliber: .177 resevoir: 200 magazine: 187 clip:5 weight: 2 lb 12 oz more like 1 lb 2 oz suggested acceszories</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355864065912</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:54:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355864081564-90</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Problem right now is the definition of an "assault rifle" The public is being duped by some uninformed folks talking as if a SEMI-automatic is like an automatic. There are sporting arms, shotguns, that are semi-automatic firearms. I own several shotgun "auto-loaders"(semi-autos) What I would ban are the guns that will hold clips that contain 10 rounds and much more. That is the proposal by a congress person right now. And if you are a law abiding gun owner?...I'd bite the bullet, and want the AR-15's the AK stuff that looks like an Arnold Swartzenagger, gun them down weapon, and make them illegal. Forget that they are semi-autos just like my shotguns. Far too many in the public are not gun owners, and it scares the bejesus out of them to just look at them! They scare me to look at them, and I use a firearem to hunt with all the time! And the public?...many are hoarding those Uzi looking weapons.....sales of them are going through the roof! And in conclusion....gun ban regs will not work!...regardless of how it is written.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355864081564</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 15:54:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355864423240-91</Id><Title>Was the Connecticut shooter inspired by Anakin’s attack on the Jedi Temple?</Title><Msg>Is this far fetched? Consider that may movies have inspired re-makes and crimes. But only one movie comes to mind wherein the villain shows up in black and kills youngsters at a school – Star Wars, Episode 3. Jesse Ventura, son, Oliver Stone son, some hot black chick, and a camera: Conspiracy Theory on True TV : The government in sending brain-waves electromagnetically tin-foil hat(s)</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355864423240</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 16:00:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355865019032-92</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy Hook and Gun control</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1355683819655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 13:50:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So now its coming out. Shooter had unlimited and hypnotic attraction to violent video games. Its a bad mix, those videos and a troubled person. Those violent videos are bad with anyone.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1355865019032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 16:10:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355865942538-93</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Based on my reaction to most of your posts, I am amazed that what you are saying and what I have been saying are pretty much the same thing! As a former newsman and editor who ALWAYS had trouble making the young creampuffs in the newsroom understand the difference between semiautomatic and automatic weapons, you are right (and agree with me that the most dangerous thing we can do is let creampuffs draft the gun control laws) BUT educating people about the difference is the job of gun advocates. The'll never learn it from the know-nothings. Semiautomatic firearms are not the problem -- the ability to touch of 30 rounds without a letup is the problem.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1355865942538</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 16:25:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355866076365-94</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner’s ‘fiscal cliff’ ‘Plan B’</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355855852994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 13:37:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no 'Plan D' only plan C-</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355866076365</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 16:27:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355866279613-95</Id><Topic><Title>Real Minutemen, Rise Up!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355840253133</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're just not capable of an intelligent response, are you, floyd?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1355866279613</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 16:31:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355866428133-96</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura is a fraud</Title><Username>stoopidlefty</Username><Timestamp>1291593641000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2010-12-05 19:00:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as for the 'hot' black chick simmer-down</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355866428133</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 16:33:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355866488359-97</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Raises Dividend 10 Percent and Resumes $3.6 Billion Share Repurchase Program</Title><Username>retiredbill</Username><Timestamp>1355799156984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 21:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wreddle, the fact that you are not up on credible analysts and the prediction of 787 not breaking even until 2021 and Boeing stock being flat for the last 3 years is a sign you need to read up on Boeing. BTW you post a lot of vulgar language so not interested in your comments. for the board here is something I noticed"Help me get this straight. The institutional shareholders pressure Boeing to abandon the established airplane development model so it can be done on the cheap. The executives cook up a 787 outsourcing scheme to meet the demands of the shareholders and it nearly bankrupts the company. The $5 billion development cost of the 787 thus baloons to $25 billion and is years late. The engineering and technical community rolls up its sleeves and finds ways to save the program and increase rate on the 737 and 777 to keep the lights on. This finally begins to show benefits and turns the company around to post record profits. With the amazing feat accomplished, the shareholders and executives who created the problem get REWARDED while the company simultaneously proposes to cut the compensation package for the engineers and techs</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355866488359</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 16:34:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355866567091-98</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your account neglects to actually say he murdered anyone, Don.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1355866567091</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 16:36:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355866932121-99</Id><Topic><Title>26 children were killed........AT WACO ...by our own Government !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355792236179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 19:57:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Sonny Bono (before he was mysteriously murdered)" You always state things as a fact and then back it up with a sh*tload of the words "he believes what happened", "claims to have seen", or "a friend of a friend claims to have witnessed all of this." Those aren't facts.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1355866932121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 16:42:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355867391081-100</Id><Topic><Title>26 children were killed........AT WACO ...by our own Government !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355792236179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 19:57:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>duh sometimes sparty needs to be told tjhe truth repeatetedly don't turn your back on him he's too old to take a good #$%$whippin' and so am I IAM/SPEEA</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355867391081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 16:49:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355867639700-101</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>30 rounds... ?</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355867639700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 16:53:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355868079519-102</Id><Topic><Title>26 children were killed........AT WACO ...by our own Government !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355792236179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 19:57:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was born a crossfire hurricane met a bar-room quuen in Memphis but Let It Be -cool hand LUKE ? and John.....</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355868079519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 17:01:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355868765262-103</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Twinkie educating a Creampuff.........too funny!!!!!</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1355868765262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 17:12:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355868980859-104</Id><Title>God Bless President Obama!!</Title><Msg>Obama is the right man, for the right job, at the right time !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355868980859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 17:16:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355869151854-105</Id><Topic><Title>God Bless President Obama!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355868980859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 17:16:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and so does the sun god RA...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355869151854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 17:19:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355869749134-106</Id><Title>More than okay...</Title><Msg>shake it up fiscal cliff talk just one thing</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355869749134</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 17:29:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355871148873-107</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA is not IAM</Title><Username>gdogsdad</Username><Timestamp>1222107586000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2008-09-22 14:19:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>que ??? get over it...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355871148873</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 17:52:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355871498991-108</Id><Topic><Title>Man Attempts to Open Fire on Crowd at Movie Theater, Armed Off-Duty Sheriff’s Deputy Drops Him With One Bullet</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355841823195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absoluely they can. Most mass murders are chicken schits, and choose places they think there is no one that has a gun.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355871498991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 17:58:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355872107928-109</Id><Topic><Title>Union Bullying Activity Should Be a Hate Crime</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1355755044875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 09:37:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As the nation mourns the loss of what took place at Sandy Hook, we should all promote laws that promote good conduct and civilized behavior. Banning assault weapons in the hands of the public and making certain bullying activities hate crimes would be most meaningful.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1355872107928</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 18:08:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355873068608-110</Id><Title>BA 73.5</Title><Msg>if i had a dollar for every ace I've drawn Abilene alone would have the power to absolve many in the southern hemisphere got no chance of losing this time thnx in advance</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355873068608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 18:24:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355873750112-111</Id><Topic><Title>Union Bullying Activity Should Be a Hate Crime</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1355755044875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 09:37:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wouldn't it just be easier to ban demented idiots from posting their anti American Communist propaganda on stock message boards?</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1355873750112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 18:35:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355874181697-112</Id><Topic><Title>This board is like watching The View</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1355829785805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 06:23:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!!!!!</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1355874181697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 18:43:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355874343489-113</Id><Topic><Title>Union Bullying Activity Should Be a Hate Crime</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1355755044875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 09:37:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>anytime we win the battle of the bulge and we are in belgium is a good day for the losers</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355874343489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 18:45:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355876305223-114</Id><Topic><Title>Union Bullying Activity Should Be a Hate Crime</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1355755044875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 09:37:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The idea that laws can promote good conduct and civilized behavior is a bit naive. Especially given the numerous instances where those writing those laws are the most corrupt and uncivil.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355876305223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 19:18:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355876328673-115</Id><Title>I must admit The Patriots and their fans...</Title><Msg>in 34 degree rain and foggy mist at midnight put up a pretty good game the seahwaks ?</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355876328673</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 19:18:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355877162058-116</Id><Title>There are rumors floating out there about Cool Hand Luke, Let it Be...</Title><Msg>and the fiscal cliff TAKE NOTES Near the middle of Cool Hand Luke on the AMC was Let It Be... cha ching</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355877162058</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 19:32:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355877956788-117</Id><Topic><Title>I must admit The Patriots and their fans...</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355876328673</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 19:18:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is how we won the 1975 NBA Champioship 4 games to none v. well , we out-scored them Wasington Bulletts we out-hustled them we sank more free-throws and we just beat their #$%$ despite being the underdogs thnx to vincent al attles clifford ray george johnson rick berry keith wilkes and some other white guys ThaT is how we did it....</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355877956788</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 19:45:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355878801287-118</Id><Topic><Title>I must admit The Patriots and their fans...</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355876328673</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 19:18:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boston can have Geoge Johnson and three NBA titles was not my decision</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355878801287</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:00:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355880285030-119</Id><Topic><Title>26 children were killed........AT WACO ...by our own Government !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355792236179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 19:57:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Waco and Ruby Ridge should never have happened as well as others. They will forever be a blemish on the BATF and FBI. Yes, the timing of Sonny Bono's death was suspicious and could he be included as one link of a long chain of people who died known as Clinton's dead body trail? I think so. It happened all because of Clinton's war on guns. Looks like we're headed for another. Remember the first move Obama made similar to Clinton? Do a search for what has happened to the Michigan Militia.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355880285030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:24:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355880935897-120</Id><Title>THE LIGHT FROM OUR MOON</Title><Msg>A. IsSabout one second away B. IS one second away C. IS more than one second away and what do IS say about christians anyways</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355880935897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:35:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355881148856-121</Id><Topic><Title>THE LIGHT FROM OUR MOON</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355880935897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:35:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>W@hat do IS say let us ask IS</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355881148856</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:39:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355881438551-122</Id><Topic><Title>THE LIGHT FROM OUR MOON</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355880935897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:35:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I took the LSAT once for fun scored in the 110th bracket ....</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355881438551</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:43:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355881518209-123</Id><Topic><Title>THE LIGHT FROM OUR MOON</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355880935897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:35:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but there was a book on a shelf called Revelle</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355881518209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:45:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355881990187-124</Id><Topic><Title>Real Minutemen, Rise Up!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355840253133</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong YET AGAIN DIK..You are wrong with monotonous regularity. Lets hear what the actual writer of the second amendment had to say who the "Milita" was ok...not some left wing peter puffer. "I ask, sir, what is the militia? It is the whole people, except for a few public officials." — George Mason Dik...read carefully...thats the "WHOLE PEOPLE" not the Reserves and the National Guard....get it? Understand it...LIVE IT...now #$%$</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355881990187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:53:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355882177485-125</Id><Topic><Title>26 children were killed........AT WACO ...by our own Government !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355792236179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 19:57:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since you are so outraged about Newtown, where is your anger over the thousands of children killed by US drones in endless and illegal wars in the Middle East ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355882177485</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 20:56:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355882859074-126</Id><Topic><Title>Real Minutemen, Rise Up!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355840253133</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hooking comes naturally and part of the game -clifford ray</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355882859074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 21:07:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355884159963-127</Id><Topic><Title>Real Minutemen, Rise Up!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355840253133</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and so anyways hooking is still legal in the NBA with either hand above the waist and clear the lane to the hoop</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355884159963</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 21:29:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355884442670-128</Id><Topic><Title>This board is like watching The View</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1355829785805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 06:23:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its either that or posting here.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1355884442670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 21:34:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355885011954-129</Id><Title>Sipped tea with the future king and queen of England in St. Moritz</Title><Msg>and they didn't disaprove bcause.... -george harrisson</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355885011954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 21:43:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355885221677-130</Id><Topic><Title>This board is like watching The View</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1355829785805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 06:23:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll only watch the View if someone pays me to. Whoopi!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1355885221677</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 21:47:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355885527555-131</Id><Topic><Title>Sipped tea with the future king and queen of England in St. Moritz</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355885011954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 21:43:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>steam locomotive lake not frozen yet light snow HEAD skiis no pony tea is at 3 or4 4 P.M.* * we/us</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355885527555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 21:52:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355886337957-132</Id><Title>SEATAC airport security -</Title><Msg>make a wrong turn or try to go thru the wrong gate and all hell **SHOULD** BREAK LOOSE. But the following should make everyone feel safe- security is ON the Job ?? Police in SeaTac, Wash., are asking for help in tracking down thieves who they said stole $2 million worth of Nintendo Wii gaming consoles. The thieves managed to get away with 7,000 portable Wii gaming consoles after raiding a warehouse at SeaTac's Seattle Air Cargo. "I've been a cop for 28 years, and I've never seen anything like this," said Sgt. Cindy West. "This has come straight out of the movies." West explains the thieves drove two large diesel trucks into a Nintendo distribution site inside Seattle Air Cargo on Saturday evening around 9 o'clock. The thieves worked together to #$%$ up thousands of consoles by operating forklifts within the warehouse. Afterward, they loaded the Wiis into two 53-foot semi-truck trailers waiting outside the center along with another large box-truck van. By noon on Sunday, employees inside the business noticed empty Nintendo pallets on the warehouse floor and missing trucks. Police have no information on the thieves and say it's unclear just how many were inside the warehouse during the time of the heist. "If we don't get any tips ahead of time, it will be the selling of these consoles that will lead to their capture," said West. "It's gonna be pretty hard to hide 7,000 Wii game consoles."</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1355886337957</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 22:05:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355886479309-133</Id><Title>Life is Dangerous.....Ban Everything !</Title><Msg>Although the tragic, senseless murder of 20 children in a Connecticut shooting last Friday has been hyped to demonize the 2nd Amendment, is it possible to ban everything that causes children harm just because one sick person decides to commit a heinous crime? According to the National Center for Health Statistics, firearm homicides account for 2.7 child deaths (which includes all children under the age of 19) per 100,000 people here in America. To put this statistic in perspective, motor vehicle injuries account for nearly three times as many deaths at 8.1 children per 100,000. School bus accidents have killed whole classes of children in one fatal moment, but no one is clamoring to ban cars and school buses. The 2011 F.B.I. Uniform Crime Report actually shows that American violence is down across the country. Violent crimes such as murder have officially dropped for the 5th year in a row; the number of American murders is now the lowest it has been in more than 40 years. Children are the most fragile members of society. Unfortunately, history shows that gun bans do not stop mentally disturbed people from finding ways to commit school massacres. Private ownership of guns is banned in China and almost completely forbidden in Japan. Over the years, gruesome mass school stabbings have become a familiar happening in those countries. In June 2001, a former janitor diagnosed with numerous mental disorders entered an Osaka elementary school and began stabbing children and teachers. He ultimately killed eight children and seriously wounded another 13 before he could be stopped. The crime reportedly took place in only ten minutes. A Chinese man stabbed eight children to death as they were waiting for their parents outside an elementary school in March 2010. Elsewhere in China the following month, a man broke into a primary school and stabbed 18 students and a teacher. The very next day, the nation mourned when a man locked himself inside a kindergarten class with a knife and committed what was dubbed a copycat crime. Four more children died that day, and another 28 were wounded, including five left in critical condition. In fact, just hours before Adam Lanza broke in to Sandy Hook School in Newtown, Connecticut and opened fire, another man walked into a Chinese elementary school armed with a kitchen knife and stabbed 23 children, reportedly because he was “psychologically affected” by the Mayan calendar predicting the end of the world. Reports claim some of these children were found to have had their ears and fingers cut off. This terrible scene is starting to become a common occurrence. Knives are useful tools for many things, but the UK has banned carrying a knife in public “without good reason” unless the blade is three inches long or less. UK hospitals are not required to report knife-related crimes like gun crimes there, so there is no official reliable data on them. Still, should we ban knives here too, just in case? While the Connecticut massacre is horrible, it is not the worst school massacre in American history. In 1927, a man decided to bomb a school in Bath Township, Michigan, ultimately killing 38 elementary children before killing himself in the final of three explosions. In his insanity, the man was able to murder nearly 40 children at a school with a single weapon, no gun involved. Nearly 170 children died in the 1995 Oklahoma City bombing, as the Alfred P. Murrah Federal Building included an onsite daycare, again, no gun involved. Hands are used to set incendiary devices. Should hands be banned? According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, drowning is the leading cause of death for children under the age of four and the second-leading cause for children between ages one and 14. Water kills lots of children every year. Should we ban water? More people get fat with the aid of a fork and spoon than any other object, and obesity has been found to cause detrimental health effects that can lead to death. Should we ban eating utensils? After all, New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg, who has now launched a campaign against guns, has already banned large sugary drinks. The National Safety Council reports that more people die of intentional self-harm each year than either auto accidents or assault. Should we ban ourselves? Gun control has been shown to increase crime. Not to make light of the Connecticut tragedy, but where does it end? A 2006 Harvard study titled, “Would Banning Firearms Reduce Murder and Suicide?” exhaustively reviewed American and European firearm laws and found no correlation between gun ownership and violent gun crimes. Instead, evidence showed that murders and suicides were usually based upon social, economic, and cultural factors regardless of weapon availability. Data also showed that the nine European nations with the most private gun owners had three times fewer murders than the nine nations with the lowest rates of gun ownership. As for the blatant anti-gun agenda now being foisted upon us on nearly every news channel in the wake of the Sandy Hook School shooting, none of it is about keeping our children safe. It’s ultimately about taking away our rights and the government maintaining its power and control over the people. Like Rahm Emanuel said: “Never let a good crisis go to waste.”</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355886479309</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 22:07:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355886518948-134</Id><Topic><Title>This board is like watching The View</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1355829785805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 06:23:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The rumor is that Chrissy "switch hits" . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1355886518948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 22:08:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355886659572-135</Id><Topic><Title>Sipped tea with the future king and queen of England in St. Moritz</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355885011954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 21:43:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't need no pony to play frozedn lake polo those days as if they would show up anyways on the bunny slopes tea is at 3:00 on the spot and the St. Moritz tea-drinker crowd went crazy about LOVE</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355886659572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 22:10:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355886675719-136</Id><Topic><Title>Real Minutemen, Rise Up!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355840253133</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of "Minutemen" I have had dates with some "minute men" if you know my drift. But as long as they donate . . . .</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1355886675719</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 22:11:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355887130377-137</Id><Topic><Title>Real Minutemen, Rise Up!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355840253133</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 09:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dik, your lilly livered terds are never going to rise up for anything except a #$%$, or a hand out . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1355887130377</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 22:18:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355887508031-138</Id><Topic><Title>This board is like watching The View</Title><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1355829785805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 06:23:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The View is made up of bobble head Liberal parrot has-beens from the Liberal news/entertainment industry . It makes Chrissy pine for the fjords . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1355887508031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 22:25:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355888546082-139</Id><Topic><Title>Sipped tea with the future king and queen of England in St. Moritz</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355885011954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 21:43:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>skiing in st. moritz not sipping tea wishing for frozen 'lake with a pony' to play no too shabby considering the conditions in St. Moritz about LOVE*</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355888546082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 22:42:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355888617780-140</Id><Topic><Title>Sipped tea with the future king and queen of England in St. Moritz</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355885011954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 21:43:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>soschi 2014-16 alert ny 'people'....</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355888617780</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 22:43:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355888619656-141</Id><Topic><Title>Life is Dangerous.....Ban Everything !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355886479309</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 22:07:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK first to be banned is assault rifles...followed by Donald Trump....then idiots with laptops.....</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1355888619656</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 22:43:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355891388149-142</Id><Topic><Title>26 children were killed........AT WACO ...by our own Government !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355792236179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 19:57:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is an outlandish statement, and I bet you don't have a shred of proof to back it up. Even if you count rightful and wrongful shootings by law enforcement, you are got going to come anywhere near the other shootings, especially if you include the accidental shootings, like the guy who wore his gun to the theatre after the Colorado theatre shooting and accidentally shot himself in the #$%$.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1355891388149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 23:29:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355891500075-143</Id><Topic><Title>Sipped tea with the future king and queen of England in St. Moritz</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355885011954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 21:43:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the lake in st. mortiz was frozen and the future king of england sent out lady di .... and she coont skii wirth beans either</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355891500075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 23:31:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355891900610-144</Id><Title>Jamie Foxx "I kill all the white people" echos</Title><Msg>Just a few weeks ago vocal obama supporter Jamie Foxx joked on SNL about killing all white people and the libs thought it was great, just a joke, 1st amendment right, etc. Because libs have a real selective memory here is the quote: “I got a new movie coming out, Django, check it out…Django Unchained, I play a slave. How black is that? In the movie, I have to wear chains. How whack is that? But don’t be worried about it, because I get out [of] the chains, I save my wife, and I kill all the white people in the movie. How ​great is that? And how black is that?” Look at the pictures of the victims and tell me what color you see.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1355891900610</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 23:38:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355892513587-145</Id><Title>787 electrical failures</Title><Msg>BA Not very transparent on the issue, but another United 787 has come down with the same problem.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1355892513587</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 23:48:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355893089674-146</Id><Topic><Title>787 electrical failures</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1355892513587</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 23:48:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>un billet to ski... mont blanc everyday for a week M-F before dawn ode to joy give me a ticket or we/ussums gonna leave</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355893089674</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 23:58:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>