<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351574809355-1</Id><Topic><Title>remember Robert Reich telling Americans that high gas prices was due to GOP Speculators</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351571308026</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really it is because obama continued the Bush policy of trashing the dollar, Funny how the libs blame Bush for everything except that. Mitt said Uncle Ben has got to go and I agree</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1351574809355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 01:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351579095210-2</Id><Title>Start Drinking the "Kool-AID" LIBERALS ***Gallup: Romney UP 52%-45% in Early Voting</Title><Msg>There "IS" a GOD!!!!!!!!!!!!! **GALLUP SHOCK** Romney Up 52-45% Among Early Voters By John Nolte This Respected Election Forecasting Model Says Romney Wins By James Pethokoukis, American Enterprise Institute READ All About IT Where "The REAL News Matters"!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351579095210</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 02:38:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351585070682-3</Id><Topic><Title>Ann Coulter 'Retard' Remark Unconscionable</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351495806485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 03:30:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When did Obama do that? I recall he apologized for saying his bowling made him look like a spaz or something, but I believe you're spewing either your own pseudo-memories or an outright LIE about any reference to Palin's kid.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351585070682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 04:17:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351585202543-4</Id><Topic><Title>the truth on Obama</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351573290032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 01:01:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've imagined quite a few reasons to hate. And I do mean "imagined."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351585202543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 04:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351587537080-5</Id><Topic><Title>the truth on Obama</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351573290032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 01:01:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unmitigated CRAP. All of it.You're a gullible #$%$</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1351587537080</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 04:58:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351590133033-6</Id><Title>A Big Storm Requires Big Government</Title><Msg>Most Americans have never heard of the National Response Coordination Center, but they’re lucky it exists on days of lethal winds and flood tides. The center is the war room of the Federal Emergency Management Agency, where officials gather to decide where rescuers should go, where drinking water should be shipped, and how to assist hospitals that have to evacuate. Disaster coordination is one of the most vital functions of “big government,” which is why Mitt Romney wants to eliminate it. At a Republican primary debate last year, Mr. Romney was asked whether emergency management was a function that should be returned to the states. He not only agreed, he went further. “Absolutely,” he said. “Every time you have an occasion to take something from the federal government and send it back to the states, that’s the right direction. And if you can go even further and send it back to the private sector, that’s even better.” Mr. Romney not only believes that states acting independently can handle the response to a vast East Coast storm better than Washington, but that profit-making companies can do an even better job. He said it was “immoral” for the federal government to do all these things if it means increasing the debt. It’s an absurd notion, but it’s fully in line with decades of Republican resistance to federal emergency planning. FEMA, created by President Jimmy Carter, was elevated to cabinet rank in the Bill Clinton administration, but was then demoted by President George W. Bush, who neglected it, subsumed it into the Department of Homeland Security, and placed it in the control of political hacks. The disaster of Hurricane Katrina was just waiting to happen. The agency was put back in working order by President Obama, but ideology still blinds Republicans to its value. Many don’t like the idea of free aid for poor people, or they think people should pay for their bad decisions, which this week includes living on the East Coast. Over the last two years, Congressional Republicans have forced a 43 percent reduction in the primary FEMA grants that pay for disaster preparedness. Representatives Paul Ryan, Eric Cantor and other House Republicans have repeatedly tried to refuse FEMA’s budget requests when disasters are more expensive than predicted, or have demanded that other valuable programs be cut to pay for them. The Ryan budget, which Mr. Romney praised as “an excellent piece of work,” would result in severe cutbacks to the agency, as would the Republican-instigated sequester, which would cut disaster relief by 8.2 percent on top of earlier reductions. Does Mr. Romney really believe that financially strapped states would do a better job than a properly functioning federal agency? Who would make decisions about where to send federal aid? Or perhaps there would be no federal aid, and every state would bear the burden of billions of dollars in damages. After Mr. Romney’s 2011 remarks recirculated on Monday, his nervous campaign announced that he does not want to abolish FEMA, though he still believes states should be in charge of emergency management. Those in Hurricane Sandy’s path are fortunate that, for now, that ideology has not replaced sound policy. NYT editorial 30 Oct</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351590133033</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:42:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351590307928-7</Id><Topic><Title>Romney pins all his hopes</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351558641932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:57:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you are pinning all of YOUR hopes on YOUR failed propaganda mission. Go spam another board loon, nobody wants you here and take your aliases with you.</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1351590307928</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:45:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351590687649-8</Id><Topic><Title>the truth on Obama</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351573290032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 01:01:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hate has nothing to do with it loon. America, love it or leave it.</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1351590687649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:51:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351590782366-9</Id><Topic><Title>Romney pins all his hopes</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351558641932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:57:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>=nobody wants you here and take your aliases with you.= Speak for yourself, #$%$ You and you aliases are probably less wanted than any others around here.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351590782366</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351591985632-10</Id><Title>Romney Up 52 to 45 Per Gallup Early Voting Poll</Title><Msg>Obama Will Fall Hard!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351591985632</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 06:13:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351598518058-11</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Gets Knocked for Misleading Jeep Claims</Title><Username>the_loading_dock</Username><Timestamp>1351590797187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:53:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fiat Said Chrysler and Jeep, Bailed out by American Tax Payers, May Indeed Move Production Overseas... Perhaps to Italy or China. Loading man, Fiat, an Italian Company, Ownes Chrysler.... Romney was Right!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351598518058</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 08:01:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351599347738-12</Id><Topic><Title>the truth on Obama</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351573290032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 01:01:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America -- change it or lose it.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351599347738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 08:15:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351600776252-13</Id><Title>Dems Try to Blame George Bush for Storm</Title><Msg>Doesn't work.....people are getting wise to Obama and the Democrats and their Marxist policies.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1351600776252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 08:39:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351600995903-14</Id><Title>America is Rejecting Obama and His UnAmerican Marxist policies</Title><Msg>....he obviously hates the idea of individual liberty.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1351600995903</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 08:43:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351604693642-15</Id><Topic><Title>the truth on Obama</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351573290032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 01:01:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A record. That post gets "Liar Of The Year" award. More lies there than in any single post, even considering your target-rich history.</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1351604693642</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:44:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351605217553-16</Id><Topic><Title>A Big Storm Requires Big Government</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351590133033</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:42:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is the responsibility of smart people to bail out stupid people? If a state is so stupid as to continuously develop property on sinking land and areas that have been flooding for hundreds of years and continues to put up power lines next to trees why is that my problem? If you keep bailing out idiots you reward idiotic behavior. Why haven't these states done more to prevent storm vulnerability? If states choose to be wreckless why is that my problem?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351605217553</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351605442226-17</Id><Topic><Title>A Big Storm Requires Big Government</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351590133033</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:42:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the country followed the gospel according to Willard we should have 50 presidentsl. And we should privatize the governors and make them CEOs answerable only to wealthy fat cat boards of directors selected by people who have the most money in that state.. Come to think of it that is pretty close to the way it is in most red states now.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1351605442226</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351605642244-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Looking Presidential, Christie Praising Obama, Romney Getting Slammed...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351604312275</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:38:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As Christie Said, Now is No Time for Politics... Liberals Don't Get It...No Wonder Obama is Sinking in the Polls, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351605642244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:00:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351605738642-19</Id><Topic><Title>GALLUP: ROMNEY UP 52%-45% AMONG EARLY VOTERS...</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1351604748105</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:45:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The polling agencies all use models and there are filters that very greatly from model to model. How you tweek/tune the model affects the results. Take this storm on the East coast. Each model will account differently for its impact on voter turnout. As for trust in accuracy it's like picking a money manager, you look for the group with the best track record over longer time frames.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351605738642</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:02:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351606039574-20</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are Democrats Terified of Passing a Budget?</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1351605435758</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:57:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's beyond this president's ability. He's a welfare queen at heart and only knows how to take and spend.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351606039574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351606389242-21</Id><Topic><Title>A Big Storm Requires Big Government</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351590133033</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:42:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point. In fact the Federal gov't promotes the development of known and flood and tidal surge property through the National Flood Insurance Program. People build homes and develop properties along vulnerable coastal property and flood zones only because the Feds provide the insurance to bail them out when Sandy's come along which will surely eventually happen.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351606389242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351606667887-22</Id><Title>The Public Option</Title><Msg>Having a publicly funded health care option will bring the costs down pronto. It's called competition and the Repubs are always babbling how much they like competition. .Current American health care costs are completely outrageous. Private health insurance companies and the party politicians they have brought -the Repubs- will fight to keep their gravy train running. The party that has always lavished tax cuts on the ultra wealthy is the Repub party. They do it, even though they know it will wreck the government, create huge deficits and destroy the economy. They are reckless clowns with a greedhead ideology</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1351606667887</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351607004438-23</Id><Topic><Title>A Big Storm Requires Big Government</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351590133033</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:42:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Repub Governors to Federal government in the wake of storms: "Gimmie, gimmie, gimmie!"</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1351607004438</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351607681662-24</Id><Topic><Title>The Public Option</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1351606667887</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:17:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hokey dokes usual bagger kneejerk apology. Spends every waking hour sucking down republiwhoppers and regurgitating them on this board. Not much else for him to do around the trailer park.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1351607681662</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351608053114-25</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are Democrats Terified of Passing a Budget?</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1351605435758</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:57:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A budget just gets in the way when you want to give your friends some government money.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1351608053114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:40:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351608277049-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Looking Presidential, Christie Praising Obama, Romney Getting Slammed...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351604312275</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:38:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have got to remember to take your meds.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1351608277049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:44:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351608296884-27</Id><Topic><Title>The Public Option</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1351606667887</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:17:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shocked - Competition is fine. t is already happening in package delivery with the Post Office. I'm good with it.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351608296884</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:44:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351608715142-28</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Gets Knocked for Misleading Jeep Claims</Title><Username>the_loading_dock</Username><Timestamp>1351590797187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:53:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Dems don't care about right or wrong. The truth just gets in the way for leftists. Of course Romney is right. It's just like in the debate when Romney questioned Obama on Libya! These leftist Dems are so funny, they couldn't tell the truth ever. The truth is just something to spin for them.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1351608715142</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:51:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351608850980-29</Id><Title>Oh My: Romney Leads 52/46 in National Early Voting?</Title><Msg>"In US, 15% of Registered Voters Have Already Cast Ballots." But then there's this, fresh from Gallup: Survey of those who have already voted - Romney 52%, Obama 46%.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351608850980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:54:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351609105173-30</Id><Title>Pro-Life Group Hits Back on Obama Administration's Mammosham</Title><Msg>Last week Katie Pavlich brought you a mini fact check of President Obama's claims the abortion giant Planned Parenthood provides mammograms. They don't, it's a sham known as mammosham. Now, the pro-life Susan B. Anthony list has released an ad responding to not only mammosham, but a whole series of falsehoods, including contraception mandates for religious institutions through ObamaCare, being perpetuated by the Obama campaign and Planned Parenthood itself this election season. “With Obamacare and the HHS Mandate, President Obama has launched an unprecedented attack on freedom of religion and the rights of conscience. President Obama knows this – and in an effort to distract the media and grassroots, he and his team have resorted to using scare tactics with women’s health,” said Marjorie Dannenfelser, President of SBA List. “Planned Parenthood’s own annual report reveals that it is the largest abortion provider in the nation – it does not provide comprehensive, whole woman’s health care, including mammograms. The HHS mandate forces religious institutions and Americans of faith and conscience to violate their beliefs and pay for coverage of abortion-inducing drugs. Women want and deserve leaders that care about access to comprehensive, whole woman care, not those who promote only abortion-centered institutions and policies.”</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351609105173</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:58:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351609141969-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Looking Presidential, Christie Praising Obama, Romney Getting Slammed...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351604312275</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:38:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Life is good today..." I suppose so for a guy who likes to have his toes in the water.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351609141969</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:59:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351610045534-32</Id><Title>Romney is a douche!</Title><Msg>why does America think Romney is such a douche...?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351610045534</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:14:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351610314475-33</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Looking Presidential, Christie Praising Obama, Romney Getting Slammed...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351604312275</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:38:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said! Voters realizing romney lies, the chameleon candidate. Latest fabrication about Jeep moving production to China catches up with the magic underwear candidate. romney is almost comical in pursuit of WH! Kamakure</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351610314475</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:18:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351610705230-34</Id><Title>Left Turning Violent and Vulgar - Knows Romney is Winning</Title><Msg>Watch how the lefties will start calling Romney names and increase their violent acts on conservatives now that Romney is clearly beating Obama. It's like little children trowing tantrums because they can't have their way.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351610705230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:25:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351610929432-35</Id><Topic><Title>LIbDums Soon Silent</Title><Username>locost7777</Username><Timestamp>1351610068733</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:14:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't wait until sparty's dumbo / mobro jihad is defunded taxpayers have been funding the enemy within, direct and indirect, for decades also tired of gov't using our money to advertise gov't, on the airwaves and internet</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1351610929432</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351611083783-36</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a douche!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351610045534</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:14:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to the latest polls is appears that over 50% of "America" doesn't think Romney is a douche. Perhaps you should rephrase that question to, "why do retards thinks Romney is a douche?". I'm sure you're qualified to answer it.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351611083783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:31:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351611275764-37</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a douche!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351610045534</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:14:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>im just reporting the facts Mr..</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351611275764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351611438927-38</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a douche!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351610045534</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:14:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, you're not.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351611438927</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:37:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351611930287-39</Id><Title>Millions without power tell Romney to Go to hell</Title><Msg>we'll if they haven't told Romney to Go to hell ... they should !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351611930287</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:45:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351612204975-40</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a douche!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351610045534</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:14:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at least 47% think so ...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351612204975</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:50:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351613451107-41</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Dick Hertz...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351611320720</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:35:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The states getting slammed the hardest by Sandy are blue (Obama) states according to the intrade electoral map. Karma?</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351613451107</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351613785745-42</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351613227496</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's for sure. Just 10,000 years ago, a blink of an eye in the 4.5 billion years that the earth has been spinning around, New York was under 5,000 feet of ice.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351613785745</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:16:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351615448040-43</Id><Title>No redneck Polls - just Facts!!</Title><Msg>Obama is most favorite to win</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351615448040</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:44:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351616194243-44</Id><Topic><Title>Millions without power tell Romney to Go to hell</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351611930287</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:45:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why? Sticky man you are getting tacky.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351616194243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351616269255-45</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Dick Hertz...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351611320720</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:35:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dik, You are One Idiot and Fool, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351616269255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:57:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351616336007-46</Id><Topic><Title>No redneck Polls - just Facts!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351615448040</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:44:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep Drinking Your Own Bath Water, Ugh!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351616336007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:58:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351616370160-47</Id><Topic><Title>Left Turning Violent and Vulgar - Knows Romney is Winning</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351610705230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:25:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have been called names and heard the righties call Obama and other liberals every name in the book the for decades how about you take a flying freaking leap off a bridge into reality.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351616370160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:59:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351616457240-48</Id><Topic><Title>Left Turning Violent and Vulgar - Knows Romney is Winning</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351610705230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:25:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals Have Always Been the Most Racist and Vulgar Fools....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351616457240</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:00:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351616610827-49</Id><Topic><Title>Left Turning Violent and Vulgar - Knows Romney is Winning</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351610705230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:25:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It goes without saying libtards will always accuse you of everything they're guilty of doing. They're funny when they're trowing tantrums</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351616610827</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:03:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351616775026-50</Id><Title>UNINSTALLING OBAMA.....……………. ███████████████████▒▒ 94% complete</Title><Msg>Mitt's winning the early vote by 52% to 45% Mitt's winning Ohio by 2% Mitt's winning Pennsylvania by 2% and even Democrat Ed Rendell concedes that Mitt could win the state. Bye, bye Barack</Msg><Username>parkplacebob</Username><Timestamp>1351616775026</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:06:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351616863353-51</Id><Title>Obama's Early Voting Lead Collapses 22 Points Compared to 2008 Smoldering Peanuts!</Title><Msg>GALLUP: OBAMA'S EARLY VOTE ADVANTAGE COLLAPSES 22-POINTS OVER 2008 by JOHN NOLTE 30 Oct 2012, 6:46 AM PDT 209 POST A COMMENT My pal Guy Benson found a juicy nugget that helps to bring more clarity to the news from Gallup yesterday that shows Romney leading Obama in the early vote by a full seven points, 52-45%. Almost exactly four years ago (October 28, 2008), according to Gallup, Obama was massacring John McCain among early voters with a fifteen-point lead, 55-40%. That means, at least according to Gallup, that Obama's early vote advantage has dropped 22 points when compared to '08. Benson also notes that the percentage of voters who have or intend to vote early was 33% in 2008 and remains at 33% today. As Don Surber said in this tweet, "People don't wait in line to vote for the status quo[.]" In his email to me, Benson makes The Point: "Obama had a 55/40 lead on McCain with early voters in '08, but only led by 3 pts with the election day crowd. He ended up winning by 7 overall." In other words, among those who actually voted on Election Day, Obama's advantage over McCain was only three-points. Obama won by seven overall because of the early vote margins he had accumulated. If Gallup is correct about 2012 and Romney being ahead by seven with early voters, that means Obama's in very deep trouble. Even polls that show Obama with a small lead in states like Ohio confirm Romney will win among those who vote on Election Day. Like me, Benson is skeptical of Gallup because, like its daily tracker that gives Romney a five point lead over Obama nationally, this early voting poll defies the CorruptMedia's conventional wisdom. But there are a few things you have to keep in mind.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351616863353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:07:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351616993972-52</Id><Topic><Title>Left Turning Violent and Vulgar - Knows Romney is Winning</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351610705230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:25:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO Republicans are such weasels.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351616993972</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:09:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351617041821-53</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Looking Presidential, Christie Praising Obama, Romney Getting Slammed...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351604312275</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:38:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obama Looking Presidential" - It's about time. With only one week left, he finally is trying to do his job. Can't say that for Benghazi. Or the economy. Or jobs. Or foreign policy. Or relations with our ONLY real ally in the Middle East, Israel. Or national harmony.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351617041821</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:10:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351617249159-54</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Early Voting Lead Collapses 22 Points Compared to 2008 Smoldering Peanuts!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351616863353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:07:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read it and weep. http://fivethirtyeight.blogs.nytimes.com/</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351617249159</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:14:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351618363286-55</Id><Topic><Title>No redneck Polls - just Facts!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351615448040</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:44:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>to a redneck; a poll is a man from Poland... to immacom; a poll is what right-wing stroke... eh?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351618363286</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351618887468-56</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Early Voting Lead Collapses 22 Points Compared to 2008 Smoldering Peanuts!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351616863353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:07:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not weeping. Maybe another Hoozdik post illustrating his lack of self-initiative and inablity to think, would get me weepy. :-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351618887468</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:41:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351619053029-57</Id><Topic><Title>Millions without power tell Romney to Go to hell</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351611930287</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:45:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i forget im speaking to children; - for his Lies, Romney is not going to Heaven, he will forever ferment in the pit !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351619053029</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:44:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351619622813-58</Id><Title>Heh Heh Heh: Anti-Romney Vandals Accidentally Target Obama Supporters</Title><Msg>It's amusing when pro-Democrat criminals screw up and inadvertently target their own fellow partisans. This story comes from -- where else? -- California: CBS2 and KCAL9 reporter Rob Schmitt spoke to Ken Slown, owner of one of the keyed vehicles. Slown actually supports President Obama! He explained to Schmitt that he and his wife — both currently unemployed — are staying with her parents and it’s her parents who support Romney. “I don’t know if they were trying to get a point across, to vote for Obama,” said Slown, “but to do something like this is not going to get the point across.” He estimates the damage to both of his vehicles at about $3,400. In addition to both cars being keyed, his wife’s vehicle had her seats slashed, as well. Said Slown, “They pretty much cut the backs of all of the seats.” A neighbor, who also has a Romney/Ryan sign in their front yard, were also hit. “Obama” keyed in the hood and on the black gate of an SUV. So the unemployed victims support Obama, but they're living with mom and dad, who back Romney. Perfect. I wonder if these Republican parents will generously help cover some of the property damage inflicted by their daughter and son-in-law's political kindred spirits. Click if you like this post!</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351619622813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351619942810-59</Id><Title>GOP Takes High Road on Weather Disaster, Libs Take Low Road... Politicize It</Title><Msg>Pathetic... No Wonder Obama is Plummenting in the Polls!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351619942810</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:59:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351621044453-60</Id><Topic><Title>Is this the ‘built to last’ economy Obama promised?</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1351606431280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where have you been??? Most of the statement in your article took place during Bush's administration.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351621044453</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:17:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351621163646-61</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Early Voting Lead Collapses 22 Points Compared to 2008 Smoldering Peanuts!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351616863353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:07:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Early voting by states would be more telling</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351621163646</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:19:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351621264430-62</Id><Topic><Title>Another Quote</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351613431719</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:10:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep repeating the lie Goebels. The context is that running up the national debt is immoral.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351621264430</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:21:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351621368125-63</Id><Topic><Title>Is this the ‘built to last’ economy Obama promised?</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1351606431280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you forgot to ask where all the jobs are the Bush tax cuts created.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351621368125</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:22:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351621858727-64</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Takes High Road on Weather Disaster, Libs Take Low Road... Politicize It</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351619942810</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:59:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh ... so Repugnantcons DON'T try to politicize Sandy? You lie your a** off you have no a** left, and soon the rest of you will be gone too. Former FEMA Director Michael Brown offered criticism of President Obama’s early responses to Hurricane Sandy yesterday, including a dig at the administration’s response to last month’s attack in Libya. Yesterday, ahead of the storm’s pummeling of the eastern seaboard, Brown gave an interview to the local alternative paper, the Denver Westword, on how he believed the Obama administration was responding to Sandy too quickly and that Obama had spoken to the press about Sandy’s potential effect too early. Brown turned then to a reliable right-wing attack on the President’s response to the attack on a U.S. diplomatic outpost in Benghazi that killed four Americans: “One thing he’s gonna be asked is, why did he jump on [the hurricane] so quickly and go back to D.C. so quickly when in…Benghazi, he went to Las Vegas?” Brown says. “Why was this so quick?… At some point, somebody’s going to ask that question…. This is like the inverse of Benghazi.”</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351621858727</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351623335392-65</Id><Title>No matter how you slice it: Obama Wins!</Title><Msg>National polls are meaningless at this stage in the election. At this stage in the election, like any sufficiently close election, the fate of the candidates rests with fewer than a half-dozen states. The continuing snapshots of national polls are useful for pollsters and academics, who are interested in things like expected vote share or the probability of victory in the national popular vote. Most stakeholders care only about the likelihood of victory in the Electoral College, and a national poll is not very useful at this point. This is why most prognosticators consider Obama to have a far higher chance of victory than the national polls would suggest. The Signal has Obama at a 65 percent chance of victory, while Nate Silver gives him a 75 percent chance against Romney Any way you slice it, Obama is leading in states that account for well over 270 electoral votes. As we've said a million times before, Obama needs only Ohio, Florida or Virginia to prevent Romney from reaching 270 electoral votes in most scenarios. Romney needs all three.</Msg><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1351623335392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:55:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351623379108-66</Id><Topic><Title>Now Romney refuses to talk about FEMA</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351619465040</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:51:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He doesn't need to talk NOW - He already has!! See below!! I'm SURE all the battered states agree with his position and will refuse any assistance from the Feds!! During a GOP primary debate last year, Romney had said he supported the idea of states and private sector groups taking over responsibility for disaster relief, adding that he would "absolutely" shut down FEMA. “Governor Romney believes that states should be in charge of emergency management in responding to storms and other natural disasters in their jurisdictions,” said campaign spokeswoman Amanda Henneberg.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351623379108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:56:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351624950200-67</Id><Topic><Title>Millions without power tell Romney to Go to hell</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351611930287</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:45:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Millions without power tell Romney to ..." Stick, I am trying to imagine how people without power are able to communicate anything - let alone expressing your fantasies about their political opinions. More than likely, they are looking to recover from the mess, perhaps find food and water. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351624950200</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:22:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351625699497-68</Id><Title>President Obama; - Country before Politics..!!</Title><Msg>Our President is out there fighting the fight for America to stay Safe.... domestic and foreign... 100%</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351625699497</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:34:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351625877291-69</Id><Title>Go and look up Dangerous Lessons of 1937</Title><Msg>We did not learn from the past, and now they want to spend more money we don't have to fix NY and NJ California is already in recession</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351625877291</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351626550564-70</Id><Topic><Title>Millions without power tell Romney to Go to hell</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351611930287</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:45:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bb - dont blow a circuit trying to imagine... Trust me; Romney is Going To Hell...and taking Billy Graham with!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351626550564</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:49:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351626675243-71</Id><Topic><Title>Millions without power tell Romney to Go to hell</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351611930287</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:45:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And on the way there do not pause at "Go"</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351626675243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351626835684-72</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Takes High Road on Weather Disaster, Libs Take Low Road... Politicize It</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351619942810</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:59:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That idiot BROWNIE! Doing a great job, my #$%$ Just imagine what a mess the East Coast would be in if Bushleague were still President!</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351626835684</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:53:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351629153906-73</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama; - Country before Politics..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351625699497</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Domestic today, Maybe, but Foreign, Definitely Not Obama has Benghazi Blood on his hands... a total Failure</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351629153906</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351629622624-74</Id><Topic><Title>No matter how you slice it: Obama Wins!</Title><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1351623335392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:55:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a Nitwit, eh? Related to Dikl?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351629622624</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:40:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351629824175-75</Id><Topic><Title>What does Obama mean when he says We have come to far to turn back now?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351624943943</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:22:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hussein Obama is a Liar and the American People Now Know it! The Documented Lies are Numerous! Any Wonder Why Obama is Cratering in the Polls? Heavy Drinking in Chicago!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351629824175</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:43:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351630083426-76</Id><Title>So Amusing! Libs Now Say Polls are Meaningless... Must Mean Obama is Losing, eh?</Title><Msg>What a Bunch of Desperate Fools Grasping at Straws... Fools! Dik, You are at the Head of the List!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351630083426</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:48:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351630124906-77</Id><Title>Obama ‘playing president’ for Sandy, not Benghazi</Title><Msg>As Hurricane Sandy was approaching the Jersey Shore, President Barack Obama has suspended his campaign activities to be at the ready for the pending crisis. But on Monday’s broadcast of Fox News Channel’s “Special Report,” Washington Post columnist Charles Krauthammer wasn’t convinced it wasn’t just for political imaging purposes. Krauthammer compared Obama’s willingness to be out front on Sandy to his lack of willingness to be out front on Benghazi, which he said suggested political opportunism. “He says he’s not concerned about the impact on the elections,” Krauthammer said. “I’m sure he’s very sincere on that. It is a little odd that he shows up in the briefing room, where he hasn’t shown up in the briefing room for about, what — a month and a half on Libya, or for everything else for that matter? Then you get the photo-ops of him in the situation room deploying, I guess, the utility crews who will restore power all over America. Whereas you would think he might want to use the situation room and had convened high-level people during the nine hours our people were under attack in Benghazi.” Krauthammer went on to explain why the onus of the disaster prep and relief isn’t on the president, but on the governors of states. But in this instance he suggested it is serving as an opportunity for the commander-in-chief to steer the momentum of the election back his way. “It’s hard to look at this, playing the president, playing the commander-in-chief in what’s a natural disaster that really doesn’t a lot of leadership from the White House,” Krauthammer said. “It’s up to the governors mostly. The White House and the governors release money. That’s about all that they do. And he’s really good at releasing money and pretending it’s not about politics. He wants to use this to show himself in command and I think he might actually be the beneficiary of the fact that all national attention is drawn away for three days. Romney clearly had the momentum, it slowed down but it was still heading in his direction. It’s not clear what happens when the country sort of wakes up out of this in three days and restarts attention on the campaign, whether the momentum will be gone or not. I mean, that’s an open question.”</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351630124906</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:48:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351630274462-78</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ‘playing president’ for Sandy, not Benghazi</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351630124906</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Has Blood on his Hands in Benghazi.... Obama Has Lied Multiple Time on Benghazi... the American People Know it... Reflects in the polls!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351630274462</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351630506791-79</Id><Topic><Title>as we saw with Colin Powel and Morgan Freeman the black card will be played out this election 20% unemployment is not a factor</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351624056576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:07:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals are Racists and Religious Bigots!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351630506791</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351630649934-80</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ‘playing president’ for Sandy, not Benghazi</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351630124906</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that`s pretty freaking creative , I bet you folks could somehow link the leaky faucet in my last hotel room to Obama somehow. guys been a better President than any Republicans ever has.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351630649934</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:57:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351631086089-81</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ‘playing president’ for Sandy, not Benghazi</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351630124906</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rockstar: Is That What Your Union Steward Told You Say Today, eh? You are a Good Little "Useful Fool", eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351631086089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:04:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351631224220-82</Id><Topic><Title>The Nate Silver backlash</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351631122475</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:05:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trash... More of Dik's Blue Wall Nonsense...... Comical!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351631224220</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:07:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351631363385-83</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ‘playing president’ for Sandy, not Benghazi</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351630124906</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>imaccom you`re a know nothing loud mouth #$%$ up!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351631363385</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351631539156-84</Id><Topic><Title>Frankenstorm and the Zomney Apocalypse</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351631315516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:08:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep! GOP Takes the High Road, Obama Takes the Low Road and Politicizes the Storm.... No Wonder Obama is Falling Like a Rock in the Polls.... Chicago Just Doesn't Get it!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351631539156</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351631739785-85</Id><Topic><Title>It Takes A Village Of (Public and Often Union) Workers</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351631580031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:13:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dik, You are Getting Extremely Desperate in Your Posts as You See Obama's Re-Election Chance Slipping Away.... Romney Will Crush Obama!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351631739785</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:15:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351631757506-86</Id><Title>Democrats are Racists and thery love playing the race card.</Title><Msg>The Democrats Party has always been a party of racists. That's why Democrats started the KKK.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351631757506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351631845792-87</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats are Racists and thery love playing the race card.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351631757506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats Have Always Been Racists and Bigots!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351631845792</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:17:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351631887105-88</Id><Topic><Title>Millions without power tell Romney to Go to hell</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351611930287</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:45:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Trust me; Romney is Going To Hell...and taking Billy Graham with!!" Stick, now this is the kind of judging that Jesus particularly said don't do.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351631887105</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:18:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351632027494-89</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney Is Just Not That Into Federal Disaster Relief</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351631826706</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:17:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Garbage... Dik is Getting Desperate as Obama Continues to Sinks in the Polls Their Articles are Getting More and More Humorous as Reality sets in!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351632027494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:20:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351632151624-90</Id><Topic><Title>The Nate Silver backlash</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351631122475</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:05:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I read a column by Paul Krugman regarding Nate Silver which I felt was valid. Krugman pointed out that Silver is transparent with his model tweeking, which he is, and weights things differently than other polling folks. I wrongly thought Nate was just a partisan hack until I researched his methodology. For example Nate weights local polls heavier than others. He may be right or he may be wrong but to me there is nothing wrong with this because Nate isn't hiding anything and time will tell if his methodology is correct. I'm all for competition as I've stated in an earlier post so let Nate compete with the big boys and if he does better say "Nice Job Nate!".</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351632151624</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:22:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351632164789-91</Id><Title>The Term"union worker" is an Oxy#$%$.....</Title><Msg>hoozdik is just a #$%$</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351632164789</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:22:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351632168845-92</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats are Racists and thery love playing the race card.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351631757506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I find people who need to bring up race all the time or just out of the blue as their main subject line are most likely a racist trying to defend their denial</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351632168845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:22:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351632253815-93</Id><Topic><Title>The Nate Silver backlash</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351631122475</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:05:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul Krugman is a Joke!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351632253815</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:24:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351632272200-94</Id><Topic><Title>The Term"union worker" is an Oxy#$%$.....</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351632164789</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:22:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, playwithyourself, what an intelligent post. LOL</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1351632272200</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351632328138-95</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is now surging on intrade</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351632139837</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:22:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are Drinking as Heavily as the Fools in Chicago?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351632328138</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:25:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351632570229-96</Id><Title>Republicans are the biggest beneficiaries of government Spending</Title><Msg>they are indeed the largest recipients.... and biggest spenders of ...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351632570229</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:29:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351633170305-97</Id><Topic><Title>Millions without power tell Romney to Go to hell</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351611930287</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:45:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OIC - sneaking Jesus into this... thats what the Billy Grahams would do!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351633170305</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:39:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351633419512-98</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing encouraging outsourcing to mexico</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1351274654419</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 14:04:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn’t Boeing learn anything from their internationally sourced 787? Its time to end Boeing TAX breaks. This company needs to show American spirit.... How disappointing on what used to be a good American company.. It’s time to revoke Boeing’s 3 billion tax break that Washington State taxpayer’s gave to Boeing for the complete 787 final assembly rights. OK Ms Cantwell now what, train Washington State workers in aerospace so they can move to Mexico and make nothing all day long? Let’s see Washington State taxpayer’s give Boeing tax breaks and build infrastructure per Boeings requirement and Boeing moves to Chicago, open a second 787 line in SC and “ it is not due to wages “ it is due to unions, clearly Boeing management does not want any worker to have any rights . One of the reasons for moving Corporate Headquarters from Seattle is that it is very easy for executives to not be troubled by the concerns about the impact on the community as jobs are sent overseas. Boeing should lose taxpayer subsidy, the government should end the research, technology and intellectual property that Boeing gets free. These passenger planes are competitive to Airbus now at the existing pricing, so there is no reason, but greed to move jobs overseas. If American people cannot make a living wage then all the real estate will never come back in value.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1351633419512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351633475922-99</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama; - Country before Politics..!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351625699497</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>neocons are awesome at foreign policy.... how many soldiers died under buscho... eh? how many flags draped so you and the Romnster can be here to tell your silly lies</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351633475922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351633584209-100</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing loses federal labor case in South Carolina</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1351457129635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 16:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see McNerney is not stealing margin, nope , he is moving the subcontractors to mexico, what a guy "Didn’t Boeing learn anything from their internationally sourced 787? Its time to end Boeing TAX breaks. This company needs to show American spirit.... How disappointing on what used to be a good American company.. It’s time to revoke Boeing’s 3 billion tax break that Washington State taxpayer’s gave to Boeing for the complete 787 final assembly rights. OK Ms Cantwell now what, train Washington State workers in aerospace so they can move to Mexico and make nothing all day long? Let’s see Washington State taxpayer’s give Boeing tax breaks and build infrastructure per Boeings requirement and Boeing moves to Chicago, open a second 787 line in SC and “ it is not due to wages “ it is due to unions, clearly Boeing management does not want any worker to have any rights . One of the reasons for moving Corporate Headquarters from Seattle is that it is very easy for executives to not be troubled by the concerns about the impact on the community as jobs are sent overseas. Boeing should lose taxpayer subsidy, the government should end the research, technology and intellectual property that Boeing gets free. These passenger planes are competitive to Airbus now at the existing pricing, so there is no reason, but greed to move jobs overseas. If American people cannot make a living wage then all the real estate will never come back in value.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1351633584209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:46:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351633849042-101</Id><Title>Romney has no honor or Morals!</Title><Msg>The Romney campaign canceled campaign events for Tuesday and set up what they call a "storm relief" event, coincidentally in the swing state of Ohio. Bringing donations, food, clothing and water, Romney supporters flocked to see the Republican nominee who is now put himself in a position where he can only scratch his head. If Romney continues to campaign, he looks heartless, adding to the stigma that he is a greedy businessman who only cares about the wealthy. But if Romney stops campaigning, he loses an opportunity to push his closing message in the final week of the election. Not knowing what to do, Romney held the party line, calling Republican governors from Virginia and New Jersey, but never reached out to Gov. Martin O'Malley, Democrat from Maryland, or Connecticut Gov. Daniel Malloy, also a Democrat.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351633849042</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:50:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351634365659-102</Id><Title>WOW......HERE IS A TWIST, DISHONESTY AT IT'S PEAK...</Title><Msg>Lockheed has announced they are laying off 123,000 employees. Obama has asked them not to announce this until after the election. I want an American to lead us not a Muslim that hates us...</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1351634365659</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:59:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351634806035-103</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats are Racists and thery love playing the race card.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351631757506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's too bad, because it's not going to happen</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1351634806035</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:06:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351634952202-104</Id><Topic><Title>Millions without power tell Romney to Go to hell</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351611930287</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:45:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stick, it is important to understand whether or not "going to hell" is something to be made light of or not. I took it in your original post the use of the expression was the typical, though always inappropriate, invective or casual curse - as opposed to making a judgment regarding one's state in eternity. So, I did not comment relative to that at first. Your response and clarification saying "Trust me; Romney is Going To Hell...and taking Billy Graham with!!" is taking upon yourself to declare what are the consequences of something or everything in their lives. Something that is up to the Lord. It was not clear how Billy Graham entered into the picture, though it may have had something to do with the endorsement of Romney. You may have sufficient understanding of the Bible (I hope that that is the case) to declare that "unbelief" (in Jesus) is the path to hell, but you cannot judge any individual's heart or mind to say for certain if they will be in hell. For example, Obama declares that he is a Christian. I cannot say that that is not true. I don't know his heart - I only know my own. Just as you only know your own heart. However, I am able to observe what Obama does (his "fruit"). In my opinion, he has taken this nation in directions that makes him out to be disobedient to God's Word - in terms of lessening support of Israel as well as increasing the hostility around Israel, in terms of supporting unfettered abortion, in terms of supporting same-gender marriage, and in terms of being hostile to the Christian community while embracing the Islamic community. - BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351634952202</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351634970096-105</Id><Topic><Title>Millions without power tell Romney to Go to hell</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351611930287</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:45:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They can't because their phones don't work.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1351634970096</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:09:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351635871083-106</Id><Title>Obama 'outstanding'</Title><Msg>One of Mitt Romney's biggest supporters, New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie, had nothing but praise for President Barack Obama today, as his state prepares to rebuild from the damage caused by Hurricane Sandy. "I have to say, the administration, the president, himself and FEMA Administrator Craig Fugate have been outstanding with us so far," Christie said on Good Morning America. "We have a great partnership with them." Christie told ABC's George Stephanopoulos that Obama called him on Monday night around midnight to ask if there was anything else the federal government could do to help. Christie added that they worked together to move forward with a Major Disaster Declaration for New Jersey. The Major Disaster Declaration provides funding for recovery efforts, including infrastructure projects, temporary housing, low-cost loans to cover uninsured property loss and assistance to individuals and businesses. "He worked on that last night with me…offered any other assets that we needed to help," Christie said. "I want to thank the president personally for his personal attention to this." Appearing on Fox News, Christie said the storm is bigger than the election. "I have a job in New Jersey that is much bigger than presidential politics," Gov. Chris Christie said on the show Fox &amp; Friends. "I couldn't care less about that."</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1351635871083</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:24:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351637671103-107</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Takes High Road on Weather Disaster, Libs Take Low Road... Politicize It</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351619942810</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:59:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But if Brownnose were still in charge, not one dressage horse would be lost in Cyclone Sandy.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351637671103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:54:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351640088911-108</Id><Topic><Title>Is this the ‘built to last’ economy Obama promised?</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1351606431280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good boy! You spelled "horde" correctly about 3 consecutive times. See? You really can get better. Next thing is to work on the facts a lot more, but take heart: you have PROVEN you can improve. Keep up the good work and some day your family won't be ashamed of you any more.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1351640088911</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:34:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351640405676-109</Id><Title>President AWOL</Title><Msg>"I don't want to point any fingers, but obviously people in the White House were watching this happen. Real time. They -- someone in the White House, or many people in the White House watched the events unfolding and knew that if they gave the order to stand down, that my son would die. They watched my son die. As far as I'm concerned, there are people in the White House -- whoever it was that was in that room watching that video of my son dying, their cries for help, their order 'don't help them at all, let them die' -- whoever it might be, might be numerous people, you have the blood of my son, you have the blood of an American hero on your hands. I don't know who you are, but one of these days the truth will come out. I still forgive you, but you need to stand up." CHARLES WOODS, father of Tyrone Woods</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351640405676</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:40:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351640897147-110</Id><Title>can anyone verify the SOP re lase designators ?</Title><Msg>as a possible answer to the following- why would a ex- SEAL keep a laser on target unless he believed some sort of weapon was ready to fire ? copied from another site Another reader, Thomas Wictor, weighs in on this point via email: The Benghazi coverup is much worse than you think. Clearly there were air assets on the scene above the CIA annex and they were denied permission to fire. Tyrone Woods was painting a target with a ground laser designator (GLD). Those are only used when the air asset is overhead, ready to fire. The jihadis can use cell phones with night-vision capabilities to see the laser beam, which then pinpoints the location of the person using the GLD. As a former Navy SEAL, Woods would’ve known that. He would only have exposed himself if he thought that the mortar squad was about to be taken out. The air asset didn’t fire, and Woods and Glen Doherty were killed by the mortar squad. There was either a Spectre gunship or an armed Predator or Reaper drone overhead, and it was denied permission to fire. That’s the only explanation that fits. Woods would not have used his GLD for any other reason than to paint a target for an immediate air strike. Only the commander of AFRICOM and the president have the authority to tell the air asset to not fire in this situation.” +++ sounds plausible ????</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1351640897147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:48:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351640979910-111</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351635479249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As Christie said, NO Politics During the Recovery from the Disaster... Christie was Clear About That. Liberals Like dik are too Stupid to Understand!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351640979910</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:49:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351640984203-112</Id><Topic><Title>The Nate Silver backlash</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351631122475</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:05:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't often agree with Krugman often but I always do my own research, and Nate is just a little guy that made good on the American Dream and he did it on his own. I'm not going to trash someone like that. I want more people that work hard and make good.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351640984203</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351641636063-113</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351635479249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, Yesterday, this is what you said about Gov Christie: "I just read that only five Hostess Cupcake trucks could get to Chris Christie's place instead of the usual fleet of ten." Today, you are quoting him as a reason "why we need Barack Obama in the White House". The Bible says, "A double minded man is unstable in all his ways." (James 1:8)</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351641636063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351642165536-114</Id><Title>BO and Hillary in church before Sandy landfall</Title><Msg>They were praying for a real bad weather scene to detract from Lybia</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1351642165536</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351642174327-115</Id><Title>GOP Voting Tsunami Coming! Obama Deluged</Title><Msg>Some see GOP voting tsunami coming Paul Bedard Washington Secrets The Washington Examiner Some see GOP voting tsunami coming Democrats more than Republicans are getting their most loyal supporters to vote early, but with polls showing a close race among those who have voted so far, concerns are being raised about a GOP tsunami on the actual Election Day, next Tuesday. According to a GOP analysis of early voting and absentee ballot requests provided to Secrets, the Democrats are turning out their most reliable, or so-called "high propensity voters" than Republicans, leaving fewer for Election Day. The GOP is pushing weaker supporters to vote early, expecting high enthusiasm to drive their regular supporters to the polls next week. "Democrats are cannibalizing their high-propensity voters in advance of election day to get stories that they are winning," said a GOP analyst. "But in effect they are stealing from Peter, or Election Day, to pay Paul, or early voting." For example, in Ohio, the Democrats have turned out 43 percent of the most loyal supporters to vote, compared to just 27 percent of the GOP. In Iowa, the difference is 43 percent to 29 percent. "Republicans will have more reliable voters available on Election Day and are spending our efforts turning out low propensity voters in the absentee and early voting periods," added the analysis. Even with the difference in turnout of loyal supporters, Gallup finds that among early voters, Romney is beating Obama 52 percent to 45 percent, though some state totals show an Obama advantage.Plus in states like North Carolina, Colorado and Iowa, the GOP has seen huge requests for last-minute absentee ballots this month.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351642174327</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:09:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351642355535-116</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351635479249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dik is an Idiot and Fool and Everyone Knows Including Dik Himself!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351642355535</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:12:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351642561657-117</Id><Title>Tall ship crew very lucky</Title><Msg>If the Coast Guard took Penetta's lying ways, they wouldn't have went into harms way till someone reported it safe to go. Re Lybia</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1351642561657</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:16:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351642743954-118</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351635479249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you Ask Michael Moore the Same Question?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351642743954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:19:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351643197286-119</Id><Title>Romney Plunges Into Once "Safe" Dem Turf... Obama Scrambling to Protect "Safe" States!</Title><Msg>Romney, GOP suddenly plunging onto Democratic turf Oct 30, 6:18 PM (ET) By THOMAS BEAUMONT and BRIAN BAKST MINNEAPOLIS (AP) - Mitt Romney is suddenly plunging into traditionally Democratic-leaning Minnesota and Pennsylvania, and his GOP allies are trying to put Michigan into play. It's forcing President Barack Obama to defend his own turf - he's pouring money into television ads in the states and dispatching top backers - in the campaign's final week. The question is: Why this Republican move? GOP efforts in the trio of Rust Belt states could indicate that Romney is desperately searching for a last-minute path to the needed 270 Electoral College votes - without all-important Ohio. Or just the opposite, that he's so confident in the most competitive battlegrounds that he's pressing for insurance against Obama in what's expected to be a close race. Or perhaps the Republican simply has money to burn. Use it now or never.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351643197286</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:26:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351643552886-120</Id><Title>FaceBook Censoring Negative Navy SEAL Criticism of Obama? Pathetic!</Title><Msg>FACEBOOK CENSORS NAVY SEALS TO PROTECT OBAMA ON BENGHAZI-GATE by AWR HAWKINS 30 Oct 2012, 1:20 PM PDT 233 POST A COMMENT Over the weekend, Facebook took down a message by the Special Operations Speaks PAC (SOS) which highlighted the fact that Obama denied backup to the forces being overrun in Benghazi. The message was contained in a meme which demonstrated how Obama had relied on the SEALS when he was ready to let them get Osama bin Laden, and how he had turned around and denied them when they called for backup on Sept 11. I spoke with Larry Ward, president of Political Media, Inc -- the media company that handles SOS postings and media production. Ward was the one who personally put the Navy SEAL meme up, and the one who received the warning from Facebook and an eventual 24 hour suspension from Facebook because Ward put the meme back up after Facebook told him to take it down. Here's what Ward told me: We created and posted this meme on Saturday after news broke that Obama had known and denied SEALS the backup they requested. Once the meme was up it garnered 30,000 shares, approx. 24,000 likes, and was read by hundreds of thousands of people -- all within 24 hrs. On Sunday, I went into the SOS Facebook page to post something else and found a warning from Facebook that we had violated Facebook's Statement of Rights and Responsibilities with our meme. So I copied the warning, put it on the meme as as caption, and re-posted the meme to the Facebook page. Along with the re-posted meme, Ward put a link to the Facebook "feedback comment" inbox so visitors to the SOS page could send a message to Facebook if they were as outraged over the meme being jerked down as he was.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351643552886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351644021997-121</Id><Title>Obama Should Fire his Campaign Staff for Incompetence or His... GOP Celebrates!</Title><Msg>Obama's Chicago Thugs Really Screwed Up Obama's Re-Election Chance... Hopelessness and Hate did Not Sell to the American People!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351644021997</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351644065346-122</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351635479249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For Michael Moore, I believe it is Chief of the Office of Liberal Propaganda. By the way, Hooz, that was a good retort (the clock) to my earlier post. Gluttony: "Put a knife to your throat if you are given to appetite." (Proverbs 23:2) which may be a tad dire, and, more instructive, "If you have found honey, eat only enough for you, lest you have your fill of it and vomit." (Proverbs 25:16) By inference gluttony and obesity is not being obedient, "So, whether you eat or drink, or whatever you do, do all to the glory of God." (1 Cor 10:31)</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351644065346</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351644682802-123</Id><Topic><Title>No matter how you slice it: Obama Wins!</Title><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1351623335392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:55:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nate Silver, who in his fivethirtyeight blog correctly predicted 49 of 50 states in the last election, predicts that Obama could breeze to victory with a 75 percent chance of winning. Silver's results reveal a psychologically disturbing fact: we live in an uncontrollable, unpredictable world. Obama is a moderately popular incumbent running against a relatively uncharismatic one who’s not that well liked even among conservatives. A rainy election day and upswing in the economy could do more to affect the small slice of undecided voters in swing state for Obama. Get in with the in crowd. Yeah, baby!</Msg><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1351644682802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:51:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351644856550-124</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is now surging on intrade</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351632139837</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:22:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, baby! Obama is S-U-R-G-I-N-G!</Msg><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1351644856550</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:54:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351644968898-125</Id><Topic><Title>Tall ship crew very lucky</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1351642561657</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:16:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good on the CG of course. Same goes for emergency responders all over the country, who go into harms ways with out the Penetta doctrine.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1351644968898</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:56:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351645053010-126</Id><Topic><Title>BO and Hillary in church before Sandy landfall</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1351642165536</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:09:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BO spent 2 days at the whitehouse almost. Most time he spent there in 4 years.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1351645053010</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:57:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351646070169-127</Id><Title>Remember General Betrau us</Title><Msg>Damn could those dim wits be right? General Petreaus took to the new job of head of the CIA, a lot of good will and respect from his previous positions. I certainly had high hopes. Now he has come out and said that the CIA did not refuse help to the Benghazi Libya ambassador. Well who do you suppose told CIA people not to help. Penettia of course refused military help. Wonder if that shipment of shoulder fired missiles that he didn't get stopped influenced the C130. The spine of an earth worm.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1351646070169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:14:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351646754764-128</Id><Topic><Title>Remember General Betrau us</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1351646070169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:14:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Good General and Current Head of the CIA said Clearly his Agency did Not Refuse Help to the SEALs in Benghazi.. the Refusal came From a Higher Authority... Guess Who that Nitwit Is? It is Becomming Clear Obama Overruled his Military Commanders and Got Four Americans Killed even After They Asked for Help Four Times! Obama Put Politics First and American Lives Dead Last!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351646754764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:25:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351647354494-129</Id><Title>One day to go</Title><Msg>The total deliveries as of today look like only 44 planes. Twenty six 737's. (Very low number). Three 747's. Two 767's. Seven 777's. Six 787's. Hoefully they can get more 737's delivered tomorrow. With the exception of January (28) the 737 monthly deliveries have been in the 30's.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351647354494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:35:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351651123100-130</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney Is Just Not That Into Federal Disaster Relief</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351631826706</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:17:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, he turned a campaign rally into a Sandy "relief" rally in which he asked everyone to bring a can of food. Anyone who actually understands how to deal with disasters will tell you, unequivocally, the number one need is CASH. Sorting and delivering food consumes far too much time and energy when it can be bought and delivered wholesale. Once again, Romney proves he's completely out of touch with the reality in which we the 99% live.</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1351651123100</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 22:38:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351652054215-131</Id><Topic><Title>Romney can pound Sand !!!!!!!</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351635679338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In your heart you know the president is a communist but you just can't make yourself admit it to those around you. Come to the light dear Paul.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351652054215</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 22:54:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351653489430-132</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351635479249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A double minded man. . . ." This surely explains your repeated and chronic case of bearing false witness. Your confession may help.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1351653489430</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351654271356-133</Id><Topic><Title>Romney can pound Sand !!!!!!!</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351635679338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If this is the Boeing message board I must be speaking to communists who believe they're progressive liberal democrats.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351654271356</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:31:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351655547722-134</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351635479249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>iam...666, Fascination with your choice of screen ID aside, didn't you get the message? I don't care what you think about the "false witness" thing. You simply cannot handle the truth and are in denial. Take Obama and Benghazi, as an example. There is enough truth out there to take SOMETONE from the White House and possible try and convict them for treason. The President says one thing ("I ordered that they do whatever can be done"), the SecDef says another ("We couldn't send anyone into the battle because we did not know enough"), the SecState offers her assessment ("it was the fog of war"), State Department employees said something contrary to their boss's assessment ("we were following the events in real time") and the CIA director says something altogether different ("no one in the CIA told anyone to 'stand down' "). Here is the truth: either the President was completely incompetent or he had nefarious intent to not provide aid and support to those being attacked. They did nothing. How is that truth unable to seep into your closed mind? Now did they do nothing because of cowardice? Did they do nothing for political reasons? Or did they do nothing for reasons that only a traitor would understand? If Obama somehow gets re-elected, he better hope that he has a solide Democrat Congress, because he will face impeachment in short order. "They perish because they refused to love the truth and so be saved. For this reason God sends them a powerful delusion so that they will believe the lie and so that all will be condemned who have not believed the truth but have delighted in wickedness." (2 Thess 2:10-12) BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351655547722</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>