<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-15"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355547687495-1</Id><Title>Will the World End on December 21st ?</Title><Msg>Not a chance... However I wanted to see if Yahoo would ALLOW this kind of idiotic propaganda to effect the weak minded...(if the link below is allowed to be posted I guessed right) while at the same time continue its policies of censoring REAL issues affecting our country.... http://news.yahoo.com/video/nasa-video-debunks-end-world-210513293.html Yep...right again</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355547687495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 00:01:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355555070490-2</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy Hook Elementary School massacre by yet another gun nut!</Title><Username>natsu4fun</Username><Timestamp>1355536363058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:52:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was it Brian Ross of ABC News?</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1355555070490</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 02:04:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355555235272-3</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy Hook Elementary School massacre by yet another gun nut!</Title><Username>natsu4fun</Username><Timestamp>1355536363058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:52:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Adam is also a Tea Party Supporter " What more does one need to know?</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1355555235272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 02:07:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355557061728-4</Id><Topic><Title>“The NRA is the enabler of mass murderers”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355531425388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 19:30:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bears repeating: “Al-Qaida killed 3,000 people in the World Trade Center in 2001. The United States went to war because of that. Because of the NRA, we’ve lost 10,000 people last year unnecessarily. It’s time we went to war,” he said. “And you have to say the National Rifle Association is the enabler of mass murderers. And we’ve got to stomp on them instead of kowtowing to them.”</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1355557061728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 02:37:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355557171856-5</Id><Topic><Title>cars should be banned along with guns cause they kill, mean old cars they are bad bab bad</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1355531628442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 19:33:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you ever heard of anyone who bought a car to kill people?</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1355557171856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 02:39:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355564649558-6</Id><Title>The G.O.P.’s Existential Crisis</Title><Msg>We are not having a debt crisis. It’s important to make this point, because I keep seeing articles about the “fiscal cliff” that do, in fact, describe it — often in the headline — as a debt crisis. But it isn’t. The U.S. government is having no trouble borrowing to cover its deficit. In fact, its borrowing costs are near historic lows. And even the confrontation over the debt ceiling that looms a few months from now if we do somehow manage to avoid going over the fiscal cliff isn’t really about debt. No, what we’re having is a political crisis, born of the fact that one of our two great political parties has reached the end of a 30-year road. The modern Republican Party’s grand, radical agenda lies in ruins — but the party doesn’t know how to deal with that failure, and it retains enough power to do immense damage as it strikes out in frustration. Before I talk about that reality, a word about the current state of budget “negotiations.” Why the scare quotes? Because these aren’t normal negotiations in which each side presents specific proposals, and horse-trading proceeds until the two sides converge. By all accounts, Republicans have, so far, offered almost no specifics. They claim that they’re willing to raise $800 billion in revenue by closing loopholes, but they refuse to specify which loopholes they would close; they are demanding large cuts in spending, but the specific cuts they have been willing to lay out wouldn’t come close to delivering the savings they demand. It’s a very peculiar situation. In effect, Republicans are saying to President Obama, “Come up with something that will make us happy.” He is, understandably, not willing to play that game. And so the talks are stuck. Why won’t the Republicans get specific? Because they don’t know how. The truth is that, when it comes to spending, they’ve been faking it all along — not just in this election, but for decades. Which brings me to the nature of the current G.O.P. crisis. Since the 1970s, the Republican Party has fallen increasingly under the influence of radical ideologues, whose goal is nothing less than the elimination of the welfare state — that is, the whole legacy of the New Deal and the Great Society. From the beginning, however, these ideologues have had a big problem: The programs they want to kill are very popular. Americans may nod their heads when you attack big government in the abstract, but they strongly support Social Security, Medicare, and even Medicaid. So what’s a radical to do? The answer, for a long time, has involved two strategies. One is “starve the beast,” the idea of using tax cuts to reduce government revenue, then using the resulting lack of funds to force cuts in popular social programs. Whenever you see some Republican politician piously denouncing federal red ink, always remember that, for decades, the G.O.P. has seen budget deficits as a feature, not a bug. Arguably more important in conservative thinking, however, was the notion that the G.O.P. could exploit other sources of strength — white resentment, working-class dislike of social change, tough talk on national security — to build overwhelming political dominance, at which point the dismantling of the welfare state could proceed freely. Just eight years ago, Grover Norquist, the antitax activist, looked forward cheerfully to the days when Democrats would be politically neutered: “Any farmer will tell you that certain animals run around and are unpleasant, but when they’ve been fixed, then they are happy and sedate.” O.K., you see the problem: Democrats didn’t go along with the program, and refused to give up. Worse, from the Republican point of view, all of their party’s sources of strength have turned into weaknesses. Democratic dominance among Hispanics has overshadowed Republican dominance among southern whites; women’s rights have trumped the politics of abortion and antigay sentiment; and guess who finally did get Osama bin Laden. And look at where we are now in terms of the welfare state: far from killing it, Republicans now have to watch as Mr. Obama implements the biggest expansion of social insurance since the creation of Medicare. So Republicans have suffered more than an election defeat, they’ve seen the collapse of a decades-long project. And with their grandiose goals now out of reach, they literally have no idea what they want — hence their inability to make specific demands. It’s a dangerous situation. The G.O.P. is lost and rudderless, bitter and angry, but it still controls the House and, therefore, retains the ability to do a lot of harm, as it lashes out in the death throes of the conservative dream. Our best hope is that business interests will use their influence to limit the damage. But the odds are that the next few years will be very, very ugly. December 13, 2012 PAUL KRUGMAN</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1355564649558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 04:44:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355566475772-7</Id><Topic><Title>cars should be banned along with guns cause they kill, mean old cars they are bad bab bad</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1355531628442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 19:33:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you ever heard of someone posting idiotic leftist ramblings after a tragedy just to push their anti American Communist agenda?</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1355566475772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 05:14:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355566662081-8</Id><Topic><Title>Now here's a thought...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355520990585</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:36:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why doesn't your little "hero" from Kent, Kim Jung Raven, think that's such a good idea and would rather see America turn into North Korea?</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1355566662081</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 05:17:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355566769715-9</Id><Topic><Title>Now here's a thought...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355520990585</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:36:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kim Jung Raven, You are a flaming idiot. Harry</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1355566769715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 05:19:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355566851591-10</Id><Topic><Title>HOORAY for the Second Amendment -- Again!</Title><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1355511843206</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:04:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a wing nut.</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1355566851591</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 05:20:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355570153105-11</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy Hook Elementary School massacre by yet another gun nut!</Title><Username>natsu4fun</Username><Timestamp>1355536363058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:52:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's 6 am and not a word anywhere in the news about Adam Lanza being a lifetime member of the NRA, nor about his political affiliation, 'cept now he may have been a "goth" or suffer from a developmental disorder, Asperger’s syndrome. natsu4fun, you are posting the same false information as others tried immediately after each of the slayings which have occurred during the last couple of years. It didn't stick then and won't stick now, unless it turns out to be a valid statement, but since it's early on in the investigation and considering the cost of life membership and Adam Lanza's young age, I seriously doubt you are telling the truth. Your credibility lacks.documentation, so you become an unreliable source of information.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355570153105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 06:15:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355570453548-12</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy Hook Elementary School massacre by yet another gun nut!</Title><Username>natsu4fun</Username><Timestamp>1355536363058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:52:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is your source of information? Is it the same as natsu4fun's? I seriously doubt you are telling the truth. Your credibility lacks.documentation, so you become an unreliable source of information.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355570453548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 06:20:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355570810068-13</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy Hook Elementary School massacre by yet another gun nut!</Title><Username>natsu4fun</Username><Timestamp>1355536363058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:52:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One news source now informs us that Adam Lanza was taking anti-depressants. Maybe prescriptions for anti-depressants should be banned instead!</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355570810068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 06:26:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355571367271-14</Id><Topic><Title>787 Teathing Issues</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1355529209542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:53:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 787 wiil be grounded for good soon. Hopfully before one crashes and shatters like glass.</Msg><Username>john.kloczkowski</Username><Timestamp>1355571367271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 06:36:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355571464904-15</Id><Topic><Title>"I know there's not a parent in America who doesn't feel the same overwhelming grief that I do," Obama</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355526679554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:11:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I know there's not a parent in America who doesn't feel the same overwhelming grief that I do," Obama. This is a direct quote of Obama. It is the first words from his mouth which the media now ignores, after his gaff. It reflects his narcissistic personality. Tell me what part is not true or becomes political in my following statement. I seriously doubt that !!! Only those parents who lost their loved ones or others who have lost a child in the past can feel what they are feeling! Why does Obama always have to turn events into something about him? The SAME overwhelming grief ...NO WAY!! Obama DID NOT personally lose a child of his in this tragedy. It is callous of him to claim his grief is as strong or stronger than any one of the parents who did !! It is his narcissistic personality tendencies turning every event into something about himself that I find absolutely offensive and insensitive to those who lost THEIR CHILDREN today !! It is a shame Obama chose to insert himself into this tragedy in this way. Obama has politicized the event as are the rest of the antipgunners before the bodies have been removed from the crime scene. Shame on all of you !!</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355571464904</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 06:37:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355572606953-16</Id><Topic><Title>cars should be banned along with guns cause they kill, mean old cars they are bad bab bad</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1355531628442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 19:33:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have read of cars being used to intentionally kill people. It happens too frequently, so by the standards you are trying to set for guns, similar ones need to be instituted for cars, and which organization do you suggest we lay all the blame? Triple AAA?</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355572606953</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 06:56:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355573340358-17</Id><Topic><Title>787 Teathing Issues</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1355529209542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:53:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've worked with composite materials. It is difficult to get reliable, dependable, repeatably consistent flawless results with some composite materials. I personally think management is pushing composites before they are ready for mass production. Time will tell. It isn't the first time an aircraft company has tried to get ahead of the competitors by taking too big of a risk in design which ends badly.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355573340358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 07:09:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355574726448-18</Id><Title>Boeing stock price may not go up for another 9 years read why!</Title><Msg>The Boeing Company told the Times on December 10 that it “remains confident [that it will earn] low single digit” profit margins on the first 1,100- 787 planes, which includes deliveries into 2021. However the UBS aerospace analyst and expert, Strauss, calls foul on that Boeing Management promise, Mr. Strauss, said, just like Boeing Management being wrong on the delivery date for the 787, off and late by over 3 years and the original budget estimate off and wrong by 30 billion dollars over budget. Expert , Strauss said that Boeing’s latest promise on 787 plane break even time and point is wrong. Strauss calls foul on that breakeven point. As long as the 787 is not able to make money the Boeing stockholder can expect another 9 years of no stock price increase like the last 3 years in which Boeing has hovered around 75 or lower , while other Dow Jones companies have made gains that are keeping up with the 3 year stock market rally. For example Bank of America, BAC is up 90% this year while Boeing is up .9%, that is less than one percent all year. . Strauss said the 787 will lose between $4 billion and $5 billion on the 787 over the next three years and it will take until 2021 to start making a profit.UBS expert Strauss, said the 787 lists for $206.8 million, but the Boeing shareholder’s are losing $116 million on each plane delivered, no way to get a Boeing stock price gain. Based on the way Boeing Management has flubbed the 787 so far, Boeing’s ability fix the 787′s technical glitches and earn back its investment on the plane is very doubtful. The problem is 60% of the design was outsourced and so Boeing shareholders are responsible for all the late and failed airplanes, but the Boeing company has lost all control of the parts manufacturing process control.. It is like all the Boeing shareholders are on the Titanic and can see the iceberg but are not smart enough to get in a life boat. The iceberg is there to see, it has been there for three years now. For those Boeing investors the problem was first described by Bruce Henderson, a manufacturing expert, Bruce noticed in 1936 that any manufacturer needs to learn how to make the product faster and at less cost to make any money. So far the Boeing 787 hole is deep, 3 years late, just to get to the original expected original delivery date, or start, now with the constant fixes the 787 has been delayed at least seven times in production and at least 7 times after delivery, , and the cost is over 120% more than Boeing management budgeted. With some 865 orders for the 787, and less than 40 planes delivered, just do the math, the Boeing Company 787 order book does not have enough planes to break even( at least 1500) let alone, enough 787 planes to make any a profit .. Boeing stock price for the last the 3 years has been a dead stock while the overall market has been on a run up for 3 years now. So Boeing stock price tends to , tank at $ 75 and dividend taxes were 15% and now going up to 50%, Given the Boeing 787 problem which is one of the main cause of the poor stock price , this Boeing stock price may stagnate for at least another 9 years until 2021. So for any enthusiastic, Boeing investor , also have the Fiscal Cliff and the sequestration cuts which the Defense Department says it has begun planning for the roughly $500 billion in program cuts. SPEEA and IAM wage and benefits have nothing to do with 60% of the design and parts production. The story of Union-Manager labor strikes is nothing but a management scapegoat to fool investors. The stock price is due only to mismanagement of the 787 business plan. . Wages of Boeing worker account for only 4% of the plane costs , unless you add management costs then it is up to 8%.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355574726448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 07:32:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355575000499-19</Id><Topic><Title>787 Teathing Issues</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1355529209542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:53:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>worse yet if you read up on the 787 the break even pint is according to a analyst much farther out than Boeing claims which is why the Boeing stock price is dead at 75 or lower while the stock market has been on the 3 year run up. So Boeing stock may be at 75 for another 9 years unless the 787 crashes and is cancelled then the stock tanks not a good risk when the government really subsidizes banks like BAC up 90% year to dat compard to Boeing up 9/10th on 1 percent year to date and for those enthusiastic Boeing shreholders who claim dividend well that 15%tax is going up to about 50% now so if you own Boeing stock your on the titanic and looking at the iceberg and not smart enough to get in a lifeboat and go to a better stock</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355575000499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 07:36:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355575266143-20</Id><Topic><Title>787 Teathing Issues</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1355529209542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:53:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thre has never been a mass produced successful mass produced large passenger plane, Boeing mismangment sholdbe fired for fiduciary failure this was a experiment. Aluminum should have been used the comet failed and that was the first jet engine and the large windows gave Boeing the next and best plane and they can not learn from history what failures these airplanes need to fly 24-7=365 for 30 years and get banged around by flight crew and ground employees a aluminum dent is easy to see a damaged carbon fiber dent may go as ok until it fails at 30000 feet and makes the plane crashe</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355575266143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 07:41:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355575389088-21</Id><Topic><Title>787 Teathing Issues</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1355529209542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:53:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this was a total experiment on shareholder dime a carbon fiber large plane for civilian use has never been done this is Boeings version of BOAC comet and may kill Boieng I think MD BOD is deliberately doing this to get even with Boeing for killing their company , using the same method too outsourcing</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355575389088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 07:43:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355575514939-22</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Boeing.. You Should Outsource Management</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1355504596817</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:03:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>terminate managment and do a reshuffle, the MD outsourcing business plan failed so take the golden parachute and MD boys and be gone .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355575514939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 07:45:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355575831732-23</Id><Topic><Title>Qatar airlines to drop Boeing and go with Airbus? , Harsh words for Boeing !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355446155297</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 19:49:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the 380 has a lot of problems for sure but the Boeing shine a caca 747 is 2 years late and 2 billion over budget and the market is not big enough for 2 super jumbos so it does nt matter the Boeing cash cow 747 is done or at least not a cash cow , just a cow now Boeing had form 1970 to when th airbust guys figured out allan mulally was stringing them on about a groupd team of airbust and boeing all new plane, that was unethical of allen, gee go figure !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355575831732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 07:50:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355576013346-24</Id><Topic><Title>Qatar airlines to drop Boeing and go with Airbus? , Harsh words for Boeing !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355446155297</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 19:49:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well we know 3 years late and 30 billion over budget and 7 times delayed in production and 7 fails after delivery and less than 40 make so you bet a lot more not so secret failures on the 787. This plane is the comet of Boeing the management killed the goose that laid the golden egg they went with cheap 60% outsourced design and the plane is dead and so is the Boeing stock price too</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355576013346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 07:53:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355576161114-25</Id><Topic><Title>Two leaders a Boeing Executive a American President both Harvard Graduates! result!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355438905222</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 17:48:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Boeing company is pitting labor against management to attempt to cover the real problem executive failure and excessive executive pay, hence the 787 prime example of bad managment</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355576161114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 07:56:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355578255082-26</Id><Topic><Title>"I know there's not a parent in America who doesn't feel the same overwhelming grief that I do," Obama</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355526679554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:11:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Obama, how can you possibly think your grief is as intense or overwhelming as the grief of the parents who lost their children yesterday?</Msg><Username>bobbobareno</Username><Timestamp>1355578255082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 08:30:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355578451081-27</Id><Title>Boeing stock price to fail until 2021 or for another 9 more years</Title><Msg>UBS aerospace analyst, Strauss said that Boeing Company claim that the 787 airplane will start to make money in 2015 is wrong. Strauss, said the first plane to make money will be in 2021.The 787 learning curve has shifted 9 years into the future, now each plane costs the shareholder 116 million loss. While the stock market has been on a 3 year run up BA stock has not kept pace , Strauss said he does not agree that Boeing will breadk even in 2015, and that means the Boeing stock price stays at 75 dollars or less. level. This will continue as ong as the 787 can not make a profit. The BA dividend is also not going up in fact it must go down, as the government has changed the dividend tax rate which in January will go from 15% to 45% or more. Next the Defense spending will be cut by 500 billion so Boeing will not make as much revenue in the defense side of the company. Meanwhile the DOW Jones stocks that are supported like BAC a bank is up 90% year to date and BA is up only .01% year to date.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355578451081</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 08:34:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355579405000-28</Id><Title>Boeing's 787 fuel-line connectors and the fix</Title><Msg>The Federal Aviation Administration is ordering airlines to inspect all of Boeing’s 787s for improperly installed fuel-line connectors that could result in leaks or even fires. UBS thinks the 787 will not break even until after 2021 so the share price should stay at the current price until the 787 starts to make money. BA stockholders would be smart to move to the general stock market and make some monye BA is up less than a percent this year while the Dow is up over seven percent and the nasdaq is up over fourteen percent individial stocks like Bank of America have almost doubled in stock value so nine more years of fail on Boeing shre price appreciation or move on or you can go for that divident, oh I forgot the fifteen percent tax just went up next year to over fourty percent well if you really think Boeing stock is a hold you can stay will seventyfive dollars and dream about eight or one hundred percent gain or actually get the gain on other stocks .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355579405000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 08:50:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355580783313-29</Id><Topic><Title>Two leaders a Boeing Executive a American President both Harvard Graduates! result!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355438905222</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 17:48:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harvard a center for socialism. FDR brought on a decade of pain with his socialist experiment, and Obama is doing the same with virtually the same model for failure. The both promoted big centeralized govt rather than the private sector. Socialist leaders like Obama think you are DUMB, and you need their big govt plantation. Liberals accept that they are dumb. Republican conservatives anyway, think self sufficiency is the right direction with much smaller govt getting involved.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355580783313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 09:13:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355580806450-30</Id><Topic><Title>"I know there's not a parent in America who doesn't feel the same overwhelming grief that I do," Obama</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355526679554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:11:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"dude, you watch too much Fox News." And exactly where is Fox hiding/shading facts such as your likely news sources that would probably defend Obama if HE were the murderer, providing he used some method other than guns of course?</Msg><Username>cws2012wc</Username><Timestamp>1355580806450</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 09:13:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355580842323-31</Id><Topic><Title>"I know there's not a parent in America who doesn't feel the same overwhelming grief that I do," Obama</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355526679554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:11:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, we get it Obama, so you think there's not one parent in America who doesn't feel the SAME("same" being the key word to understanding my anger and disappointment) overwhelming grief that you do? I BET I CAN POINT TO A FEW WHOSE GRIEF IS MUCH, MUCH MORE OVERWHELMING than yours!</Msg><Username>bobbobareno</Username><Timestamp>1355580842323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 09:14:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355582118098-32</Id><Topic><Title>Two leaders a Boeing Executive a American President both Harvard Graduates! result!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355438905222</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 17:48:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dude you don't know soschulism from your own #$%$ so why try to display your ignorance of the subject on this board</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1355582118098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 09:35:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355582637407-33</Id><Topic><Title>"I know there's not a parent in America who doesn't feel the same overwhelming grief that I do," Obama</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355526679554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:11:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Y A W W N N N...</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1355582637407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 09:43:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355582871988-34</Id><Topic><Title>"I know there's not a parent in America who doesn't feel the same overwhelming grief that I do," Obama</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355526679554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:11:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And to further that point....there are lots, and lots of parents who don't even know who their kids are...fathered kids they don't even know who they are. You libs live in lyin la-la land.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355582871988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 09:47:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355583176105-35</Id><Topic><Title>Two leaders a Boeing Executive a American President both Harvard Graduates! result!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355438905222</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 17:48:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ever see a video, a u-tube maybe of that Harvard campus?...looks like kooksville in San Fransisco....earrings out the wazzoo, hair all over the place, and they haven't bathed in a week. I think today is the day they all get together and bathe.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355583176105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 09:52:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355585572024-36</Id><Topic><Title>Will the World End on December 21st ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355547687495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 00:01:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Corporate State Run Media is now inflitrated (compartmentalized to be sure...but STILL infiltrated at the top ..and bought off by bailouts, contributions and favors) with the previso that the cowards play ball by weeding out ALL anti-whitwhouse links.....Comet Niburu and Poll #$%$ and other "end of the world stuff" are allowed to go through...just dont mention REAL AMERICAN ending stuff like the Pentagon now works with AlQaeda in Bengazi and Syria or that our El Presidente gives guns to Mexican drug Lords to demonize the second amendment.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355585572024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 10:32:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355585699666-37</Id><Topic><Title>1938 : Fascists Understood The Importance Of Gun Control</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355533251205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:00:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It might be time for "The Poem"</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355585699666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 10:34:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355586086024-38</Id><Topic><Title>"I know there's not a parent in America who doesn't feel the same overwhelming grief that I do," Obama</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355526679554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:11:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I cried when I heard about the wails of terror that happened when they said their will be no more children entering the firehouse! I was also angered and shocked when a right wing gun lobbyist insisted that more guns would have prevented this and other slaughters of little children. I hope that this time this tragedy will not be forgot with nothing done about the gun insanity. Why wait until your child is gunned down before doing something so it will not happen to another child! Now that your child is alive and you can hug your child do call all your elected officials and demand the worlds strictest gun control. Please everyone I beg you to demand that our children stop being slaughtered by these gun nuts.</Msg><Username>natsu4fun</Username><Timestamp>1355586086024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 10:41:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355586993855-39</Id><Title>Operation Fast and Furious</Title><Msg>With all this talk about Gun Control, the Next thing ya know we will have an Attorney General giving Guns to Mexican Drug Lords to demonize firearms. Or a Tim McVeigh who had the Leading Mind Control Expert in the country as his personal therapist.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355586993855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 10:56:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355587125841-40</Id><Topic><Title>Operation Fast and Furious</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355586993855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 10:56:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are the leading whackjob here on the BA board. Mr. Section 8 himself.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1355587125841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 10:58:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355587162636-41</Id><Topic><Title>1938 : Fascists Understood The Importance Of Gun Control</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355533251205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:00:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed. It would make a great Christmas present to the board!</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1355587162636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 10:59:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355587385537-42</Id><Topic><Title>Operation Fast and Furious</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355586993855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 10:56:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No way. You are nuttier than anyone here.</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1355587385537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 11:03:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355588134310-43</Id><Topic><Title>Operation Fast and Furious</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355586993855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 10:56:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO, what happened was we had a previous administration that used Fast &amp; Furious as a method of identifying who the bad guys were...who the Mexican drug lords were...identify them by giving them guns as the bait, and dropped because it was a bad idea. Along comes Obama, and Holder, and decides to use the program as a way of creating gun control through international law and avoiding our constitution, and the 2nd Ammendment. Because of the too many deaths at the border they'd get gun control enacted via international law. Fortunately for the Progressive Movement, and those supporting aggressive, radical activity, Obama prevented the facts from coming out through Executive Order. That's what appears to be the case anyway. Obama, and Holder stopped the key emails they had from ever surfacing.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355588134310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 11:15:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355588262915-44</Id><Topic><Title>Operation Fast and Furious</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355586993855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 10:56:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes...Attorney General caught red handed giving guns to Mexcican drug lords and because I dont bow down and hero worship this kind of activity like the Dik and the Raven, Im considered nuts. When living in Insane times...if one does not go along with insane policies, one is considered insane...youd have to be insane to believe that.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355588262915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 11:17:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355588423245-45</Id><Topic><Title>1938 : Fascists Understood The Importance Of Gun Control</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355533251205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:00:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What constantly bugs me is the left has hated the JEWS. They blame the JEWS for causing 9-11. They blame the JEWS for causing terrorism. YET, the JEW votes democrat in this country. Many, many Jews are self-reliant folks. They made it in America given nothing, but there will to think, and work hard, and many became rich. So what's the deal? Why do they vote democrap?</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355588423245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 11:20:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355588575434-46</Id><Topic><Title>The G.O.P.’s Existential Crisis</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1355564649558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 04:44:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"In fact, its borrowing costs are near historic lows" Since the Chinese no longer want to buy our debt and the only folks willing to buy Government bonds is the US Treasury, I can see why our "costs are at historic lows.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355588575434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 11:22:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355589196512-47</Id><Topic><Title>787 Teathing Issues</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1355529209542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:53:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have probably NOT worked with ANY version of advanced composites. Otherwise you wouldn't have such a vacuous statement.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1355589196512</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 11:33:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355592873814-48</Id><Topic><Title>The G.O.P.’s Existential Crisis</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1355564649558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 04:44:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course checkn would stick with Larry Sinclair's literary "masterpiece." After all, it's # 169,826 on their best seller rank.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1355592873814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:34:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355593172882-49</Id><Title>Pro Lifers should be pro gun control</Title><Msg>but I doubt if it works that way</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1355593172882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:39:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355593337500-50</Id><Title>Secretary of state faints, sustains concussion</Title><Msg>Hmmmm! a likely story. More like she didn't want to testify next week on Benghazi. How would it look to have a pres. fainting every time the going got tough? Search the subject for the article.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1355593337500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:42:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355594070354-51</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355593416703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:43:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The man who shot and killed a number of people at Gabrielle Gifford’s campaign rally and the man who killed the people in the movie theater are still alive. There is no doubt that these men killed these people. Their mental state, either before or after the shootings, is irrelevant. They should be dead by now. We need some public executions to send a message.</Msg><Username>catipillardoodoo</Username><Timestamp>1355594070354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:54:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355594541164-52</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355593416703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:43:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Maher: “We Need To Promote Death” "The planet is too crowded – let’s kill the right people" During a recent appearance on the StarTalk Radio Show, Real Time host Bill Maher expressed his desire to see more people killed via abortion, suicides and the death penalty because “the planet is too crowded and we need to promote death.” Bill is getting his wish for more death.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355594541164</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:02:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355594836287-53</Id><Topic><Title>Secretary of state faints, sustains concussion</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1355593337500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:42:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The concussion will of course result in loss of memory on the Benghazi mess. and any other troublesome issues. Vince will be able to laugh about this one.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1355594836287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:07:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355594959841-54</Id><Topic><Title>Its all Obama's Fault !!!!! There can be no one else to blame !!!!</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1355535329495</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:35:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You bragging about cheap $3.29 gas just shows how bad it is. 7.9% unemployment is a real warm and fuzzy - let the good times roll</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1355594959841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:09:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355596186294-55</Id><Topic><Title>Two leaders a Boeing Executive a American President both Harvard Graduates! result!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355438905222</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 17:48:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>extremely well stated, except FDR brought a half Century or longer of pain, many big government counter productive programs that only succeeded in prolonging the depression still exist</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1355596186294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:29:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355596388838-56</Id><Topic><Title>787 Teathing Issues</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1355529209542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:53:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have worked with advanced composites. You are making some pretty wild statements considering you know nothing of my work history.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355596388838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:33:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355597381780-57</Id><Topic><Title>Two leaders a Boeing Executive a American President both Harvard Graduates! result!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355438905222</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 17:48:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some people have a very fragile grasp of historical knowledge. It's like they were carrying a jigsaw puzzle of history and dropped it, then put it back together with big chunks in the wrong places.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1355597381780</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:49:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355597854911-58</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355593416703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:43:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What message would you want to send? That you can be just as much of a barbarian as the murderer? Public executions don't have a deterrent effect, if that's what you're thinking.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1355597854911</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:57:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355597944400-59</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day II</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355594727318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:05:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gun Owners of America, which has about 300,000 members and headquartered in Springfield, Va. “Gun-control supporters have the blood of little children on their hands,” Larry Pratt, the group’s executive director, said. “Federal and state laws combined to insure that no teacher, no administrator, no adult had a gun at the Newtown school where the children were murdered. “This tragedy underscores the urgency of getting rid of gun bans in school zones,” he added. “The only thing accomplished by gun-free zones is to ensure that mass murderers can slay more before they are finally confronted by someone with a gun."</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355597944400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:59:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355598230968-60</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355593416703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:43:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell Bill Maher. It's his idea.</Msg><Username>catipillardoodoo</Username><Timestamp>1355598230968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:03:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355599399097-61</Id><Topic><Title>787 Teathing Issues</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1355529209542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:53:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wayne- you are 105 % clueless- stay away from the comic books. composite assemblies have been flying on BA planes for years including major parts on 777 as in horiz stabilizer While some types of damage are not obvious, neither are they prone to brittle faillure. Forget the old fiberglass corvette myths yes I've also worked with composites, including designing tools for cutting/grinding ( brazed diamonds ), drilling, drilling equipment, and developing a process for copper plating of composites. And that was over 20 years ago. The comet failure was due to stress risers at the corners of ' square" windows, combined with pressurization cycles. The material of course was aluminum- very prone to fatigue fractures unless properly designed and fabricated.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1355599399097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:23:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355599872023-62</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day III</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355599496847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:24:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And there wasn't a standing army or navy and no one could have dreamed of an air force</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1355599872023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:31:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355600010480-63</Id><Topic><Title>Two leaders a Boeing Executive a American President both Harvard Graduates! result!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355438905222</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 17:48:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very top management needs to take an 8% pay cut to show they are more dedicated to the company rather than their excessive toys they "have" to have to be considered successful</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1355600010480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:33:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355600105514-64</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day III</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355599496847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:24:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So let the criminals keep their 20-30 round clips and their semi-auto pistols, which I might add become more difficult to conceal with 20-30 round clips attached, and the rest of us get to defend ourselves using muskets with flintlocks against them? Is that your idea of giving law abiding people the advantage against criminals? Is this how you plan to balance the power between the good and the bad?</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355600105514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:35:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355600334757-65</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Boeing.. You Should Outsource Management</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1355504596817</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:03:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>McNerney gets some blame but shouldn't get the bulk of it........blame Condit &amp; Stonecipher........remember when Condit offered his resignation to the BOD and they finally said "OK,....goodbye".....</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1355600334757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:38:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355600532894-66</Id><Topic><Title>HOORAY for the Second Amendment -- Again!</Title><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1355511843206</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:04:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There are far worse things then mass shootings.....like for example" more brain dead Repubs getting elected or re-elected</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1355600532894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:42:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355601161065-67</Id><Topic><Title>HOORAY for the Second Amendment -- Again!</Title><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1355511843206</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:04:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get help. You are sick.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355601161065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:52:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355602243222-68</Id><Topic><Title>'Right To Live Life In Complete, Stunned Horror,' Added To Constitution</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355601295260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:54:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get help. You are sick.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355602243222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 15:10:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355602290459-69</Id><Topic><Title>'Right To Live Life In Complete, Stunned Horror,' Added To Constitution</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355601295260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:54:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes Hoozie you have the right to" spend every waking moment utterly terrified at the thought of a deranged stranger with a semiautomatic combat rifle gunning you down,” You have fulfilled your potential and your destiny as a total and unmitigated pu$$ie !</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355602290459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 15:11:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355604050718-70</Id><Title>Stop calling these Warmongering, Gun Grabbers.. "Liberals"!!!!</Title><Msg>Obama is bombing 8 countries and passed the NDAA to secretly arrest Americans but he is a Peace Prize winner so it is ok. Obama said “I don’t want to go after your guns” but now the liberals are expoiting every tragedy as a pretext to disarm 310 milion Americans.... Statistcally shootings are down per capita but they don't even care. And for all you Moronic Liberal Cult members who say “you're just mad cause your guy lost…NO …that’s not what this is about..Romney was almost as bad and both are run by the same Mega Banks who want us disarmed so they can rob the day lights out of us Do you NOT understand that every authoritarian society wants their population disarmed ? Do you NOT know about the Globalist UN treaty coming up to restrict the second amendment ? Within MINUTES of the school shootings it was all over the State Run Media at CNN and MSNBC to “get rid of the Guns” STOP CALLING THESE AUTHORITARIANS “Liberals”</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355604050718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 15:40:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355604385597-71</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355593416703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:43:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shooting Scoring Disarming the American public (as in the Diks post) ...will help fill the Eugenics agenda in YOUR post...both by the unspeakable Globalist minion Bill Maher. Good luck...we are all gonna need it</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355604385597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 15:46:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355604534237-72</Id><Topic><Title>Stop calling these Warmongering, Gun Grabbers.. "Liberals"!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355604050718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 15:40:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He does not SOUND paranoid and crazy, he IS paranoid and crazy.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1355604534237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 15:48:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355604672961-73</Id><Topic><Title>Stop calling these Warmongering, Gun Grabbers.. "Liberals"!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355604050718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 15:40:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After Drones flying over American Soil, endless undeclared unprovoked wars, the NDAA over turning the Magna Carta and the Patriot Act and Warrantless wiretapping, Agenda 21, , bought off media trying to brainswash a Dumbed down public...and the evisceration of the second amendment including a record number of Executive orders...we have REASON to be paranoid.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355604672961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 15:51:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355604948279-74</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355593416703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:43:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did 6 million unarmed people walk silently to the gas chambers without fighting back ? ============== "The most foolish mistake we could possibly make would be to allow the subject races to possess arms. History shows that all conquerors who have allowed their subject races to carry arms have prepared their own downfall by so doing. Indeed, I would go so far as to say that the supply of arms to the underdogs is a sine qua non for the overthrow of any sovereignty. So let's not have any native militia or native police. German troops alone will bear the sole responsibility for the maintenance of law and order throughout the occupied Russian territories, and a system of military strong-points must be evolved to cover the entire occupied country." --Adolf Hitler, dinner talk on April 11, 1942</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355604948279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 15:55:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355605721965-75</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day III</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355599496847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:24:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course Principal Dawn Hochsprung, a quintessential heroine, having nothing other than her own body to lunge at the shooter, did so, and the gunman cut her down. That is because there is a "zero tolerance" for weapons in schools - even to protect themselves. Had she had access to a gun to protect the students, there may have been a chance that there would be more survivors. Hooz, you are of the stereotypical liberal delusion that banning guns (or most guns) will result in zero New Town type of massacres. But the fact is that the U.S. Government, under the leadership of one Att Gen Holder, allowed almost 1400 weapons of a similar type used in New Town to be used by the cartels to mow down nearly 200 Mexican citizens. The key here is that the government only has the capability to regulate people willing to be regulated. It fails everywhere else. And the criminals and crazy folks will find the tools that they need to create havoc and death. Timothy McVeigh, for example, used common materials to create a bomb that also killed about 20 children, and 168 people total. No guns there. Perhaps what is wrong with our society was illustrated at a gathering in September of politically minded folks where God was initially banned from their political platform and then booed when they felt a perfunctory obligation to put Him back in - amongst the abominations. I suspect that He was not impressed with the haughty spirit.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1355605721965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 16:08:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355607080232-76</Id><Topic><Title>Do We Have the Courage to Stop This?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355605992215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 16:13:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Night of the Broken Glass (Kristallnacht)--the infamous Nazi rampage against Germany's Jews--took place in November 1938. IT WAS PRECEDED BY THE CONFISCATION OF FIREARMS from the Jewish victims. On Nov. 8, the New York Times reported from Berlin, "Berlin Police Head Announces 'Disarming' of Jews," explaining: The Berlin Police President, Count Wolf Heinrich von Helldorf, announced that as a result of a police activity in the last few weeks the entire Jewish population of Berlin had been "disarmed" with the confiscation of 2,569 hand weapons, 1,702 firearms and 20,000 rounds of ammunition. Any Jews still found in possession of weapons without valid licenses are threatened with the severest punishment.1 On the evening of Nov. 9, Adolf Hitler, Propaganda Minister Joseph Goebbels, and other Nazi chiefs planned the attack. Orders went out to Nazi security forces: "All Jewish stores are to be destroyed immediately . . . . Jewish synagogues are to be set on fire . . . . The Führer wishes that the police does not intervene. . . . All Jews are to be disarmed. In the event of resistance they are to be shot immediately."2 All hell broke loose on Nov. 10: "Nazis Smash, Loot and Burn Jewish Shops and Temples." "One of the first legal measures issued was an order by Heinrich Himmler, commander of all German police, forbidding Jews to possess any weapons whatever and imposing a penalty of twenty years confinement in a concentration camp upon every Jew found in possession of a weapon hereafter."3 Thousands of Jews were taken away. Invading Nazi troops in Holland in 1940 immediately nailed up posters announcing a ban on all firearms. From Die Deutsche Wochenshau, May 15, 1940. (Photo by Moser + Rosié, Berlin) Searches of Jewish homes were calculated to seize firearms and assets and to arrest adult males. The American Consulate in Stuttgart was flooded with Jews begging for visas: "Men in whose homes old, rusty revolvers had been found during the last few days cried aloud that they did not dare ever again return to their places of residence or business. In fact, it was a mass of seething, panic-stricken humanity."4 Himmler, head of the Nazi terror police, would become an architect of the Holocaust, which consumed six million Jews. It was self evident that the Jews must be disarmed before the extermination could begin. Finding out which Jews had firearms was not too difficult. The liberal Weimar Republic passed a Firearm Law in 1928 requiring extensive police records on gun owners. Hitler signed a further gun control law in early 1938.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355607080232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 16:31:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355607841317-77</Id><Topic><Title>Do We Have the Courage to Stop This?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355605992215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 16:13:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do what Israel did.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355607841317</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 16:44:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355607947070-78</Id><Topic><Title>Do We Have the Courage to Stop This?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355605992215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 16:13:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Throughot history....and without EXCEPTION, slave hae to be DISARMED.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355607947070</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 16:45:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355608737281-79</Id><Topic><Title>"I know there's not a parent in America who doesn't feel the same overwhelming grief that I do," Obama</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355526679554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:11:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. To pick apart every single word he uses, you musyt REALLY hate Obama, don't you?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1355608737281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 16:58:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355608960022-80</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day III</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355599496847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:24:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New Rule: All Teachers Should Be Allowed to Carry Guns</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355608960022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 17:02:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355609849401-81</Id><Topic><Title>"I know there's not a parent in America who doesn't feel the same overwhelming grief that I do," Obama</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355526679554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:11:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't you find it strange the media no longer shows the first words that came out of Obama's mouth? They all cut in somewhere shortly afterwards and continue the clip from there. It was a major mistake attributed to Obama himself to suggest his grief was anywhere near to that of the victims families.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355609849401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 17:17:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355610612234-82</Id><Title>Boeing stock price and the 787 being late, overbudget and a failed outsourced plane are tied together</Title><Msg>However the UBS aerospace analyst and expert, Strauss, calls foul on that Boeing Management promise, Mr. Strauss, said, just like Boeing Management being wrong on the delivery date for the 787, off and late by over 3 years and the original budget estimate off and wrong by 30 billion dollars over budget. Expert , Strauss said that Boeing’s latest promise on 787 plane break even time and point is wrong. Strauss calls foul on that breakeven point. As long as the 787 is not able to make money the Boeing stockholder can expect another 9 years of no stock price increase like the last 3 years in which Boeing has hovered around 75 or lower , while other Dow Jones companies have made gains that are keeping up with the 3 year stock market rally.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1355610612234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 17:30:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355612037805-83</Id><Topic><Title>"I know there's not a parent in America who doesn't feel the same overwhelming grief that I do," Obama</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355526679554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:11:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah shut up.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1355612037805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 17:53:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355612170492-84</Id><Topic><Title>"I know there's not a parent in America who doesn't feel the same overwhelming grief that I do," Obama</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355526679554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:11:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your a paid Troll Fact</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355612170492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 17:56:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355612443564-85</Id><Title>I agree with the gun lobby</Title><Msg>I agree with the gun lobby about re-opening many of the mental health hospitals that have been closed in order to give huge tax break to top earners.That surely was penny wise and pound foolish! However we certainly also need the worlds best gun regulations and many ideas on this board are great like the yearly police visit to homes of gun owners to make sure they are sane and sober and the guns are locked up safely!Also the tax stamps on guns and bullets is a good idea to pay for the needed new sane gun regulations! The slaughter of little children is not acceptable so this unregulated gun industry must be made responsible!</Msg><Username>lostcityundead</Username><Timestamp>1355612443564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 18:00:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355614007130-86</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy Hook Elementary School massacre by yet another gun nut!</Title><Username>natsu4fun</Username><Timestamp>1355536363058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 20:52:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This would implicate drug companies and Psychologists not the NRA.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355614007130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 18:26:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355614465135-87</Id><Topic><Title>Do We Have the Courage to Stop This?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355605992215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 16:13:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>leftwing fascist soicalists wanting to take away our guns...nothing new. Kinda tells you the virdict on Fast and Furious without even knowing the virdict due to Obama's Executive Order. They all spew the same crapola coming out of #$%$ pinko central headquarters.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355614465135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 18:34:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355614701517-88</Id><Topic><Title>787 Teathing Issues</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1355529209542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:53:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably best not to argue with the troll. He probably thinks "composites" are brick and adobe. He clearly has zero idea about the 767 parts 31 years ago, 777 floor beams &amp; 48 section, etc.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1355614701517</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 18:38:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355615021460-89</Id><Topic><Title>I agree with the gun lobby</Title><Username>lostcityundead</Username><Timestamp>1355612443564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 18:00:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are literally thousands of gun laws and regulations at the federal and state levels, below is a few of the federal laws, so the term "unregulated gun industry" does not square with the facts National Firearms Act (1934) Omnibus Crime Control and Safe Streets Act of 1968 (1968) Gun Control Act of 1968 (1968) Firearm Owners Protection Act (1986) Gun-Free School Zones Act (1990) . Brady Handgun Violence Prevention Act (1993) Federal Assault Weapons Ban (1994–2004) (expired)</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1355615021460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 18:43:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355616955333-90</Id><Topic><Title>I agree with the gun lobby</Title><Username>lostcityundead</Username><Timestamp>1355612443564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 18:00:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with you that more has to be done - but first, the existing gun laws should be evforced. No one enforces the existing laws anymore - for example, 40 years ago, a cop pulled you over for speeding or running a red light - how often do you see that anymore?</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1355616955333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:15:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355617026051-91</Id><Topic><Title>I agree with the gun lobby</Title><Username>lostcityundead</Username><Timestamp>1355612443564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 18:00:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great post....</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355617026051</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:17:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355617127781-92</Id><Topic><Title>"I know there's not a parent in America who doesn't feel the same overwhelming grief that I do," Obama</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355526679554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:11:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coming from you, spartapus, that is high praise.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1355617127781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:18:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355617444215-93</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355593416703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:43:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean the part about Bill Maher being in favor of mass Eugenics ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355617444215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:24:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355617480048-94</Id><Title>Forget Gun Control .</Title><Msg>We need nut control . Put the butterfly net on 'em just like they did in the "good old days ." The idea of altering society, or depriving the general public of constitutional rights in order to let fruitcakes run loose is a silly Liberal idea whose time has gone . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1355617480048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:24:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355617787044-95</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Gun Control .</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1355617480048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:24:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean you really want to lock up all the Baggers?</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1355617787044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:29:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355618123064-96</Id><Topic><Title>Do We Have the Courage to Stop This?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355605992215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 16:13:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Holocaust was started by Gun Regulation...and most naive saps back then, said Eugenics could never happen in Gernmany...but it did. Bill Maher, and the people who pay him, believe in Eugenics too. Its not that you keep espousing repeated anti American nonsense that is so troubling, its that it is amazing that their are ignorant individuals like yourself that can lap up "liberal" talking points repeatedly without understanding that history repudiates everything you regurgitate here and giving multiple reasons (likethe Holocaust) .....despite the fact that there is Nothing "liberal" about giving up personal responsibility. I told you there were worse things then shootings at schools or movie theatres....and there are.....what you advocate is the first step down that path.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355618123064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:35:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355618533339-97</Id><Title>Some 787s Grounded</Title><Msg>It is outrageous some improperly assembled 787s passed inspection at Boeing. Then we have this guy here who claims to be a union engineer at Boeing for 22 years and is clueless that Boeing has any standards. It would not surprise me if this individual and his buddies had something to do with these defective airplanes getting the approval for delivery to airline customers.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1355618533339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:42:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355618616898-98</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Gun Control .</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1355617480048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:24:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unlike the violent OWS, baggers are harmless.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355618616898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:43:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355619069218-99</Id><Topic><Title>Do We Have the Courage to Stop This?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355605992215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 16:13:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is magical misinformed thinking at its best. Chicago has the most restrictive gun regulations in the land and there were 33 gunshot homicides in November 2012. More kids die every 6 weeks in Chicago than died in the Sandy Hook shooting yet Obama had no tears for the last 4 years for Chicago kids.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355619069218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:51:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355619280659-100</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355593416703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:43:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing Maher uses his balls for is to teabag #$%$.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355619280659</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:54:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355619712910-101</Id><Topic><Title>Do We Have the Courage to Stop This?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355605992215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 16:13:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your own "liberal" web site at the Huffington Post said Mass shootings are NOT on the rise. google it. I will end my teaching to the ignorant with the great quote from General Yamomoto...."You cannot invade the mainland United States. There would be a rifle behind each blade of grass." And so it is with free men</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355619712910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:01:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355619727622-102</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Gun Control .</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1355617480048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:24:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Attention jUmBooosCa*skiBB: Good idea. But you need to make sure to watch out for the man with the net.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1355619727622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:02:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355619807191-103</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355593416703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:43:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did Obama's tears and lowering flags help? As many kids die in Chicago every 6 weeks but they don't get tears from the president or flags at 1/2 mast.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355619807191</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:03:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355619833071-104</Id><Topic><Title>Some 787s Grounded</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1355618533339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>787 inspections? HAR HAR HAR HAR.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1355619833071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:03:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355619985163-105</Id><Topic><Title>787 Teathing Issues</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1355529209542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:53:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wayne ..."thre has never been a mass produced successful mass produced large passenger plane," Uhhhh - you mean there is no such thing as a 747 ? Its all virtual ?? Or are ewe talking about Large PASSENGERS - with oversized egos ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1355619985163</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:06:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355620876211-106</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Gun Control .</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1355617480048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:24:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The shutting down of all the public mental hospitals is a right wing accomplishment. The right wing wants all them hospitals replaced with privatized prisons!</Msg><Username>lostcityundead</Username><Timestamp>1355620876211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:21:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355621609342-107</Id><Title>Gun control is a mith!</Title><Msg>The only gun control in the world is the person that holds the gun!</Msg><Username>barbing1965</Username><Timestamp>1355621609342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:33:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355622096550-108</Id><Topic><Title>Non-Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355620516083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:15:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Immaterial. We also do not know for sure...whether King Leonidas ever stated "molṑn labé" in a classical expression of defiance in response to the Persian army's demand that the Spartans surrender their weapons at the Battle of Thermopylae. There is no mistaking what it means...and STILL means to All men who honor freedom in the face of Tyranny ...NOW...or then!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355622096550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:41:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355622183254-109</Id><Topic><Title>Gun control is a mith!</Title><Username>barbing1965</Username><Timestamp>1355621609342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:33:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gun Control is Sight Alignment and Sight Picture</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355622183254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:43:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355622399030-110</Id><Topic><Title>Gun control is a mith!</Title><Username>barbing1965</Username><Timestamp>1355621609342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:33:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being a former Investagative detective, I know more than the average person about homicides!</Msg><Username>barbing1965</Username><Timestamp>1355622399030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:46:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355623097661-111</Id><Topic><Title>Non-Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355620516083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:15:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Japan didnt invade though did it? ....The high command KNEW that there was a "rifle behind every blade of grass", regardless whether Yamomoto stated it EXACTLY that way or not it or not. Cant get more "Material" then that. Leonaides may or may not have said Molan Labe. Doesnt matter to free men who know freedom in the face of Tyranny is not free.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355623097661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:58:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355623774363-112</Id><Title>Greatest political quote of all time.</Title><Msg>James Carville quote as to why he became a Democrat operative..."because liberals are stupid" HAHA And they sure haven't disappointment James since he retired after getting Slick Willy elected.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1355623774363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 21:09:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355623792312-113</Id><Topic><Title>Operation Fast and Furious</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355586993855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 10:56:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post as usual Spartacus. 5 stars!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1355623792312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 21:09:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355624853192-114</Id><Topic><Title>Secretary of state faints, sustains concussion</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1355593337500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:42:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Must of been scripted into the act. Geez, these people are pathetic! Anyone want to hear a Hillary quote like, "She had gone on what she thought would be a great jog. She was going down to Battery Park, she was going to go around the towers. She was going to get a cup of coffee and --- that's when the plane hit." Hillary Clinton, about daughter Chelsea, who watched the 9/11 attacks on TV about 40 blocks north of Ground Zero. That woman couldn't tell the truth even if her husband's life depended on it!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1355624853192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 21:27:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355624883639-115</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Gun Control .</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1355617480048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:24:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only people who write stuff like "Attention jUmBooosCa*skiBB:" need to worry about the net . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1355624883639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 21:28:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355626052923-116</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Gun Control .</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1355617480048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:24:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1.) Yeah, sure . They are always to blame, always . They're under your bed, too . 2.) Whatever keeps the nut in the bag . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1355626052923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 21:47:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355627366788-117</Id><Title>A stretch of credulity</Title><Msg>"Secretary of State Hillary Clinton will not be able to testify before House and Senate committees next week on the Benghazi issue due to a concussion, the State Department said Saturday. Clinton was a scheduled to testify Thursday on the Sept. 11 terror attacks on the U.S. Consulate in Benghazi, Libya, in which U.S. Ambassador Christopher Stephens and three other Americans were killed. Deputy Assistant Secretary of State Philippe Reines said Saturday that Clinton is suffering from a stomach virus, fainted and hit her head, which caused the concussion." Up until now, or with this as a continuing "saga", there have been nothing but lies give to the American pulbic about Benghazi. Now, I would like to believe that this is the truth, but the on-going record of lack of transparency is not helpful.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1355627366788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 22:09:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355629464595-118</Id><Title>THIS POST GOES OUT TO REAL AMERICANS</Title><Msg>Arn't my fellow Red blooded Americans tired about being lectured by dweebs about things like the second amendment (that is CLEARLY A RIGHT IN THE CONSTITUTION) and yet condone and even applaud things that are CLEARLY NOT in the constitution like health care. Those that lecture us about shootings at schools but applaud unending wars that kill more children then we can count overseas ? WHY ? .....or an Attorney General that gives guns to drug lords a'la "Fast and Furious." Freedom for Privacy is attacked as our Government knows EVERYTHING ABOUT US and we know nothing about our own President (who has hid his personal records from the public for years). A President that now, through Executive Order via the NDAA, can rendition you to Gitmo, with no Judge and No Jury yet continuously says that he can pardon anyone at will. A President that circumvents the Constituional requirement of having Congress declare War by stating he takes his war powers from the United Nations. A 4th amendment that mandates the right to privacy and "probable Cause" but why is it our wives get felt up at the AirPort by the TSA ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355629464595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 22:44:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355629760098-119</Id><Topic><Title>A stretch of credulity</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1355627366788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 22:09:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Expect nothing less than softball pitches from Mr. Skull and Bones Kerry. It is said he will replace the matriarch of the Democrats as Secretary of State during Obama’s second term. Even Fox News thinks there’s something fishy about an arms transfer that went down at the time of ambassador Stevens’ death. “A mysterious Libyan ship — reportedly carrying weapons and bound for Syrian rebels — may have some link to the Sept. 11 terror attack on the U.S. Consulate in Benghazi,” Fox News reported on October 25. On the night of Sept. 11, in what would become his last known public meeting, Stevens met with the Turkish Consul General Ali Sait Akin, and escorted him out of the consulate front gate one hour before the assault began at approximately 9:35 p.m. local time. Although what was discussed at the meeting is not public, a source told Fox News that Stevens was in Benghazi to negotiate a weapons transfer, an effort to get SA-7 missiles out of the hands of Libya-based extremists. And although the negotiation said to have taken place may have had nothing to do with the attack on the consulate later that night or the Libyan mystery ship, it could explain why Stevens was traveling in such a volatile region on the 11th anniversary of the 9/11 attacks. “In politics, nothing happens by accident. If it happens, you can bet it was planned that way,” said FDR. According to the official explanation published by the establishment’s premier propaganda tool, the New York Times, the Obama administration was “worried about the consequences of its hidden hand in helping arm Libyan militants,” in other words al-Qaeda. Following NATO’s violent overthrow of Gaddafi and the murder of 30,000 Libyans, al-Qaeda received a large cache of weapons, including surface-to-air missiles. Stevens was working with the CIA under State Department “diplomatic cover” and overseeing the transfer of these weapons from al-Qaeda in Libya to al-Qaeda in Syria when he was killed.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355629760098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 22:49:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355631635928-120</Id><Topic><Title>Some 787s Grounded</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1355618533339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The danger of a fire occurring on one of these 787s is nothing to laugh at.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1355631635928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 23:20:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355633039930-121</Id><Topic><Title>Some 787s Grounded</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1355618533339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MBfield shares his vast knowledge with the world.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1355633039930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 23:43:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355633094230-122</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Gun Control .</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1355617480048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:24:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Easy there jumbot. You're blathering. Again. Even worse than last time.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1355633094230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 23:44:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355633528774-123</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Gun Control .</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1355617480048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:24:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leave jumbohoneybooboot alone. He simply can't help it. Didn't you learn not to pick on the disabled?</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1355633528774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 23:52:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>