<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350207490081-1</Id><Topic><Title>jolly Joey</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1350186373371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 23:46:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought Joe's laughing was briliant. It was the most polite way possible to say, "you're a friggin' lying a s s h o l e." And that's exactly what Rmoney and his side kick Lyin' Ryan are.</Msg><Username>alan_gonquin_is_queer</Username><Timestamp>1350207490081</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 05:38:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350207605244-2</Id><Topic><Title>What to expect if Romney Ryan win</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1350176445845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:00:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...and murders.</Msg><Username>alan_gonquin_is_queer</Username><Timestamp>1350207605244</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 05:40:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350208463172-3</Id><Topic><Title>What to expect if Romney Ryan win</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1350176445845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:00:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chrissy, Is that a promise?</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1350208463172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 05:54:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350214443703-4</Id><Topic><Title>What to expect if Romney Ryan win</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1350176445845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:00:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who are you talking to, which message are you replying to?</Msg><Username>bottomline5182</Username><Timestamp>1350214443703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 07:34:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350214476986-5</Id><Topic><Title>Friday activity</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1350158633355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:03:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the update.</Msg><Username>mrstock52</Username><Timestamp>1350214476986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 07:34:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350218707027-6</Id><Topic><Title>What to expect if Romney Ryan win</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1350176445845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:00:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just hope we don't all off ourselves before Mitt gets in and fixes all the obama caused problems: From the CDC: Study looks at suicide rates from 1928–2007 The overall suicide rate rises and falls in connection with the economy, according to a Centers for Disease Control and Prevention study released online today by the American Journal of Public Health. The study, "Impact of Business Cycles on the U.S. Suicide Rates, 1928–2007" is the first to examine the relationships between age-specific suicide rates and business cycles. The study found the strongest association between business cycles and suicide among people in prime working ages, 25-64 years old. "Knowing suicides increased during economic recessions and fell during expansions underscores the need for additional suicide prevention measures when the economy weakens," said James Mercy, Ph.D., acting director of CDC's Injury Center's Division of Violence Prevention. "It is an important finding for policy makers and those working to prevent suicide."</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1350218707027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 08:45:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350219197234-7</Id><Topic><Title>Imagine a world with 0% taxes....</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1350083423672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For 1/2 this county no imagination is needed - they already don't pay taxes, and 47 million don't pay for food, same with obamaphones, housing, etc.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1350219197234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 08:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350219484301-8</Id><Title>Joe Biden -- a "Real" American.</Title><Msg>Joe Biden is probably the most naturally human politician this country has had since Lyndon Johnson and Jack Kennedy roamed Washington, D.C. It's a huge tribute to Biden's core humanity that he has not allowed the modern media to shrink his candor, heart and compassion for the average American. Ryan and his suffocating Randian ideology, math-challenged budgets, medieval religious beliefs, and his well-rehearsed cliches were in way over his head with Fact Check Biden. Biden said he woldn't impose his religious beliefs on others; he believes in the separation of church and state, a core American belief. Ryan can't separate religion from other things, including the state....that's just plain unAmerican, like most of the RomneyHood master plan to soak the masses and deliver buckets of tax cut gold to millionaires, billionaires and hedge fund managers in distress. I believe the Nov 6 2012 election will be the Official Cease and Desist Order for the modern GOP. Joe Biden hit it completely out of the park - bravo !</Msg><Username>bottomline5183</Username><Timestamp>1350219484301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 08:58:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350221731769-9</Id><Topic><Title>jolly Joey</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1350186373371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 23:46:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hear hear!</Msg><Username>engineer_eds_buttplug</Username><Timestamp>1350221731769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 09:35:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350222140075-10</Id><Title>Early Voting Election Results 59%-31%</Title><Msg>Obama leads Romney by 59 percent to 31 percent among early voters, according to Reuters/Ipsos polling data . Early voting is likely to play a bigger role this year than in 2008, when roughly one in three voters cast a ballot before Election Day. Voting is already under way in some form in at least 40 states.</Msg><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1350222140075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 09:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350225737239-11</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Biden -- a "Real" American.</Title><Username>bottomline5183</Username><Timestamp>1350219484301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 08:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EXCELLENT!</Msg><Username>demfascists45</Username><Timestamp>1350225737239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 10:42:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350226029132-12</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Biden -- a "Real" American.</Title><Username>bottomline5183</Username><Timestamp>1350219484301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 08:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The operative term is "malarky".</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1350226029132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 10:47:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350228433453-13</Id><Topic><Title>BA Accelerated Rate of Movement... How Long can BA Last??</Title><Username>houstonhart228</Username><Timestamp>1350137564939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:12:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hoping it's good. Thanks for the link.</Msg><Username>vargasboris55</Username><Timestamp>1350228433453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 11:27:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350229457334-14</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Biden -- a "Real" American.</Title><Username>bottomline5183</Username><Timestamp>1350219484301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 08:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you provide one example of a Biden lie during the debate? Lyin' Ryan told at least 24.</Msg><Username>demfascists45</Username><Timestamp>1350229457334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 11:44:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350229561804-15</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Biden -- a "Real" American.</Title><Username>bottomline5183</Username><Timestamp>1350219484301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 08:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you talking about your continual sanctimonious scripture readings?</Msg><Username>wellsaid_1234</Username><Timestamp>1350229561804</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 11:46:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350230525320-16</Id><Topic><Title>Imagine a world with 0% taxes....</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1350083423672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No police, firefighters, Army/Navy/ Air Force/ Marines/ CG, no Infrastructure such as roads power grids/power generation/dams/water management/ municipal services, no corporate welfare or R+D, no general welfare support / Social Security/ Medicare, no postal services and of course no Laws of any kind and no schools ( which obviously doesn't matter to an idiot that would post a topic like this)...GLTY sir...</Msg><Username>manferfish</Username><Timestamp>1350230525320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 12:02:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350231383090-17</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Biden -- a "Real" American.</Title><Username>bottomline5183</Username><Timestamp>1350219484301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 08:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How, then, can they call on the one they have not believed in? And how can they believe in the one of whom they have not heard? And how can they hear without someone preaching to them?" (Rom 10:14) Let's imagine that I said that I was going to vote for Obama and I also subscribed to Hooz's erroneous notion of "Jesus is a liberal". The tune would be different. You may have convinced yourself that your issue is with with me, but it is actually the message. You can loathe me for eternity but you cannot escape the message. You can search on any one of my messages and you will not find a disparaging comment directed towards anyone on this message board, yet some of you spew hate and evil from your mouths. Look in the mirror.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1350231383090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 12:16:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350231782193-18</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Biden -- a "Real" American.</Title><Username>bottomline5183</Username><Timestamp>1350219484301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 08:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BVD Skidmark, you say "I believe the Nov.6 2012 election will be the Official Cease and Desist Order for the modern GOP". Wake up. The Democrats were handed a cease and desist order (a shellacking using Obummer's word) back on Nov. 2, 2010. In the last National elections the Republicans gained 63 seats In the House of Representatives, the largest exchange for a midterm election in 72 years, and recaptured the majority. The Republicans also gained 6 seats in the Senate. The republicans in 2010 also gained 680 seats in state legislative races the largest gain ever recordered. Further, The Republicans also took control of 29 of the 50 State Governorships. Come Nov. 6, 2012 I believe the cease and desist order that the Democrats were handed in 2010 will become "OFFICIAL" when the Republicans not only win back the Presidency but the majority in both Houses of Congress.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1350231782193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 12:23:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350234673721-19</Id><Title>Boeing airplane order book,political spammers, uni-foul</Title><Msg>The Boeing order and delivery books, illustrates how ridiculous all the attention paid to the yearly order totals race is! It is very simple Airbus at whatever order numbers has taken away 50% of Boeings passenger plane business! With all the readily available financial numbers like stock price, gain or loss of stock price year to date, stock price range per year, cost of the development of the planes like the 787(20-30 billion) earnings, revenue. However using plane order comparisons is meaningless without comparing the cost of the plane to develop and the discounts to large plane orders and the penalty and all the costs for being late by 4 years and selling a reworked “dirty plane” to the customer etc, using orders to compare Boeing or for that matter EADS on plane orders makes no sense. How is it that the order “race” has taken on such a perceived significance in the business press or by uni-foul pumps?; Plane orders which may or may not ever result in any revenue or profit?! . A rather shocking problem with Boeing is the smartest man at Boeing by position is Jim McNerney so the GE-MD management style is in effect, the same one that bankrupted MD. Next the cheap labor that cost an extra 20-30 billion on the development of the 787 is a real cost and assures that the 787 will never make any money. While the 20-30 billion cost overrun is at 100% the profit margin is at 5.7% that will never work and Boeing will most likely be bankrupt in 5 more years and it is only fitting the leadership that bankrupted MD will bankrupt Boeing. Plane order race numbers, . I can see why uni-foul loves them; they’ve unsuccessfully used them to create the impression that Boeing is a much more successful company than the Boeing actually is. If uni-foul were to track Boeing’s value related to real world guidelines especially the Boeing, stock price, then uni-foul would have a real picture of the Boeing Company., something easily proved by the financials, but seldom mentioned when the order numbers are being hyped! The uni-foul hype of plane orders forgets that better companies are killing Boeing in bottom line investor stock price. The fact is that Boeing stock investor price is down 2% year to date. For a reference comparison to Boeing, down 2% while the Dow Jones stock average is up over 9% year to date. So the information that Boeing in 10 months has lost 2% all Boeing investors money compared to the Dow or other averages is, well a shameful waste of your investment. The other Boeing false pump is that Boeing traders are making money trading the stock price up and down, well yes on Friday due to positive economic numbers you could have easily make 1% until the bears came in and ran the stock market down. The problem with that pump is you could have made 8% on many of the coal stocks on Friday or 10 to 30% in the week using the same positive economic news. BTW Boeing has never made 30% in five trade days on a stock price of JRCC level much easier to buy and make money on a less costly investment. Or if you are a trader then the gain for apple was 75% until a month ago and now it is 55% year to date( Boeing has lost 2% year to date) or if you shorted Apple at the peak you just made another 20% going short on apple and then you have dividends and yes apple pays dividends. If any Boeing pump suggests that they are trading the range on Boeing the stock has very little range basically a 65 to 75 over too long a time period, mainly and not much movement same story for 15 years. If you want to make money in this stock market you need to trade and review your stocks on a regular basis or go with a ETF or a major fund that tracks the DOW or the NASDAK. If you are waiting for Boeing to make a 100 dollars, that is the uni claim and is false, prepare to be disappointed JRCC, a coal company actually made 30% last week and any investor, especially the political spammers here who are so silly as to argue politics when they can use political statements about coal to make a ton of money like they had 6 days to get in and make more money in one day than Boeing has lost in 10 months. 2%! So congrats uni-foul and the political opinion spammers I make money while you people sit on your worthless opinions.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1350234673721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 13:11:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350237984004-20</Id><Topic><Title>Friday activity</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1350158633355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:03:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks.</Msg><Username>misterceek</Username><Timestamp>1350237984004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 14:06:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350239696251-21</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Biden -- a "Real" American.</Title><Username>bottomline5183</Username><Timestamp>1350219484301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 08:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It came from this man voting to put two wars on a credit card...I was there. I voted against him." Biden voted for both the Iraq war and the Afghanistan war.</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1350239696251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 14:34:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350240453671-22</Id><Title>Biden - The Delaware Doofus</Title><Msg>always seemed likeable despite withdrawing in disgrace from a Presidential election after plagiarizing a speech, despite lying about his academic record, despite his buffonish grasp of history claiming FDR got on TV in the 20s -- despite all this and more he's always been a likeable clown, good for comic relief however, his job in the debate was to shore up the democrat base - i.e. people that are rude, obnoxious, filled with envy, hate and rage who think the whole world owes them a living -- he may have been successful in that regard but he lost the respect of all those who, despite his moronic gaffes, considered him "likeable"</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1350240453671</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 14:47:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350242452213-23</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Biden -- a "Real" American.</Title><Username>bottomline5183</Username><Timestamp>1350219484301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 08:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't underestimate buyers' remorse.</Msg><Username>i_like_ike99</Username><Timestamp>1350242452213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 15:20:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350242569271-24</Id><Topic><Title>BA Accelerated Rate of Movement... How Long can BA Last??</Title><Username>houstonhart228</Username><Timestamp>1350137564939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:12:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for all your supports and views.It would bring back my confidence i would like to share my money with this organization.</Msg><Username>v.roman61</Username><Timestamp>1350242569271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 15:22:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350244600172-25</Id><Topic><Title>BA Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>kevininthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1350243540781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 15:39:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ok so as far as I can see this is free. i just tried it and it works pretty well</Msg><Username>peelingoutsummer</Username><Timestamp>1350244600172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 15:56:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350248484525-26</Id><Title>Global Warming STOPPED 16 Years Ago... Liberals Fret! Obama Stopped in November... America Celebrates</Title><Msg>U.K. Home News Sunday, Oct 14 2012 9PM Global warming stopped 16 years ago, reveals Met Office report quietly released... and here is the chart to prove it The figures reveal that from the beginning of 1997 until August 2012 there was no discernible rise in aggregate global temperatures This means that the ‘pause’ in global warming has now lasted for about the same time as the previous period when temperatures rose, 1980 to 1996 By DAVID ROSE The world stopped getting warmer almost 16 years ago, according to new data released last week. The figures, which have triggered debate among climate scientists, reveal that from the beginning of 1997 until August 2012, there was no discernible rise in aggregate global temperatures. This means that the ‘plateau’ or ‘pause’ in global warming has now lasted for about the same time as the previous period when temperatures rose, 1980 to 1996. Before that, temperatures had been stable or declining for about 40 years.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1350248484525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 17:01:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350248585750-27</Id><Topic><Title>jolly Joey</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1350186373371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 23:46:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>get your head out off your butt,just look what the administration has , and has not done to this once great nation............................ks</Msg><Username>kingslmon6</Username><Timestamp>1350248585750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 17:03:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350249237677-28</Id><Title>Big Mouth Joe Is of NO Help to O'Bummer</Title><Msg>Both the Gallup and Rasmusson likely voter polls show Romney at 49% and O'Bummer at 47% -- same as before the veep debate. Big Mouth Joe gave Broke O'Bummer NO BOUNCE Bye bye, Barack!</Msg><Username>parkplacebob</Username><Timestamp>1350249237677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 17:13:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350249349905-29</Id><Topic><Title>Imagine a world with 0% taxes....</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1350083423672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From The Lexus and the Olive Tree: “Well, my freshmen Republican friends, come to Africa – it’s a freshman Republican paradise.” Yes sir, nobody in Liberia pays taxes. There’s no gun control in Angola. There’s no welfare as we know it in Burundi and no big government to interfere in the market in Rwanda. But a lot of their people sure wish there were….. No, Liberians may never again have to worry about government red tape … the only regulation I saw at the Executive Mansion … was a sign taped to a bullet-shattered window at the front door. It said: “Deposit Your Weapons Here.” … Employers don’t have to fret at all about pesky worker-safety rules in Angola, let alone service for the handicapped. The 70,000 Angolans who have had their limbs blown off by land mines … seem to make do just fine on their own … hustling for food and using tree limbs as a substitute for the human variety. And in Rwanda and Burundi no one was asked to pay for Head Start, unemployment insurance, Medicaid, national service or student loan programs. Instead they just have brutal competition for scarce land, energy and water, with … tribesmen taking turns downsizing each other. They should come to war-torn Africa and get a real taste of what happens to countries where there is no sense of community, no sense that people owe their government anything, no sense that anyone is responsible for anyone else, and where the rich have to live behind high walls and tinted windows, while the poor are left to the tender mercies of the marketplace. I don’t want to live in such a country, or such a world. It is not only morally wrong, it will become increasingly dangerous.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1350249349905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 17:15:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350249876357-30</Id><Topic><Title>Big Mouth Joe Is of NO Help to O'Bummer</Title><Username>parkplacebob</Username><Timestamp>1350249237677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 17:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big mouth Joe scared the hell outta most people -- showed he's not fit to be a heartbeat away from the top. Can you imagine Big Mouth Joe negotiating across the table with Russia's Putin?.-- be afraid, be very afraid if something bad happens to O'bummer before January 20. We won't need to worry about big mouth Joe after that date as O'Bummer will be resuming his career as a community organizer on January 21.</Msg><Username>parkplacebob</Username><Timestamp>1350249876357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 17:24:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350264294544-31</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Biden -- a "Real" American.</Title><Username>bottomline5183</Username><Timestamp>1350219484301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 08:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, I suspect that Mississippi was not the only place that such a person and group might get shot in 1965. Maybe even more so today. Your post reminded me that there is really no accurate or definitive description of Jesus. Perhaps that is just as well. I didn't recall any decscription of Jesus in the Bible save for at His "transfiguration". I found this on the internet (gotoquestionsDOTorg) and thought that it capsulized the issue: "Most artistic portrayals of Jesus are of a Caucasian male with blue eyes and long light-brown hair. It is important to understand that this common portrayal is likely not at all what Jesus looked like. Jesus was ethnically Jewish, so He likely had light to dark brown skin, brown eyes, and dark brown or black hair. Jesus would have looked like a typical middle easterner. The Bible nowhere gives a physical description of Jesus, so no one should be dogmatic about His appearance. And, ultimately, we have to realize that what He looked like does not matter. If it mattered, the Bible would contain a physical description." And the Apostle Paul wrote that a man having long hair was a "shame" (per custom) so it is less likely that Jesus had long hair, though who knows? Maybe He did just to irritate the Pharisees. - BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1350264294544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 21:24:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350264455961-32</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Biden -- a "Real" American.</Title><Username>bottomline5183</Username><Timestamp>1350219484301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 08:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Makes me think if Genna will ever take a late night stoll in the South Hill neighbor of Tacoma, Wa.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1350264455961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 21:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350265177664-33</Id><Topic><Title>At the Vice Presidential Debate: Ryan Told 24 Myths in 40 Minutes</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1350168230627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:43:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No match for Joe who told one every time he moved his lips.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1350265177664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 21:39:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350267282855-34</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Obama and Romney Neck-and-Neck in Typically Red Arizona</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1350262352375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 20:52:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep....probably due to the fact that you dont need I.D. or be registered to vote to answer a "poll" question on the phone. There is a method to the maddness to letting people vote without having any form of I.D. and you can probably figure that out. It will be interesting to see how many people will be turned away on election day nation wide due to fraudulant identification or no I.D.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1350267282855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 22:14:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>