<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348979709338-1</Id><Topic><Title>No apologies needed from Fox</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348934477572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's NO way Obama can win the debate...............based on conservative's observations.....you see when 95% of the polls (including Fox's) say Romney shouldn't be feeling like he has a lock - the conservs say polls are "smoke &amp; mirrors" - products of Palin's (where is she????) "lamestream" media - if Obama were to perform well in the debates, since they have proven in the past of being in complete denial what makes you think they would give him his justice AND if the main stream (Extremely left leaning ;-) ) media says he performed the better of the two .........well of course the conservs are going to claim conspiracy.......so let's save the TV air time and declare Romney the winner but have no fear - people won't go rushing to him anyway.....admit it you conserves hold your nose when you speak highly of him yourselves</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1348979709338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:35:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348979844741-2</Id><Topic><Title>No apologies needed from Fox</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348934477572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet you don't believe we recently sent a probe to the planet of Mars......couldn't have because it takes science to do something like that and that's something conserves disavow</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1348979844741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:37:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348980516407-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Cabinet Flunks Disclosure Test With 19 of 20 Ignoring Law...</Title><Username>libsrwhiners</Username><Timestamp>1348847102301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:45:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TRAVELGATE</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1348980516407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:48:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349000950526-4</Id><Topic><Title>delivery floodgates open</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348849682771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the update.</Msg><Username>mrstock52</Username><Timestamp>1349000950526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 06:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349000991850-5</Id><Topic><Title>another satellite launch contract</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348871742363</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 18:35:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the update.</Msg><Username>mrstock52</Username><Timestamp>1349000991850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 06:29:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349008226467-6</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne Madsen reveal Obama's gay lifestyle</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348981597156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:06:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound every bit as obsessed with homosexuality, in that perverse sort of way, as AnalGonqueer is. Perhaps the two of you should "meat" up and explore your innermost desires with each other. It might be good for YOUR mental health and Anal's as well. And ours too.</Msg><Username>analgonqueen11</Username><Timestamp>1349008226467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 08:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349010338981-7</Id><Title>BA Board Bagger Berzerk Bonkers</Title><Msg>The usual one or two conservative multi-ID baggers who spend their miserable lives posting what they hear from Foxvda and El Flushbo on this board are hysterical over the inevitability of the dusky hued gentleman occupying the White House for four more years. In the words of Supreme Court Justice Antonin Scalia, "They shoud get over it".</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1349010338981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349011676917-8</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne Madsen reveal Obama's gay lifestyle</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348981597156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:06:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't Mr Madsen work for Donald Trump on whether Obama was born in the USA or not. Was he the undisclosed investigator that DT said was going to return with all kinds of shocking and scandalous info from his trip out to Hawaii???? I prefer to hear about that Mr Madsen than this trumped up story you're pushing about a gay bath house.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1349011676917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:27:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349012296320-9</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne Madsen reveal Obama's gay lifestyle</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348981597156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 01:06:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you just jealous that it's a chicago bath house and not the KENT BATH HOUSE????? HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1349012296320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:38:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349015752247-10</Id><Title>Boeing and the Milk Industry</Title><Msg>Exorbitant (subcontracting costs) feed(parts) costs and lower( discounts ,late delivery fee’s massive ,rework overtime labor costs , in the USA to fix the 787 problems) are just the same as the milk prices and huge number of milk producers going bankrupt now . . The Midwest drought has led to corn and soybean costs(outsourcing costs) increasing by more than 50 percent this summer(Boeing since day one on the 787), stressing dairymen(Boeing share price down on the year about 5% compared with the Dow up 10%) from Wisconsin and Minnesota to Missouri( Boeing share price down all over the world). But in California(Washington State and Carolina) milk prices(787 production costs are excessive) have also lagged behind( so no profits on the 787 will ever be made) those in the rest of the nation, exacerbating the crisis. And while milk revenues in California have soared to over $7.5 billion in 2011, making milk the top agricultural commodity, higher revenues mean little, famers say, because it costs so much more to produce the milk.Just like production of the 787 is so high the Boeing shareholder and company is losing money and within 5 years Boeing will be bankrupt. "I don't think there's a milk producer in the state who is profitable right now," said Michael Marsh, CEO of Western United Dairymen. Boeing can claim a profit margin of 5.7% but that is Boeing figure like the story that the 787 would be ready and instead was 4 years late and at least 20 billion over budget.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1349015752247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:35:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349017815562-11</Id><Title>Remember Pearl Harbor</Title><Msg>Everytime we deal with Iran.That was the time we were still talking with Japan while they were already bombing Pearl Harbor. America beware.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349017815562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349017879142-12</Id><Topic><Title>BA Board Bagger Berzerk Bonkers</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1349010338981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are pretty hysterical yourself, but entertaining for a crazy person.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1349017879142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:11:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349017959975-13</Id><Topic><Title>Remember Pearl Harbor</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349017815562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:10:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America is way too dumb to beware, sorry!</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1349017959975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:12:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349018368384-14</Id><Title>Let us win one for the Four Americans</Title><Msg>By repaying them this coming November. Say enough to those that failed to protect their lives.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349018368384</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:19:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349018699082-15</Id><Title>Boeing Managment has compressed the learning curve</Title><Msg>Boeing management warned it might move future work out of the region if it can't keep down the cost of engineers. Congratulations Boeing management team, you have compressed your learning curve If Boeing management has become more efficient at anything, it's in its ability to compress the amount of time it takes to repeat colossal mistakes in judgment..Boeing Executive Leadership has unsuccessfully "been there, done that" with the 787, and everyone felt the pain including workers, mgmt, and shareholders. Attention, attention Chicago Management Team, question for you, . How is threatening people who did their best to fix your 787 mismanagement outsourcing failure, showing them you want to work with them? If the executives raises and pensions and bonuses were the same % as Boeing workers ...then Chicago Management would be walking the talk. Unfortunately the shareholders and the world know that the executive team got huge raises losing as much as 32 billion on a program( outsourcing the 787)...yet they complain about the people that design and build being greedy, for doing their best to fix the 787 a plane that will never work at any rate, too much is wrong with it because it was taken outside Boeing for design and engineering to work as planned by the dreamers in Chicago. How does a man who was in charge of post it’s and a failed GE engine man become the CEO of a airframe making enterprise, Lew Platt, what were you thinking? It also shows not only Boeing executives greed but the stupidity. The outsourced the engineering and build of the 787 to such a great failure? What a joke on the Chicago mismanagement team,....only when they brought the failed work back or had IAM workers fix it on the line, did Boeing workers with great difficulty make as good a fix as we could for this failed 787 disaster. BTW we all know in the shop and the engineering floor that the 787 plane will never be right , it was outsourced too far and taken in the wrong direction for too long with the wrong companies to ever make right. The 787 massive over cost and late fee guarantee that the plane will never make a dime, and when the customers realize they cannot move them around like boxcars and bump into ramps and that they will not show damage like aluminum planes and take huge costs to keep flying, these planes will be parked all around the world on the tarmac. Aluminum dents carbon fiber cracks and then shatters like the tail on a Airbust all at once it is gone, same thing for a 787. No dent to see, but major damage and while flying poof it is gone like a comet airplane built before the technology was ready, the windows were all wrong with the comet, and the 787 everything is wrong. The sad thing about the 787 airplane is that the only Boeing designed and assembled part of the 787 is the Boeing emblem. Remember if it’s not Boeing I am not going? Remember, the outsourced 787 is a imposter Boeing plane. No other Boeing plane was 4 years late and at least 20 billion over budget, figure it out or not, but remember one thing, never fly on a 787 outsourcer(the 787 is not a Boeing made or designed plane) it is a hobbled together mismanagement idea of failure a” Chicagodreamfailure” , very risky. We did our best to fix the chicago nightmare plane but it was too far gone to make right.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1349018699082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:24:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349031838632-16</Id><Topic><Title>On Polls...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_777</Username><Timestamp>1348865541932</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"" "" Wrong, they are using 2008 turnout data, not any perceived demographic shift It is no conspiracy theory at all. The polling methodology is public information. And you show me someone who thinks the democrat advantage will be larger than 2008 and I will show you a someone that cuts and pastes from liberal blog sites and presents it like it is credible information. Now let's use the 2010 turnout data and see what the polls say? LOL!! Not fair you say? And you would be correct. But the actual turnout by affiliation will be somewhere right in between 2008 and 2010. Oh and do keep in mind, Rasmussen was in fact the most accurate in 2008 so they are much more likely to be doing something right, wouldn't you say?</Msg><Username>xraythrives</Username><Timestamp>1349031838632</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349033873727-17</Id><Title>Preview of Univision’s “bombshell” report on Fast &amp; Furious</Title><Msg>Univision to blow the whistle on "fast and Furious" Holder and company could be asked to resign pending prosecution. Search the subject title for the article and vidio</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1349033873727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:37:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349035184027-18</Id><Topic><Title>Preview of Univision’s “bombshell” report on Fast &amp; Furious</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1349033873727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I won't hold my breath.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349035184027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:59:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349035279051-19</Id><Topic><Title>Let us win one for the Four Americans</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349018368384</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:19:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got you working on Sunday? Do they pay you overtime for weekend posting?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349035279051</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:01:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349035512573-20</Id><Topic><Title>To Cripple Boeing or not?</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1348971404754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:16:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349035512573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:05:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349036026832-21</Id><Topic><Title>To Cripple Boeing or not?</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1348971404754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:16:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How would you feel if you were retired and Boeing took away your medical benifits especially if they were part of your calculations to see if you were in a position to retire? The Union is not just looking after current employees, but the retire's also who had no plans to return to the workforce. Without the SPEEA Union, no one would be looking out for retire's nor have any avenues to protect themselves.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1349036026832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349036028291-22</Id><Topic><Title>Let us win one for the Four Americans</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1349018368384</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:19:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>weekends they 7.5 cents per RWNJ post via the Koch-sucker politcal machine but they not feed the [RWNJ] fish on weekends with RWNJ drivel unless they actually think or watch the 24/7 Faux News political propaganda channel</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349036028291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349038854635-23</Id><Title>SEALs Say, We Eliminated America's #1 Enemy, Voters Eliminate America's #2 Enemy in November</Title><Msg>Romney will Crush Obama in the Debates this Week... even the DNC Believes Romney will Win!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349038854635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349039609431-24</Id><Title>Shoulda bought more BA @ $69</Title><Msg>one lot to hold for the div the other lot to make for a short-term profit BA - going to the moon and we thank you just like the RWNJ's/Myth Rmoney and Lytin' Ryan thank the veterans</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349039609431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:13:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349040375121-25</Id><Topic><Title>Ohio, Virginia, Florida...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_777</Username><Timestamp>1349039087999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:04:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Life begins when a single sperm sets off a chain poly-reaction over the entire surface of an ovum making it inpertrenable to all others, according to the electron microscope and all other data. But that don; t mean that it is for me oe\r you. BHO v. WMR wear your thermo-nuclear asbestos laden mittens and there is still room on Mt. Rushmore for BHO</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349040375121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:26:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349040493044-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 347, Romney 191</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_777</Username><Timestamp>1349039216298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:06:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IAM surprised it is that close, let's ask SPEAA... how to 'enegineer' an elction of such great importance Vote American! Vote BHO!</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349040493044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:28:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349040590682-27</Id><Title>Anyone Wonder Why the Buffoon Biden is not on the Campaign Trail!</Title><Msg>Because Biden is Walking Idiot and Obama will be Naked Wednesday without his Pacifier(TelePrompter) When Romney Crushes Obama in the Debates. Can't Wait for Ryan to Embarrass Biden in the VP Debates as Well!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349040590682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:29:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349041510885-28</Id><Title>ABC/DIS/World news with Diane Sawyer in under 15 minutes...predicts an Obama win</Title><Msg>and then there is typing with two fingers and George Stephnapolous on.... we are so far ahead that the RWNJ's will be embarrssed to show up and vote about the ISSUES help,,,</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349041510885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349042785729-29</Id><Topic><Title>ABC/DIS/World news with Diane Sawyer in under 15 minutes...predicts an Obama win</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349041510885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:45:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Love me out of it..."</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349042785729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:06:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349043098233-30</Id><Title>Vote Early/Vote Often</Title><Msg>not since 1968-1972 or 1992-1996 have I been so energized myth rmoney and lyin' ryan ? Get real!</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349043098233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:11:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349043835129-31</Id><Topic><Title>Vote Early/Vote Often</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349043098233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:11:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vote Often Says it All, Nitwit!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349043835129</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:23:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349044024468-32</Id><Topic><Title>To Cripple Boeing or not?</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1348971404754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:16:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Boeing goes broke your medical and retirement benfits will be severly lowered.</Msg><Username>petcorkie</Username><Timestamp>1349044024468</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:27:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349044150507-33</Id><Topic><Title>Ohio, Virginia, Florida...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_777</Username><Timestamp>1349039087999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:04:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All Three States are Ripe Pickings for Romney as Romney Will Make a Fool of Obama in the Debates on Wednesday! No Pacificer, no TelePrompter for the Affirmation Action Queen!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349044150507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349044280199-34</Id><Title>Almost cut my hair...</Title><Msg>Some USA Nazi specialist didn;t like my mustache or work o\in the 130th station hospital Not giving an inch to fear... shaves-d it. but not my hair..... hello</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349044280199</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:31:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349044578488-35</Id><Topic><Title>Almost cut my hair...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349044280199</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$.. Get Help Through Obama Care... You Will Need to Wait Six Months to See Someone though.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349044578488</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349044720830-36</Id><Topic><Title>Ohio, Virginia, Florida...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_777</Username><Timestamp>1349039087999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:04:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once upon a time there was a Myth Rmoney and Lyin' Ryan ticket [insert the ending of Tzahkovsjki's 1812 overature here]</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349044720830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349044890378-37</Id><Topic><Title>Almost cut my hair...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349044280199</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>self-aid buddy-aid myth rmoney immacom sucking head wound 3:10 to Yuma</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349044890378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349045683340-38</Id><Topic><Title>Vote Early/Vote Often</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349043098233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:11:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to the U.S. Constitution the Electoral College says it all and Obama is way ahead in that category but the low-IQ right-wins bigots with a sucking head wound want to say otherwise self-aid for a sucking RWNJ head wound... omg a JNJ band-aid</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349045683340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:54:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349046305007-39</Id><Topic><Title>GOP voter form scandal spreads</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_777</Username><Timestamp>1349042586189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:03:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More Republican cheating. No surprise here.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1349046305007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:05:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349047118482-40</Id><Title>We will defend our integirty and borders...</Title><Msg>the United STATES of America against the onslaught//// of....</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349047118482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:18:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349047190221-41</Id><Topic><Title>We will defend our integirty and borders...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349047118482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:18:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>would you lijke to play a "fair game"... j =</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349047190221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349048789008-42</Id><Topic><Title>I said I was bipartisan, deficit reducer, job creator a president of Hope and Change, open government reporting and so many other things</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349042814978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gregjanetomdoofus: Rarely has one post had so much that is simply wrong. You are wrong on jobs, wrong on the stimulus, wrong on unemployment, wrong on % of folks on welfare, wrong on the deficit, wrong on what the President inherited, and wrong on energy. You even contradict yourself on that wild claim about Obama's sex life. You are either a proud Fox News viewer or you simply can't do any better. Now go find a job, support your family, and make something of your life instead of incessantly posting such drivel on a BA stock bulletin board.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1349048789008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:46:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349048855629-43</Id><Topic><Title>We will defend our integirty and borders...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349047118482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:18:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if J = The united sTATES OF aMERICA WOUYLD j LIKE TO PLAY A "fair game' when "J" has most of the cards in a 'fair game' called... If Not All ah da cards</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349048855629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:47:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349051035023-44</Id><Topic><Title>We will defend our integirty and borders...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349047118482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:18:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>per usual we cannot county on\ Geogia]]] as she is : a woman</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349051035023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 20:23:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349052062381-45</Id><Topic><Title>We will defend our integirty and borders...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349047118482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:18:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If we , The United STATES of America sounded like Georgia, it might sound like a George Harrisoin via George Martin pluckin' three string son the electric guitar v. the Myth Rmoney/Lawrenece Elk Singers ... with interest</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349052062381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 20:41:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349055700496-46</Id><Topic><Title>We will defend our integirty and borders...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349047118482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:18:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the United STATES of America accepts the votes for BHO from Georgia on top of the facts</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349055700496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349057947827-47</Id><Title>IAM is one of ours</Title><Msg>and so is SPEAA should we/us go to world war III -the United STATES of America, includes Georgia hence the shortage of bacon...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1349057947827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 22:19:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349057968491-48</Id><Topic><Title>billion and many other who do not have a dime to invest are confused with Cronie Capitalism and Free Market Capitalism or rewards on merit</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349034184626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:43:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your post,Greg,is not hard to understand. It's logical and precise. Those who have chosen to renounce your logic are unwilling to except the true reality of the information that's been presented to them. My conclusion: Liberal Progressive Dupes are unwilling to admit basic fundamentals of logic.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1349057968491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 22:19:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349063200211-49</Id><Title>Is this a message board for Boeing or a facebook page for idiot who want to talk about their hair ?</Title><Msg>Is this a message board for Boeing or a facebook page for idiot who want to talk about their hair ? You people need to get a job</Msg><Username>mixsterbuys</Username><Timestamp>1349063200211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:46:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349063949795-50</Id><Topic><Title>On Polls...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_777</Username><Timestamp>1348865541932</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It’s not the polls, it’s the policies. Now that’s a reason for Republicans to be depressed." - How do you feel about that statement Mr Limbaugh</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1349063949795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:59:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349063961730-51</Id><Topic><Title>GOP voter form scandal spreads</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_777</Username><Timestamp>1349042586189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:03:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let Not Leave Out The Cheating Democrats!</Msg><Username>carthom09</Username><Timestamp>1349063961730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:59:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>