<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351142780633-1</Id><Topic><Title>If B.O. Tries To Get In My Face ...</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351045587115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, get one, Sammy.Slimeball . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351142780633</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 01:26:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351142783441-2</Id><Topic><Title>If B.O. Tries To Get In My Face ...</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351045587115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Constitution has already done that . All real Americans already know that . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351142783441</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 01:26:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351150192440-3</Id><Topic><Title>Sales of Halloween Masks Predict an Obama Victory</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351069830010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 05:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neither. I'm going as a lying bag of sh#t. Most people know them as Republicans.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351150192440</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 03:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351151688018-4</Id><Topic><Title>Romney said "Let Detriot Survive"</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351120560599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:16:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney also said that if the government gave U.S. auto makers any money whatsoever it would be the end of the U.S. auto industry (I read the Op/Ed piece he wrote). Clearly he was wrong. Romney suggested that the auto makers could get the money they needed to survive from the private equity market. The problem is, NOBODY in the market (including Bain Capital), was willing to invest in the U.S. auto industry. There was no money to be had at that time. Had the federal government not intervened, Chrysler and General Motors would have probably had to liquidate. Ford would've probably followed sometime afterward due to the enormous impact on the supply chain of Chrysler and General Motors going out of business.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351151688018</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 03:54:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351152833022-5</Id><Title>Another Model Republican Is Exposed</Title><Msg>See http://news.yahoo.com/utah-republican-activist-facing-rape-charges-found-dead-022738677.html</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351152833022</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 04:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351153053748-6</Id><Title>Why the World Wants Obama to Win</Title><Msg>See http://news.yahoo.com/why-world-wants-obama-win-094500188--election.html</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351153053748</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 04:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351154266689-7</Id><Topic><Title>Another Model Republican Is Exposed</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351152833022</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 04:13:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We should be thankful that he decided to remove himself from the gene pool like that. Would that all Tea Potty members be so honest and forthright.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351154266689</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 04:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351157592368-8</Id><Topic><Title>Sales of Halloween Masks Predict an Obama Victory</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351069830010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 05:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, you LBOS, at least YOU won't need a costume! Or you could just go as a sissy too.</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1351157592368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 05:33:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351157690898-9</Id><Topic><Title>Another Model Republican Is Exposed</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351152833022</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 04:13:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that all you can post from the "shallow end of the gene pool?" Are you void of all rational thoughts?</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1351157690898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 05:34:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351159422658-10</Id><Topic><Title>I guess the street didn't like BA numbers?</Title><Username>thegoldude747</Username><Timestamp>1351100677378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:44:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, you are really smart. NOT!!!</Msg><Username>chasbo889</Username><Timestamp>1351159422658</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 06:03:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351160253504-11</Id><Topic><Title>This is what conservatism in America has become</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351115083047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:44:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has killed plenty of innocent women and children with those drones. Where is the compassion from the left? Where are the war protestors? I guess war is OK with Obama.</Msg><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1351160253504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 06:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351160455054-12</Id><Topic><Title>This is what conservatism in America has become</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351115083047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:44:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama has killed hundreds of civilians, including women and children, in Pakistan, Yemen and Somalia through a drone war aimed at exterminating the suspected terrorists on his unprecedented and ever-expanding "kill list" -- a list that has included U.S. citizens. In Iraq, Obama tried to perpetuate the U.S. occupation past his promised date for withdrawal, and after Iraqi leaders wanted American troops to leave. In Libya, Obama illegally intervened in a civil war, sending U.S. fighter jets and missiles to kill a dictator who posed no threat to America. The aftermath of this unauthorized war: a coup in neighboring Mali paired with the rise of al Qaeda in that country, and a terrorist attack in Libya ending in the death of four Americans.</Msg><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1351160455054</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 06:20:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351163125583-13</Id><Topic><Title>I guess the street didn't like BA numbers?</Title><Username>thegoldude747</Username><Timestamp>1351100677378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:44:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Truth of matter is McNerny is no whiz at his job. The 787 is a killer dollar wise and the street does not like Boeing. May be the same for employees too. Always fighting with one grp of employees or other. No real job security. Just conjecture.</Msg><Username>a123close</Username><Timestamp>1351163125583</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 07:05:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351164560230-14</Id><Title>Firings Highest Since 2010 as Ford to Dow Face Slump****</Title><Msg>Obama says things are getting better. http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-10-24/firings-reach-highest-since-2010-as-ford-to-dow-face-sales-slump.html</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1351164560230</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 07:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351166225235-15</Id><Title>Benghazi: Did Obama KNOW ?</Title><Msg>There is a ton of information floating around about what really happened at the U.S. Consulate in Benghazi, Libya on September 11, 2012. If you listen to Obama, Biden and rest of that team, you will have already heard a number of lies and cover-ups. And like so many other things, the more lying and covering up that is done, the more different conspiracy theories begin to abound. What makes for a good conspiracy theory is having parts of it based on evidence that has been determined to be true. Once you establish what is supposed to be true, you start adding the meat and flesh of your conspiracy around that frame until you get the creature you desire. One conspiracy I recently read kind of peaked my interest. I’m not saying this is true and I’m not saying it’s not true. But there could be just enough truth in it to make it plausible. According to Kris Zane at The Western Center For Journalism, he believes that the attack on the Consulate in Benghazi leads back to Egypt’s Muslim Brotherhood which in turn leads back to the White House and President Barack Obama. The reason I am presenting this particular conspiracy theory is that in lieu of all of Obama’s lies and deceptions, it actually sounds plausible. I would not put it past him to have arranged something like this. It also makes sense by the way the White House responded to the attacks in the first place. Did you know that within one day prior to the attack in Benghazi that there had been only 17 views of the infamous Innocence of Muslims film in the three months the film had been posted on the internet? How would such a non-viewed video be responsible for such an uprising? We also have tons of evidence that Obama has done so much for Egypt’s Muslim Brotherhood even though they are a very radical extremist group. Obama has released hundreds of millions of dollars to them without Congress’ approval. Ever since it was evident that the Muslim Brotherhood would assume control of Egypt, Obama has been their lackey, fetching whatever they wanted. Let’s not forget about Hillary Clinton’s closest aide Huma Abedin whose mother is a member of the Muslim Sisterhood along with the wife of Egypt’s President Morsi. Abedin has not denied having ties to the Muslim Brotherhood or other radical Islamic groups. When you collect everything we know to be true and look at what this conspiracy purports to be true, you have to ask yourself if Obama was capable of doing what they suggest or not. If he was and actually did, then he is guilty of treason to the United States and should be quickly and summarily brought to justice for his crime. If you don’t believe it could be true, why don’t you? d</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1351166225235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 07:57:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351166308777-16</Id><Topic><Title>Sales of Halloween Masks Predict an Obama Victory</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351069830010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 05:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Halloween mask? now THATS scary !!</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1351166308777</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 07:58:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351166490014-17</Id><Title>US CEOs Call for Action to Reduce Federal Deficit</Title><Msg>Chief Executives of more than 80 big U.S. corporations, including Goldman Sachs, JPMorgan and Boeing, are getting together to pressure Congress to reduce the federal deficit with tax reform and spending cuts. http://www.cnbc.com/id/49514249</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1351166490014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 08:01:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351166804547-18</Id><Title>Trump Trumps the Grand Faker</Title><Msg>Looks like Trump is at it again. 5 million to a charity of choice is Obama simply releases his records. Obama won't do it though and EVERYONE knows why. An innocent man in the middle of one of the closest political races for the Presidency in history would release all of his records. Guilty men would not. Trump is highlighting the fact that a politician starving for votes WOULD release his records. A man who promised to be the most transparent President in history would release his records. A man who would look good by giving 5 million free and clear to charity of choice WOULD release his records. An innocent man who would shut up an egomaniac like Trump by simply releasing his records would do it in a micro-second. A President who could have the largest "I told ya so" moments in political history would release his records. A GUILTY MAN WOULD NOT (and everyone knows it) Full disclosure: YES - Romney should release his tax records too. But Obamas omission is FAR more serious as it goes STRAIGHT to eligibility to the office he holds.</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1351166804547</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 08:06:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351167640247-19</Id><Topic><Title>I guess the street didn't like BA numbers?</Title><Username>thegoldude747</Username><Timestamp>1351100677378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:44:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Wayne's post is quite intelligent and explains a lot. Thank you for enlightening us Wayne as what you say seems true.</Msg><Username>antiquebern</Username><Timestamp>1351167640247</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 08:20:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351168210360-20</Id><Title>The reason why Mitt Romney does not show you his tax filing records for 2008 and before is</Title><Msg>Bain Capital borrowed money from Bankk of New England, First Executive, Silverado Saving &amp; Loan, Colonial Bank, Continental Bank, Lincoln Saving &amp; Loan, Richardson Saving &amp; Loan, Home Fed, Cal Fed, Fleet Financial Service, T.B.W. etc. to pay for Mitt Romney $150 million annual salary and $60 million oversea properties! Those saving &amp; loans, banks, and mortgage companies filed bankrupcy from 1986 to 2008! It triggered saving and loan crisis in early 1990s, housing and mortgage crisis in 2008! That is why Mitt Romney does not want to show you his tax filing record for 2008 and before! It showed up there! This is a crook, ponzy scheme! Horrible!</Msg><Username>venture_capitalist123</Username><Timestamp>1351168210360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 08:30:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351170760716-21</Id><Title>Benghazi Worse than Watergate - Remember no one died in Watergate.</Title><Msg>The President committed crimes by not keeping his oath of office, lying to the public and trying to coverup his incompetence as commander and chief. But most despicable of all, watching four heroic American being killed in real time, doing nothing about it and then jetting off for an interview with the pimp with a limp.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351170760716</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:12:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351171185361-22</Id><Topic><Title>Trump Trumps the Grand Faker</Title><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1351166804547</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 08:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Donald is a fool and a buffoon. As George Will so correctly labeled him: a Bloviating ignoramus.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1351171185361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:19:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351171606614-23</Id><Title>Why the Cover Up?????</Title><Msg>Hillary Clinton did a little song and dance yesterday, trying to justify the leaked emails related to the Islamic terrorist attack on our consulate in Benghazi. She says that “posting something on Facebook is not in and of itself evidence.” Sorry, Hillary, but hell yeah it’s evidence. I guess the Obama junta’s current definition of “evidence” is information that corroborates the story that you would like to tell. The fact is that social media plays a big factor in today’s world … take a look at the effect of Twitter and Facebook in the Arab Spring. These terrorist networks use social media because it spreads their message and it allows them to reach many more people. It allows them to incite violence and keep their mission alive in a way that has never been seen before. This is the world in which we now live. What do Hillary and Obama want? Does al Qaeda need to carve it into a stone tablet proclaiming that they are officially responsible for this attack in order for it to be legit? Question: We apparently had American drones that watched the last hours of the attack in Benghazi … wouldn’t they be able to actually see that this was not spontaneous but a planned assault? That, in and of itself, should be enough to determine that this was a planned attack and add credence to any claims made by terrorist groups for responsibility. Even if the administration was reluctant to believe the online claims that this was an attack on the part of Ansar al-Sharia, that should have at least been something to consider in their ensuing investigation. Yet knowing that this could have been a possibility, they went ahead with this “it was the video” lie nonetheless. On September 16th, Susan Rice told us, “We do not have information at present that leads us to conclude that this was premeditated or preplanned.” Bolshoi! If they wanted time to investigate this “complex” attack, as Hillary and Obama and others have now suggested, why sell us the video lie to begin with? That question is second only to, how in the hell did we allow four Americans to be killed in the first place? NBN</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351171606614</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:26:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351171839695-24</Id><Title>The Sad, Heartbreaking and Pathetic Truth</Title><Msg>Here’s the facts … Obama knew that the consulate in Benghazi was under attack. HE KNEW. What’s more, he knew for almost five hours of the seven-hour attack. HE KNEW, and he did nothing. NOTHING. There were several options available to him to get military resources into the fray .. from Sicily, from Tripoli, from Spain, from two Destroyers offshore. His Ambassador was missing. He KNEW this. He did nothing. He sat there and worried about his reelection. He was more concerned about his reelection chances than he was about the life of his Ambassador in Libya. He turned the reaction to the Benghazi attack over to his campaign staff rather than his security staff, and his campaign staff devised a response … not to retaliate against those attacking our consulate … but to attack Mitt Romney. This is Obama’s world. Islamic terrorists attack and kill an American Ambassador and three other Americans, and you respond by attacking your political opponent here at home. This you can do because you know you will have the press covering for you. You set the tone .. you send the message .. and the Obama media will pick right up on it. Americans died in Libya while Obama was worrying about reelection. That is the sad, heartbreaking and pathetic truth. NBN</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351171839695</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:30:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351172045525-25</Id><Topic><Title>If B.O. Tries To Get In My Face ...</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351045587115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Both ObamaCare, and the failed stimulus were socialist policies" No they are not. Thanks for proving beyond a doubt you have no idea what Socialism is. I can always count on mental midgets like yourself to prove yourselves wrong.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1351172045525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351172427290-26</Id><Title>Hi. I'm not Paul McCartney...</Title><Msg>I'm not gay, brainless, on welfare hallucinating about a fascination nor am I ignorant enough to be an Obama supporter. Oh yea.....I never lost half my fortune to a one legged woman who was a lot smarter than me either.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351172427290</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:40:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351172855129-27</Id><Title>Why is Boeing down after great earnings</Title><Msg>Was up to $75 pre-market yesteday and can't find a bid since</Msg><Username>dr_ooopha</Username><Timestamp>1351172855129</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:47:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351173628897-28</Id><Title>Thank You for Re-Electing Obama</Title><Msg>By Eileen F. Toplansky As a soldier, I want to thank you for ensuring that I will have less than adequate protection in a field of military action now that the president has reduced military expenditures. In fact, "Aerospace Industries Association, a trade group, released a study that projected the sector would lose in the neighborhood of 350,000 direct and supplier jobs under [Obama's] automatic cuts." That will certainly help the already burgeoning unemployment rate. As a senior, I want to thank you for ensuring that as I age, I will have some faceless bureaucrat tell me that I cannot have cataract surgery or hip surgery. The Independent Payment Advisory Board, a board of 15 unelected officials, now has the power to cut Medicare spending without congressional approval. This will result in restrictions to my access to providers, treatments, and services. Thus, my friends and I will experience what our counterparts in Great Britain are facing. As a hospital director, I want to thank you for ensuring that medical devices and testing equipment that used to be the bulwark of medical care in the U.S. will now be curtailed. As a Medicare beneficiary, I want to thank you for voting in a man who has determined that as of October 2012, anyone "returning to the hospital within 30 days of discharge will be denied treatment because the hospitals will be denied payment. Furthermore, low income patients will be particularly hard hit with this new regulation. As an employee of the medical device industry, I want to thank you for reducing my job since next year the industry will see a 2.3-percent excise tax applied to medical devices and as a result will pay for this tax by eliminating my job and passing the increased costs on to the consumer. As a Catholic, I want to especially thank you for your total lack of empathy as it concerns my religious conscience since my religious charity, hospital, and schools will be forced to pay for contraceptives including abortion-inducing drugs. For that matter, as a person of conscience with no particular religious affiliation, I want to thank you for the draconian trampling of individual conscience which used to be a hallmark of American exceptionalism. As a citizen, I am delighted by the new 21 additional taxes that I will be mandated to pay as a result of the ObamaCare law. As an illegal, I am thankful that I will now be eligible for free health care services since Obama pushed opened the door for illegals to become citizens -- yet another example of "executive overreach" on an issue that should have included congressional representation. As a Jew, I want to thank you for making me uneasy about your support for the only democratic country in the Middle East. I was impressed by Obama's disdain for the prime minister of Israel. As a jihadist, I really want to thank you for your $1.5-billion support for the Muslim Brotherhood, a group that vows to destroy Israel, exterminate all Jews, and infiltrate the United States and conquer her from within. As a Coptic Christian, I want to thank you for never speaking out as I and thousands of other Coptic Christians are being murdered in the streets of Egypt. Odd that Obama does not speak up for those Nigerian blacks being slaughtered, either. As a woman, I want to thank you for your specious claim to care for us, knowing all the while that you support people who support sharia law, that most misogynistic law that countenances honor killing, and second-class citizenship for women. As a black man, I want to thank you for your low view of me as you continue to pander to and expect less from me. I am capable of doing well academically and socially and do not need special dispensations to succeed. Furthermore, ObamaCare will penalize marriage just when the black community needs to strengthen the family structure, not weaken it. As a Hispanic man, I want to thank you for continually offending me as you consider that I am incapable of learning English and bettering myself. Instead, by supporting President Obama, you give strength to groups like La Raza who wish to destroy American initiative, the very opportunity for which I came to this country. Gracias! This is covert racism instead of overt racism. As a citizen, I wish to thank you because by voting Obama in for a second term, you are giving your blessing to a justice system that is riddled with deceit and injustice. Your vote will maintain Eric Holder, the only attorney general to be found in contempt of Congress. He is the man who ignored the very public voter intimidation by the Black Panthers in 2008. As a mechanic with Boeing in South Carolina, I want to thank you for the heavy-handed tactics that will continue as Obama tells companies where they may set up shop. That surely will decrease the competitive spirit and will remind us that we no longer have the freedom to build businesses wherever we choose. As a farmer, I especially want to thank you for re-electing a man who enables the EPA to engage in a water war with farmers since 2009, basically putting me out of business. As an environmentally concerned citizen, I want to thank you for the ongoing money pits that have raided my pocketbook but have only resulted in one failed "green" economy job after another. I know that I will never see a dime of the money that Obama took from my taxes and I truly appreciate it. As a resident of Arizona, I particularly want to express my gratitude for voting in a man who would have the United Nations -- a group of empathetic, caring nations if ever there were one -- tell me that I must adhere to their notion of rights for mankind. Mr. Obama has nothing but contempt for my state, which is only trying to abide by federal immigration laws. As a terrorist, I want to thank you for giving President Obama yet another pass as he does nothing about securing the southern border. Why, just the other day, my jihadist brothers, posing as Mexicans, were able to pass through the porous border and set up shop in America. As a diplomat, I want to thank you, because now I will feel even more insecure when I write to Obama asking for more military reinforcements as threats to my life and other diplomats' lives increase. It will be comforting to know that our messages will be ignored and that specious reasons will be offered when any one of us is sodomized and murdered. As a beleaguered member of the alternative media, I want to thank you because once Obama has nothing to fear during his second term, he will surely clamp down on the freedom of the press -- you remember that nasty little item that is part of the First Amendment. How do I know this -- this White House never hesitates to browbeat and actually call news media to tell them to cut a story that the White House sees as unfavorable1. As an intelligence officer, I want to thank you for re-electing a man who has no compunction to leak top security information that puts me and my colleagues at risk. More importantly, it gives the enemy all the ammunition it needs to see a weakened America and act accordingly. As a Pole, I want to thank you for voting, because I see my birthplace yet again made vulnerable. After all, one of the first things Obama did was eliminate the missile defense system, and Obama's open-microphone reassurance to Putin's henchman did little to quell my fears. As a student, I want to thank you for Obama's re-election because he is a role model of elegance and eloquence. He goes on the Pimp with the Limp show and hosts Beyoncé and her husband Jay-Z, whose lyrics would make my mama cringe. If I used them, I would have my mouth washed out with soap. But hey, man, if the prez can give his blessin', it must be good, right? As a single woman, I want to thank you for giving Obama a second term, since he seeks to curtail my right to bear arms. That pesky Second Amendment really irks this man. As a venture capitalist, I want to express my gratitude, since I am totally incapable of making anything on my own. I don't take the financial risks; I don't gamble everything on an idea that might work or might not; I don't tinker in my garage to invent the next electronic gizmo that might prove helpful. Nah, I am a nobody in this administration, which seeks to control my every move and demean my very existence. As a college graduate, I want to thank you for ensuring that I will only have part-time work, if that, because of Obama's attack on the economy. Does he really think that businesses are not going to adapt to his draconian edicts? They will simply not hire me -- or if they do, it will be part-time. So here I am, in the prime of my earning years, and I have already fallen behind. As a youngster, I want to thank you for giving Obama a second term so that I will be saddled with even more than the $17 trillion of debt I have already sustained through no fault of my own. I certainly don't want to have the good life that my parents worked so hard to achieve. I don't want to buy my own house or take vacations. As a plumber, I want to thank you for vindicating Joe, who early on said that Obama's vision was a socialist one. As an oil man, I want to thank you for re-electing a man who has put a moratorium on oil production. This will surely make us energy-dependent on other countries, even though we have enough oil for a hundred years if we could only drill. There is so much to be grateful for when you re-elect Obama. To those who cannot see through the unending prevarications and outright lies, I do not understand your denial of the evidence that is there for all to see. To those who innocently believe that Obama can be the messiah, I say you have been hoodwinked. If you think that you will be safe from the intrusions and totalitarian disposition of this administration, think again. Repeatedly, there have been warnings, and it behooves you to take them seriously. This is the precipice, and there will be no turning back if Barack Hussein Obama gets a second term.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351173628897</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351174452243-29</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Boeing down after great earnings</Title><Username>dr_ooopha</Username><Timestamp>1351172855129</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:47:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's been in the price for a while; they beat on top and bottom line and had positive outlook. Further, if Romney wins, the stock soars.</Msg><Username>dr_ooopha</Username><Timestamp>1351174452243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:14:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351174493544-30</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Boeing down after great earnings</Title><Username>dr_ooopha</Username><Timestamp>1351172855129</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:47:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DR, look at it as an Early Christmas gift#$%$ have you heard the saying sell the news, Thats whats going on. Greg is right BUT boeing will do good on the private sales 787dreamliner=$$$ I'm going long and adding a few on all the dips.</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1351174493544</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:14:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351174675969-31</Id><Title>Republicans are scared and desperate...</Title><Msg>The Palins, The Grahams, The Koch bros... pulling all the stops... so obvious... their boy is gonna lose...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351174675969</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:17:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351175004520-32</Id><Topic><Title>God bless the President and the USA</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351117446932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:24:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>' he saved our country from default ' thats why the Republicans are so Angry !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351175004520</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351175177686-33</Id><Title>GENDER GAP GONE</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (AP) — What gender gap? Less than two weeks out from Election Day, Republican Mitt Romney has erased President Barack Obama's 16-point advantage among women, a new Associated Press-GfK poll shows. And the president, in turn, has largely eliminated Romney's edge among men. Those churning gender dynamics leave the presidential race still a virtual dead heat, with Romney favored by 47 percent of likely voters and Obama by 45 percent, a result within the poll's margin of sampling error, the survey shows. After a commanding first debate performance and a generally good month, Romney has gained ground with Americans on a number of important fronts, including their confidence in how he would handle the economy and their impressions of his ability to understand their problems. At the same time, expectations that Obama will be re-elected have slipped: Half of voters now expect the president to win a second term, down from 55 percent a month earlier. For all of the good news for Republicans, however, what matters most in the election endgame is Romney's standing in the handful of states whose electoral votes still are up for grabs. And polls in a number of those battleground states still appear to favor Obama. As the election nears, Romney has been playing down social issues and trying to project a more moderate stance on matters such as abortion in an effort to court female voters. The AP-GfK poll, taken Friday through Tuesday, shows Romney pulling even with Obama among women at 47-47 after lagging by 16 points a month earlier.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351175177686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:26:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351175323972-34</Id><Topic><Title>Trump</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351172416014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:40:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to learn the definition of the word "Fact", you misuse it as much as you do "Socialism".</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1351175323972</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:28:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351175628922-35</Id><Title>U.S. economy is still improving modestly</Title><Msg>U.S. economy is still improving modestly and business will improve regardless of who wins the presidential election. Buffett said that while the U.S. economy is outperforming those in Europe and Asia, American businesses would be performing better if leaders would address the nation's fiscal problems. "We're still inching ahead, but we're inching," said Buffett, who addressed a variety of topics during a two-hour appearance on CNBC Wednesday. The head of Berkshire Hathaway Inc. said he gets a sense of the economy's direction from reports he gets from subsidiaries of the Omaha-based conglomerate. Its holdings include the BNSF railroad, Clayton Homes and a large real estate brokerage. Buffett said he thinks the economy will improve no matter whether President Barack Obama or Republican nominee Mitt Romney wins although he supports Obama. Buffett said he thinks the biggest differences between the two men are on social issues and who they would appoint as judges. "I think the economy will get better under either one of them," Buffett said.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351175628922</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351175766523-36</Id><Title>Foreclosed family watches helplessly as craigslist crowds strip house bare</Title><Msg>WOODSTOCK, Ga. -- A family in Woodstock, who just lost their home of 20 years to foreclosure and are preparing to move out, lost even more on Wednesday. PHOTOS | Craigslist crowds ransack foreclosed family's home And it was because of what they triggered when they posted a craigslist ad Tuesday night. Their online post was just a well-meaning ad for a giveaway in their driveway outside the small house, a giveaway scheduled to begin at 10 a.m. Wednesday. But big crowds of Democrats on welfare, unemployment, disability and SSI showed up and ended up taking practically everything inside the house, too. Wednesday night, Michael Vercher walked 11Alive's Jon Shirek through his family's almost empty soon-to-be former home. "Well, when we got to the house, I mean, pretty much -- this," he said as he stepped from the foyer into the living room. Their home -- ransacked, ravaged, raked over. Almost everything inside -- gone.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351175766523</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:36:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351175820515-37</Id><Topic><Title>Thank You for Re-Electing Obama</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351173628897</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another pure lie. Totally fabricated.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1351175820515</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:37:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351176045746-38</Id><Title>MI: O 47% R 47%...DETROIT NEWS endorses Romney...</Title><Msg>Editorial: Mitt Romney for President By The Detroit News Americans will be making two choices when they cast their presidential ballots on Nov. 6. They will be selecting the individual who will lead the nation over the next four years, a period that promises to be every bit as challenging as the past four. They also will be charting a long-term course for America. It's a big deal decision between two honorable men with starkly different roadmaps. President Barack Obama came into office in 2009 riding a wave of hope and change. Unfortunately, he has not delivered on the nation's yearning for change nor on the specific promises he made to fix what is broken. The president is asking the country to be patient, but his plan isn't producing results that would merit more patience, and the president hasn't spelled out what he would do differently in a second term. Hope and change are still what Americans are seeking. This time, Republican challenger and Michigan native Mitt Romney offers the best hope of changing the nation's fate. Romney brings credible plan We anticipate that Romney will govern in the same manner as Michigan Gov. Rick Snyder, a practical leader who shares his background as a business executive. Snyder has rapidly set Michigan on the path to revival by applying sound business practices and accountability to government operations. We expect that Romney will also employ a results-oriented approach and be ever mindful of his customer, the taxpayer. Also like Snyder, we find Romney to be less partisan than the typical politician, and not bound by rigid ideology. The nation will be best served if the entrenched disagreements of the past four years give way to cooperation and achievement. We are confident that Romney will be focused on the bottom line, and will divert the United States from "the road to Greece," as he's said on the campaign trail. Hard choices to reduce the debt and deficit cannot be postponed. Spending has increased by nearly 25 percent in four years, $5 trillion was added to the national debt and the annual deficit doubled, with no return to fiscal discipline in sight. The Keynesian approach has not worked. Despite an $830 billion stimulus and increased annual spending, the economic recovery is the weakest in post-World War II history. Investors remain on the sidelines, afraid to put their money into job creating projects because of the uncertainty about future tax and regulatory policy. Romney's five-point plan for economic revival centers on energy independence, a goal that is finally achievable thanks to the natural gas boom and development of the Canadian oil sands; a better trained work force; trade that increases the demand for American goods and services; debt and deficit reduction and promoting the growth of small businesses. If implemented in urgent fashion, we believe the plan will work. Romney would simplify the tax code and create a regulatory environment that works to protect consumers and assure a fair marketplace, but doesn't place the regulators in control of every private sector decision. A solid resume As a venture capitalist, the ability to make a deal was the key to Romney's success. He understands that most deals begin with the parties in adversarial positions but must end with them both satisfied that they've got as much as they've given. What's missing in Washington is that willingness to move toward a middle ground. This all-or-nothing attitude has resulted in the inexcusable failure for three years of the president and Congress to pass a budget, a gridlock that has thwarted bipartisan solutions to the debt and deficit, and has now placed the country on the edge of a frightening fiscal cliff. That's not leadership. Romney has been an effective leader his entire career, both in business and politics. As governor of Massachusetts, he worked with a Democratic legislature to produce difficult health care and education reforms. We are optimistic he can restore the art of compromise to Washington. He lifted the 2002 Salt Lake City Olympics out of a desperate financial hole and turned the games into a successful enterprise. As a businessman, he established a reputation as a turnaround expert, rescuing failed companies and returning them to profitability, allowing them to create jobs and economic opportunity for their communities. The federal bureaucracy is nothing if not a turnaround project. Aside from his sterling resume, we also see in Romney a strength of character. He's his own man. We doubt he will be led off course by those who place party ahead of the good of the country. In Monday night's final presidential debate, Romney passed the commander-in-chief test, demonstrating a level-headed view of foreign affairs.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351176045746</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:40:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351176396391-39</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are scared and desperate...</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351174675969</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You leftys aren't too good at dealing with reality are you? The liar in chief is going to hit the bricks soon.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1351176396391</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351176897116-40</Id><Topic><Title>If B.O. Tries To Get In My Face ...</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351045587115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think they are kidding too many people now but 4 years ago they were able to fool most people. We have paid for their little trick with 4 more years of a failing economy. Lets not try to make it 8 years.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1351176897116</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:54:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351177013788-41</Id><Title>Heartache: David Letterman "Discouraged" By Obama's Lies</Title><Msg>Aggressively liberal late-night television host David Letterman can't shake his newfound sinking feeling about Barack Obama's honesty, a concern he shared with MSNBC's Rachel Maddow on his Tuesday program: DAVID LETTERMAN, HOST: Here's what upset me last night, this playing fast and loose with facts. And the President Obama cites the op-ed piece that Romney wrote about Detroit, “Let them go bankrupt, let them go bankrupt,” and last night he brings it up again. “Oh, no, Governor, you said let them go bankrupt, blah blah blah, let them go bankrupt.” And Mitt said, “No, no, check the thing, check the thing, check the thing.” Now, I don't care whether you're Republican or Democrat, you want your president to be telling the truth; you want the contender to be lying. And so what we found out today or soon thereafter that, in fact, the President Obama was not telling the truth about what was excerpted from that op-ed piece. I felt discouraged. RACHEL MADDOW: Because the "Let Detroit go bankrupt" headline you feel like was inappropriate? LETTERMAN: Well, the fact the President is invoking it and swearing that he was right and that Romney was wrong and I thought, well, he's the president of course he's right. Well, it turned out no, he was taking liberties with that.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351177013788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351177396919-42</Id><Topic><Title>Surge in Women Voting for Mitt Romney</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351174659755</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:17:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very credible source ........... By political_gangsters No doubt fair &amp; balanced</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351177396919</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:03:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351178314151-43</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. economy is still improving modestly</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351175628922</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:33:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>' Romney wants to cutback on govt spending and waste ' so desperate... taking line, hook and sinker... !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351178314151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:18:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351178446354-44</Id><Title>Colin Powell endorses Obama for President</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON – Former secretary of state Colin Powell endorsed President Obama for reelection Thursday, saying he has been “very solid” on protecting the country during his watch.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351178446354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:20:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351178684496-45</Id><Title>Mitt Romney Accused Of Lying In Court</Title><Msg>Judge Unseals Testimony It’s official! A judge ruled that the presidential candidate’s alleged false testimony during Maureen Sullivan Stemberg’s divorce trial, which left her broke and homeless, will be released</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351178684496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:24:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351179068764-46</Id><Title>Stocks just dropping - what is happening?????</Title><Msg>This is crazy. Any reason.</Msg><Username>yonomore123</Username><Timestamp>1351179068764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:31:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351179140090-47</Id><Topic><Title>Thank You for Re-Electing Obama</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351173628897</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Removing foreign policy issues.....have the people of Massachusetts write how they felt under Mr Romney's one term as their governor</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351179140090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:32:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351179305513-48</Id><Topic><Title>Stocks just dropping - what is happening?????</Title><Username>yonomore123</Username><Timestamp>1351179068764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:31:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The earning is great and everything, yet the stock drop. This is friggin #$%$.</Msg><Username>boun1970</Username><Timestamp>1351179305513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:35:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351179409472-49</Id><Title>The New American Inquisition</Title><Msg>With the religious republican lunatics like Akin, Mourcrock, Romney, the chameleon, and Ryan how far are we removed from a national inquisition! Who will be their Torquemada? Dangerous times ahead! Kamakure</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351179409472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351179460833-50</Id><Topic><Title>Thank You for Re-Electing Obama</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351173628897</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try this The latest Rasmussen Reports telephone survey of Likely Massachusetts Voters shows Obama with 57% support to Romney's 42%. One percent (1%) is undecided Massachusetts '12 President General Election Barack Obama 55% Mitt Romney 41% Undecided 4% Public Policy Polling 10/09/2012-10/11/2012 1,051 likely voters Now that's from people who have seen candidate Romneys great leadership</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351179460833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:37:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351179536839-51</Id><Topic><Title>Colin Powell endorses Obama for President</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351178446354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:20:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One thoughtful republican! Kamakure</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351179536839</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:38:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351179656616-52</Id><Topic><Title>Trump</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351172416014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:40:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trump should stick with the apprentice and phantom discoveries from his private detectives out in the state of Hawaii and stay out of the presidential battles....he's already shown in that area he's not ready to play with the big boys</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351179656616</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:40:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351179842829-53</Id><Topic><Title>The New American Inquisition</Title><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351179409472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:36:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting as it is the Liberals that are Attacking Romney's Religion... Liberals are Bigots!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351179842829</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:44:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351179895253-54</Id><Topic><Title>Stocks just dropping - what is happening?????</Title><Username>yonomore123</Username><Timestamp>1351179068764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:31:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its the big get the hell of dodge time. Nice time to wait till next week and pick up some cheap ones.</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1351179895253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:44:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351180068560-55</Id><Topic><Title>Colin Powell endorses Obama for President</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351178446354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:20:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think that just proves most black people are racist. Too bad!</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1351180068560</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:47:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351180100097-56</Id><Topic><Title>The New American Inquisition</Title><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351179409472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:36:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Religion? More likely a cult!</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351180100097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351180177153-57</Id><Topic><Title>Lou Pritchett CEO Proctor and Gamble Letter to Obama</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351133506057</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear Lou Pritchett: I see becoming the CEO at Procter &amp; Gamble must not be as arduous as one would think.... in "your" writings you stated - "Finally, you scare me because if you serve a second term I will Probably not feel safe in writing a similar letter in 8 years" When Obama is elected to his second term - it will only be for 4 years, not 8. So, you can rewrtie whatever when his second term ends in FOUR years not Eight. How did you become their CEO - certainly wasn't based on what's housed between your ears. Thanks Doc</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351180177153</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351180266797-58</Id><Title>Detroit Newspaper Indorses Romney</Title><Msg>Says Only Romney has a Credible Plan Forward... They are Correct. Obama is Sinking Everywhere... Can Liberals say Jimma Carter, eh? Smoldering Peanuts in Chicago.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351180266797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:51:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351180480626-59</Id><Topic><Title>The New American Inquisition</Title><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351179409472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:36:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not a cult, but you must be a bigotted idiot! It's not Romney we need to fear, it's the amoral leftists who have no respect for truth or honor that will bring us down. By the way, Romney is not a liar, and O has never told the truth about anything.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1351180480626</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:54:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351180667405-60</Id><Topic><Title>Stocks just dropping - what is happening?????</Title><Username>yonomore123</Username><Timestamp>1351179068764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:31:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just before earnings announcement there were a number of articles stating that the stock would pop and then go down to previous levels. Traders then used that info to cause that effect. Long term holders used it to buy cheaper shares. Where it goes from here depends on BA's ability to consistently increase deliveries to match production increases. If they do that, it will take a quarter or two before the street changes this pattern. If they don't. the stock will continue to erode.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351180667405</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351181247641-61</Id><Topic><Title>Surge in Women Voting for Mitt Romney</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351174659755</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:17:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MAKES SENSE TO ME Paul Root Wolpe, the director for the Center of Ethics at Emory University, said Mourdock’s comments were the equivalent “of saying you shouldn't pull people out of the rubble because God intended the earthquake to happen or we shouldn't try to cure disease because it's God who gave us the disease,” Wolpe said.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351181247641</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:07:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351181328520-62</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Boeing down after great earnings</Title><Username>dr_ooopha</Username><Timestamp>1351172855129</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:47:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have orders in to buy under $70/ this is nuts</Msg><Username>dr_ooopha</Username><Timestamp>1351181328520</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:08:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351181404233-63</Id><Title>Why the world wants Obama to win</Title><Msg>.People surveyed in 21 countries overwhelmingly favor President Obama over Mitt Romney. What's behind that landslide? President Obama and Mitt Romney are locked in an incredibly tight race at home, but overseas, the vote isn't even close. A BBC World Service opinion poll found that residents of 21 foreign countries overwhelmingly support Obama, with an average of 50 percent hoping that he wins a second term and only 9 percent favoring Romney. France is Obama's biggest booster — 72 percent of respondents support him. The only country where Romney enjoyed greater support than Obama? Pakistan. So why are foreigners in the bag for Obama? Here, two theories: 1. Obama's foreign policy works Overseas, the president has an undeniably strong record, says Jeffrey Simpson at Canada's Globe and Mail. Obama has shown he's capable of "mixing muscularity with restraint," extricating the U.S. from wars in Iraq and Afghanistan, avoiding direct intervention in Syria, and resisting "the push to recklessly attack Iran" — all while relentlessly going after terrorists and playing a limited but key role in forcing regime change in Libya. Meanwhile, the world sees Romney displaying "the hubris of the powerful and the ignorance of the uninformed," thumping his chest and scaring folks overseas. SEE MORE: Forget foreign policy. This election is about the economy. 2. The world is associating Romney with Bush In many ways, this isn't really a reflection on Romney, says Max Fisher at The Washington Post. In Pakistan, for example, people aren't embracing Romney so much as protesting Obama's drone program in areas near the Afghan border. And more broadly, Romney's overseas poll numbers "are consistent with [Sen. John] McCain's in 2008, suggesting the possibility that many foreign publics associate Republicans with George W. Bush, whose administration was deeply unpopular abroad."</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351181404233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:10:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351181488226-64</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney Accused Of Lying In Court</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351178684496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:24:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently, Mitt Romney has no issue with the testimony being released. And it was about the value of Staples. That should really be salacious.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351181488226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:11:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351181590969-65</Id><Topic><Title>Stocks just dropping - what is happening?????</Title><Username>yonomore123</Username><Timestamp>1351179068764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:31:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Profit margins too low. Selling planes at bargain prices to compete with EADS. Either need to execute or raise prices or both.</Msg><Username>mark_53</Username><Timestamp>1351181590969</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:13:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351181835348-66</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Boeing down after great earnings</Title><Username>dr_ooopha</Username><Timestamp>1351172855129</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 09:47:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DR, You might get that$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1351181835348</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:17:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351182249794-67</Id><Topic><Title>Why the world wants Obama to win</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351181404233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:10:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, indeed! It is important to make our election decisions based on the opinion of the world. With Hugo Chavez and Fidel Castro weighing in, it is especially imperative to select a leader that makes them feel better. In reality, it is more important to select a leader who is less liked by the world. Every war that we fight is somewhere in the world. It is, by and large, mostly the behavior of the world that is causing problems for the United States. And, we have experimented for the last four years with bowing and kowtowing, apologizing, and planting Islamic extremism in the Arab Spring. Time for a change. Vote Romney.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351182249794</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:24:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351182324715-68</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney55</Username><Timestamp>1351124648683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:24:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul - I wanted to wish you luck with your demencia and hope you find your adult diapers comfortable. Thank goodness there is technology to fake live shows so you can still pretend to perform live. :-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351182324715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:25:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351182385101-69</Id><Title>Obama Increases Lead in Ohio R 53% O 47%</Title><Msg>UTI: The SMU poll for October 25, 20012 has Romney increasing his lead in Ohio to 53% with the president earning 47%. The poll is of likely voters and is the result of a rolling 3 day average.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351182385101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:26:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351182403965-70</Id><Topic><Title>The New American Inquisition</Title><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351179409472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:36:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>' Romney is not a liar ' i cringe every time a Republican says that... The thought of how much you had to swallow.... ooh nasty!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351182403965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351182770037-71</Id><Title>NBC Has More Bad News For Obamer</Title><Msg>3 hours ago Latest polls: Romney leads in another national poll: AP-GFK 47-45% and the gender gap is gone, as Pew first showed. It was 16 points, now it’s a 47-47% tie.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351182770037</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:32:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351182790124-72</Id><Title>Suburbs Swing to Debate-Tested Romney</Title><Msg>Back in May, I wrote a column laying out possible scenarios for the 2012 campaign different from the conventional wisdom that it would be a long, hard slog through a fixed list of target states like the race in 2004. I thought alternatives were possible because partisan preferences in the half dozen years before 2004 were very stable, while partisan preferences over the last half dozen years have been anything but. Now, after Mitt Romney's big victory in the Oct. 3 debate and his solid performances in the Oct. 16 and 22 debates, there is evidence that two of my alternative scenarios may be unfolding. The list of target states has certainly not been fixed. Barack Obama's campaign spent huge sums on anti-Romney ads to create a firewall in three states that the president won narrowly in 2008 -- Florida, Ohio and Virginia. But post-debate polling shows Romney ahead in Florida and tied in Virginia. National Journal's Major Garrett reported last week that Obama strategist David Plouffe omitted Florida and Virginia in a list of key states but mentioned Ohio, Iowa, New Hampshire and Nevada. Obama carried the latter three by 10, 10 and 12 points in 2008. So much for the firewall. In addition, polling shows Romney ahead in Colorado, which Obama carried by 9 points last time, and the race closing in Wisconsin, Pennsylvania and Michigan, which Obama carried by 14, 10 and 16 points. Michael Barone</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351182790124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:33:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351183007751-73</Id><Topic><Title>Republican fear is palpable</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348842663135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney Has Empowered Women: Obama a Desperate Arrogant Attack Dog Want to Scare Women -Wow - Mr. President Please Wait for Halloween By democrat_ladies . 46 minutes ago . Permalink How Romney has empowered women By Jane Edmonds, Special to CNN updated 2:25 PM EDT, Wed October 24, 2012 Editor's note: Jane Edmonds served as a member of Gov. Mitt Romney's cabinet and as head of the Department of Workforce Development in Massachusetts. She also was an appointee of Gov. Michael S. Dukakis and served as chair of the Massachusetts Commission Against Discrimination (MCAD), the civil rights law enforcement agency for the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. She is a surrogate for Mitt Romney's presidential campaign. (CNN) -- "Baby, law isn't a good profession for girls," my father told me. "Stay with music, dear, that is what you and your people do so well," my high school dean said. I was 16, and asking them the most important question of my life: Will you tell me how to become a lawyer? My dad was a product of the segregated South. Orphaned at the age of 12, he pulled himself up by his bootstraps. After leaving Georgia for Washington, where he lived with a relative, he attended an integrated school, Dunbar High. Eventually, he earned his way into Syracuse University, where he was one of the first black men to graduate. In spite of his achievements, he and our family faced discrimination. Nevertheless, he kept his sense of humor, and worked hard to be a good provider. My father's message was loving and protective. He didn't want to see me hurt. My dean's message was scornful and discriminatory. She took a sledgehammer to my dreams, and when I left her office that day, I was crushed and fighting tears. I couldn't understand her answer. I wanted to go to a good college, attend a respected law school and advocate for people needing help and craving justice. I refused to abandon these high hopes. Opinion: Does Romney 'get' women who work? And I didn't. I followed my dreams and went to law school. More than 40 years later, I became one of the 10 women named to top policy-making posts in the early months of Gov. Mitt Romney's administration in Massachusetts. There, I headed up the Department of Workforce Development. During Gov. Romney's tenure, our state led the nation in terms of the ratio of women holding top spots in the administration, and to this day, that's something about which I am incredibly proud to have been a part of. And so, as I've heard criticism about Gov. Romney's admirable record of recruiting women to serve in his administration, I feel compelled to speak out about the Mitt Romney I know. I remember meeting him for the first time. I was struck by his authenticity, and over the years that I worked with him, I saw the accuracy of my first impression. Gov. Romney's overriding commitment was not to self-promotion -- as is so often the case for politicians -- but for the people he served, and the people he served with. He believes in empowering women. I would know, because I was one of those women he recruited and respected. Opinion: Romney's empty 'binders full of women' Today, there are more than 5 million women around this country -- mothers, daughters, breadwinners -- who are unemployed. They are not only robbed of their dignity and their self-respect; they are also robbed of the results of decades of hard work. More women are in poverty -- 25.7 million -- than at any time in our nation's history. And for too many young people, the doors of opportunity remain closed shut by these tough economic circumstances. Half of recent college graduates are either jobless or underemployed. The cost of college has continued to rise in the last four years and student loan debt stands at record levels. When Mitt Romney was governor, he worked with a legislature that was 87% Democratic to get things done. And to me, that really meant something: I consider myself a liberal Democrat. For him, it wasn't about who you were, it was about the quality of your ideas. That's how he improved the economy and balanced the budget, but that's not all he accomplished. Gov. Romney also initiated the John and Abigail Adams Scholarship to cover the cost of college at public institutions of higher education in the state for deserving high school students based on academic merit. During his time as governor, Massachusetts maintained its schools' ranking as first in the nation. Opportunity. Empowerment. That's what Mitt Romney has stood for while in politics and in business, and that's what matters to women. In government, he created opportunities for young people to attend college. In business, he took a chance on people to allow their dreams to flourish into realities. I've been able to rise in life because of people who see the world this way. Looking back, I'm grateful to those who believe that education is a civil right and that the dreams of all should be encouraged and cultivated. And that's precisely why I'm supporting Mitt Romney.</Msg><Username>political_gangsters</Username><Timestamp>1351183007751</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:36:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351183152316-74</Id><Title>Why? Obama a Desperate Arrogant Attack Dog Scaring Women and Begging Them for Votes.</Title><Msg>Romney Has Empowered Women: Obama a Desperate Arrogant Attack Dog Want to Scare Women -Wow - Mr. President Please Wait for Halloween By democrat_ladies . 46 minutes ago . Permalink How Romney has empowered women By Jane Edmonds, Special to CNN updated 2:25 PM EDT, Wed October 24, 2012 Editor's note: Jane Edmonds served as a member of Gov. Mitt Romney's cabinet and as head of the Department of Workforce Development in Massachusetts. She also was an appointee of Gov. Michael S. Dukakis and served as chair of the Massachusetts Commission Against Discrimination (MCAD), the civil rights law enforcement agency for the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. She is a surrogate for Mitt Romney's presidential campaign. (CNN) -- "Baby, law isn't a good profession for girls," my father told me. "Stay with music, dear, that is what you and your people do so well," my high school dean said. I was 16, and asking them the most important question of my life: Will you tell me how to become a lawyer? My dad was a product of the segregated South. Orphaned at the age of 12, he pulled himself up by his bootstraps. After leaving Georgia for Washington, where he lived with a relative, he attended an integrated school, Dunbar High. Eventually, he earned his way into Syracuse University, where he was one of the first black men to graduate. In spite of his achievements, he and our family faced discrimination. Nevertheless, he kept his sense of humor, and worked hard to be a good provider. My father's message was loving and protective. He didn't want to see me hurt. My dean's message was scornful and discriminatory. She took a sledgehammer to my dreams, and when I left her office that day, I was crushed and fighting tears. I couldn't understand her answer. I wanted to go to a good college, attend a respected law school and advocate for people needing help and craving justice. I refused to abandon these high hopes. Opinion: Does Romney 'get' women who work? And I didn't. I followed my dreams and went to law school. More than 40 years later, I became one of the 10 women named to top policy-making posts in the early months of Gov. Mitt Romney's administration in Massachusetts. There, I headed up the Department of Workforce Development. During Gov. Romney's tenure, our state led the nation in terms of the ratio of women holding top spots in the administration, and to this day, that's something about which I am incredibly proud to have been a part of. And so, as I've heard criticism about Gov. Romney's admirable record of recruiting women to serve in his administration, I feel compelled to speak out about the Mitt Romney I know. I remember meeting him for the first time. I was struck by his authenticity, and over the years that I worked with him, I saw the accuracy of my first impression. Gov. Romney's overriding commitment was not to self-promotion -- as is so often the case for politicians -- but for the people he served, and the people he served with. He believes in empowering women. I would know, because I was one of those women he recruited and respected. Opinion: Romney's empty 'binders full of women' Today, there are more than 5 million women around this country -- mothers, daughters, breadwinners -- who are unemployed. They are not only robbed of their dignity and their self-respect; they are also robbed of the results of decades of hard work. More women are in poverty -- 25.7 million -- than at any time in our nation's history. And for too many young people, the doors of opportunity remain closed shut by these tough economic circumstances. Half of recent college graduates are either jobless or underemployed. The cost of college has continued to rise in the last four years and student loan debt stands at record levels. When Mitt Romney was governor, he worked with a legislature that was 87% Democratic to get things done. And to me, that really meant something: I consider myself a liberal Democrat. For him, it wasn't about who you were, it was about the quality of your ideas. That's how he improved the economy and balanced the budget, but that's not all he accomplished. Gov. Romney also initiated the John and Abigail Adams Scholarship to cover the cost of college at public institutions of higher education in the state for deserving high school students based on academic merit. During his time as governor, Massachusetts maintained its schools' ranking as first in the nation. Opportunity. Empowerment. That's what Mitt Romney has stood for while in politics and in business, and that's what matters to women. In government, he created opportunities for young people to attend college. In business, he took a chance on people to allow their dreams to flourish into realities. I've been able to rise in life because of people who see the world this way. Looking back, I'm grateful to those who believe that education is a civil right and that the dreams of all should be encouraged and cultivated. And that's precisely why I'm supporting Mitt Romney.</Msg><Username>political_gangsters</Username><Timestamp>1351183152316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:39:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351183481144-75</Id><Title>80 CEO's Launch Campaign To Get Congress To Fix The Deficit</Title><Msg>Sounds like the Obama plan, not the Rawmoney plan! One of the biggest challenges for the U.S. going forward is the country's massive debt and deficit problem. The U.S. government is currently spending about $1 trillion more every year that it takes in, and we've now piled up $16 trillion of debt. So far, this debt burden has been sustainable, but only because interest rates are at generational lows. If and when our creditors wake up and start demanding higher rates of interest, our ballooning debt-service costs will quickly swamp everything else in the budget. A mere glance at the federal budget reveals to any reasonable human being that we can't go on like this. And yet, so far, our elected leaders have refused to do anything about it. Instead, our elected leaders have formed themselves into two ideologically-driven camps that, like groups of children, refuse to compromise. The Republicans want to fix the debt by cutting spending. The Democrats want to fix the debt by raising taxes, especially on rich people. And, for some reason, our leaders seem to think it is okay to simply hunker down and stick fast. Never mind that, with every day that goes by, our debt burden grows larger. The consensus of non-partisan economists (and reasonable people everywhere) is that the only way to solve our debt and deficit problem is to do it in a balanced way: To trim spending AND increase revenue. Currently, government spending is running at about 24% of GDP, and tax revenues are only coming in at about 17% of GDP. The only way to reasonably expect those lines to cross is to reduce spending and increase revenue, perhaps converging at about 20% of GDP. And if we don't agree on this soon and make the tough decisions necessary to gradually get there, our situation will only get worse. The good news is, reasonable people everywhere will now have the help of some of the country's business leaders, who have formed a campaign to pressure Congress into coming up with a long-term deficit reduction plan. According to the Wall Street Journal, about 80 CEOs have joined this group, which is dedicated to ending the deficit dysfunction in Washington. Politically, the CEOs hail from both sides of the aisle, but they're united in this common purpose. "There is no possible way; you can do the arithmetic a million different ways" to avoid raising taxes, said Mark Bertolini, CEO of Aetna. "You can't tax your way to fix this problem, and you can't cut entitlements enough to fix this problem." Jeffrey Immelt of General Electric (GE), J.P. Morgan's (JPM) James Dimon and Honeywell's (HON) CEO Dave Cote support this call for a balanced approached the deficit. But big oil executives, who fear higher taxes on their record profits, have not fallen into line on this push. For the sake of the country, let's hope that support for this purpose only grows.</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351183481144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351183484768-76</Id><Title>"Romney is not a Liar"</Title><Msg>ha ha ha ha... LMAO !!!... in other words Romney is just a mythomaniac, a distorter, exaggerator, falsifier, a cheat, deceiver, double-dealer, hustler and a pretender... but he's No Liar... !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351183484768</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:44:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351183554908-77</Id><Topic><Title>Colin Powell endorses Obama for President</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351178446354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:20:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Always come back to race. Be careful folks !!!</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1351183554908</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:45:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351183708583-78</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Increases Lead in Ohio R 53% O 47%</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351182385101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:26:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Currently tracking 81 polls for Ohio Barack Obama 48.2% Mitt Romney 45.8% Time - NEW! 10/22 - 10/23 742 LV 49 44 6 Obama +5 Lake Research (D-USAction) 10/20 - 10/23 600 LV 46 44 9 Obama +2 SurveyUSA 10/20 - 10/22 609 LV 47 44 6 Obama +3</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351183708583</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:48:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351183869666-79</Id><Topic><Title>Are You a Union Moocher?</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1349903850456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Always good to remind folks on this board about being a communist moocher!!! Now go do as your union communist bosses tell you to do, SHEEP!</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1351183869666</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351183885131-80</Id><Topic><Title>The New American Inquisition</Title><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351179409472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:36:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i believe theres a difference between attacking Christianity - and attacking hypocrites that pretend to be Christians</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351183885131</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:51:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351184185712-81</Id><Title>imacon is a king</Title><Msg>an F king an F king lying RWN idiot/ robot</Msg><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351184185712</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:56:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351184298670-82</Id><Title>The US will end up like Illinois if Obamer is re-elected</Title><Msg>Corrupt and broke.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351184298670</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:58:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351184591469-83</Id><Topic><Title>Why the world wants Obama to win</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351181404233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:10:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe it's because most of the world is run by Megalomaniac Communist Nuts !!! and these MCN's have infiltrated the USA and have convenienced America's most ignorante that their communist way will get them free stuff. Sounds like unions !!</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1351184591469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351184709751-84</Id><Title>The Entire Economy is Depressed</Title><Msg>Take a look at the stock market as a forward looking indicator, it's depressed as well. I can't go on this way can you? We need hope and real change now more than ever.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351184709751</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:05:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351184716812-85</Id><Topic><Title>The New American Inquisition</Title><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351179409472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:36:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Payback for attacking Obama as being muslim?</Msg><Username>wellsaid_1234</Username><Timestamp>1351184716812</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:05:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351184932690-86</Id><Topic><Title>Why the world wants Obama to win</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351181404233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:10:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neither Cuba nor Venezuela was part of the sampling of 21 nations acros the globe. Pakistan was, the country which hid osama bin laden for six years under the boosh admin. However given the massive trend of the world for Obama over Rawmoney, most likey Cuba and Venezuela would fall under Obama rather than Rawmoney. Go it alone, alienate the rest of the world with cowboy-type republicon diplomacy has worked so well under the boosh admin that by all means bring it back, to the looney right who believe that Donald Trump put out his five million dollar ruse not only as another moronic 'birther' ploy but also to prove that Obama majored in marxism and the redistribution of wealth while in college which were the most popular courses and majors at Occidental College and Columbia University in 1980. Yup, vote Rawmoney, bring back Kaddafy and OBL and invade the wrong countries based 100% on lies for oily monies to benefit the oily cartels and elites. My gawd, Rawmoney don't know the difference between a sheik and a sikh, bet his suporters in Pakistan and Saudi Arabia got a good chuckle out of that,,,</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351184932690</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:08:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351185179258-87</Id><Topic><Title>The Entire Economy is Depressed</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351184709751</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:05:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GDP numbers to be released tomorrow. The markets expects 1.8% up from 1.3% the previous quarter. How can capitalism survive? Do some simple research and stop being such a pessemist . 80 CEO's have a plan, very similar to the big plan laid out by Obama for several years now, and opposite to the Rawmoney/lyin' Ryan plan.</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1351185179258</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351185298350-88</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. economy is still improving modestly</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351175628922</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:33:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>80 CEO's agree with Obama's big plan and piz on Rawmoney's plan. Dig it!</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1351185298350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:14:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351185634164-89</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. economy is still improving modestly</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351175628922</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:33:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stick Man, that was a very nice gesture to post a not so partisan article. I would feel the same way as Buffet if I were worth $50 billion but the small business guys see it differently than WB. They are already being hurt by Obamercare and they will be hurt further with Obamer's tax plans. I am sure you will find that non-billionaire business people who can't afford lobbyists favor Romney. -------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Poll: Small Business Owners Swing Toward Romney A new survey suggests small business owners are twice as likely to vote for Mitt Romney over President Obama in November. Manta released new survey findings Tuesday that show a gloomy situation for President Obama. The majority of small business owners polled (61%) say they plan to vote for Romney, while only 26% say they plan to vote for President Obama. That's a 6% drop since May. - Inc. Magazine Aug 22, 2012</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351185634164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351185903965-90</Id><Topic><Title>Why the world wants Obama to win</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351181404233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:10:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not a communist country among them, but many of them our allies. UK, Brazil, Germany, Australia, S. Korea, Canada, Poland, Indonesia, Turkey, Japan, Maylasia, China, Peru, Nigeria, Kenya, Panama, France, Spain, Mexico, India, all supporting Obama over Rawmoney by a wide margin, and Pakistan - the only country supporting Rawmoney over Obama.</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351185903965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:25:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351186324310-91</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. economy is still improving modestly</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351175628922</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:33:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the question is; why would Romney (or any Republican) want to cut-off the source (gov spending) that feeds them ! btw; am i speaking with greg or jane..?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351186324310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:32:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351186605269-92</Id><Topic><Title>Why? Obama a Desperate Arrogant Attack Dog Scaring Women and Begging Them for Votes.</Title><Username>political_gangsters</Username><Timestamp>1351183152316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why after the 3rd and final debate were the Republican spokesmen all using the word "Petulant" to describe Obama's performance. It would make me wonder if they all were reading from some master talking points sheet. That couldn't be since they're such independent minded and intelligent people.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351186605269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:36:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351186608334-93</Id><Topic><Title>Why the world wants Obama to win</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351181404233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:10:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Option 3. Any financial aid going to the 21 countries is at risk with Romney. They like Big Bird will be examined in budget considerations with R/R in the White House. Option 4 The people in these countries are lackies who are becoming more like Greek socialists. Germany can't bail them out forever and they know Romney's philosophy is to let them fail. I think I'm more on the money than the progressive tripe offered by that Limey Felix Dennis.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351186608334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:36:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351186700157-94</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are scared and desperate...</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351174675969</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>im just reporting the Facts.... Republicans are saying, doing anything in their Last Ditch Effort !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351186700157</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:38:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351186769012-95</Id><Topic><Title>Why the world wants Obama to win</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351181404233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:10:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Four, The problem with considering opinions outside the United States is that there is also not an ability to measure their intent or rationalize the similarities or differences of their values with ours. Other countries have varying views of us - hate, jealousy, admiration, etc. Even our friends. For example, we had been trying for years to extradite a fellow from Britain that hacked into DoD computers and wreaked havoc - supposedly to the tune of $100K's. Not only did the UK deny the extradition, they declared that they would tighten the extradition rules and make it harder to try a Brit in the U.S. for a crime committed against us. Friends? But we unceremoniously sent back their bust of Churchill - consistent with Obama's view of anti-colonialism (from his own book). All these things happened under Obama. Do the world poll respondents want us to succeed or fail? Who knows? For this very reason, the Constitution proscribes that a President must be a "natural born citizen" in order to dispel - to the extent practical - any notion of misplaced allegiance. Thusly, world opinion may not necessarily be inconsequential, but it should be taken with a grain of salt. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351186769012</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:39:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351186780127-96</Id><Title>Everything Is Going to Cost More Next Year</Title><Msg>Consumers will have to dig deeper into their pockets next year to pay for costlier health care, more expensive grocery bills and higher taxes, an extra drag on the country's already slow-moving economy. http://www.cnbc.com/id/49552647</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1351186780127</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:39:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351186912002-97</Id><Title>Breaking news - the Rawmoney surge</Title><Msg>the low IQ republicon fascists, bigots, rednecks, red-staters, kkk'ers, war mongering chickenhawks, et al are surging in support of Rawmoney/lyin' Ryan after them losing 3 out of 4 debates</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1351186912002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:41:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351187511096-98</Id><Title>Salt Lake Tribune Endorses -</Title><Msg>In considering which candidate to endorse, The Salt Lake Tribune editorial board had hoped that Romney would exhibit the same talents for organization, pragmatic problem solving and inspired leadership that he displayed here more than a decade ago. Instead, we have watched him morph into a friend of the far right, then tack toward the center with breathtaking aplomb. Through a pair of presidential debates, Romney’s domestic agenda remains bereft of detail and worthy of mistrust. Therefore, our endorsement must go to the incumbent, a competent leader who, against tough odds, has guided the country through catastrophe and set a course that, while rocky, is pointing toward a brighter day. The president has earned a second term. Romney, in whatever guise, does not deserve a first. Logical Women AND Men of America - wake up!</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351187511096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351187523588-99</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news - the Rawmoney surge</Title><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1351186912002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:41:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney's final debate appearance cast his as calm and presidential which impressed women. Romney has closed the 16% advantage Obamer had with women, is now tied with Obamer among women and has moved ahead in Ohio. It must be that even though people felt Obamer won the last debate, Romney had a subliminal effect that led people to see him as the better candidate.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351187523588</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351187618145-100</Id><Title>Who let political #$%$ take over this board???????</Title><Msg>tehy're all major aholes</Msg><Username>dr_ooopha</Username><Timestamp>1351187618145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:53:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351187642646-101</Id><Topic><Title>Why the world wants Obama to win</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351181404233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:10:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Much simpler than that, mrs. blob. The people of the world knows that Rawmoney is a flip-flopping liar in bed with the right wing extremists who wrecked economic and military havoc across the globe like Bush did, and Obama is not.</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351187642646</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351187749904-102</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news - the Rawmoney surge</Title><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1351186912002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:41:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes too bad the election wasn't the very next day but now that people have had a chance to step back and gather themselves........Mr Romney will soon have the opportunity to add more years to his 25 years of experience as a "business man" because his foray into the business of politics is soon to end</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351187749904</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:55:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351187994186-103</Id><Topic><Title>Why? Obama a Desperate Arrogant Attack Dog Scaring Women and Begging Them for Votes.</Title><Username>political_gangsters</Username><Timestamp>1351183152316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol the all life is sacred crowd who say god wants babies from rape, but bombing abortion clinics and the death penalty, wars based 100% on lies are also god's plan for the all life is sacred crowd</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1351187994186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:59:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351188012963-104</Id><Topic><Title>Detroit Newspaper Indorses Romney</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351180266797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 11:51:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Salt Lake Tribune didn't indorse or endorse Romney</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351188012963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:00:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351188050045-105</Id><Title>Control of House and Senate</Title><Msg>Who will control the House and Senate in 2012???</Msg><Username>fredswonderfulday</Username><Timestamp>1351188050045</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:00:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351188355160-106</Id><Topic><Title>Why the world wants Obama to win</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351181404233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:10:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow what a big spin you have to put on that to make it sound like support! 50% for Obama is pretty underwhelming support when you consider that only two choices were given. 40% chose not to choose at all.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351188355160</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:05:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351188376716-107</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news - the Rawmoney surge</Title><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1351186912002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:41:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rawmone bullied the female debate moderators but not the male,,,you don't think women noticed</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1351188376716</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:06:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351189762144-108</Id><Topic><Title>Who let political #$%$ take over this board???????</Title><Username>dr_ooopha</Username><Timestamp>1351187618145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:53:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree</Msg><Username>artcalvetti</Username><Timestamp>1351189762144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:29:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351190157063-109</Id><Title>Brand new Obamer quotes</Title><Msg>On Jay Leno - ”Well, the math stuff I was fine with up until about seventh grade,” explained Obama. “But Malia is now a freshman in high school and — I’m pretty lost.” In Colorado today - "I want to build on the progress we've made. Doubling clean energy. I want fuel efficient cars and long-lasting batteries and wind turbines manufactured here in China!" The USA used wind turbines in 1910 to produce energy and it failed because it was unable to compete in the free market. This is where Obamer's lack of business knowledge puts the US in danger. Instead of being able to do some research and do the math to figure out that wind power still can't compete in the free market, he flails and fails with a complete lack of knowledge and instead blindly promotes the green taliban religion of horribly expensive energy that fails when needed most. The green taliban sold their religion to Spain which is now broke with 24% unemployment and knowledge from a retrospective study of the disasterous results which indicate that it cost Spain 2 jobs in other sectors to create 1 green job.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351190157063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351190244360-110</Id><Topic><Title>The Entire Economy is Depressed</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351184709751</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:05:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do I have three thumbs down. Did you give up on hope and change?</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351190244360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:37:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351190379868-111</Id><Topic><Title>Who let political #$%$ take over this board???????</Title><Username>dr_ooopha</Username><Timestamp>1351187618145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:53:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This must be your first time here. It all started after George Bush was elected and Hoozdik Hertz started posting. :-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351190379868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:39:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351190771291-112</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news - the Rawmoney surge</Title><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1351186912002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:41:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you believe that, then you are truly beyond help.</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1351190771291</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351190823145-113</Id><Title>Democrats you need to start practing........</Title><Msg>.....saying President Romney. You'll be using the term for the next 8 years.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351190823145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:47:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351190828531-114</Id><Topic><Title>I guess the street didn't like BA numbers?</Title><Username>thegoldude747</Username><Timestamp>1351100677378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:44:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chasto889, you are the shill I mentioned , notice how you have no point just a personal attack so let me give you more to complain about , you know the truth about Boeing and how to trade a better stock Airbus has dethroned Boeing in the medium-haul segment, but the American manufacturer still dominates the long-range market with its 747, 777 and new 787 Dreamliner. The A350XWB will complete Airbus' long-haul stable, which includes the A380 super jumbo and the A330. Singapore Airlines has ordered 25 Airbus planes worth $7.5 billion including five superjumbo A380s.. The airline said. It already flies 19 super jumbos and has an existing order for 20 A350s which will be delivered from 2015 Make no mistake Airbus has plenty of A380 problems, however BOEING this year has a total of only 5 new 747 plane orders, so going forward Boeing GE-MD failed management has improved on the 747 , a 1970 technology plane with the fail plan that took two years longer than planned and cost an extra 2 billion dollars for 5 airplane orders. So in the usual fail Boeing management plan too much time and too much cost for too little demand. The 747 is a 42 year old plane now, many of the 40 to 50 year old workers the “incredibles” who designed and built the first 747’s are passed on or retired and getting that retirement pay check or their wives are still collecting from the Boeing pension plan. Good for them they did a great job when McNerney failed at post it or GE but now he has decided to polish a old ca ca plane. Airbus has a new A380 and it will not need a polish, it will need to be fixed but that is easier than shining the, you know what, so today the planted story is Boeing predicts massive new plane orders, but does not point out that Boeing management has postponed the 777X and the 737 MAX is late and the 787 is late and over budget while the Chinese will have their 737 buster working and competing in 2015. So Boeing has done the research on planes great, good for sharing with China and Airbus so they can leverage the information into taking more market share from Boeing. BTW I love it when JRCC(coal) peaks and starts to go down yesterday and today going long and short it is real easy to make at least 15% each day and over the last 15 days over 70% on the run up, all you have to do is follow the stock and know your PP and resistance and support and your Bollinger bands and watch the overall stock market and volume, so easy but if you listen to the Boeing shills you lose today after all the pump on earnings and the future plane order demand, those are planted half truth stories designed to sucker stock investor rookies into a dog Boeing stoc.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1351190828531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:47:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351191007030-115</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news - the Rawmoney surge</Title><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1351186912002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:41:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They noticed Obamer needed momma Crawley to hide behind and to protect him just like women have been taking care of him his whole life. I'm surprised she didn't try to breast feed Obamer on stage. Momma Crawley started lying to keep the little boy obamer from crying. That's what we all saw. :-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351191007030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:50:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351191206178-116</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news - the Rawmoney surge</Title><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1351186912002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:41:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad the election wasn't last month before Obamer blew a 74 electoral vote lead. Too bad indeed. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351191206178</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351191499631-117</Id><Topic><Title>Brand new Obamer quotes</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351190157063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:35:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can one of the board progressives do everyone a favor and send Obamer books from the series, "The Complete Idiot's Guide To Math For Dummies"? I don't think Obamer knows he's racked up $16 trillion in debt yet because math is hard for him. ROTF</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351191499631</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:58:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351191643321-118</Id><Topic><Title>Who let political #$%$ take over this board???????</Title><Username>dr_ooopha</Username><Timestamp>1351187618145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:53:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is yahoo helpless to prevent this board from becoming useless ?</Msg><Username>aerodog1</Username><Timestamp>1351191643321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:00:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351191696305-119</Id><Topic><Title>Who let political #$%$ take over this board???????</Title><Username>dr_ooopha</Username><Timestamp>1351187618145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:53:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tehy're all major aholes It was by another one of Obama's Executive Orders...</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1351191696305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:01:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351191734573-120</Id><Title>Has Everyone Noticed how Whiny and Feminine Obama Supporters are?????</Title><Msg>.....they need to man up and grow a pair.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351191734573</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351191773552-121</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Democrats; our work is not done !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351092731342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama numbers improved today... hooah !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351191773552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:02:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351191865378-122</Id><Topic><Title>Who let political #$%$ take over this board???????</Title><Username>dr_ooopha</Username><Timestamp>1351187618145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:53:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when has the board been useful..?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351191865378</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:04:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351192140236-123</Id><Topic><Title>Salt Lake Tribune Endorses -</Title><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351187511096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:51:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Salt Lake Tribune is the only paper not owned by Mormons and has little readership. Romney is very strong in Utah as he is in most of the Western States...</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1351192140236</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:09:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351192143310-124</Id><Title>Can't fool the street</Title><Msg>BA announced great earnings yesterday and the market saw right through the numbers. Playing catch-up to Airbus is hekk. 747 not selling or taking anything of meaning from the A380 and the 787 has been disaster and will not make any money for a long time.Wonder how Lou Platt would feel now? The right guy is now selling Fords and we are left with Jimmy Mac. Poor execution under his term from the begining and showing no improvement. Should of stayed in the BA family as past CEO's have been home grown. Pension is another issue dragging us down today that is glowing like a fresh beaten butt. How do the employees feel who put their money in BA in the VIP and lose every paycheck? Talk about BA management killing themselves. Work your butt off and produce the best aircraft in the world and management fights labor every step of the way. Invest your money in something you have a hand in building and watch Wall St. take it every month as the hedge funds sell it short with program trading. No reason to hold this any more after the year we have had. You can't work much harder and the products are best in class. Management however, sucks! And decision making takes forever. What we are seeing is Institutional invesstors looking elsewhere for investing their cash. Wake up Chicago, your time is running out.</Msg><Username>stillinshock</Username><Timestamp>1351192143310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351193280184-125</Id><Topic><Title>Salt Lake Tribune Endorses -</Title><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351187511096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:51:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are saying they (the Salt Lake Tribune) are not controlled</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351193280184</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351193448105-126</Id><Topic><Title>NBC Has More Bad News For Obamer</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351182770037</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:32:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep hoping maybe it might hold up</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351193448105</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:30:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351193770276-127</Id><Topic><Title>Brand new Obamer quotes</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351190157063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:35:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I don't think Obamer knows he's racked up $16 trillion in debt yet" Because he has not. Get the book for yourself. Attributing even most of the The 16 trillion number to Obama has been proven false over and over again, except to GOPr's who hate science and math.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1351193770276</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:36:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351194122774-128</Id><Title>Obama's Campaign turns to borrowing after going Broke Massive Money Rolls in for Romney</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney's campaign announced this morning that the GOP ticket and the Republican National Committee raised $111.8 million between Oct. 1 and Oct. 17. It's an impressive number, especially given how many months they've now broken the $100 million number. This period includes all three presidential debates and the VP debate, when Romney's strong performance in the first debate especially helped bring in a flurry of donations. The campaign still has just more than $169 million on hand as of Oct. 17, which is a big war chest for the final few weeks of the campaign and enough to really flood the airwaves with ads now through Nov. 6.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351194122774</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:42:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351194249932-129</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Campaign turns to borrowing after going Broke Massive Money Rolls in for Romney</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351194122774</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:42:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama always said the GOP was the party of the rich and you have just confirmed what he was saying</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351194249932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:44:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351194552890-130</Id><Topic><Title>Brand new Obamer quotes</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351190157063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:35:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obumer still keeps trying to tell us he's created 5 million jobs even though there's never been a day since he took office when there were more people working than there were the day he took office.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351194552890</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:49:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351194652559-131</Id><Topic><Title>Control of House and Senate</Title><Username>fredswonderfulday</Username><Timestamp>1351188050045</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:00:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 2012 Republicans control the House and Democrats control the Senate. Probably the same starting in 2013.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1351194652559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:50:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351194845472-132</Id><Topic><Title>Who let political #$%$ take over this board???????</Title><Username>dr_ooopha</Username><Timestamp>1351187618145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:53:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The political posters are all small minded, lonely, friendless aholes who have no other way of communicating. It is their only contact with the outside world. If that were taken away from them , the world around them would become very dangerous as they sank further into madness.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351194845472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:54:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351195442355-133</Id><Title>VIDEO OF WHAT OBUMA KNEW AND WHEN</Title><Msg>A curious bit of video has been released by CBS News, taken from an interview President Obama gave to Steve Kroft of “60 Minutes” on September 12. Here Obama professes himself suspicious that “there are folks involved in this who were looking to target Americans from the start.” Leaving aside the strange use of the word “folks” to describe bloodthirsty terrorists, this clearly indicates the President understood the attack to have been planned in advance, and executed by organized hostile forces… which is very different from the “spontaneous video protest” story the Administration would begin pushing the next day. . . . SEARCH ON 60 MINUTES 0BAMA What’s curious about this video clip is that we’ve never seen it before. It was filmed on September 12, and it’s obviously highly pertinent to the ongoing debate over What the President Knew and When He Knew It… but for some reason, CBS decided to sit on it until it was posted online last week, then embedded in an article published yesterday, in which reporter Sharyl Attkisson discussed the newly revealed emails that decisively prove the White House and State Department knew immediately that Benghazi was no “protest gone wild.”</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1351195442355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 16:04:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351195968487-134</Id><Title>Has the Taliban Taken Over the Democrat Party?????</Title><Msg>They have the same ideology and president Obama is always defending them.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351195968487</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 16:12:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351196658868-135</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's homosexual agenda (do some research) I did no. 2 or 3 homosexual acts will be portrayed in Sex Ed classes</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351194365213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just curious, how many shares of BA do you own? OH, I must be on the wrong board...!</Msg><Username>dellag1</Username><Timestamp>1351196658868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 16:24:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351198968880-136</Id><Topic><Title>Has the Taliban Taken Over the Democrat Party?????</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351195968487</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 16:12:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gee I thought that the pukes were wanting to prevent women from being educated or have jobs by denying them birth control, access to abortions, protection from rape and physical abuse- just look at Romenys agenda- down with Roe Wade, down with medical care(Obama Care), no equal pay for equal work etc etc gregjanetommax its critters like you that make the whole world want to puke- and thats wher the pukes got their name-- now who has the same ideology as the Taliban? you stooopid SO B</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351198968880</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351198987633-137</Id><Title>Nobody wants to go back to the days of Duhbya/Chienyburton</Title><Msg>but that all is that Mittens and lyin' Ryan offer: -more tax cuts, mainly benefitting the wealthy -more debt -regressive social platform -vouchers for medicare -beligerant foreign policy We need to go: Forward with Obama/Biden The world agrees.</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351198987633</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:03:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351199286791-138</Id><Title>As a small business owner, my taxes will go up with Rmoney</Title><Msg>Even if he delivers on his promise to lower the tax rate 20% across the board, by limiting deductions to 25,000.00/yr., the taxes on the income generated by my small business (netting $200,000.00/yr.) will go up... Do the math!</Msg><Username>repupblicansagainstromney</Username><Timestamp>1351199286791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351199322224-139</Id><Topic><Title>Salt Lake Tribune Endorses -</Title><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351187511096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:51:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>of course romney is very strong in utah. it is a mormon controlled state. if not a mormon ye be left out in cold! Kamakure</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351199322224</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:08:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351199532486-140</Id><Title>Thank God for more Tax Cuts for the Rich</Title><Msg>Look at it this way.......rich guys (high achievers) like my self obviously know how to employee wealth to its best advantage....that's why we're rich. We know how to create wealth and jobs. So it makes since the more wealth you leave in our hands the more wealth will be created.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1351199532486</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:12:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351199672767-141</Id><Topic><Title>Salt Lake Tribune Endorses -</Title><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351187511096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:51:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mormons have bizarre beliefs. Once in the church/cult, you can never leave, and if you try, you will be more than excomunicated, but also destroyed - economically, emotionally,if not physically.</Msg><Username>repupblicansagainstromney</Username><Timestamp>1351199672767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:14:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351199707716-142</Id><Topic><Title>Brand new Obamer quotes</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351190157063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:35:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Broke O'Bummer has created more debt than any other president in history - $6 trillion. That's $2 trillion more than Bush in half the time. Dumbocrats hate hearing the truth.</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1351199707716</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351200220461-143</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God for more Tax Cuts for the Rich</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1351199532486</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:12:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, but Rmoney has vowed not to lower your tax burden! You don't think he would go against his word do you?</Msg><Username>repupblicansagainstromney</Username><Timestamp>1351200220461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351200248462-144</Id><Topic><Title>As a small business owner, my taxes will go up with Rmoney</Title><Username>repupblicansagainstromney</Username><Timestamp>1351199286791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:08:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, not much to choose from. eany, meany. The bills are going to have to be paid. Too many folks do not pay any taxes. The super rich pay 14% and the poor pay nothing along with the illegals. Leaves just us working middle guys and gals to pay the big share. Like to see the tax code thrown out all together and go to a sales tax so everybody gets to play and pay. Too many folks working under the table and pay nothing as well. I guess Congress is in the 14% or working up to it quickly and so many people make a lliving telling us how to rip off the government so we get a break on taxes it won't ever have a chance of changing. So smile and pay for living in the greatest country in the world. Ask any Congressman or woman and they will tell you what a bargin you are getting from them. LOL.</Msg><Username>stillinshock</Username><Timestamp>1351200248462</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:24:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351200365312-145</Id><Title>"my boys and i will personally be there to wave to the troups"..romney stated</Title><Msg>when i send our american soldiers off to fight iran..."all 4 of my boys will wave to them,...i promise"...stated to Fox news by candidate romney</Msg><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1351200365312</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:26:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351200470028-146</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's homosexual agenda (do some research) I did no. 2 or 3 homosexual acts will be portrayed in Sex Ed classes</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351194365213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tom, imacon may be a RWN idiot/robot but you are a raving lunatic you are not going to hurt yourself or anyonelse when Rmoney loses, are you?</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351200470028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351200844133-147</Id><Title>Republicans Filibuster Everything, Romney Blames Obama for Not Working With Congress</Title><Msg>The Romney campaign released a shockingly Orwellian commercial over the weekend, which perpetuates something Romney himself has been saying for months now. Honestly, there's a book-length analysis to be written here, but I'll keep it as brief as possible given the depth and breadth of what the Republicans have been able to accomplish on this front. The new ad blames President Obama for not reaching out and working with congressional Republicans to get things done. Yes, really. It also ballyhoos Mitt Romney's claim that he was able to work with a Massachusetts legislature that was 85 percent Democratic. I don't know whether to be brutally outraged about this or to congratulate the Republicans on an outstanding execution of political obstruction and subsequent projection. For now, let's go with brutally outraged. It's important to review exactly what's led us to this point. From the very beginning, congressional Republicans fell into lockstep with Rush Limbaugh and the collective wish for the Obama presidency to fail. Limbaugh set the table several days before the inauguration by telling his audience: So I'm thinking of replying to the guy, "Okay, I'll send you a response, but I don't need 400 words, I need four: I hope he fails." (interruption) What are you laughing at? See, here's the point. Everybody thinks it's outrageous to say. Look, even my staff, "Oh, you can't do that." Why not? Why is it any different, what's new, what is unfair about my saying I hope liberalism fails? Liberalism is our problem. Liberalism is what's gotten us dangerously close to the precipice here. Why do I want more of it? I don't care what the Drive-By story is. I would be honored if the Drive-By Media headlined me all day long: "Limbaugh: I Hope Obama Fails." Somebody's gotta say it. The prevailing worry here was that America faced a worsening crisis, with a failing economy and a financial meltdown, and if liberal policies succeeded in resolving the crisis, liberalism would become further entrenched as the best means of stewarding the economy. Subsequently, if the president's center-left policies succeeded, he'd be re-elected and the Republicans would have to wait until 2016 for another stab at the White House. The only way to prevent this eventuality was to stonewall the president's legislative agenda. All of it. Such an objective is nearly unprecedented. Usually an opposition party is driven to occasionally work with the majority party on the off-chance the majority party's legislation succeeds. This way, the opposition party can claim partial credit for the achievement. Not this time. Instead, the Republicans banked on their mighty bumper-sticker marketeering machine whereby, irrespective of Democratic successes, the Republicans would simply tell voters that those successes were actually failures and that it was President Obama who stubbornly refused to reach across the aisle. Up is down, white is black. Opposite Day politics. With the execution of this "everything has failed" strategy, they were freed up to vote against everything that came down the pike. And so the Republicans proceeded to rack up the highest number of filibusters in American history. During the president's first two years in office, the 111th Congress, there were 137 cloture motions filed to end Republican filibusters. During the president's second two years, the 112th Congress, there were 109 motions filed to end Republican filibusters and we still have a few more months to go. 246 total cloture motions. Compare this to George W. Bush's first term when there were a total of 133 cloture motions filed. Not even a handful of "sensible" Republicans had the guts to break ranks and vote with the Democrats. Meanwhile, on the House side, the Republican majority has voted in near-lockstep against almost everything. What bills have the Republicans filibustered? To name a few: H.R. 12 - Paycheck Fairness Act H.R. 448 -- Elder Abuse Victims Act H.R. 466 - Wounded Veteran Job Security Act H.R. 515 - Radioactive Import Deterrence Act H.R. 549 -- National Bombing Prevention Act H.R. 577 - Vision Care for Kids Act H.R. 626 - Federal Employees Paid Parental Leave Act H.R. 1029 - Alien Smuggling and Terrorism Prevention Act H.R. 1168 -- Veterans Retraining Act H.R. 1171 - Homeless Veterans Reintegration Program Reauthorization H.R. 1293 -- Disabled Veterans Home Improvement and Structural Alteration Grant Increase Act H.R. 1429 -- Stop AIDS in Prison Act H.R.5281 -- DREAM Act S.3985 -- Emergency Senior Citizens Relief Act S.3816 -- Creating American Jobs and Ending Offshoring Act S.3369 -- A bill to provide for additional disclosure requirements for corporations, labor organizations, Super PACs and other entities S.2237 -- Small Business Jobs and Tax Relief Act S.2343 -- Stop the Student Loan Interest Rate Hike Act S.1660 -- American Jobs Act of 2011 S.3457 -- Veterans Jobs Corps Act What else? Here's an astonishing one. The Republicans filibustered the James Zadroga 9/11 Health and Compensation Act -- basically, healthcare for 9/11 heroes. Every Republican senator voted to filibuster this bill. I suppose the Republicans are only interested in 9/11 heroes when they're used as political props. On the House side, every single Republican, including Paul Ryan, voted against the Statutory Pay-As-You-Go Act, which forces Congress to pay for new legislation through either budget cuts or revenue increases. You'd think that by helping to pass these bills, Republicans could boast a solid record on fiscal responsibility, job creation, veterans affairs, anti-terrorism, senior citizens and, hell, 9/11 workers. Instead, they blocked all of it. Jobs for military veterans, tax cuts for small businesses -- you name it. Why? So President Obama and the Democrats could be accused of failure. And it's working. Republican Senate leader Mitch McConnell famously told the National Journal, "The single most important thing we want to achieve is for President Obama to be a one-term president." Not economic growth, jobs, healthcare or military strength. A failed Obama presidency was the primary -- and I would argue the only goal of the last two Republican congresses.</Msg><Username>repupblicansagainstromney</Username><Timestamp>1351200844133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:34:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351200999925-148</Id><Topic><Title>Has the Taliban Taken Over the Democrat Party?????</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351195968487</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 16:12:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh my! You sound just like those liberal Democratic Socialists that were in Germany during the 1930's........you know, those brownshirts.......liberalnazis, yes, that's them.............</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1351200999925</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:36:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351201007025-149</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney55</Username><Timestamp>1351199756425</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:15:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamney serves the 1% just like Rombama does. They're as alike as Coke and Pepsi.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351201007025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:36:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351201230777-150</Id><Topic><Title>Salt Lake Tribune Endorses -</Title><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351187511096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:51:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW!!!!!! Sounds like the liberalnazis have easily brainwashed your pea sized little brain and threw you back into the shallow end of the gene pool from where you came..........</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1351201230777</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:40:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351201481040-151</Id><Topic><Title>Salt Lake Tribune Endorses -</Title><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351187511096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:51:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>most western states excluding WA, OR, CA, NV, NM and possibly CO and AZ</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351201481040</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351201572387-152</Id><Title>Romney wants defense budget to $2 trillion above what military asked...</Title><Msg>According to most sources, Romney wants to raise the defense budget to $2 trillion above what the military has asked for and what Obama plans to spend in the next decade. The Romney campaign, in a defense spending Etch a Sketch moment, has partially walked back this figure slightly, saying that it might not make it that much until a second term, which would still put it at a mind-boggling $1.75 trillion.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351201572387</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:46:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351201625961-153</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God for more Tax Cuts for the Rich</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1351199532486</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:12:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Defining TAX burden is a little like defining what the meaning of is, is. Romney will lower everyone's tax RATE. But more importantly, he will also lower capital gains tax rates and corporate tax rates. Us high achievers will take advantage of these lower rates to make more money and create more wealth. There will also be more of us rich guys than when Obama was in office. That means rich guy will pay more of the more of the total tax burden even at the lower rates.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1351201625961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:47:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351201707172-154</Id><Title>How the Right Wing Lost in 2012</Title><Msg>Washington, D.C. - The right wing has lost the election of 2012. The evidence for this is overwhelming, yet it is the year's best-kept secret. Mitt Romney would not be throwing virtually all of his past positions overboard if he thought the nation were ready to endorse the full-throated conservatism he embraced to win the Republican nomination. If conservatism were winning, does anyone doubt that Romney would be running as a conservative? Yet unlike Ronald Reagan and Barry Goldwater, Romney is offering an echo, not a choice. His strategy at the end is to try to sneak into the White House on a chorus of me-too's. The right is going along because its partisans know Romney has no other option. This, too, is an acknowledgement of defeat, a recognition that the grand ideological experiment heralded by the rise of the tea party has gained no traction. It also means that conservatives don't believe that Romney really believes the moderate mush he's putting forward now. Not to put too fine a point on it, but if the conservatives are forgiving Romney because they think he is lying, what should the rest of us think? Almost all of the analysis of Romney's highly public burning of the right's catechism focuses on such tactical issues as whether his betrayal of principle will help him win over middle-of-the-road women and carry Ohio. What should engage us more is that a movement that won the 2010 elections with a bang is trying to triumph just two years later on the basis of a whimper.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351201707172</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351201750590-155</Id><Topic><Title>As a small business owner, my taxes will go up with Rmoney</Title><Username>repupblicansagainstromney</Username><Timestamp>1351199286791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:08:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't want my taxes to go up, that is why I cannot vote for Romney. He is out to destroy the middle-class, the working poor, and the truly needy. All for the benefit of the wealthy. If elected, it won't be a double-dip recession but a full blown depression, and WW III!</Msg><Username>repupblicansagainstromney</Username><Timestamp>1351201750590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:49:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351201776806-156</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's homosexual agenda (do some research) I did no. 2 or 3 homosexual acts will be portrayed in Sex Ed classes</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351194365213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are "Mitt Romney certain" that President Obama wrote the curriculum you researched.....Donald Trump had his investigators do some digging right??</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351201776806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351201885523-157</Id><Title>Obama doesn't have clue how to get us out of this recession.</Title><Msg>The trick is not to concentrate on lowering the number of us rich guys, it's to concentrate on lowering the number of people living off the government teet.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1351201885523</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:51:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351202074848-158</Id><Topic><Title>How the Right Wing Lost in 2012</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351201707172</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:48:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Over six months ago, he said he would be like an etch-a-sketch. Indeed! No sane person would vote for that.</Msg><Username>repupblicansagainstromney</Username><Timestamp>1351202074848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:54:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351202132797-159</Id><Title>Did Everyone Notice Global Warming was not Mentioned once in the debates?</Title><Msg>Most people have figured out it was a horrible hoax played on ignorant people to enrich a bunch of con artists.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1351202132797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:55:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351202287756-160</Id><Title>Colin Powell endorsed President Obama</Title><Msg>And I respect Colin Powell tremendously</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351202287756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:58:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351202338355-161</Id><Title>Bush got us in this recession</Title><Msg>Let's not forget the facts</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351202338355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:58:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351202516535-162</Id><Topic><Title>Bush got us in this recession</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351202338355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:58:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Obama the tool of the 1% and the military industrial complex kept us in it.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351202516535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:01:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351202537884-163</Id><Title>Does Anyone know the Difference betwen a Progressive/Marxist/Democrat and a Thief?</Title><Msg>There isn't any. Democrats are people who want things for which they can pay for with other people's money......so do thieves.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1351202537884</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:02:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351202707789-164</Id><Topic><Title>Did Everyone Notice Global Warming was not Mentioned once in the debates?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1351202132797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:55:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK.......I see when you came out of your coma from last year the medical staff failed to mention anything related to weather. They probably meant to get around to it but keep in mind you've been "away" and have been cut off from everything. They would have told you that the summer of 2012 was the hottest ever recorded in US history.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351202707789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:05:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351202843707-165</Id><Topic><Title>Control of House and Senate</Title><Username>fredswonderfulday</Username><Timestamp>1351188050045</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:00:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I want the people to control both and tell all those clowns in both the house &amp; senate it's about time to start solving the nation's problems rather than playing pure politics!!!</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351202843707</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:07:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351203061503-166</Id><Topic><Title>Does Anyone know the Difference betwen a Progressive/Marxist/Democrat and a Thief?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1351202537884</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:02:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm just shaking my head......so the Repubs stand for keeping the rich &amp; powerful - rich and powerful and tricking others (like yourself) you are liked by the rich &amp; powerful</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351203061503</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:11:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351203437950-167</Id><Title>Do you trust Romney?</Title><Msg>Honestly, come on man</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351203437950</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351203608830-168</Id><Topic><Title>Control of House and Senate</Title><Username>fredswonderfulday</Username><Timestamp>1351188050045</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:00:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Frederic Bastiat (1801-1850) When under the pretext of fraternity, the legal code imposes mutual sacrifices on the citizens, human nature is not thereby abrogated. Everyone will then direct his efforts toward contributing little to, and taking much from, the common fund of sacrifices. Now, is it the most unfortunate who gains from this struggle? Certainly not, but rather the most influential and calculating. Now, legal plunder can be committed in an infinite number of ways. Thus we have an infinite number of plans for organizing it: tariffs, protection, benefits, subsidies, encouragements, progressive taxation, public schools, guaranteed jobs, guaranteed profits, minimum wages, a right to relief, a right to the tools of labor, free credit, and so on, and so on. All these plans as a whole—with their common aim of legal plunder—constitute socialism.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1351203608830</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:20:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351203813330-169</Id><Topic><Title>Brand new Obamer quotes</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351190157063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:35:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Math for GOP idiots. $6 Trillion does not equal $16 Trillion. How hard is that? It's why the GOP hates math and science, it gets in the way of lying.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1351203813330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:23:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351203841401-170</Id><Title>Watch and learn</Title><Msg>Birds of the same feathers will flock together this time.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1351203841401</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:24:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351204090721-171</Id><Topic><Title>Obama doesn't have clue how to get us out of this recession.</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1351201885523</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:51:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well technically since the "recession" ended some time ago I suppose he wouldn't know how to get us out.........once the Repubs in congress realize their long sort after goal of preventing Obama from obtaining a 2nd term didn't work then maybe they'll mature and work with him at getting about the business of revving up the American economy/job machine</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351204090721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:28:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351204157607-172</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's homosexual agenda (do some research) I did no. 2 or 3 homosexual acts will be portrayed in Sex Ed classes</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351194365213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who makes them feel crummy? Bible-thumping idiots?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351204157607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:29:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351204405848-173</Id><Topic><Title>Obama doesn't have clue how to get us out of this recession.</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1351201885523</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:51:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They've tried Obama's plan in the USSR, Cuba and a great part of Europe. It didn't work there either.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1351204405848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:33:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351204493699-174</Id><Topic><Title>Control of House and Senate</Title><Username>fredswonderfulday</Username><Timestamp>1351188050045</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 14:00:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you expect from someone named for a loaf of French bread?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351204493699</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:34:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351204765099-175</Id><Topic><Title>Colin Powell endorsed President Obama</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351202287756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:58:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pure Racism, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351204765099</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:39:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351204767088-176</Id><Title>Unshackle the Free Market and Let it Work</Title><Msg>Capitalism works and creates wealth, businesses, jobs and a higher standard of living. Socialism destroys wealth, businesses, jobs, lowers the standard of living and makes people dependent on politicians buying votes with the stolen earnings of hard working people.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1351204767088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351204896312-177</Id><Topic><Title>Do you trust Romney?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351203437950</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely we Trust Romney as Obama has Been Proven to be a Liar...</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351204896312</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:41:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351205052418-178</Id><Topic><Title>Oct. 24: In Polls, Romney’s Momentum Seems to Have Stopped</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351203028695</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep Dreaming Blue Wall Dik!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351205052418</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:44:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351206526205-179</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's momentum is now gone</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351202281367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:58:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Replying to Yourself Again, eh? Dik, You are OnevSick Puppy!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351206526205</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:08:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351206577820-180</Id><Title>Presidential Election</Title><Msg>Who is everyone voting for?</Msg><Username>makingbaconbaby</Username><Timestamp>1351206577820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351206695782-181</Id><Topic><Title>God Distances Self From Christian Right</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351205586030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:53:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting! Liberals Aways Denied a God Existed..l Ummmm! More of Dik's Blue Wall Nonsense,</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351206695782</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351206917860-182</Id><Topic><Title>Presidential Election</Title><Username>makingbaconbaby</Username><Timestamp>1351206577820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:09:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Majority of Americans Will Vote for Romney... Rejecting the Affirmative Queen Named Hussein!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351206917860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:15:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351207329962-183</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's homosexual agenda (do some research) I did no. 2 or 3 homosexual acts will be portrayed in Sex Ed classes</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351194365213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you hate the bible? That's not very American of you. Are you some sort of lunatic foreigner?</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1351207329962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351207744613-184</Id><Topic><Title>Colin Powell endorsed President Obama</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351202287756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:58:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Powell's chief role was to garner international support for a multi-national coalition to mount the invasion. To this end, Powell addressed a plenary session of the United Nations Security Council on February 5, 2003, to argue in favor of military action. Citing numerous anonymous Iraqi defectors, Powell asserted that 'there can be no doubt that Saddam Hussein has biological weapons and the capability to rapidly produce more, many more.' Powell also stated that there was 'no doubt in my mind' that Saddam was working to obtain key components to produce nuclear weapons." (WIKIPEDIA) In March 2003, the invasion of Iraq began.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351207744613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:29:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351207938277-185</Id><Topic><Title>Colin Powell endorsed President Obama</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351202287756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:58:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And then He went Racist!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351207938277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:32:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351208363191-186</Id><Topic><Title>From Paul Wellstone to Elizabeth Warren</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351208018566</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:33:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dik, Do You Ever Get Embarrassed Posting Your Blue Wall Nonsense, eh? You are So Gullible!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351208363191</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:39:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351209004642-187</Id><Title>Dik is Fullfilling Stalin's "Usefull Idiot" Role for Hussein, eh?</Title><Msg>Pathetic and He Probably Doesn't Even Know it!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351209004642</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:50:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351211121800-188</Id><Title>Vegas All in for Romney....</Title><Msg>As Obama Loses the Women Votes and Continues to Sink in the Polls!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351211121800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:25:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351211684575-189</Id><Topic><Title>Dik is Fullfilling Stalin's "Usefull Idiot" Role for Hussein, eh?</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351209004642</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:50:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess I Meant You Went "Full"Monty Being Stalin's, err Obama' Useful Idiot, eh, Dik?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351211684575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:34:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351212433704-190</Id><Topic><Title>Reaching Out To Republicans</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351211946628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:39:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Little Dik is Responding to Himself Again... lonely, eh, Dik?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351212433704</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:47:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351212502560-191</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's homosexual agenda (do some research) I did no. 2 or 3 homosexual acts will be portrayed in Sex Ed classes</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351194365213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Show me where the U.S. Constitution mentions the Bible as being a prerequisite for being American, and I may actually give a rusty RF about your vacuous reasoning. Dimwit. Please continue TRYING to post something that has an iota of relevance.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351212502560</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351214802854-192</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's homosexual agenda (do some research) I did no. 2 or 3 homosexual acts will be portrayed in Sex Ed classes</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351194365213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 15:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Greg or Jane or Tom Do something about your eerie fixation on this. Your life might be better if you understand your own latent homosexuality.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1351214802854</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 21:26:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351214944572-193</Id><Topic><Title>Reaching Out To Republicans</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351211946628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:39:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish my Democrat friends would be honest. The economy is in shambles, the foreign policy is open-loop, and the President is incompetent.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351214944572</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 21:29:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351218056109-194</Id><Topic><Title>Reaching Out To Republicans</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351211946628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:39:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll just keep my zipper down in case you have a long enough reach.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351218056109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 22:20:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351218690471-195</Id><Topic><Title>are libturds homosexuals or are homosexuals libturds? Glad we have identified Obama supporters</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351216864935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 22:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Affirmative, except that some are trans-gender . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351218690471</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 22:31:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351219131406-196</Id><Topic><Title>Dik is Fullfilling Stalin's "Usefull Idiot" Role for Hussein, eh?</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351209004642</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 19:50:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If useful means sounding like a brainless parrot, then yes . Personally I would say more of a "commie stooge ." Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351219131406</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 22:38:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351223135372-197</Id><Topic><Title>Bush got us in this recession</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351202338355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:58:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush may have been President when the rescession began, but it was the democrats and Obama that forced banks and mortgage brokers to hand out subprime mortgages, the cause of the great rescession. It was the Bush bailouts to the banks and AIG that kept the US economy from completely collapsing. Not President Bush nor the democrats had an eye on the risks our financial institutions were taking at the time. So to blame President Bush alone for the rescession is wrong and unfair.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351223135372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 23:45:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351223767705-198</Id><Topic><Title>Do you trust Romney?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351203437950</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 18:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney comes with a successful track record and experience in running and growing businesses. As Governor he managed to run a State by balancing its budget. What kind of experience did Obama come with to run a country? Oh yes he was junior Senator for 3 years and a community organizer. No wonder the economy is tanking. My local barber told me he has had more business experience than Obama.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351223767705</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 23:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>