<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-24"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351069830010-1</Id><Title>Sales of Halloween Masks Predict an Obama Victory</Title><Msg>Seen on the news last night ... A U.S. company that makes Halloween masks has correctly predicted the winner of the presidential election every ear since 1996, determined by which candidate's mask sells the most units. Sales of the Obama mask lead sales of the Romney mask 60% to 40%. Sorry imaccom, you little douche bag. : )</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351069830010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 05:10:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351071596462-2</Id><Topic><Title>Sales of Halloween Masks Predict an Obama Victory</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351069830010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 05:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you going as a LOON or a Kent Bath House patron?</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1351071596462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 05:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351072460695-3</Id><Topic><Title>Busy day today at Boeing</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351017161456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:32:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the update.</Msg><Username>mrstock52</Username><Timestamp>1351072460695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 05:54:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351077333439-4</Id><Title>What ever happened to the India 787 were the landig gear jammed up?</Title><Msg>So what ever happened and were was the ship built?</Msg><Username>john.kloczkowski</Username><Timestamp>1351077333439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:15:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351078606688-5</Id><Topic><Title>Liar in Chief Caught Lying again</Title><Username>locost7777</Username><Timestamp>1351054490487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:54:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We heard mixed messages coming from the White House and President explaining the Libyan attack in three different ways: 1. calling it a spontaneous demonstration that got out of hand. 2. a calculated terrorist attack 3. We don't know and are investigating what happened. From these now revealed e-mails along the President knew what was going on. What a way to run a country.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351078606688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:36:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351078663947-6</Id><Topic><Title>What ever happened to the India 787 were the landig gear jammed up?</Title><Username>john.kloczkowski</Username><Timestamp>1351077333439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:15:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may want to re-read the article! there was no landing gear jamm issue.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1351078663947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:37:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351079132630-7</Id><Title>Boeing Reports Third-Quarter Results and Raises 2012 Guidance</Title><Msg>Boeing Reports Third-Quarter Results and Raises 2012 Guidance  Earnings per share of $1.35 reported on revenue of $20.0 billion  Operating earnings rose at Commercial Airplanes and Defense, Space &amp; Security  Backlog grew to $378 billion driven by $24 billion of new orders  Operating cash flow before pension contributions* totaled $2.3 billion  Cash and marketable securities of $11.2 billion provide strong liquidity  Guidance increased for revenue, EPS and operating cash flow CHICAGO, October 24, 2012 boeing Financial Presentation (PDF) boeing BA Chart marketwatch Analyst Estimates marketwatch URLs at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351079132630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351081775178-8</Id><Title>Libya and Lies</Title><Msg>It was a little much when President Barack Obama said that he was "offended" by the suggestion that his administration would try to deceive the public about what happened in Benghazi. What has this man not deceived the public about? Remember his pledge to cut the deficit in half in his first term in office? This was followed by the first trillion dollar deficit ever, under any President of the United States -- followed by trillion dollar deficits in every year of the Obama administration. Remember his pledge to have a "transparent" government that would post its legislative proposals on the Internet several days before Congress was to vote on them, so that everybody would know what was happening? This was followed by an ObamaCare bill so huge and passed so fast that even members of Congress did not have time to read it. Remember his claims that previous administrations had arrogantly interfered in the internal affairs of other nations -- and then his demands that Israel stop building settlements and give away land outside its 1967 borders, as a precondition to peace talks with the Palestinians, on whom there were no preconditions? As for what happened in Libya, the Obama administration says that there is an "investigation" under way. An "on-going investigation" sounds so much better than "stonewalling" to get past election day. But you can bet the rent money that this "investigation" will not be completed before election day. And whatever the investigation says after the election will be irrelevant. The events unfolding in Benghazi on the tragic night of September 11th were being relayed to the State Department as the attacks were going on, "in real time," as they say. So the idea that the Obama administration now has to carry out a time-consuming "investigation" to find out what those events were, when the information was immediately available at the time, is a little much. The full story of what happened in Libya, down to the last detail, may never be known. But, as someone once said, you don't need to eat a whole egg to know that it is rotten. And you don't need to know every detail of the events before, during and after the attacks to know that the story put out by the Obama administration was a fraud. The administration's initial story that what happened in Benghazi began as a protest against an anti-Islamic video in America was a very convenient theory. The most obvious alternative explanation would have been devastating to Barack Obama's much heralded attempts to mollify and pacify Islamic nations in the Middle East. To have helped overthrow pro-Western governments in Egypt and Libya, only to bring anti-Western Islamic extremists to power would have been revealed as a foreign policy disaster of the first magnitude. To have been celebrating President Obama's supposedly heroic role in the killing of Osama bin Laden, with the implication that Al Qaeda was crippled, would have been revealed as a farce. Osama bin Laden was by no means the first man to plan a surprise attack on America and later be killed. Japan's Admiral Yamamoto planned the attack on Pearl Harbor that brought the United States into World War II, and he was later tracked down and shot down in a plane that was carrying him. Nobody tried to depict President Franklin D. Roosevelt as some kind of hero for having simply authorized the killing of Yamamoto. In that case, the only hero who was publicized was the man who shot down the plane that Yamamoto was in. Yet the killing of Osama bin Laden has been depicted as some kind of act of courage by President Obama. After bin Laden was located, why would any President not give the go-ahead to get him? That took no courage at all. It would have been far more dangerous politically for Obama not to have given the go-ahead. Moreover, Obama hedged his bets by authorizing the admiral in charge of the operation to proceed only under various conditions. This meant that success would be credited to Obama and failure could be blamed on the admiral -- who would join George W. Bush, Hillary Clinton and other scapegoats for Obama's failures. Thomas Sowell</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351081775178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:29:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351081796906-9</Id><Topic><Title>TIC TOC I hope your ready for the drop</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351007476668</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 11:51:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, it dropped all the way up to $75 earlier. Nice call. Don't worry, Wal-Mart is doing seasonal hiring, so you can make your money back.</Msg><Username>lllllinnnndaaa</Username><Timestamp>1351081796906</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:29:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351081876988-10</Id><Topic><Title>TIC TOC I hope your ready for the drop</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351007476668</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 11:51:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats funny!</Msg><Username>krc007</Username><Timestamp>1351081876988</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:31:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351082170131-11</Id><Title>Democrats begin their Dirty Tricks and Voter Suppression.</Title><Msg>Fla. Republicans receiving fake ineligibility letters aimed at suppressing their vote The Florida Department of State’s Division of Elections is investigating a number of fraudulent letters sent to voters in the state questioning their citizenship and voter eligibility, in a possible attempt to keep them home on Election Day. “The Florida Department of State unequivocally opposes all attempts at voter fraud or intimidation and will pursue every avenue to ensure free, fair and open elections for all eligible voters,” Florida Secretary of State Ken Detzner said in a statement. “Voter fraud and intimidation can deny voters their voice in government and will not be tolerated.” The statement alerted the public of the fraudulent letters, which claim to be from Florida election officials and imply that the recipient might be ineligible to vote. Charles Callaghan, a Republican from Ponte Vedra, received one of the fraudulent letters Saturday. “Basically, when I read the letter, I got the impression that I was not going to be able to vote, because my citizenship was being questioned,” Callaghan told The Daily Caller. “I wasn’t quite sure why it would be, because I was born in the United States, and I’ve always been a United States citizen, and nothing has changed in my life … that would cause my citizenship to be called into question.” Callaghan noticed that his letter lacked a return address and included faulty contact information and a Seattle, Washington postmark. “I said to my wife, somebody is just trying to keep me from voting,” Callaghan said. “To put that doubt in my mind that I can’t vote and then not give me a way that I could dispute it — because they didn’t give me a phone number or address — they are thinking I am going to get frustrated and just not go vote. ” The Romney campaign said it is aware of the possible fraud.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351082170131</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:36:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351083201031-12</Id><Title>Voters Decide on President by Body Language: Romney Won</Title><Msg>Words don't matter as much as body language when voters decide on the man they trust to lead the nation. Despite all the policy debates, all the fact checking, all the pundits, we don't weigh and balance and research, not most of us. We don't even use our forebrains. We use the most primitive part of our brains, the part that can smell danger, that smells who is the alpha male, who is the omega, who is the rogue. The nose knows who is the real leader. We can smell a winner. Mitt Romney passed the smell test for the third time last night, and Barack Obama failed. Choosing a president isn't a beauty contest, although good looks help. It is about masculinity. It is about confidence and calm strength. Romney was the happy warrior of the debate. He was the guy so big he doesn't have to pick fights or show off his muscles. They are obvious from his stature and how he conducts himself. Obama was the junk yard dog, trying to protect his turf by mean looks and threatening to bite. He didn't actually get his teeth into Romney a single time. Obama's attempt at a steely gaze came across as unpleasant, hostile, even silly. He didn't faze Romney, and he didn't win anyone's confidence. He made himself smell nasty. A snapping dog doesn't make people feel safe. The contest to lead the nation touches our most basic instincts. Our brains evolved 100,000 years ago when we roved the earth in small bands, guided by elders but led by warriors. There was no room for error, and mistakes were fatal. Those who followed a vacillating leader were wiped out. Those who chose a capable leader passed their genes on. This is something people understand deep in their guts. I have spent many hours observing wolves in the wild. Some packs thrive, others disappear. Some raise their pups in security because they hold onto big, prosperous territories. Other packs are pushed into marginal areas where tough winters decimate them, and they are preyed upon by rival packs. Being an alpha male is a demanding role. It is not based on something as simple as size - it also requires a higher level of aggressiveness, with the guts to dominate every situation. The alpha defends his territory through intimidation and if necessary, through battle. The alpha male never hesitates to fight to protect his pack. Voters, like wolves, don't want a leader who will fight to the death. They do want a leader who will never run from a fight and will win every time. They go for the one who smells like a winner. Think of the presidential contests of the last fifty years. Kennedy was more upbeat, confident, more the virile alpha male than Nixon, who came across as Obama does, mean, a whiner. But when Nixon was matched against Humphrey, he was the more virile. LBJ passed the sniff test. Carter didn't have much, but he beat Ford. Reagan could have bottled it. Dukakis smelled like a wimp, making George Walker Bush look good in comparison. Clinton again was the more upbeat, confident, virile top dog. Kerry, the French poodle with the rich wife, never had a chance against George W. Bush. McCain, although a war hero and in fact the more capable male than Obama, wasn't willing to fight the messiah and disqualified himself. And so we were left for the last four years with a fake alpha. Obama has the easy virility of the charmer. Great on promises, but not trustworthy. Definitely not someone to go to the mat for you. At the end of the day, for Obama, it's all about Obama. He and Michelle have been having a ball in the White House while 23 million Americans are unemployed, their lives in tatters. He's having fun being lionized by Hollywood and going to Las Vegas fundraisers, while our Libyan ambassador is denied security, is given no military back up during the 6 hour firefight in Benghazi, and is dragged through the streets. Obama shows up for the funeral photo op. That is not an alpha male. The kids in college still think Obama's great, because they don't know the difference between cool and manhood. They want the free stuff and pretty dreams he peddles. Adults can smell something is off. Obama has been worse than a weak leader. He is something America has never seen, and that is why he was able to fool people. It is why our country is such a mess. He is a false leader. He never believed in our pack. He never wanted to protect our territory. He is a leftist ideologue who wanted to bring our pack down to size and give the other packs a bigger share. The landslide victory and fawning press of his 'historic' election gave him control over both Houses of Congress. He used the opportunity to crush our economy with Obamacare, EPA regs, and a trillion-dollar-a-year payoff to his base, that has brought our economy to its knees. He has deprived more Americans of the ability to be self-supporting, independent adults than any time since the Great Depression. Obama wanted to shrink us on the world stage, and went far beyond bowing and apologizing. He purposefully, foolishly and oh so dangerously destabilized the Middle East. Obama got positive headlines for pushing out dictators, only to invite terror organizations -- the Muslim Brotherhood and Al Qaeda -- to take over Egypt and possibly Libya. He has allowed the mullahs of Iran to achieve the brink of going nuclear. He doesn't really believe in the jihadi movement. They're the third world victims and we're the insensitive, greedy bad guys. Most Americans don't know details of foreign policy, and don't care. But they watched two men sit at a table last night and fight over who is qualified to lead our country. Most of the public doesn't know enough about Iran or Libya or Egypt to tell Romney's facts from Obama's fictions. They can be fooled by a brazen and charming serial liar who tells us he's done a great job, nothing to worry about with Egypt, Libya, Iran, move along. Obama's lies are echoed by a politically corrupted press. But the public can't be lied to any more about the economy, because they are living it. They can't be fooled into thinking Obama has any intention of doing a course correction and improving his performance in the next four years. They've been looking for a new alpha, a real one. After the three debates, they've found him. His name is Mitt Romney. Karin McQuillan</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351083201031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:53:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351083779666-13</Id><Title>SHOCKER: More Cronyism Revealed in the Obama Administration</Title><Msg>Put on your shocked faces: Another Crony Joe Biden scheme comes to light In a nutshell: James Biden isn’t a big name in the business of residential housing development, so what exactly qualifies him to work at a construction company and share in the winnings of a $1.5 billion project to build affordable homes in Iraq? If you said it has something to do with his last name, the one shared by his older brother Vice President Joe Biden, you wouldn’t be far off. At least that’s the guess of some Wall Street analysts who cover the Marlton, NJ-based company Hill International and think they’ve seen yet another sordid tale of crony capitalism. Hill has been around for decades; its main business is managing construction projects in the Middle East and here in America. It’s built a good reputation over the years, as has the father-son team who run it, Irv and David Richter. But the bursting of the real-estate bubble took its toll; Hill shares are down 80 percent since 2008. Since 2011, the company has reported losses. Its Middle East business has also been stymied by the Arab Spring uprisings; in Libya alone, Hill is out $60 million in payments that it’s still trying to recover. But it got some good news not long after its housing subsidiary hired James Biden as an executive vice president in late 2010. Just six months later, Hill won one of its biggest contracts ever, a $1.5 billion deal to build at least 100,000 affordable homes in Iraq. A good deal for Hill, a relative newcomer to building homes — and for James Biden, who as one partner will get a good share of that $1.5 billion. The deal is contingent on the Iraqi government providing financing, which it has yet to do, but Hill execs tell analysts the money could start flowing by the end of the year. That’s when everyone involved, James Biden included, will start collecting on tens of millions of dollars in profits.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351083779666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:02:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351084052948-14</Id><Title>Does James Biden’s name ring a bell?</Title><Msg>It Should......brother James and the VP’s lobbyist son Hunter were caught up in a shady financial scheme that exposed the family’s nepotism-dependent business. Refresher: “Average Joe” Biden wants you to believe he hangs with the regular guys at Home Depot. But the BFFs (Best Friends Forever!) of the Bidens wear pin-striped suits, not coveralls. They carry briefcases, not toolboxes. And you can bet they’re not driving pick-up trucks. One lucrative cloud seeded by “rainmaker” William Oldaker showered generous benefits on both Hunter Biden and his dad. In 2005–06, the Chicago-based personal injury law firm of Cooney and Conway paid Oldaker, Biden &amp; Belair $220,000 to push its tort reform proposals. At the same time, Cooney and Conway gave Senator Biden’s political campaigns more than $70,000. The firm’s founding co-partner John Cooney told the Chicago Daily Law Bulletin that he struck up a friendship with Biden in 2004 over a legislative battle before Biden’s Senate Judiciary Committee. Cooney was part of a small group that strategized with Biden on campaign matters at his Delaware home. Cooney and Conway represent clients claiming asbestos-related injuries. Biden sided with the trial lawyers, actively opposing measures to reduce frivolous lawsuits and reduce the returns on future lawsuits. Other heavy-hitting law firms that pitched in to Biden’s campaigns: Baltimore-based Peter Angelos, whose law firm gave Biden $156,250; Wilmington-based Young Conaway Stargatt &amp; Taylor, which kicked in $127, 979; and Pachulski Stang Zielhl &amp; Jones, which donated $145,625, according to The American Lawyer. Philip Howard, author and founder of Common Good, a bipartisan coalition that advocates for legal reform, summed up his record: “Senator Biden has a pretty clear record of being close to the trial lawyers. To people who are interested in restoring reliability to the legal system, he’s probably unlikely to be the champion.” Disgraced trial lawyer Richard Scruggs donated $11,500 to Biden in 2008. After Scruggs was convicted of attempting to bribe a federal judge, Biden tried to show his ethical bona fides by donating the money to a worthy charity. But Biden couldn’t steer clear of nepotism. The money ended up with the National Prostate Cancer Coalition—a charity where, The American Lawyer pointed out, Biden’s son Hunter sits on the board of directors. Another Biden family pal in the trial lawyers’ community: Jeff Cooper. With his partner John Simmons, the 39-year-old Cooper built one of the biggest asbestos litigation firms in the country. SimmonsCooper, based in Madison County, Illinois, has donated a whopping $196,050 to Biden’s campaigns since 2003, according to the nonpartisan Center for Responsive Politics in Washington, D.C. In that same time frame, the firm poured $6.5 million into lobbying against the same tort reform bill that fellow asbestos litigators Cooney and Conway opposed—and which Senator Biden worked hard to defeat. Without a hint of irony, Cooper extolled Biden’s anti-tort reform stance: “He understands the plight of the little guy and is against huge corporate interest.” But what Biden did was help fuel lucrative business for the tort bar. When courts in SimmonsCooper’s home base in Illinois finally started cracking down on what had become “America’s No. 1 judicial hellhole” for filing out-of-control tort claims, the firm turned East. And in Joe Biden’s Delaware, they created a new sanctuary. The Wall Street Journal explained: SimmonsCooper is a big asbestos player, and Madison County was until recently one of America’s meccas for jackpot justice. But the story gets better: Mr. Biden has been helping the tort bar turn his home state of Delaware into a statewide Madison County. SimmonsCooper made hundreds of millions of dollars on asbestos cases in Madison County, but that started to change in 2004. The business community helped to elect conservative Lloyd Karmeier to the Illinois Supreme Court. Madison County Circuit Judge Daniel Stack also took over the asbestos docket, was determined to clean house, and began dismissing suits filed by residents outside his jurisdiction. SimmonsCooper and other firms started shopping for a new legal goldmine. And where better than Delaware? Many companies incorporate there, which means a list of defendants usually includes a Delaware target. Beginning in mid-2005, SimmonsCooper began transferring its suits to Bidenland. The trial bar’s strategy has been to overwhelm Delaware’s once-sensible legal system, taking advantage of rules that pressure companies to settle. In the 22 months following SimmonsCooper’s first asbestos filing in Delaware, the state was hit with 412 suits, primarily from SimmonsCooper and fellow asbestos giant Baron &amp; Budd. According to the Madison County Record—a legal journal that has doggedly followed this story—clerks in Wilmington were “working nights and weekends to keep up” with the filings. The trial lawyers drew sympathetic judges that have already overseen big verdicts against defendants, primarily Detroit auto makers. Plaintiffs have obtained certain procedures that raise the costs of defense, and restrict defendants’ ability to take discovery. Cooper first befriended Biden’s sons, Hunter and Beau, before deepening his financial and political relationship with their dad. There’s a personal connection: Cooper’s wife went to high school with Hunter Biden’s wife, Kathleen. And as Biden the Elder was carrying water for the trial lawyers in the U.S. Senate, SimmonsCooper was working another Biden channel through the Wilmington, Delaware, law firm of Bifferato, Gentilotti &amp; Biden, where Joe’s son and Hunter’s brother, Beau, was a partner. SimmonsCooper found Delaware an attractive new magnet for its asbestos litigation racket because many of the firm’s defendants included clients who had incorporated in the state. SimmonsCooper recruited Beau’s firm to work as co-counsel on Delaware asbestos litigation cases. The Illinois firm steered dozens of cases Beau Biden’s way. He dropped an asbestos defense client to accommodate his deep-pocketed family friend. SimmonsCooper then forked over $35,000 to Beau Biden’s successful run for state attorney general in 2006. Steve Hantler, president of the American Justice Partnership Foundation, observed, “Delaware is fast becoming asbestos lawsuit central.…A tsunami of lawsuits being filed by the SimmonsCooper firm, along with the flow of campaign dollars to Delaware politicians is quite the troubling coincidence.” Even more troubling was the financial partnership Hunter Biden and his Uncle James (Senator Biden’s brother) attempted to forge with SimmonsCooper. The Bidens approached SimmonsCooper with a proposition: Team up with the family to buy a hedge fund investment firm for $21 million. Cooper agreed to chip in $2 million in exchange for 10 percent interest. The Bidens negotiated the hedge fund buyout of Paradigm Global Advisors with business partner Anthony Lotito Jr. in 2006. As Paradigm chairman, Hunter Biden oversaw half a billion dollars of client money invested in hedge funds while remaining a lobbyist at Oldaker, Biden &amp; Belair. But things fell apart. In their haste to clean up the Biden image, they ended up with dirtier hands. According to Lotito, the Bidens pursued the venture to help get Hunter Biden out of the lobbying business before Dad launched another presidential campaign. The Madison County Record, which tracked the dealings of the Bidens and SimmonsCooper closely, laid out the timeline: According to court records filed by Lotito, Joe Biden wanted Hunter Biden to find a different line of work because he couldn’t afford to run for president as father of a lobbyist. Lotito claims he and James Biden discussed Hunter Biden’s job prospects. Lotito met James Biden in 2002 and they invested together in 2005, according to Lotito. Lotito introduced James Biden and Hunter Biden to lawyer John Fascian[a], and the four began planning to buy Paradigm Capital Management. Majority owner James Parks had started Paradigm in 1991 and successfully promoted it as less volatile than most hedge funds. Everyone agreed that the Bidens and Lotito would form a corporation to buy 54 percent of Paradigm for $21.3 million in cash. They would install Hunter Biden as chief executive officer at a salary of $1.2 million. In April 2006, they formed LBB Limited Liability Corporation. In May 2006, SimmonsCooper invested $1 million. In June 2006, according to Lotito, the Bidens told him to stay away. In August 2006, according to Lotito, the Bidens formed a corporation, executed a promissory note for $8.1 million, and purchased Paradigm’s assets. In September 2006, Lotito signed an agreement relinquishing his third of LBB. He sued the Bidens in January 2007, alleging fraud and breach of fiduciary duty. Lie down with shady partners, get up with a public relations nightmare. Lotito maintained that the Bidens cut a secret deal and tried to fraudulently trick him into signing away his interest in the LLC that they had formed together. In court filings, Lotito’s lawyer asserted that the Bidens used their political clout to intimidate his client: “Ultimately, the Bidens threatened to use their alleged connections with a former U.S. Senator to retaliate against counsel for insisting that his bill be paid, claiming that the former Senator was prepared to use his influence with a federal judge to disadvantage counsel in a proceeding then pending before that court.” The Bidens shot back that Lotito had neglected to mention that the lawyer he connected them with, John Fasciana, was a crook. Fasciana had been convicted in July 2005 on federal charges of conspiracy and wire and mail fraud over a scheme to cheat Electronic Data Systems (Ross Perot’s computer services company) of millions of dollars. Fasciana was sentenced in 2008 to four years in prison, but has appealed the case. He sued the Bidens for nearly $200,000 in legal fees; they countersued Fasciana for overbilling him and committing fraud by concealing his criminal conviction. Hunter and James Biden also countersued Lotito in February 2007 seeking $10 million. The Bidens asserted that Lotito “hid debts and falsely claimed he held securities licenses to lure them as partners in the planned $21.3 million acquisition,” the Washington Post reported. “Had James and Hunter Biden known the truth about Anthony Lotito, they never would have gone into business with him,” their complaint alleged. Where did this leave SimmonsCooper, which had kicked in half of a $2 million investment at the request of the Bidens? The Illinois firm had withdrawn from the deal after watching $1 million of its investment allegedly squandered by Lotito. The investment “converted to debt,” which Hunter and James Biden then attempted to shift to Lotito. A New York judge didn’t go along with the Bidens’ attempt to play the victim card. In May 2008, he rejected their bid after concluding they should have vetted the fund more carefully and performed their own due diligence. Cutting through the ploy, the judge ruled that the Bidens’ counterclaims “seek only to foment uncertainty and chaos between the parties in the event that plaintiff is successful in presenting the main claims.…Such pleading will not be countenanced.” Moreover, he ruled, “Certainly defendants do not claim that the law permits sophisticated investors to rely on whatever representations a potential advisor makes without the need for a diligent inquiry by defendants, and that such representations are actionable if they wind up to have been faulty.” In January 2009, court papers announced that the legal fracas had been settled confidentially —preventing any disclosure or discussion whatsoever regarding the nature of the settlement or the subject matter of the action. The record did note that the lawsuit was resolved “without cost to any party.” For anyone paying close attention, however, the cost to the Biden family’s “just folks” reputation was clear. Alas, the settlement didn’t end the sordid story for the Bidens… From one smelly crony scheme to the next, Stimulus Sheriff Joe and his fam keep laughing all the way to the bank. Malkin</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351084052948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:07:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351085003424-15</Id><Title>Uh O.......Emails: White House Knew Libya Was a Terrorist Attack Within Two Hours</Title><Msg>The White House story line on Libya just keeps falling apart. Reuters got their hands on damning official emails showing the White House and State Department knew the attack on the U.S. consulate on 9/11 was a terrorist attack carried out by extremist groups linked to al Qaeda, within two hours. Previously, we found out through intelligence sources the White House knew within 24 hours the attack was in fact a terrorist attack, despite President Obama refusing to classify the attack as a terrorist attack until 14 days after it happened. For weeks, the White House and the State Department claimed the attack was a result of a YouTube video insulting Islam. This latest round of news further proves "the video" was used a distraction and clearly shows an effort by the White House to cover-up what really happened. The records obtained by Reuters consist of three emails dispatched by the State Department's Operations Center to multiple government offices, including addresses at the White House, Pentagon, intelligence community and FBI, on the afternoon of September 11. The first email, timed at 4:05 p.m. Washington time - or 10:05 p.m. Benghazi time, 20-30 minutes after the attack on the U.S. diplomatic mission allegedly began - carried the subject line "U.S. Diplomatic Mission in Benghazi Under Attack" and the notation "SBU", meaning "Sensitive But Unclassified." The text said the State Department's regional security office had reported that the diplomatic mission in Benghazi was "under attack. Embassy in Tripoli reports approximately 20 armed people fired shots; explosions have been heard as well." A third email, also marked SBU and sent at 6:07 p.m. Washington time, carried the subject line: "Update 2: Ansar al-Sharia Claims Responsibility for Benghazi Attack." Considering the State Department's Charlene Lamb testified before Congress that she watched the attack happen live, it makes sense they knew within two hours what kind of attack this was. As a refresher: And a reminder of what President Obama said during the second presidential debate at Hofstra University in New York last week. “The suggestion that anybody on my team would play politics or mislead when we’ve lost four of our own, Governor, is offensive … That’s not what I do as president. That’s not what I do as commander-in-chief.” It'll be interesting to see how White House Press Secretary Jay Carney spins the two hour news today.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351085003424</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:23:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351085585629-16</Id><Title>Hoofbeats of Electoral Doom?</Title><Msg>There is a picture on Townhall this morning of US Special Operations Forces riding horses into Afghanistan in 2001. Contrary to the President's snide comments Monday night, sometimes horses in fact still play an important role in the military -- and their work in Afghanistan will be commemorated with a statue being unveiled across from the World Trade Center site on November 11. Like so many other supercilious Obama put-downs, the comments about "horses and bayonets" are backfiring on the President. The whole episode reminds me of Ronald Reagan's brilliant assessment: "It's not that our liberal friends are ignorant; it's that they know so much that isn't so."</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351085585629</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:33:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351086602489-17</Id><Title>NC voters say ballot cast for Romney came up Obama on machine...</Title><Msg>More Democrat dirty tricks. The Democrat party has truly become like the Bolshevik communists of 1917. GREENSBORO, N.C. –The presidential election is just around the corner and voting issues have already become a problem in Guilford County. On Monday, several voters complained that their electronic ballot machine cast the wrong vote. All the complaints were made by people who voted at the Bur-Mil Park polling location. One of the voters, Sher Coromalis, says she cast her ballot for Governor Mitt Romney, but every time she entered her vote the machine defaulted to President Obama. “I was so upset that this could happen,” said Coromalis. Guilford County Board of Elections Director George Gilbert says the problem arises every election. It can be resolved after the machine is re-calibrated by poll workers. “It’s not a conspiracy it’s just a machine that needs to be corrected,” Gilbert said. After the third try, Coromalis says she was able to get her vote counted for Gov. Romney but was still annoyed. “I should have just mailed it in,” Coromalis said. Marie Haydock, who also voted at the Bur-Mil Park polling location, had the same problem. “The frustration is… every vote counts,” said Haydock. Elections officials say the machines have been fixed as of Tuesday, and no problems have been reported since. Early voting ends November 3.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351086602489</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086656325-18</Id><Topic><Title>Hoofbeats of Electoral Doom?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351085585629</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>also....the marines still use bayonets.</Msg><Username>makboe</Username><Timestamp>1351086656325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:50:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086946880-19</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats begin their Dirty Tricks and Voter Suppression.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351082170131</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:36:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wonderful news ..anything to keep up with your vile pukes supressing votes in many states ....see thoose billboards they took down in Ohio ,puke?? Think big bird put them up ?? Pub party is built on #$%$ and voter stupidity ..They welcome you</Msg><Username>eddiew37</Username><Timestamp>1351086946880</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:55:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087457089-20</Id><Topic><Title>What ever happened to the India 787 were the landig gear jammed up?</Title><Username>john.kloczkowski</Username><Timestamp>1351077333439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:15:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok Bath Salts, Someown needs to break it down for you. 1) Why did the landing gear door not close ? 2) Which plant was it made ? You should post information that is has value. Your sexual frustration comes out in your post. Get a mag and go to the rest room and "have at it". You will feel like a new man for at least an hour and you can do it again.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1351087457089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087509438-21</Id><Topic><Title>Does James Biden’s name ring a bell?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351084052948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:07:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Every day Joe" is a slick con artist like Obama. Both crooks out to enrich themselves without producing anything of value but the expense of the people they deceive.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351087509438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:05:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351088261666-22</Id><Topic><Title>What ever happened to the India 787 were the landig gear jammed up?</Title><Username>john.kloczkowski</Username><Timestamp>1351077333439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:15:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Forbes: It turns out that because of a faulty hydraulic valve the landing gear had not lowered automatically as it was supposed to and had to be deployed manually. No emergency call was made, and after circling we landed just fine, although this particular jet was then grounded for repair. It went back into service the next day.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351088261666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:17:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351088292449-23</Id><Topic><Title>TADF BIG OCTOBER NEWS.TADF 2000% GAINS POSSIBLE ON ACQUISITIONS ANNOUNCED. Undervalued and CHEAP@ 0.0007.READ</Title><Username>bestpennies</Username><Timestamp>1350929752150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:15:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Something big about happen.</Msg><Username>hugemargins</Username><Timestamp>1351088292449</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:18:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351088430884-24</Id><Title>GALLUP: R 51% O 46%... OHIO: R 48% O 48%...</Title><Msg>Romney surging and as usual, Democrats have turned to cheating as their ace in the hole.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351088430884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351088817677-25</Id><Topic><Title>Billy Graham buys election ads after Romney meeting</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351087731373</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:08:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Senators and Representatives before mentioned, and the members of the several state legislatures, and all executive and judicial officers, both of the United States and of the several states, shall be bound by oath or affirmation, to support this Constitution; but no religious test shall ever be required as a qualification to any office or public trust under the United States.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351088817677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:26:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351089558640-26</Id><Topic><Title>Billy Graham buys election ads after Romney meeting</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351087731373</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:08:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A good reason to vote for Obabma, bloated anti union thug sheldon adelson supports willard! Kamakure</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351089558640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:39:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351090173735-27</Id><Title>Republicans defend rape as God Intended</Title><Msg>The NRSC Chairman called Democratic attacks on Mourdock's controversial comments "irresponsible and ridiculous." National Republican Senatorial Committee (NRSC) Chairman John Cornyn (Texas) is standing by Indiana state Treasurer Richard Mourdock (R) after his Tuesday night comments that pregnancy resulting from rape can be "something God intended." In a statement released Wednesday, Cornyn points out that Mourdock's Senate opponent, Rep. Joe Donnelly (D-Ind.), is also against abortion rights and calls Democratic attempts to attack Mourdock on the issue "irresponsible and ridiculous.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351090173735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:49:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351090316869-28</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans defend rape as God Intended</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351090173735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:49:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so... if Richard Mourdock receives it in the booty... then we can all applause God's intention !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351090316869</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:51:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351091055166-29</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Increasing his Lead... Obama Snickering!</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351038003994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:20:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>....Romney is a joke</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351091055166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:04:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351091266647-30</Id><Topic><Title>What ever happened to the India 787 were the landig gear jammed up?</Title><Username>john.kloczkowski</Username><Timestamp>1351077333439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:15:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Messier-Bugatti-Dowty was selected in March 2004 by The Boeing Company to supply the main and nose landing gear structure for the new 787 Dreamliner commercial jet. Messier-Bugatti-Dowty is responsible for the design, development, testing and manufacture of the main and nose landing gear structure. The 787 program is Messier-Bugatti-Dowty’s first prime contract with Boeing for a commercial aircraft. The parts are made in many foreign facilities and final assembly for the landing gear is at MBD facility in Everett Washington.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351091266647</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351091648614-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Mocks Romney at his Face</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351038324274</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:25:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>love it !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351091648614</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:14:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351091650924-32</Id><Topic><Title>The Enlightened GOP</Title><Username>the_loading_dock</Username><Timestamp>1351072329372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 05:52:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good god, what a sick, and sickening party.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351091650924</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:14:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351091696162-33</Id><Topic><Title>What ever happened to the India 787 were the landig gear jammed up?</Title><Username>john.kloczkowski</Username><Timestamp>1351077333439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:15:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What language is that?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351091696162</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:14:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351091860685-34</Id><Topic><Title>The man without a soul</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351031981162</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 18:39:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...The fact is, we don’t know which Mitt Romney would take the oath of office...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351091860685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:17:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351092731342-35</Id><Title>Obama and Democrats; our work is not done !</Title><Msg>... Not until every last Republican is sent back to the hell hole they crawled out of...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351092731342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351092961294-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Democrats; our work is not done !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351092731342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your work may not be done, but it is futile.......America has finally faced the reality that they've been lied to by Obama and the Democrats.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351092961294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351093019518-37</Id><Title>confusing message from BA</Title><Msg>"Oct 24 (Reuters) - Boeing Co Chief Executive Jim McNerney said the company expects to deliver 28 787 Dreamliners in 2012." With the delivery of a 787 last Saturday, they have already delivered 28 787's so I assume this means they will not be deliveriing any more this year? Either he was misquoted or had his head up his butt. (: )? It is possible that the customers are not ready to take any more planes this year but that seems a stretch.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351093019518</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:36:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351093248721-38</Id><Topic><Title>Liar in Chief Caught Lying again</Title><Username>locost7777</Username><Timestamp>1351054490487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:54:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>False. "What a way to run a country" statement from somebody who supported the Iraq invasion. What a worthless hypocrite.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1351093248721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:40:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351093377585-39</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke will not be reappointed. He said the Obama's policies do not support a recovery. He represents all the guru's across America</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351092249613</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:24:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney should appoint Ron Paul to head the the Federal Reserve.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351093377585</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:42:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351093638644-40</Id><Title>Bayonet Count: More Today Than in 1916</Title><Msg>From the department of picayune fact-checking: The U.S. Army has 419,155 bayonets in its inventory. The Marine Corps has about 195,334 bayonets (and has plans to acquire 175,061 more). That's a total of 614,489 bayonets with 175,061 to be added. Keith Koffler adds everything up: Given that there were about 200,000 men in the Army and National Guard in 1916, according to National Review, that would mean that there are three times as many bayonets today and probably will be at least four times as many than before World War I.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351093638644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:47:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351093646307-41</Id><Topic><Title>Liar in Chief Caught Lying again</Title><Username>locost7777</Username><Timestamp>1351054490487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:54:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Earlier you said you hoped Willard would confront the President about that fake story that he was gay. Sheesh. The USA is doomed with citizens like you.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1351093646307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351093897363-42</Id><Title>Do we really Need a Commander in Chief who can read a teleprompter..........</Title><Msg>....or do we need one that knows what a Corpsman is and how the title is pronounced?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351093897363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094189049-43</Id><Topic><Title>Bayonet Count: More Today Than in 1916</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351093638644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:47:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That sort of minutiae cuts both ways. So our military is MUCH stronger than it was in 1916! Good job, Obama!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351094189049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:56:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094770186-44</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Democrats; our work is not done !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351092731342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>futile? ... are you a cyborg !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351094770186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:06:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351095046593-45</Id><Topic><Title>Uh O.......Emails: White House Knew Libya Was a Terrorist Attack Within Two Hours</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351085003424</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:23:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Update 2: Ansar al-Sharia Claims Responsibility for Benghazi Attack."The message reported: "Embassy Tripoli reports the group claimed responsibility on Facebook and Twitter and has called for an attack on Embassy Tripoli." UPDATE - RIGHT-WING #$%$ BELIEVE TWITTEWR/FACEBOOK OVER U.S. INTEL WHAT DID RMONEY KNOW AND WHEN DID HE KNOW IT! THIS NEEDS TO BE INVESTIGATED FOR POLITCAL REASONS, U.S. intelligence official said that during the first classified briefing about Benghazi given to members of Congress, officials "carefully laid out the full range of sparsely available information, relying on the best analysis available at the time." The official added, however, that the initial analysis of the attack that was presented to legislators was mixed. "Briefers said extremists were involved in attacks that appeared spontaneous, there may have been a variety of motivating factors, and possible links to groups such as (al Qaeda in the Islamic Maghreb and Ansar al-Sharia) were being looked at closely," the official said.</Msg><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351095046593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351095306051-46</Id><Title>I wake up in the morning and Barack Obama is President.</Title><Msg>I love it !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351095306051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:15:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351096102345-47</Id><Topic><Title>confusing message from BA</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351093019518</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:36:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(Corrects headline and 1st paragraph to "has delivered" 28 Dreamliners this year from "will deliver") Oct 24 (Reuters) - Boeing Co Chief Executive Jim McNerney said the company has delivered 28 787 Dreamliners so far this year, part of its strategy to ramp up production to improve earnings and cash flow.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351096102345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:28:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351096260727-48</Id><Title>Reuters corrects their mistake</Title><Msg>(Corrects headline and 1st paragraph to "has delivered" 28 Dreamliners this year from "will deliver") Oct 24 (Reuters) - Boeing Co Chief Executive Jim McNerney said the company has delivered 28 787 Dreamliners so far this year, part of its strategy to ramp up production to improve earnings and cash flow.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351096260727</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351096357814-49</Id><Topic><Title>Bayonet Count: More Today Than in 1916</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351093638644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:47:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know he really hit a nerve (Romney's comparison to the number of ships in 1916 was really stupid) when the RWNJ's are going crazy to intentionally misinterpreted what the pres said. For you RWNJ's who have wasted that private education by numbing your brains, I will help. The POINT is that the count of ships compared to 1916 means nothing, Naval warfare is NOTHING like it was then. Big battle ships are not focal now, AIRCRAFT are. I don't know the numbers but I am sure that we have more AIRCRAFT in the navy than ships today OR in 1916. The bigger POINT is that you need to look at these things in context, and the RWNJ's are so into celebrating their stupidity (both natural and intentional) that they miss all this. You know you have hit home when the fools (RWNJ's and their allies) nitpick the words and miss the meaning. It is another example of how the GOP celebrates stupidity, and encourages it to the point that smart people feel compelled by their party to practice it. Hmmm, doing things because it is the party line, sounds like the Taliban, or the communists. Just Pathetic.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1351096357814</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:32:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351096379928-50</Id><Topic><Title>I wake up in the morning and Barack Obama is President.</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351095306051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:15:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds More Like a Nightmare, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351096379928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:32:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351096965512-51</Id><Topic><Title>Bayonet Count: More Today Than in 1916</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351093638644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:47:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Teddy's "big stick" has been replaced by drones.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351096965512</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:42:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351097127748-52</Id><Topic><Title>Bayonet Count: More Today Than in 1916</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351093638644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:47:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, your post is from the Department Of Stupid And Worthless Analogies. Equating military strength in terms of bayonets is worthy of your overall brains, however.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1351097127748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:45:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351097191621-53</Id><Topic><Title>I wake up in the morning and Barack Obama is President.</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351095306051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:15:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wake up in the morning a take a poop which reminds me of Obama.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351097191621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:46:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351097754105-54</Id><Topic><Title>Bayonet Count: More Today Than in 1916</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351093638644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:47:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mittens is just trying to court the defocn/military vote specifically in va, etc. by echoing raygun and boosh by promising to spend $2t, even more than the pentagon has asked (and 'creating jobs ?) the only thing mittens has to explain how he is going to pay for all his empty promises and remain revenue neutral, obvious to all except the shameless rwnj's</Msg><Username>repupblicansagainstromney</Username><Timestamp>1351097754105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351097775812-55</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Democrats; our work is not done !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351092731342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're being very judgemental for a liberal. Where is all the compassion and joy in diversity?</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1351097775812</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:56:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351097970023-56</Id><Title>STUPID LYING REPUGS RELY ON FACEBOOK/TWITTER OVER INTEL</Title><Msg>White House officials maintained that the emails don't contradict what the White House believed at that point, based on the intelligence community's #$%$ment of the attack. The views of the intelligence community are valued far more than Facebook and twitter claims, officials said, describing that email as an unclassified ops alert email, not a vetted intelligence #$%$ment. It was not definitive, but rather the act of flagging open source reporting referencing a Facebook post, and - officials noted - on September 17, Ansar al-Sharia denied responsibility for the attack. Carney today told reporters that there were emails about all sorts of information that was coming available in the aftermath of the attack. "There was a variety of information coming in," Carney said. "The whole point of an intelligence community and what they do is to #$%$ strands of information and make judgments about what happened and who was responsible." Moreover, officials said, the intelligence community still believes there wasn't a tremendous amount of planning before the attack. A terrorist group carrying it out doesn't mean it wasn't an opportunistic attack, officials said.</Msg><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351097970023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:59:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351097983971-57</Id><Topic><Title>Liar in Chief Caught Lying again</Title><Username>locost7777</Username><Timestamp>1351054490487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:54:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama never tells the truth, ever. The truth doesn't work for him!</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1351097983971</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:59:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351098071995-58</Id><Topic><Title>I wake up in the morning and Barack Obama is President.</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351095306051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:15:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>then you wipe your Romney... ha ha ha !!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351098071995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:01:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351098158352-59</Id><Title>Romney’s ‘Let Detroit Go Bankrupt’</Title><Msg>Mittens looks acts, and sounds like the vulture capitalism ceo that he is rather rather than a president</Msg><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351098158352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:02:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351098181688-60</Id><Title>Romney’s ‘Let Detroit Go Bankrupt’</Title><Msg>Mittens looks acts, and sounds like the vulture capitalism ceo that he is rather rather than a president</Msg><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351098181688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351098382715-61</Id><Topic><Title>Bayonet Count: More Today Than in 1916</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351093638644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:47:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Russia and China continue to build up their fleets. They must be laughing. If I were them, I would do anything to see that Obama gets reelected.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1351098382715</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:06:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351098402635-62</Id><Topic><Title>Bayonet Count: More Today Than in 1916</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351093638644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:47:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do the number of tampons fit into the comparison of the old military to the new?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351098402635</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:06:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351098518737-63</Id><Topic><Title>Liar in Chief Caught Lying again</Title><Username>locost7777</Username><Timestamp>1351054490487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:54:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bona fide flip-flopping liars calling someone a liar is too laffable same as mittens complaining that obama criticiszing him does not a campaign make, when that is all mittens has done. time and time again miottens has been asked about his tax plan, etc., and time and time again has not answered the question(s). republicans of today should be truly ashamed for supporting romoney.</Msg><Username>repupblicansagainstromney</Username><Timestamp>1351098518737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:08:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351099462870-64</Id><Topic><Title>Do we really Need a Commander in Chief who can read a teleprompter..........</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351093897363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why not.....we had 8 years under Bush. cheers</Msg><Username>leftandhappy22</Username><Timestamp>1351099462870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:24:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351099515951-65</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s ‘Let Detroit Go Bankrupt’</Title><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351098181688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who's going to bail me out if my company goes BK? Pay my retirement and healthcare? You? Tax payers on the hook for failing companies is #$%$!!! We are becoming a nanny state, a nation of I DESERVE STUFF. We are more divided as a country now than the Vietnam era, time for a change!!</Msg><Username>thegoldude747</Username><Timestamp>1351099515951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:25:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351100677378-66</Id><Title>I guess the street didn't like BA numbers?</Title><Msg>Right at $75 the sell orders piled up and haven't looked back, what's up with that?</Msg><Username>thegoldude747</Username><Timestamp>1351100677378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:44:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351101023285-67</Id><Title>Thar she blows!! Timberrrrrr</Title><Msg>Welcome new BA Baggies!!</Msg><Username>client9clown</Username><Timestamp>1351101023285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351101073116-68</Id><Topic><Title>Thar she blows!! Timberrrrrr</Title><Username>client9clown</Username><Timestamp>1351101023285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:50:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being dumped like a $2 hooker</Msg><Username>client9clown</Username><Timestamp>1351101073116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:51:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351101208234-69</Id><Topic><Title>Thar she blows!! Timberrrrrr</Title><Username>client9clown</Username><Timestamp>1351101023285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:50:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This whole market is being run by crooks and shysters, that's why I short every thing in site. Soon as this pig hit 74.50 I loaded up on PUTs, the crooked hedge funds run this market. More money to be made on the dark side.</Msg><Username>client9clown</Username><Timestamp>1351101208234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:53:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351101411928-70</Id><Topic><Title>Defense Contractors</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1349127803597</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:43:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Expect layoff notices soon!</Msg><Username>cap_pig11</Username><Timestamp>1351101411928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:56:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351101653168-71</Id><Topic><Title>Vote Democrat.......</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349127784141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:43:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...........</Msg><Username>worth_repeating4</Username><Timestamp>1351101653168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:00:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351102197969-72</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans defend rape as God Intended</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351090173735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:49:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet you would change your tune if Obamer was a child created from rape. Where is your compassion? Are you unable to recognize the capacity of women and men to love all children. Do you think people desperate to adopt care if the child they are adopting was conceived by rape? You sound like quite the hater.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351102197969</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:09:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351102394324-73</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans defend rape as God Intended</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351090173735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:49:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most Republicans do not support this, Mourdock is just a #$%$ I can assure you if his wife was raped and got pregnant he would be pulling it out with a coat hanger lol If my wife was raped she would demand an abortion and she is a republican, I'm a Independent.</Msg><Username>client9clown</Username><Timestamp>1351102394324</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:13:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351102551815-74</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans defend rape as God Intended</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351090173735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:49:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stick - have you been trying to get pregnant by taking it in the booty? The statement is about pregnancy from rape not just rape.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351102551815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:15:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351103270981-75</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Increasing his Lead... Obama Snickering!</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351038003994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:20:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UNINSTALLING OBAMA.....……………. █████████████▒▒▒ 90% complete</Msg><Username>client9clown</Username><Timestamp>1351103270981</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351103452866-76</Id><Topic><Title>Vote Democrat.......</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349127784141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:43:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to fivethirtyeight, the guy Jon Stewart call the ruler of statisticstan, Obama's chance of winning has increased to 68%, the empty suit's chances are 32% -- rounding UP. The right-fringers use Rasmussen polls as a sort of night light, to keep their demons in their closets.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351103452866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:30:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351103554520-77</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s ‘Let Detroit Go Bankrupt’</Title><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351098181688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That leaves one final question: Exactly how much did the Romneys make off the auto bailout? Queries to the campaign and the Romneys’ trustee have gone unanswered. ~ G Palast.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351103554520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:32:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351103997852-78</Id><Title>Obama down to 57% on Intrade</Title><Msg>the lowest in over 3 months and down a whopping 23% from, his pre first debate high. The smart money knows what is going to happen in the election. That's why there has been this huge shift AWAY FROM BROKE OBUMMER. Suck on that, dumbocrats.</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1351103997852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:39:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351104312660-79</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Democrats; our work is not done !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351092731342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, your work is not done -- the same cannot be said for Obummer who is completely done -- stick a fork in him -- he's well done.</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1351104312660</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351104417084-80</Id><Topic><Title>Obama down to 57% on Intrade</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1351103997852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:39:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please, you and your fellow dumbcrats -- please come back on November 7, so that we can really laugh at you.</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1351104417084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:46:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351104581625-81</Id><Topic><Title>Obama down to 57% on Intrade</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1351103997852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:39:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Sorry Trump, but in the same way the U.S. doesn't negotiate with terrorists, presidents shouldn't negotiate with idiots," @the_moonface wrote.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351104581625</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351105251030-82</Id><Title>romney</Title><Msg>how can anyone vote for romney when he is supported by murdock, adkin, sheldon adelson, magic underwear and rest of right field looneys. Salt Lake City is too close to the white house, far closer than Rome. Kamakure</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351105251030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:00:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351105340400-83</Id><Title>VA Democrat congressman's son caught on undercover video discussing voter fraud...</Title><Msg>New Undercover Video: Did Congressman's Son Commit Voter Fraud? James O'Keefe has struck again. O'Keefe is the guy who broke the big ACORN scandal with his undercover video reporting. Now, he's out with a video that may land a Congressman's son in trouble for voter fraud. Watch below as Patrick Moran, the son of Virginia Rep. Jim Moran (and the Field Director for his father's campaign), is caught on tape talking to an undercover reporter about how to allegedly cast ballots deceitfully for registered voters. Folks, this is the new wave of reporting in this viral, social media world. O'Keefe may be controversial in some circles and his tactics have been criticized by some, but you can't argue with the fact that he gets people's attention. With the liberal mainstream media lacking when it comes to true investigative journalism, these type of videos will become the norm sooner rather than later. Here's part of the transcript below: Undercover Reporter: There are 100 people who don’t vote. He’s looking for two guys to help him with. … Patrick Moran: Crank it out? Undercover Reporter: Yes. He’s got a van and he and me were going to go around. … Patrick Moran: Rally these people up and get them to the polls. Undercover Reporter: Well, he was actually going to get in a van and vote for them. Patrick Moran: Ohhhh Undercover Reporter: I know, but – Undercover Reporter: It’s scary, but I’m not. … I don’t want to lose, and I’m frightened. Patrick Moran: Yeah. Then later in the video there's talk about creating fake utility bills to serve as voter identification. Patrick Moran: So, if they just have the utility bill or bank statement – bank statement would obviously be tough … but faking a utility bill would be easy enough. Undercover Reporter: How would you do that? Patrick Moran: I mean, I would just find, I don’t know, I guess. … Undercover Reporter: Microsoft Word and type it up. Patrick Moran: Yeah, something like that. To see Video go to Youtube and search "Jim Moran's (D-Va.) Field Director Conspires to Commit Voter Fraud, Forge Docs."</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351105340400</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351105343705-84</Id><Topic><Title>Vote Democrat.......</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1349127784141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:43:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe he was saying that you Dems are dim bulbs. That fact is pretty obvious for those of us with triple digit IQ's.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1351105343705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351105531120-85</Id><Topic><Title>romney</Title><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351105251030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:00:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you bad talking Mormons? Sounds like you are a typical insane lefty creep</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1351105531120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:05:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351105825536-86</Id><Title>Will the real Mitt Please Stand Up</Title><Msg>May I have your attention please? May I have your attention please? Will the real Mitt Shady please stand up? I repeat, will the real Mitt Shady please stand up? We're gonna have a problem here.. " I'm Mitt Shady, yes I'm the real Shady All you other Mitt Shadys are just imitating So won't the real Slim Shady please stand up, please stand up, please stand up?</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1351105825536</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351105870213-87</Id><Title>What 'God Intended'</Title><Msg>so come the claims from righteous hypocrites; to know what God Intended...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351105870213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106483621-88</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Democrats; our work is not done !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351092731342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a shill for the 1%, just as Romney is. Coke or Pepsi, what's the diff?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351106483621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:21:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106526444-89</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Democrats; our work is not done !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351092731342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vote 3rd party--defend democracy.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351106526444</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:22:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106554767-90</Id><Topic><Title>Obama down to 57% on Intrade</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1351103997852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:39:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gonna be a lot of disappointed and broke breckys come November</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351106554767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:22:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106792817-91</Id><Topic><Title>Massive riots when obama is flushed 11/6</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1351029082503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 17:51:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not going downtwn either. Election day the stores will be sold out of bread.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1351106792817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106873947-92</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Democrats; our work is not done !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351092731342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the third Reich had their shot...!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351106873947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:27:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106978195-93</Id><Topic><Title>Obama down to 57% on Intrade</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1351103997852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:39:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Dik, Intrade which you have been touting for the past several months now shows Romney leading Obama in the electoral count. Romney 275 Obama 263</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351106978195</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:29:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351107109728-94</Id><Title>Trump and Obama Charity</Title><Msg>Despite the plethora of "hissing adders", the offer by Trump of $5 million to any charity of Obama's choice on the proviso that Obama release all of his college and passport records and applications is really an easy one. Obama gets to help others, as would be consistent with his claims of his own purpose, while being as transparent as he claims that he is.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351107109728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:31:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351107337150-95</Id><Title>Intrade Electoral Map Romney 275 Obama 263</Title><Msg>Watch out Dik the tide is coming in and you are going under.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351107337150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:35:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351107443313-96</Id><Topic><Title>Trump and Obama Charity</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351107109728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Trump was truly genuine and actually gave a damn about people other than the guy in his mirror - he wouldn't be trying to pull this headline grabbing stunt and instead step up and donate to good causes with his $5M offer AND do it w/o being in the news</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351107443313</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:37:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351107600364-97</Id><Topic><Title>Intrade Electoral Map Romney 275 Obama 263</Title><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351107337150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:35:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intarde Electoral Map - what about the genuine USA one? I could play some scenarios and make it Obama 338 and Romney 200......the one that counts is dated Nov 6th - 2012</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351107600364</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:40:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351107661853-98</Id><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake , Kick or Dance......</Title><Msg>Obama is behind nationally, in swing states, Ohio, Florida, Virginia, Colorado, and closing in on Pennsylvania. Democrats have their head in the sand, their toes in the dirt and are gulping hot, flat beer.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351107661853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351107693634-99</Id><Topic><Title>Massive riots when obama is flushed 11/6</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1351029082503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 17:51:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I were you I would stay in the woods too......less government out there</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351107693634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351107758594-100</Id><Topic><Title>What 'God Intended'</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351105870213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Voting age women in Indiana......time to step up and do the right thing</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351107758594</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:42:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351107833344-101</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans defend rape as God Intended</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351090173735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:49:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the only benghazi atrocity was mittens rushing to give a press release trying to politicize the attack and now willard keeping his endorsement of mourdock, reflecting his mourmon values on the rape and incest of women in the mourmon family</Msg><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351107833344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:43:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351107887369-102</Id><Topic><Title>Intrade Electoral Map Romney 275 Obama 263</Title><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351107337150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:35:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed that Nov. 6 is the one that counts so why haven't you told that to the Dik who has been touting Intrade for months when it was showing Obama ahead.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351107887369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351107946716-103</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s ‘Let Detroit Go Bankrupt’</Title><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351098181688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember when all the Republicans in the presidential primaries couldn't stand Mitt Romney? You should -</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351107946716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:45:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351108136685-104</Id><Topic><Title>Intrade Electoral Map Romney 275 Obama 263</Title><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351107337150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:35:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>November 6, 2012</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351108136685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:48:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351108148535-105</Id><Topic><Title>Trump and Obama Charity</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351107109728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doc, There is no doubt that this is a "smoke 'em out" ploy. Nevertheless, it is also true that Obama has sealed into secrecy his school records - providing instead his two books which allegedly are full of fantasy. $5 million for being what he claims he is: transparent. That is the offer. As to Trump's level of personal charity, the web information is all over the map from the "least charitible billionaire" to being involved in 21 separate charities. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351108148535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:49:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351108190012-106</Id><Title>Obama challenges press to find flip-flops -- and they do...</Title><Msg>Obama today: I'm the same guy I was 10-12 years ago. Obama in 1996: Answers a questionnaire and says he supports banning assault weapons, handguns.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351108190012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:49:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351108216256-107</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s ‘Let Detroit Go Bankrupt’</Title><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351098181688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember when all the Republicans in the presidential primaries couldn't stand Mitt Romney? You should - and Obama/Biden 3-1 over Mittens/lyin'Ryan in the debates</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1351108216256</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:50:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351108413669-108</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s ‘Let Detroit Go Bankrupt’</Title><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351098181688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many companies have been bailed out??!! You seriously wanted to see Chrysler &amp; GM go belly up? If it had happened - you would have been complaining about an extremely high rate of unemployment and a lot more people collecting unemployment &amp; using food stamps. Not only are they still making cars but they are actually selling them too. I want to know what the military and country want to do with an extra $200 billion a year in Mitt's military budget.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351108413669</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351109054775-109</Id><Topic><Title>Trump and Obama Charity</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351107109728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wanna see if Myth Rawmoney's holy underwear can really stop a bullet, while he is wearing them. I wanna see 25 years of Myth Rawmoney's tax returns. How much will el trumpster pony up and when will myth rawmoney comply?</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1351109054775</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:04:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351109216484-110</Id><Topic><Title>Obama challenges press to find flip-flops -- and they do...</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351108190012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:49:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did he ever do so? Or is it just one of your trigger-happy nightmares? Romney expressed the exact same sentiments when governor (term used loosely) of Mass.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351109216484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:06:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351109287357-111</Id><Topic><Title>Trump and Obama Charity</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351107109728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, it would seem only fair: tax records for school records. However, the problem with tax records, past and present, is that they can be misused by persons of nefarious intent to commit fraud. The only problem with releasing Obama's school records is that they can be used to reveal fraud, or not, depending upon their content.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351109287357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351109568067-112</Id><Topic><Title>Trump and Obama Charity</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351107109728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only fraud is Trump and what he is trying to insinuate, and what Myth Rawmoney is trying perpetrate on us all.</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1351109568067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:12:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351110048269-113</Id><Topic><Title>Will the real Mitt Please Stand Up</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1351105825536</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:10:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is mitt even consciously aware of his lies/flip-flpos. Does he even care. Or has he been doing it so long that is incapable of understanding or caring that he is human etch-a-sketch and thus undeserving of the trust of any voter for the office which he seeks.</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1351110048269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351110875656-114</Id><Topic><Title>Trump and Obama Charity</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351107109728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spart, Regardless of what Trump may be insinuating, don't you want to know more about your candidate? Obama made his school records a secret. Now that is not in dispute. It boils down to whether you care or do not care that he has done that. He could pull the same thing he did with the long form birth certificate, release the school records, say, a week before elections, showing that he was legit, and get the sympathy bump in ratings as a result. In the mean time, $5 million from Trump to whatever Obama desires - whether that is Islamic or Christian charities. Win win! BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351110875656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351111494839-115</Id><Topic><Title>Trump and Obama Charity</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351107109728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama made his school records a secret. Now that is not in dispute Oh really. When did Obama make his school records a secret? C'mon Bob, just come out and say what you think is in Obama's college and passport records. Just to show how low you will go stumping for a religious cultist and insincere flip-floppiing liar/hypocrite. The Birther question was asked and answered long ago. Myth Ramoney's tax records, tax-plan, etc. etc. etc. have not!</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1351111494839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:44:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351111754024-116</Id><Title>Repugs have been stuck in 2008</Title><Msg>with nothing but anger and hate refusing to admit how bad it was due to the Great (R) Recession</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1351111754024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:49:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351112165275-117</Id><Title>Obama' Message to Unemployed Workers Who Lost Everything</Title><Msg>Obama: No Regrets Over Prioritizing Obamacare Over Jobs President Obama recently sat down with the editorial board of Iowa's largest newspaper, the Des Moines Register, for what his campaign stipulated would be an off-the-record discussion. No wonder he wanted it off the record. The Register's editors contrast this rigmarole from the most transparent administration evah with the access they were granted by Mitt Romney's campaign: QUESTION: “Some say you had a super majority in your first two years and had this incredible opportunity, but because of what you were talking about, as you were running, you had to go to get Obamacare done. Do you have any regrets taking on some of the economic issues, some of the issues that we're talking about for your second term, that when you had the chance, so to speak, during your first -- do you have any regrets that you didn’t do that at that time?” OBAMA: “Absolutely not, Laura.” Obama projects unflinching confidence that he was entirely correct to put jobs, economic growth, immigration reform -- everything -- on the back burner in order to jam through Obamacare. He's proud of his law, which raises government healthcare spending, hikes family premiums, adds to the deficit, rations care through an unelected panel of bureaucrats, exacerbates our doctor shortage, and boots millions off of plans they hoped to keep. All of these outcomes explicitly violate promises the president made during the national healthcare debate. Meanwhile, the nation's economic outlook remains bleak. That's not in spite of Obamacare; it's because of Obamacare, which the CBO estimates will destroy 800,000 American jobs. The Romney campaign blasts the president's answer: "In the face of a struggling economy, President Obama took his eye off the ball, and spent over a year focused on passing Obamacare – a massive government takeover of health care that cuts Medicare for today’s seniors, raises taxes on millions of middle-class families, and impedes job creation. But rather than learn from this mistake, the President would do the same in a second term, implementing even more job-destroying policies that will cost the nation over 700,000 jobs. It’s clear why Americans can’t afford four more years like the last four years. As President, Mitt Romney’s top priority will be fixing our nation’s economy by creating 12 million jobs, higher take-home pay for American workers, and a more prosperous future for all Americans."</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351112165275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:56:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351112304434-118</Id><Topic><Title>Obama challenges press to find flip-flops -- and they do...</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351108190012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:49:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow! You sound like a conspiracy nutjob! Careful LOON, you may blow a gasket over your dillusions.</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1351112304434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:58:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351112343968-119</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs have been stuck in 2008</Title><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1351111754024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:49:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has Made it Worse! Obama's Foreign Policy in Flames... Dead Ambassador... Lying to the American People and the World... Obama is a Fool.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351112343968</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351112616513-120</Id><Topic><Title>Trump and Obama Charity</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351107109728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spart, "When did Obama make his school records a secret?" Essentially by default by not allowing them to be released. Now, to be fair to Obama, apparently, that is the rule of thumb for all (or most) of the presidential candidates or Presidents. Bush's were released, much to his chagrin, showing that he was a solid "C" student. What would I expect to see in Obama's records? I want to know if he was as avidly "marxist" as is claimed during his college years - which would be reflected in the quality and quantity of such type of courses. One class in marxism, communism, or socialism would be fair - to enhance understanding; more than one course would show a preference. Given his stated preference for wealth redistribution, it would be instructive to the American public to see what they are getting. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351112616513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:03:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351112708040-121</Id><Title>Democrats in full panic mode - turn to cheating</Title><Msg>300 suspected noncitizens found on Colo. voter rolls - Fake letters spark fears of voter intimidation in Fla.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351112708040</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:05:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351113679519-122</Id><Topic><Title>Killing Ann Coulter With Thoughtful Kindness She Clearly Doesn't Deserve</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351113546997</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:19:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Acts Like a Retard... It is what it is, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351113679519</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351113767672-123</Id><Topic><Title>Sketchy In Ohio: Election Officials (Allegedly) Botch Their Most Basic Job</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351113663748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:21:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Must be Very Worried About Losing, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351113767672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:22:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351114085109-124</Id><Title>Ann is Correct as Obama Looks Like a Retard off His Pacifier, err TelePrompter</Title><Msg>Affirmation Action is Showing in Obama.....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351114085109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351114352068-125</Id><Topic><Title>Helping Republicans Find Real Voter Fraud in America</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351113932859</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More of Dik' Blue Wall Nonsense and Garbage!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351114352068</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351114501163-126</Id><Topic><Title>Frightened Men Love Romney</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351113856291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:24:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Must be Alot of Frightened Women as Romney is Soaring with Women... Dik, You Just Post More Blue Wall Nonsense, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351114501163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:35:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351114988094-127</Id><Topic><Title>They Can't Both Be Right: 'Savvy' Experts vs. Polls</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351114777713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:39:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama in Full Panic Mode... Making Stuff Up as Obama Sinks in the Polls! Desperation has Set in... Chicago Drunk!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351114988094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351115230905-128</Id><Topic><Title>This is what conservatism in America has become</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351115083047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:44:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But it all a Lie....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351115230905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:47:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351115409651-129</Id><Topic><Title>Obama challenges press to find flip-flops -- and they do...</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1351108190012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:49:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that some sort of pickle malady?</Msg><Username>wellsaid_1234</Username><Timestamp>1351115409651</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:50:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351115527947-130</Id><Topic><Title>This is what conservatism in America has become</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351115083047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:44:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a fine one to talk, hoozdik. You're campaigning for a war criminal.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351115527947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:52:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351115546393-131</Id><Title>Obama Won't Release his College Grades as Other Presidential Candidates Have</Title><Msg>What is the Affirmative Action Queen Hiding? America Finially Saw Obama Off his Pacifer and Were Repulsed... Ie. Ann's Comment!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351115546393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:52:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351115638944-132</Id><Topic><Title>This is what conservatism in America has become</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351115083047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:44:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You liberalnazi's really do love Hitler, a Social Democrat.</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1351115638944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351115687445-133</Id><Topic><Title>Killing Ann Coulter With Thoughtful Kindness She Clearly Doesn't Deserve</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351113546997</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:19:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you saying that you are a retard?</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1351115687445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351115746024-134</Id><Topic><Title>Killing Ann Coulter With Thoughtful Kindness She Clearly Doesn't Deserve</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351113546997</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:19:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She's a whole lot smarter than a dumb person and loser like you.</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1351115746024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:55:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351115832144-135</Id><Topic><Title>Trump and Obama Charity</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351107109728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another giant falsehood. After he released the long form birth certificate, the haters (you included)instantly moved on with precisely the same level of vile hatred. Hatred for irrational reasons is what marks the vast majority of the birther/tea party/Confederacy movement. A sad condition for the country, and only part of why we are doomed.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1351115832144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351116086979-136</Id><Topic><Title>Trump and Obama Charity</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351107109728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well he can move $5M away from being "least charitable billionaire" or increase by $5M to any or all of his current charities w/o playing this publicity stunt</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351116086979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:01:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351116179643-137</Id><Topic><Title>Trump and Obama Charity</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351107109728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Hissing adders": Nephi Moroni Ether Omni Mosiah Alma</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1351116179643</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:02:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351116520756-138</Id><Title>10-23 status</Title><Msg>36 planes delivered. Twebty three 737's. two 747's. One 767. Five 777's. Five 787's. No sign of deliveries today (10-24) but some flights took place. Weather in Everett was lousy.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351116520756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:08:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351117446932-139</Id><Title>God bless the President and the USA</Title><Msg>He's the hardest working President I ever seen and I am so grateful he saved our country from default</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351117446932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:24:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351117553706-140</Id><Title>No September 11th under Obama's watch</Title><Msg>We at Boeing are thankful</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351117553706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351117575515-141</Id><Topic><Title>God bless the President and the USA</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351117446932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:24:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like a funny little sissy.</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1351117575515</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:26:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351117856813-142</Id><Title>Two words Baggers</Title><Msg>ELECTORAL COLLEGE</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1351117856813</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:30:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351118540884-143</Id><Topic><Title>Two words Baggers</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1351117856813</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:30:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm glad you mentioned that, It's currently Obama 201 and Romney 206 with Romney looking like Seattle Slew coming down the home stretch.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351118540884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351119384001-144</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s ‘Let Detroit Go Bankrupt’</Title><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351098181688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Let Detroit Go Bankrupt" is the false charge Obama accused Romney of saying. Romney denied this in the 3rd debate. After all Romney's father was an American Auto leader. I read Romney's NY Times article when it came out. Romney called for the auto makers to go into a managed bankruptcy to get out from under all its huge debts including those obligations saddled by the auto unions. Romney plan was to put the auto makers back on their feet through a Chapter 11 reorganization with the aid of a bankruptcy court. To be in a position of being stronger and better and not be controlled by the auto unions.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351119384001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:56:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351119745585-145</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Release Your Tax Returns</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351119590645</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:59:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He Did and Payed More Taxes than Required... and Donated Millions to Charity....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351119745585</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:02:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351119853377-146</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s ‘Let Detroit Go Bankrupt’</Title><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351098181688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Led GM thru Bankruptcy... You Nitwit.....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351119853377</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:04:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351120130602-147</Id><Topic><Title>No September 11th under Obama's watch</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351117553706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ever Heard of Benghazi Where Obama Allowed our Ambassador and Three others American getvKilled on 9-11.... Wutang.... You are an Idiot!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351120130602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:08:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351120225425-148</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Release Your Tax Returns</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351119590645</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:59:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a Religous Bigot, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351120225425</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351120233134-149</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s ‘Let Detroit Go Bankrupt’</Title><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351098181688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just a few weeks ago, you were telling us you were all for Obama. Now it sounds like you sold out just to bust unions. A one-isue guy, like the gunfighters. This would be serious if anyone counted on you for anything.</Msg><Username>i_like_ike99</Username><Timestamp>1351120233134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351120560599-150</Id><Title>Romney said "Let Detriot Survive"</Title><Msg>"Let Detroit Go Bankrupt" is the false charge Obama accused Romney of saying. Romney denied this in the 3rd debate. After all Romney's father was an American Auto leader. I read Romney's NY Times article when it came out. Romney called for the auto makers to go into a managed bankruptcy to get out from under all its huge debts including those obligations saddled by the auto unions. Romney plan was to put the auto makers back on their feet through a Chapter 11 reorganization with the aid of a bankruptcy court. To be in a position of being stronger and better and not be controlled by the auto unions.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351120560599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:16:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351120769860-151</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s ‘Let Detroit Go Bankrupt’</Title><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351098181688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phantie/MBField has again displayed his astounding lack of understanding here. There was zero capital available in the private markets. INCLUDING BAIN, I must add. It would have been chapter 7. Liquidation. Please look up the difference and have your neighbor's high school kid explain this, leaving out the big words.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1351120769860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:19:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351120964464-152</Id><Topic><Title>This is what conservatism in America has become</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351115083047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:44:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And if Willard wins, the slave states can go back to being simply overwhelmed with life. They won't have to look at the black guy in the Oval Office. The reddest of all states have the most to lose with Willard but have been positively hoodwinked and are blissfully unaware of Willard's "human wind sock" status on all issues.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1351120964464</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:22:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351121621945-153</Id><Topic><Title>This is what conservatism in America has become</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351115083047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:44:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one can force INTELLIGENCE into the minds of graduates from Limbaugh and Fox Institute of misinformation. I hope enough voters wake up and prevent republicans from gaining power.</Msg><Username>fountain123_45</Username><Timestamp>1351121621945</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351121851298-154</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s ‘Let Detroit Go Bankrupt’</Title><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351098181688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am voting for Obama because I don't want the Republicans to mess with social security and medicare. But who do I think is better for job growth, improving the economy and most everything else -Mitt Romney. And when it comes to false propaganda, I can't let anyone get away with it not even Obama.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351121851298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:37:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351122409791-155</Id><Title>screw negotiations</Title><Msg>http://news.yahoo.com/israel-kills-one-second-day-gaza-strikes-062552365.html</Msg><Username>hirtuism</Username><Timestamp>1351122409791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:46:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351122447399-156</Id><Title>fungus</Title><Msg>moooooos destruction spreading like fungus....</Msg><Username>hirtuism</Username><Timestamp>1351122447399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:47:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351122914005-157</Id><Topic><Title>Helping Republicans Find Real Voter Fraud in America</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351113932859</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not surprised.</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1351122914005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:55:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351126302764-158</Id><Topic><Title>Billy Graham buys election ads after Romney meeting</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351087731373</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:08:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Billy Graham says, "I believe it is vitally important that we cast our ballots for candidates who base their decisions on biblical principles," he is asking voters to apply a religious test to the candidates. The Constitution forbids that. I know you understand that; you just want to SEEM as dumb as a box or rocks.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351126302764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:51:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351126505914-159</Id><Topic><Title>If B.O. Tries To Get In My Face ...</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351045587115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamunism is not just do-gooder socialism, it is Marxism using taxes to redistribute wealth from those who earned, found, built it, to those whom the gubbermint deems deserving . The one and only legitimate purpose of taxation is to support government . Anything else is just stealing . B.O. socialism seeks to control, and shape the economy, exemplified by the "green economy" programs . The government directs the economy, just like in N.K., or any communist country, burning up resources, capital, and labor, but not serving any customer, except Libtard egos . Time for Jimmy Carter's second term to end now . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351126505914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:55:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351126655337-160</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs have been stuck in 2008</Title><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1351111754024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:49:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for proving my point.</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1351126655337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:57:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351128152561-161</Id><Topic><Title>If B.O. Tries To Get In My Face ...</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351045587115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Name us the tasks you feel government should provide.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1351128152561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:22:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351129159238-162</Id><Topic><Title>I guess the street didn't like BA numbers?</Title><Username>thegoldude747</Username><Timestamp>1351100677378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:44:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thegoldude747 ,The truth is Boeing should have delivered over 200 787's by now (per the original contracts to airlines). Instead, Boeing is sitting on more than 60 787's, with the entire production chain in chaos due to loss of configuration control more than 5 years ago, from which they have never recovered. Boeing has lost nearly $50 BILLION on the 787 so far, and now has a critical CASH FLOW CRISIS that is driving the fire-sale deals, and high production rates that will hasten the end of Boeing Commercial, by flooding the market with cheap product. Yes, they are making money now, but at the expense of their long term profitability. I know that the shrill and shills will decry this post of the obvious, but, come back and talk to me in 5 years, when Boeing is on the "Too Big To Fail" subsidizes from the Federal gov't (similar to the Big Three automakers, and Airbus). That, quite frankly, is the only business model that the St. Louis mob understands, and it is their ultimate goal. Higher pension expenses HURT Boeing's third-quarter profit, but other measures for the big airplane maker and defense contractor were strong." Why didn't the headline read: "Boeing Profits Would Be Bigger If They Did Not Have To Pay Workers?" Better and more truthfully stated, it would be: "Boeing Exec Perks Take BIG Bite Out of Profits. thegoldude747, as you should or might know Boeing is in a dead cat - GE/MD- managment mode. every time the stock goes to 75 it pulls back you can not trade or invest in this stock to make any money , the truth is BA stock price for the yar is down .87 of 1% compared to a failed bank like BAC up 67%. You need to trade today not sit on a failed stock. I made a lot of money going long and then sort on JRCC a coal company today, and for the last 14 days it was a buy and a great play, contrary to the Boeing pumps this earning report is nothing, but a planted story to con potential stock rookies into a dog stock</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1351129159238</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:39:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351130059141-163</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s ‘Let Detroit Go Bankrupt’</Title><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351098181688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was the UAWs that drove the auto industry out of Detroit. I hate it when socialists fabricate lies.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351130059141</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:54:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351131800557-164</Id><Title>Union Folks are Against Romney</Title><Msg>They are afraid he will take away their lollypops.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351131800557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:23:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351132265280-165</Id><Title>What Detroit Go Bankrupt ? Another Lib False Premise</Title><Msg>Ford invented Detroit, Ford was is no danger of going bankrupt due to competent management, and took no gubbermint bail-out money . Where is Ford's reward for taking the path of prudency ? They would have picked up GM and Chrysler assets and labor if nature had been allowed to take it's course . Instead, Ford now has unbeatable competition thanks to the US taxpayer, and lenders foreign and domestic . Where is the incentive for good management, or limited reasonable union demands ? Out the window, the sky is now the limit . All so dims could play hero with OPM . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351132265280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:31:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351132289838-166</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s ‘Let Detroit Go Bankrupt’</Title><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351098181688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't Chrysler get a bailout from taxpayers and than the company went to Italy. That was a fine mess for American taxpayers.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351132289838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:31:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351132523536-167</Id><Topic><Title>Union Folks are Against Romney</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351131800557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:23:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unionists lack critical thought. Bunch of #$%$ drunks and druggies.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351132523536</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:35:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351132700720-168</Id><Topic><Title>No September 11th under Obama's watch</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351117553706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's see .....American soil and 3,000 dead........the other Libya and regrettably FOUR dead.....that's 4 .....1, 2, 3, and 4 stop. You weigh the two equally?????</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351132700720</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:38:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351133196284-169</Id><Title>Romney won't release his taxes like others candidates have, including his father.</Title><Msg>Eom</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1351133196284</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351133347558-170</Id><Title>Romney won,t release his taxes like others, including his father.</Title><Msg>So why does anyone care about Obamas grades</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1351133347558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:49:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351135389311-171</Id><Topic><Title>No September 11th under Obama's watch</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351117553706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Obama is re-elected, there will be 1460 additional days that could turn out to be like Sept 11th. So if Obama takes responsibility for Benghazi; he should be held accountable. We intend to try to make that happen! XQ</Msg><Username>xquestor</Username><Timestamp>1351135389311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351136867567-172</Id><Topic><Title>If B.O. Tries To Get In My Face ...</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351045587115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:26:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's what dJumbO said earlier: Re: Anderson Cooper--2-Jul-12 02:56 pm "Liberal, G, dim, no surprise there . Anyone else notice that cooper rhymes with pooper ? Life is full of clues . Y.T. Jumbojetski"</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1351136867567</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:47:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>