<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-31"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351657729878-1</Id><Topic><Title>Romney can pound Sand !!!!!!!</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351635679338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Revere, did you see that Dow Chemical is going to take a $1.1 billion charge for its failed battery business? LOL, sound familiar to you? It should L I B T A R D, LOL. TWO other companies filed for bankruptcy in the LAST WEEK......companies that received grants from Barak Odumber. This is the stupidity you can expect from a community organizer that becomes President. How about his failed foreign policy at Benghazi? When he needed a favor, the Navy Seals got Bin Laden. When the Seals needed a favor, he said NO and let them die. This dumb A H O L E should be impeached. He's nothing more than a criminal now.</Msg><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1351657729878</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 00:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351657844246-2</Id><Topic><Title>No matter how you slice it: Obama Wins!</Title><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1351623335392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:55:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Odumber wins, it's because we have too many moochers in this country. Expect more layoffs and higher unemployment under Odumber.</Msg><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1351657844246</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 00:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351657988305-3</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351635479249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here we have Christie praising Odumber while Hoozdumb puts Christie down. Hooz, you have no class at all. You help define the term #$%$</Msg><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1351657988305</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 00:33:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351660654126-4</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Plunges Into Once "Safe" Dem Turf... Obama Scrambling to Protect "Safe" States!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351643197286</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently you missed this little point. "... Romney is desperately searching for a last-minute path to the needed 270 Electoral College votes - without all-important Ohio." As everybody knows, Obama has more paths to 270 electoral college votes than Romney does so that's the most likely explanation. Uh oh ... : )</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351660654126</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351660785987-5</Id><Title>Republican Governor Christie Heaps Praise on President Obama, imaccom's Head Explodes, American's Cheer : )</Title><Msg>nm</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351660785987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:19:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351661082699-6</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Governor Christie Heaps Praise on President Obama, imaccom's Head Explodes, American's Cheer : )</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351660785987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:19:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nm</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351661082699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:24:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351661181740-7</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Governor Christie Heaps Praise on President Obama, imaccom's Head Explodes, American's Cheer : )</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351660785987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:19:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nm</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351661181740</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351661308927-8</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Governor Christie Heaps Praise on President Obama, imaccom's Head Explodes, American's Cheer : )</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351660785987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:19:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nm</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351661308927</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351669463544-9</Id><Topic><Title>can anyone verify the SOP re lase designators ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1351640897147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:48:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The executive director of SPEEA, Ray Goforth, denied the air asset permission to fire. Technically, only the Prof and Tech negotiating teams have that authority, but we all know how corrupt SPEEA is. Don't we Don?</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351669463544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 03:44:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351670645997-10</Id><Topic><Title>can anyone verify the SOP re lase designators ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1351640897147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:48:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah I can. Private security contractors do not use that equipment. Those guys were body guards....nothing more. There are very strict rules of engagement for State Department Security types.</Msg><Username>gerbilfood4me</Username><Timestamp>1351670645997</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 04:04:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351679003857-11</Id><Topic><Title>can anyone verify the SOP re lase designators ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1351640897147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:48:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ask Gen Ham.</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1351679003857</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 06:23:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351688123553-12</Id><Title>'Cooling Out' the Voters</Title><Msg>Confidence men know that their victim -- "the mark" as he has been called -- is eventually going to realize that he has been cheated. But it makes a big difference whether he realizes it immediately, and goes to the police, or realizes it after the confidence man is long gone. So part of the confidence racket is creating a period of uncertainty, during which the victim is not yet sure of what is happening. This delaying process has been called "cooling out the mark." The same principle applies in politics. When the accusations that led to the impeachment of President Bill Clinton first surfaced, he flatly denied them all. Then, as the months passed, the truth came out -- but slowly, bit by bit. One of Clinton's own White House aides later called it "telling the truth slowly." By the time the whole truth came out, it was called "old news," and the clever phrase now was that we should "move on." It was a successful "cooling out" of the public, keeping them in uncertainty so long that, by the time the whole truth came out, there was no longer the same outrage as if the truth had suddenly come out all at once. Without the support of an outraged public, the impeachment of President Clinton fizzled out in the Senate. We are currently seeing another "cooling out" process, growing out of the terrorist attack on the American consulate in Benghazi on September 11th this year. The belated release of State Department e-mails shows that the Obama administration knew, while the attack on the American consulate was still underway, that it was a coordinated, armed terrorist attack. They were getting reports from those inside the consulate who were under attack, as well as surveillance pictures from a camera on an American drone overhead. About an hour before the attack, the scene outside was calm enough for the American ambassador to accompany a Turkish official to the gates of the consulate to say goodbye. This could hardly have happened if there were protesting mobs there. Why then did both President Obama and U.N. Ambassador Susan Rice keep repeating the story that this was a spontaneous protest riot against an anti-Islamic video in America? The White House knew the facts -- but they knew that the voting public did not. And it mattered hugely whether the facts became known to the public before or after the election. What the White House needed was a process of "cooling out" the voters, keeping them distracted or in uncertainty as long as possible. Not only did the Obama administration keep repeating the false story about an anti-Islamic video being the cause of a riot that turned violent, the man who produced that video was tracked down and arrested, creating a media distraction. All this kept the video story front and center, with the actions and inactions of the Obama administration kept in the background. The White House had to know that it was only a matter of time before the truth would come out. But time was what mattered, with an election close at hand. The longer they could stretch out the period of distraction and uncertainty -- "cooling out" the voters -- the better. Once the confidence man in the White House was reelected, it would be politically irrelevant what facts came out. As the Obama administration's video story began to slowly unravel, their earlier misstatements were blamed on "the fog of war" that initially obscures many events. But there was no such "fog of war" in this case. The Obama administration knew what was happening while it was happening. They didn't know all the details -- and we may never know all the details -- but they knew enough to know that this was no protest demonstration that got out of hand. From the time it took office, the Obama administration has sought to suppress the very concept of a "war on terror" or the terrorists' war on us. The painful farce of calling the Fort Hood murders "workplace violence," instead of a terrorist attack in our midst, shows how far the Obama administration would go to downplay the dangers of Islamic extremist terrorism. The killing of Osama bin Laden fed the pretense that the terrorism threat had been beaten. But the terrorists' attack in Libya exposed that fraud -- and required another fraud to try to "cool out" the voters until after election day. Thomas Sowell</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351688123553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 08:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351688692785-13</Id><Title>The biggest losers in this campaign could be................</Title><Msg>.........."mainstream" journalists. Their blatant bias has dropped trust in the news media to an all-time low. It's fun Watching the Collapse of the Obama Campaign. The Navy needs more ships, Mitt Romney said in last Monday's debate. It has fewer now than in 1916. President Barack Obama pounced. "Well, governor, we also have fewer horses and bayonets, because the nature of our military's changed," he said, his voice dripping with sarcasm. "We have these things called aircraft carriers where planes land on them ... " In the spin room, some journalists laughed and applauded. Liberals imagine themselves to be intellectually and morally superior to conservatives. They love to put them down. But "sarcasm and condescension only work if the speaker's presumption of lofty superior knowledge is borne out by his command of actual facts," said Pastor Donald Sensing, a retired Army colonel. Mr. Obama was wrong on both the thrust of his argument, and on the examples he used. Aircraft carriers need smaller ships to protect them, lest they be sunk. The military has many more bayonets now than in 1916. Marines think so highly of them they've designed a new one, modeled on the famous KA-BAR fighting knife. Special Forces soldiers on horseback were critical to ousting the Taliban. The facts matter little to liberals. Their assumption of intellectual superiority isn't based on actual knowledge. Journalists declared the president the winner of the debate. But facts and civility do matter to most Americans. A CBS panel of undecided voters in Ohio chose Mr. Romney, 6-2. A video of the dismay of CBS "This Morning" co-host Norah O'Donnell when this was reported is zipping across the Internet. The Navy and shipbuilding are very important in southeast Virginia. With his wisecrack, the president may have kissed the state goodbye. It isn't just in Virginia where Mr. Obama's fortunes are plummeting. When Missouri isn't a swing state, but Minnesota is, Democrats are in big trouble. No challenger who's cracked 50 percent in Gallup's tracking poll has ever lost. Mr. Romney is polling better at this point in the campaign than did every victorious challenger from 1968 on. It's hard to see how the president can mount a comeback. His strategy of demonizing Mitt Romney collapsed when Americans saw in the first debate the GOP candidate has neither horns nor hooves. In an NBC/WSJ poll Monday, 62 percent of respondents said they want "significant change" from Mr. Obama's policies, but he's offered little in the way of an agenda for a second term. Instead he makes excuses, and ever more petty attacks. Voters now think Mr. Romney is just as "likeable" as Mr. Obama. So the question may not be whether Mr. Romney will win, but by how much. When this dawns on Ms. O'Donnell, the video will be priceless. Our politics are now so polarized I doubt that any candidate in either party -- not even JFK or Ronald Reagan -- could win much more than 52 percent of the popular vote. But law professor and blogger Glenn Reynolds (Instapundit) thinks the odds of a preference cascade are rising. Economist Timur Kuran coined the term to explain why totalitarian regimes usually collapse suddenly. A preference cascade happens when people discover millions of others share their doubts about the Great Leader. Massive media bias has made the term applicable here, Mr. Reynolds said. The Barack Obama that Americans saw in the debates bears little resemblance to the heroic figure portrayed by the news media. The crowds have been enormous at Romney/Ryan events this past week. If this is the start of a preference cascade, many Democrats may drown in the undertow. The Obama campaign has vacuumed up so much Democratic money there's little left for other candidates. In yet another fund-raising appeal on Tuesday, Mr. Obama said he and Michelle would be fine if he loses. If the president's friends are indeed buying him a $35 million mansion in Hawaii, as Chicago blogger Kevin Dujan (Hillbuzz) claims, that's certainly true. But public employee unions, crony capitalists and others who feed at the public trough have reason to panic. Underlings must wonder if there will be legal consequences for the laws they've broken. I predict an orgy of document shredding Nov. 7. The biggest losers could be "mainstream" journalists. Their blatant bias has dropped trust in the news media to an all-time low. It'll plunge further if more evidence of collusion with the administration emerges. Nobody trusts a liar. There will be bankruptcies.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351688692785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:04:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351689250930-14</Id><Title>Obamacare Is Even More Unpopular Now than in 2010</Title><Msg>One week before the election that will likely determine Obamacare’s fate, Americans support its repeal by an even wider margin than they did in the immediate aftermath of its highly unpopular passage. According to newly released polling from Rasmussen Reports, by a margin of 15 percentage points (54 to 39 percent), likely voters now support the repeal of President Obama’s centerpiece legislation. In the first three polls taken in the wake of the House’s passage of Obamacare (on March 21, 2010), Rasmussen showed that likely voters then favored repeal by margins of 13 points (55 to 42 percent), 12 points (54 to 42 percent), and 12 points (54 to 42 percent). Cementing Obamacare would be the principal focus of Obama’s second term.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351689250930</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:14:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351689663805-15</Id><Title>Get ready to fill out ObamaCare’s individual mandate tax form!</Title><Msg>If there’s one part of the president’s healthcare law (Obamacare) that Americans know they don’t like, it’s the law’s “individual mandate.” When the Kaiser Family Foundation polled Americans about their views on Obamacare earlier this year, it found that the mandate had the support of just 30 percent of respondents. If people don’t like the individual mandate much now, they will like it a whole lot less when it becomes part of their annual tax filings with the IRS. Starting in 2014, most Americans will have to purchase “qualifying” health insurance. This insurance plan can be an employer-provided plan, a plan from the individual market, or a government plan like Medicare, Medicaid, and veterans’ care. What all these plans will have in common is that they must be approved as qualified by the Department of Health and Human Services (HHS), which will get to mandate what each plan must cover and how. Failure to obtain qualifying coverage could result in payment of a tax penalty to the IRS. Depending on family size, the tax penalty will range from $695 to $2,085 (plus inflation). For many families, a higher penalty of 2.5 percent of adjusted gross income (AGI) will apply.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351689663805</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:21:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351689876179-16</Id><Title>Why Medicare Must Be Reformed</Title><Msg>Medicare is shaping up to be a deciding factor in the debate over our nation’s future. As Heritage’s Bob Moffit and Alyene Senger explain in a recent paper, “Why Traditional Medicare Must (and Will) Be Reformed,” the status quo in Medicare is unsustainable and unacceptable due to the program’s structural and financing flaws. Here are a few reasons Medicare needs to be reformed: Medicare spending is growing faster than any other federal program. Medicare spending has reached unsustainable levels and is contributing to our budget deficits more quickly than any other program. Further, over the long term, Medicare has made $37 trillion worth of benefit promises to future seniors that are simply not funded. The hospital insurance trust fund is projected to be insolvent by 2024. While seniors have paid for their benefits, their payments do not cover the costs of the program. In 2011, approximately 88 percent of Medicare’s spending was funded by taxpayers. A large part of the problem is the erroneous belief that seniors have fully paid for their benefits. In fact, Moffit and Senger explain that, “on average, a one-earner couple who retired at age 65 in 2011 and earned an average wage will have paid just $60,000 into the program but will receive an estimated $357,000 worth of benefits.” Medicare enrollment is set to skyrocket. Baby boomers have already begun to retire. At the current rate of retirement, the program will enroll 10,000 beneficiaries into Medicare every day from 2011 to 2030. Moffit and Senger explain that “enrollment is expected to jump from 48 million beneficiaries in 2011 to 81 million by 2030.” This is coupled with a 50 percent decrease in the proportion of workers contributing to the hospital insurance trust fund over the same period. The outlook: more beneficiaries and fewer workers paying taxes to support them. It’s a complex and outdated system. Medicare’s four separate parts are financed differently and operate under their own set of payment rules with different premiums, co-pays, and deductibles. Moffit and Senger write, “Medicare’s four-part complexity contributes to confusion among patients, inefficiency among providers, and higher costs for taxpayers. Care is chopped up and fragmented, reimbursed under an old and complicated fee-for-service payment system created in the 1960s that has long since disappeared from the private sector.” An outdated and limited benefit structure doesn’t meet seniors’ diverse needs. Medicare has high cost-sharing requirements and does not protect seniors from catastrophic costs. For this reason, 90 percent of beneficiaries enrolled in traditional Medicare obtain supplemental insurance, most of which is private. Seniors are thus required to pay an additional premium for additional coverage (on top of their already rising Medicare Part B premiums). And because of the way supplemental coverage (such as Medigap) is organized, it encourages excessive utilization and thus raises the entire cost of the program even more for both seniors and taxpayers. In fact, this structural flaw adds 15 percent to 25 percent to Medicare program costs. Without reform, Medicare’s future is bleak. Washington’s current policy is to perpetuate the status quo and hope that an outdated combination of price controls—or the latest Medicare payment rate tweaks imposed under Obamacare—will control costs and deliver better benefits at a lower cost. Don’t bet on it. Only reforms that inject real competition into the program and empower seniors to control their own health care decisions can save the program for the next generation.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351689876179</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:24:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351690028149-17</Id><Title>LOOK BAGGERS!</Title><Msg>Looky here baggerss. Lying to yourselves about who is winning this election will not get Willard in the White House. It won't get President Obama out of the White House. It may very well get YOU in the Nut House!</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1351690028149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351690116987-18</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney Is Just Not That Into Federal Disaster Relief</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351631826706</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:17:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he's asking to get a can of whoop#$%$!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351690116987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:28:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351690273110-19</Id><Topic><Title>No matter how you slice it: Obama Wins!</Title><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1351623335392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:55:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>up to 77% chance...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351690273110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:31:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351690713716-20</Id><Title>Important Message to Anyone Thinking About Voting for Obama</Title><Msg>Obama is a Marxist and there is more than enough evidence to support this fact. He is a statist and a collectivist and his policies reflect that. Ask Anyone who has lived under a Marxist regime. Obama has shown over and over again he will throw anyone under the bus if they get in his way of accumulating more and more power....his preacher of 20 years, his good friends like Bill Ayers, even his Grand mother. This is not a new mentality, it is the mentality of most Marxists. It is the same mentality that caused communist leaders in the USSR to kill more than 20 million of their own countrymen, it is the same mentality that caused Che Guevara and Fidel Castro to murder more than 6 million Cubans and it is the same mentality that caused Mao to kill more than 90 million of his fellow countrymen. It's the same mentality that allowed 4 Americans to be killed in Benghazi without trying to them. Many of those dead souls thought that it was “cool” to have “change” that fed off of poverty, class warfare, hatred, jealousy and envy. Only too late, did they discover the “cool guys” offering change, were far worse than they bargained. The really shocked ones were the ones that thought they were safe because they were in with the “cool guys” and part of the change force. These were the useful idiots of which Stalin spoke. But their property was taken too and their relatives were killed and sent to gulags too. And when these “useful idots” objected they were killed too. They were simply a means to an end with dictatorial totalitarianism being the end. Obama supporters don’t think they won’t come for you, if you get in their way. And don’t think the good guys who will have the task of taking back the country from these animals will have any sympathy for you who empowered the elitists who want to rule your lives. I know, I grew up in Russia and came to this country 48 years ago. Ask any immigrant from a communist country and they will tell you the same thing. Those of us who came from such environments see the same thing happening here. Just watch how violent, vulgar and uncivilized Obama supporters are getting now. Get rid of this guy and the people who embrace the Marxist ideology before it’s too late.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351690713716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:38:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351691130440-21</Id><Title>God Bless President Obama!!!</Title><Msg>and God Bless the USA!!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351691130440</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:45:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351691417196-22</Id><Title>Facebook Censors Navy SEALs to Protect Obama on Benghazi-Gate</Title><Msg>Over the weekend, Facebook took down a message by the Special Operations Speaks PAC (SOS) which highlighted the fact that Obama denied backup to the forces being overrun in Benghazi. What the message said was, "Obama called the Seals and they got Bin Laden. the Seals called Obama they got denied."</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351691417196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:50:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351691468873-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is now surging on intrade</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351632139837</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:22:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351691468873</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:51:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351691766340-24</Id><Title>White House emails: Counterterrorism group....stand down on Benghazi rescue</Title><Msg>On Tuesday night’s “On the Record with Greta Van Susteren” on the Fox News Channel, former House Speaker Newt Gingrich said that major news networks might have secret emails proving that the White House canceled plans to assist the besieged U.S. Embassy in Benghazi. Gingrich said that the bombshell emails could be revealed within the next two days. “There is a rumor — I want to be clear, it’s a rumor — that at least two networks have emails from the National Security Adviser’s office telling a counterterrorism group to stand down,” Gingrich said. “But they were a group in real-time trying to mobilize marines and C-130s and the fighter aircraft, and they were told explicitly by the White House stand down and do nothing. This is not a terrorist action.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351691766340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:56:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351691810344-25</Id><Topic><Title>One day to go</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351647354494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:35:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the update.</Msg><Username>mrstock52</Username><Timestamp>1351691810344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:56:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351691954857-26</Id><Title>REPORT: GOP voting tsunami coming...</Title><Msg>Democrats more than Republicans are getting their most loyal supporters to vote early, but with polls showing a close race among those who have voted so far, concerns are being raised about a GOP tsunami on the actual Election Day, next Tuesday. According to a GOP analysis of early voting and absentee ballot requests provided to Secrets, the Democrats are turning out their most reliable, or so-called "high propensity voters" than Republicans, leaving fewer for Election Day. The GOP is pushing weaker supporters to vote early, expecting high enthusiasm to drive their regular supporters to the polls next week. "Democrats are cannibalizing their high-propensity voters in advance of election day to get stories that they are winning," said a GOP analyst. "But in effect they are stealing from Peter, or Election Day, to pay Paul, or early voting." For example, in Ohio, the Democrats have turned out 43 percent of the most loyal supporters to vote, compared to just 27 percent of the GOP. In Iowa, the difference is 43 percent to 29 percent. "Republicans will have more reliable voters available on Election Day and are spending our efforts turning out low propensity voters in the absentee and early voting periods," added the analysis. Even with the difference in turnout of loyal supporters, Gallup finds that among early voters, Romney is beating Obama 52 percent to 45 percent, though some state totals show an Obama advantage. Plus in states like North Carolina, Colorado and Iowa, the GOP has seen huge requests for last-minute absentee ballots this month.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351691954857</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:59:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351692080840-27</Id><Topic><Title>No matter how you slice it: Obama Wins!</Title><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1351623335392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:55:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Insanity: doing the same thing over and over again and expecting different results. Albert Einstein ehh sparty, i mean ahkmed</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1351692080840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:01:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351692159200-28</Id><Title>“There is a rumor — I want to be clear, it’s a rumor —Gingrich said.</Title><Msg>Yes a rumor. No facts and in the NEWS world there is no tomorrow. If you have the news you print the news. This is just typical right wing Rovian #$%$</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351692159200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:02:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351692241986-29</Id><Topic><Title>LOOK BAGGERS!</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1351690028149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:27:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's sparty, duh baggers' bagger</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1351692241986</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:04:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351692249860-30</Id><Title>Ohio: Romney 50%, Obama 48%</Title><Msg>Florida is gone for Obama, Ohio is now gone......Pennsylvania and Wisconsin set to fall to Romney.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351692249860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:04:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351692438778-31</Id><Title>POLL: Obama dominates Romney</Title><Msg>.... in Russia...N. Korea and Cuba.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351692438778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:07:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351692553621-32</Id><Title>Mitts odds of losing increase!</Title><Msg>every time he opens his mouth !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351692553621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:09:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351693155023-33</Id><Topic><Title>Mitts odds of losing increase!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351692553621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:09:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and every time he opens his mouth - someone loses a shoe.. ha ha ha!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351693155023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:19:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351693378735-34</Id><Title>Tied</Title><Msg>Oct. 30 (Bloomberg) -- President Barack Obama and Republican challenger Mitt Romney are tied among likely voters in a national poll released eight days before Election Day.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351693378735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:22:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351693477207-35</Id><Title>Presidential Polls: Barack Obama's Ohio Lead Holds</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON -- With less than a week remaining before results are counted, the presidential race remains remarkably close, with President Barack Obama maintaining a very narrow lead in most polls over Republican nominee Mitt Romney in Ohio, the state whose outcome could well decide the election. A new Ohio poll released on Wednesday morning by CBS News, The New York Times and The Quinnipiac University Polling Institute showed Obama maintaining a 5 percentage point advantage over Romney in Ohio, the same margin as on a previous CBS/Quinnipiac survey conducted in the state two weeks ago.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351693477207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:24:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351693866257-36</Id><Title>Politics quite fickle</Title><Msg>Look at New Jersey.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1351693866257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:31:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351694013307-37</Id><Title>Romney's Response to Sandy May Be the Campaign's Most Revealing Moment</Title><Msg>Noam Scheiber October 31, 2012 | 12:00 am Oh, the cosmic injustice of it all. Barack Obama spent the critical hours before and after Hurricane Sandy dropping by the headquarters of FEMA and the Red Cross. He held conference calls with top state officials and sent hundreds of millions of dollars in relief money their way. On Wednesday, he will be surveying the wreckage and personally comforting residents in New Jersey with his new BFF, Chris Christie. And Mitt Romney? He retrofitted a previously-planned Ohio “Victory Rally” into a Don DeLillo-esque “storm relief event,” replete with canned-food drive. Under normal circumstances, you’d chalk up the contrast to the perks of incumbency: The president gets to look in-command after a disaster (unless of course he doesn’t), while the challenger has to sit around inventing politically-correct photo-ops. But in this case there’s actually some deeper significance. That’s because, unlike his rival for the Oval Office, Romney has suggested that government should have a rather limited role helping disaster-stricken people, and that private citizens should pick up the slack. I’m not just talking about Romney’s apparent support for mothballing FEMA and devolving its functions to states or private contractors. This struck me as a pretty clear primary-campaign pander, though Romney should still own every bit of it. I’m talking more about Romney’s personal philosophy of private initiative versus public responsibility, as epitomized by his own record of paying taxes and charitable giving. Romney, you’ll recall, frequently sends less than 15 percent per year to the U.S. Treasury, despite an annual income in the tens of millions of dollars and a net worth in the hundreds of millions. Much of this is accomplished through a rather aggressive use of tax loopholes, some of which we know about and many more of which we presumably don’t. When pressed on this generally legal but unseemly exercise, Team Romney often emphasizes that, combined with his large (and commendable) charitable contributions, Romney is in the habit of forking over heaping portions of his income to other entities. For example, the campaign noted in a recent release that, for 20 years starting in 1990, Romney’s “total federal and state taxes owed plus the total charitable donations deducted represented 38.49% of total [adjusted gross income].” In 2010, Romney only paid an effective federal tax rate of 13.9 percent but gave another 13.8 percent to charity. In 2011, the figures were 14.1 percent in federal taxes and 29 percent to charity. I have no reason to believe Romney isn’t sincere when he authorizes such statements. He's a genuinely compassionate man in many ways, and he often measures that compassion by the amount of money he gives away. As one longtime adviser recently told me, “Mitt is someone who is extraordinary generous with charities, in particular his church. He’s the kind of guy who, if you called him up and said, ‘Mitt’—I’m exaggerating a bit—‘I need a million bucks, I’m really in trouble,’ he’d try to help you. … If someone’s house burned down in the community, or someone is having trouble with something in the Church, you’d find him doing anything from helping send their kid to school to making them a pot of stew.” The most logical (and, um, charitable) upshot of all this is that Romney really does believe aiding those in need is best accomplished by individuals and private charities, not the federal government. It’s an especially appealing proposition for a Mormon, a community with a remarkable history of caring for its own, especially when the government either neglected or actively persecuted it. As Stephanie Mencimer recounts in a fascinating post at Mother Jones, the Church’s Bishop’s Storehouse Services became famous for the efficiency with which it distributed aid during the Great Depression, and Utah residents routinely respond to the state’s natural disasters with breathtaking coordination. In 2005, the Church showed up the federal government by almost seamlessly evacuating nearly 2,500 Mormons from New Orleans before Katrina struck. The problem, as Mencimer goes on to point out, is that the model simply doesn’t scale. You can deal with 2,500 people using private resources, or the occasional flood in Utah, but you can’t possibly manage a Sandy-like calamity. The magnitude of the disaster is simply too large—the amount of coordination required is too unwieldy, and the pot of money needed to rebuild overwhelms even the largest private organizations (at least if you have a major disaster more than every few years). It’s no surprise that Utah’s Republican governor Gary Herbert is a serial requester of disaster funds, according to Mencimer. Does any of this mean that, as president, Romney would put an end to federal disaster aid—or, for that matter, social insurance programs like Medicaid, unemployment benefits, or food stamps? Of course not. As Romney himself conceded at Tuesday’s “storm relief event,” charity can’t solve everything. And yet the degree of confidence he expressed in volunteerism was somewhat striking: There are a lot of people who [are] still going to be looking for goods even if we gathered these things. But one of the things I’ve learned in life is you make the difference you can. You can’t always solve the problems yourself, but you can make the difference in the life of one or two people. It’s not hard to believe that someone so taken with the power of charity, even during a huge crisis, would be open to the block-granting and outsourcing a GOP Congress will surely work into the budgets it sends him. So, yes, Sandy was a freakish intrusion on the campaign that showered arbitrary political benefits on the man in the White House. But arbitrary doesn’t necessarily mean unfair. Whether they intended it or not, the candidates’ responses revealed much about what’s at stake in this election.</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1351694013307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:33:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351695115794-38</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Governor Christie Heaps Praise on President Obama, imaccom's Head Explodes, American's Cheer : )</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351660785987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:19:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Roughly 14 months ago T. Willard said he would "absolutely" disband/delete FEMA.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1351695115794</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:51:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351695743250-39</Id><Title>Malignant tumors and inoperable cancers are coming get short-sellers and Romney supporters!</Title><Msg>The message of God!</Msg><Username>savvy_investor123</Username><Timestamp>1351695743250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351697047486-40</Id><Topic><Title>No matter how you slice it: Obama Wins!</Title><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1351623335392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:55:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Insanity from Fascist/censored: sparty err ahkmed err spaz err spazMO err spartyMO err fascistMO err spazlaMO err censoredMO err ahkmedMO err MOmoMOmoMO err MO</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1351697047486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351697204734-41</Id><Topic><Title>Important Message to Anyone Thinking About Voting for Obama</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351690713716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You got that right.....the most vehement opponents of Obama are immigrants from communist countries. All the ones I've talked to say too many Americans are so naive they can't see the deception of those who want to govern America with Marxist policies. Obama was fathered by a communist, raised by Marxists, his childhood mentor F.M Davis was a registered Communist and Obama said he chose to hang out with Marxist when he was in college. Yet, his supporters are so dumbed down they are in denial about him being a Marxist.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351697204734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:26:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351697207207-42</Id><Title>The economy will improve after Romney gets elected.</Title><Msg>So relax.</Msg><Username>weightbayou</Username><Timestamp>1351697207207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:26:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351697599916-43</Id><Title>Video: Billionaire Who Escaped Socialism Runs Ads Against Socialism</Title><Msg>Go to youtube and search "Thomas Peterffy - Freedom To Succeed" Thomas Peterffy is an entrepreneur who fled his native Hungary in 1965 to escape the yoke of Communism. He moved to America at the age of 21, worked hard, and ultimately earned billions as the head of a successful brokerage firm. According to his bio, he started a business that today employs thousands of people. With much at stake in the US presidential election, Peterffy is dipping into his personal fortune to warn voters about the dangers of creeping socialism, and to extol the American model of incentivizing hard work and encouraging upward mobility. It's a powerful message:</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351697599916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:33:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351697655913-44</Id><Topic><Title>Mitts odds of losing increase!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351692553621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:09:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351697655913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351697840354-45</Id><Topic><Title>The biggest losers in this campaign could be................</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351688692785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:04:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Takes one to know one.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351697840354</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:37:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351697968322-46</Id><Topic><Title>The biggest losers in this campaign could be................</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351688692785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:04:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Much too long and fatiguing! Kamakure</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351697968322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:39:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351697973699-47</Id><Title>BA Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Msg>See all BA charts - all on one screen - for free. I use this free standalone lightweight tool (does not install anything on your web browser or computer - this is not an annoying browser toolbar nor an add-in). It is called Yahoo Finance 7 Ways and lets me see all charts (e.g. 1 day, 5 days, 1 month, 3 months, etc.) on the same page for any given security. Do a web search for the website RSTNL and download it from the Downloads section of that website. You can also go to the website CNET, do a search for Yahoo Finance 7 Ways in the downloads section, and download it from there.</Msg><Username>royinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1351697973699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:39:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351699322793-48</Id><Title>Companies reporting layoffs , layoffs and more layoffs, DOW reported 20 plant closings and big layoffs</Title><Msg>Companies reporting layoffs , layoffs and more layoffs, DOW reported 20 plant closings and big layoffs</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351699322793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:02:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351700194118-49</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Odds Of Winning Have Now Surged All The Way To 77%</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351686979438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 08:36:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You mean believing the most accurate pollster of the 2008 election?" You mean Gallup -- which has Romney up b y 5 points -- is that the one you mean? LOL!</Msg><Username>parkplacebob</Username><Timestamp>1351700194118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351700325663-50</Id><Topic><Title>Mitts odds of losing increase!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351692553621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:09:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"every time he opens his mouth ! You mean the way he opened his mouth and destroyed the pres in the first debate -- is that what you mean? LOL!</Msg><Username>parkplacebob</Username><Timestamp>1351700325663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:18:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351700608426-51</Id><Title>Die has been cast</Title><Msg>Neither candidate will be a beneficiary of Sandy.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1351700608426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351700640527-52</Id><Topic><Title>Mitts odds of losing increase!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351692553621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:09:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time we cut off his access to OPM Taxpayers have been funding the enemy within for far too long</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1351700640527</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351701301870-53</Id><Topic><Title>Video: Billionaire Who Escaped Socialism Runs Ads Against Socialism</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351697599916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:33:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Go to youtube and search 'Thomas Peterffy - Freedom To Succeed'" More entertaining: go to Google and search for "bapsychdept teabagger ignorant megadoofus" and get 5,127,247 hits. Sheesh.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1351701301870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:35:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351701569598-54</Id><Topic><Title>Important Message to Anyone Thinking About Voting for Obama</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351690713716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another falsehood. The most vehement opponents of the black guy are the Confederate states, of course. Thousands of suicides feared in the Confederacy on the day after re-election.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1351701569598</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:39:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351702613647-55</Id><Topic><Title>Important Message to Anyone Thinking About Voting for Obama</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351690713716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a stupid racist post thats over the top - even for someone like you.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1351702613647</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351703395535-56</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing loses federal labor case in South Carolina</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1351457129635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 16:45:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A judge says at Boeing Charleston Boeing 787 plant has decided that Boeing broke national labor law when a human resources manager at its North Charleston plant told a mechanic not to talk about unionizing during working time. The Post and Courier of Charleston reported Sunday that Judge William Nelson Cates says Boeing can’t prohibit employees from discussing the union while allowing the Boeing Company representative to discuss not unionizing during working time. Well darn it James McNerney I guess you should not be talking directly to your worker’s through your Human Resources manager with threatening behavior about illegal union busting behavior .! BTW, James, how is that cheap non union outsourcing on the design and parts building for the 787 working for you now, 3 years late and 30 billion over budget on the 787! I know James, it’s called being a team member when the workers get paid less, because they can’t design or build the parts right, but they were cheap, just like they are worth. Such a deal and how is that 65 million in pay you get for 5 years as a Boeing employee working for you? I guess at least one Boeing employee is being overpaid, right James !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1351703395535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:09:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351704270446-57</Id><Topic><Title>Important Message to Anyone Thinking About Voting for Obama</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351690713716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he's doing what crap peddling ID #$%$s do, pretending to be other people the dumbo/mobro jihad is not but a couple multi-ID enemy useful idiots on each of the heavily trafficked msg boards, a jihad financed by dumbocrats using your tax dollars</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1351704270446</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:24:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351704823893-58</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Opens Up a 30 point lead on intrade</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351704133386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:22:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The in-crowd always goes with the smart money!</Msg><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1351704823893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:33:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351704874459-59</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Opens Up a 30 point lead on intrade</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351704133386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:22:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool! His intrade price has been going up steadily all day... I can't wait to not have to see Willtard's hangjaw Don Martin grin any more!</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1351704874459</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:34:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351705254778-60</Id><Topic><Title>BA Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>royinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1351697973699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:39:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, I just downloaded it and I might end up using this every day now...</Msg><Username>itsacalabreeze</Username><Timestamp>1351705254778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351705276034-61</Id><Title>Sell why you still can before the big drop, Start of the 2012-2013 recession</Title><Msg>Sell why you still can before the big drop, Start of the 2012-2013 recession</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351705276034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351705561924-62</Id><Topic><Title>Important Message to Anyone Thinking About Voting for Obama</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351690713716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only a complete idiot could call Obama a Marxist or a Communist. A teabaggin' idiot who never learned how to think, just parrots the RWNJ hate radio garbage on FAUX Noise.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351705561924</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:46:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351705569380-63</Id><Title>Protect your 401k's before its to late</Title><Msg>Protect your 401k's before its to late</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351705569380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:46:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351705992587-64</Id><Title>f*ing repubulicans</Title><Msg>The congressional campaign manager who confessed to spreading falsehoods on Twitter during Hurricane Sandy has resigned from Christopher Wright's New York City congressional campaign. Shashank Tripathi, under the guise of his Twitter handle @ComfortablySmug, sent out several pieces of misinformation during the worst of the storm Monday. He is being blamed for spreading the now-widely debunked rumor that the New York Stock Exchange trading floor had been flooded with 3 feet of standing water. The rumor was eventually picked up by CNN and New York Magazine until NYSE officials shot it down. In a message on his Twitter account late Tuesday, Tripathi apologized and offered his resignation on Wright's House campaign for the 12 th congressional district. Tripathi was first outed by BuzzFeed. "I wish to offer the people of New York a sincere, humble and unconditional apology," Tripathi wrote. "During a natural disaster that threatened the entire city, I made a series of irresponsible and inaccurate tweets." Other rumors included a false report that power would be shut down in all of Manhattan and that the New York subway would be closed for the entire week. Tripathi has written for a finance blog for the Stone Street Advisors hedge fund under the same pseudonym, "ComfortablySmug."</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351705992587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:53:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351706232587-65</Id><Topic><Title>Protect your 401k's before its to late</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1351705569380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:46:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's become a game of wealth transfer (verse investment), from your pockets to theirs a Romney victory will generate the volume they need to unload their overpriced equities, they'll use Romney and news, bad and good, to dump, they'll come back a year or two down the road to pick up the pieces with their ill gotten gains. if Obama wins it won't matter, the jig (scam) will be up, and market will tank with the economy.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1351706232587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351707280104-66</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is all about government waste green energy, deficit and even healthcare the tax now $3,500 when this was suppose to save Ameircans money</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351707170953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:12:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of government waste, does Romney propose to cut the bloated $800 billion military budget anytime soon?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351707280104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351707427144-67</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Repeatedly Ignores Questions About His Plans for FEMA</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351706735133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney and Obama both ignore questions about what really matters-- Respect for Constitutional liberties Respect for international laws of war Respect for simple human decency in "collateral casualties" Respect for the interests of the 99% as opposed to the 1%</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351707427144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:17:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351707515208-68</Id><Topic><Title>The economy will improve after Romney gets elected.</Title><Username>weightbayou</Username><Timestamp>1351697207207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:26:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're dreaming. Trickle-down doesn't work. Reagan while pretending to be a trickle-down president was in fact a neo-Keynsian with massive military spending.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351707515208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:18:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351707551838-69</Id><Topic><Title>f*ing repubulicans</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351705992587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You get your tail all tied into a knot over what some two two-bit campaign worker spewed over twitter yet you vote and support a guy (Obama) for President who constantly lies to you over matters which have profound impact on our lives.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351707551838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351707974328-70</Id><Topic><Title>Tied</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351693378735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You leftys don't have to worry about being brainwashed! No brain to wash.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1351707974328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351708109802-71</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Repeatedly Ignores Questions About His Plans for FEMA</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351706735133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama doesn't ignore the questions, he just makes up lies that sound good.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1351708109802</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:28:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351708152066-72</Id><Topic><Title>Tied</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351693378735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boo! The ghosts of Robert E. Lee, Jefferson Davis and "Stonewall" Jackson are going to pay you a visit tonight.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351708152066</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:29:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351711023654-73</Id><Title>Finger Pointing and Heavy Drinking in Chicago...</Title><Msg>...As the Obama Campaign Sees its Chances Swirling Down the Toilet.... Members of O's Campaign are Starting to Eat Themselves Beginning the Blame Game!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351711023654</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:17:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351711188528-74</Id><Topic><Title>f*ing repubulicans</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351705992587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:53:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fish- Romney lies with every word he utters. He has had numerous positions on everything. Don't believe me? Google what he has said about something and see how many times he has changed his position depending on who he is talking too.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351711188528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:19:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351711697663-75</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Repeatedly Ignores Questions About His Plans for FEMA</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351706735133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How worthless Willtard is as a leader! That just makes it so clear. As hopeless and helpless as Bushleague was during Katrina!</Msg><Username>demfascists43</Username><Timestamp>1351711697663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:28:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351711765009-76</Id><Topic><Title>POLL: Obama dominates Romney</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351692438778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:07:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Progressives are communists and socialists.....they believe in legalized thievery or what they call the "redistribution of wealth" that people have earned. That is also the foundation of Marxism.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351711765009</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:29:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351712272696-77</Id><Topic><Title>Important Message to Anyone Thinking About Voting for Obama</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351690713716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THE way you all are headed Ronald Regan would be considered a marxist .....too!!</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351712272696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:37:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351712291971-78</Id><Topic><Title>Important Message to Anyone Thinking About Voting for Obama</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351690713716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If welfare worked why do we still have poverty after spending $60,000 per year on every welfare recipient? That $60,000 comes from hard working Americans, many of whom earn far less than $60,000 per year.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351712291971</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:38:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351712296771-79</Id><Title>Denver Dem Mayor Says Obama Losing Early Vote... The Die is Cast</Title><Msg>Denver Mayor Hancock in Wisconsin says Obama getting beat in early voting By JEREMY MEYER The Denver Post Denver Mayor Michael Hancock has been busy pushing for President Obama’s re-election — appearing on stage Tuesday before former President Bill Clinton’s speech and even heading to Milwaukee on Sunday to push for the Badger State’s vote. Denver Mayor Michael Hancock stumps in Milwaukee on Sunday. Shown here with Milwaukee Mayor Tom Barrett, Los Angeles Mayor Antonio Villaraigosa and Wisconsin State Rep. JoCasta Zamarripa Hancock even broke news on that Wisconsin trip, telling voters if the election were to be held right now the president would lose Wisconsin and its coveted 10 electoral votes. Hancock told the crowd that the state could be lost if Dems didn’t get out the early vote. Early voting started in Wisconsin on Oct. 22. “We have not turned out the vote early,” Hancock told the newspaper. “The suburbs and rural parts of Wisconsin – the Republican base – are voting. President Obama’s base has yet to go vote. We’ve got to get our people to go vote.” The Wisconsin Democratic Party had to scale back Hancock’s statements, telling the Washington Examiner that while it appreciated Hancock’s efforts, his facts were off.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351712296771</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:38:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351712453199-80</Id><Topic><Title>Important Message to Anyone Thinking About Voting for Obama</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351690713716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you tell me who your doctor is......I want to see if he could extend my life too....but I don't want to live to be 142 yrs old like you. Leaving the Jim Crow times must have really bothered you.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351712453199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:40:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351712660251-81</Id><Topic><Title>Ties a lie</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351710411727</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:06:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you and your mighty staff gathering and processing all this data or are you deep into a bottle of Jack Daniels and just blowing hot air??!!</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351712660251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:44:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351712661383-82</Id><Title>American Votes have Discovered the Emperor (Obama) has No Clothes</Title><Msg>Opinion: Here comes the landslide By Dick Morris - 10/30/12 06:33 PM ET Voters have figured out that President Obama has no message, no agenda and not even much of an explanation for what he has done over the past four years. His campaign is based entirely on persuading people that Mitt Romney is a uniquely bad man, entirely dedicated to the rich, ignorant of the problems of the average person. As long as he could run his negative ads, the campaign at least kept voters away from the Romney bandwagon. But once we all met Mitt Romney for three 90-minute debates, we got to know him — and to like him. He was not the monster Obama depicted, but a reasonable person for whom we could vote. As we stripped away Obama’s yearlong campaign of vilification, all the president offered us was more servings of negative ads — ads we had already dismissed as not credible. He kept doing the same thing even as it stopped working. The result was that the presidential race reached a tipping point. Reasonable voters saw that the voice of hope and optimism and positivism was Romney while the president was only a nitpicking, quarrelsome, negative figure. The contrast does not work in Obama’s favor. His erosion began shortly after the conventions when Indiana (10 votes) and North Carolina (15) moved to Romney (in addition to the 179 votes that states that McCain carried cast this year). Then, in October, Obama lost the Southern swing states of Florida (29) and Virginia (13). He also lost Colorado (10), bringing his total to 255 votes. And now, he faces the erosion of the northern swing states: Ohio (18), New Hampshire (4) and Iowa (6). Only in the union-anchored state of Nevada (9) does Obama still cling to a lead. In the next few days, the battle will move to Pennsylvania (20), Michigan (15), Wisconsin (10) and Minnesota (16). Ahead in Pennsylvania, tied in Michigan and Wisconsin, and slightly behind in Minnesota, these new swing states look to be the battleground. Or will the Romney momentum grow and wash into formerly safe Democratic territory in New Jersey and Oregon? Once everyone discovers that the emperor has no clothes (or that Obama has no argument after the negative ads stopped working), the vote shift could be of historic proportions.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351712661383</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:44:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351712893361-83</Id><Topic><Title>Another Reason Obama Can't create Jobs</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1348580228204</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 09:37:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've talked to Canadians too and some didn't mind the extra they paid for their wine &amp; gasoline, etc because they said when it came to getting their kids educated or not fretting when they or someone in their family got seriously ill it was worth it.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351712893361</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351713106168-84</Id><Topic><Title>Important Message to Anyone Thinking About Voting for Obama</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351690713716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Make up a number - any number and just fling it out there right now you're using $60,000 a year - why not $70k or $80k it's all made up anyway....go for more spin with a higher number</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351713106168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351713144961-85</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Odds Of Winning Have Now Surged All The Way To 77%</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351686979438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 08:36:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>=You mean Gallup -- which has Romney up b y 5 points --= As of MONDAY, 29 Oct; i.e., has not been updated since then due to Sandy! Get a clue, twit.</Msg><Username>ahkmed_the_id_homo</Username><Timestamp>1351713144961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:52:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351713263467-86</Id><Title>“Don’t Ask, Don’t Tell’ is back…</Title><Msg>… It’s President Obama’s new policy for questions about Libya.”</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351713263467</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:54:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351713276061-87</Id><Title>Obama's Vision for America...</Title><Msg>Eurozone unemployment hits new high More than one in four people out of work in Greece and Spain as jobless rate rises to 11.6%, according to Eurostat data Julia Kollewe and Phillip Inman guardian.co.uk, Wednesday 31 October 2012 15.46 EDT Pedestrians walk past graffitti in Athens – a growing number of Greek workers remain nominally employed but have not been paid for some time. Unemployment in the eurozone has risen to a new record, with more than one in four out of work in Spain and Greece. There are now 18.49 million people without jobs in the 17 countries sharing the euro, said the European statistics office Eurostat on Wednesday with an extra 146,000 joining the ranks of the unemployed last month. Youth unemployment – joblessness among under-25s – rose to 23.3%, up from 21% during the same month a year ago.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351713276061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:54:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351713291028-88</Id><Topic><Title>Denver Dem Mayor Says Obama Losing Early Vote... The Die is Cast</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351712296771</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:38:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How would the mayor know the first frigging thing about it? You don't suppose he illegally opening ballots and counting them already, do you?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351713291028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:54:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351713403465-89</Id><Title>Obama running on the strength of his I.O.U.</Title><Msg>When he said "Forget what I have done in the past. Vote for what I will do." What then if he will default? We will be holding the bag all over again.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1351713403465</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:56:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351713411005-90</Id><Topic><Title>Denver Dem Mayor Says Obama Losing Early Vote... The Die is Cast</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351712296771</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:38:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chrissy/Dih: It's called Exit polling... geez You Libs can Be Stupid!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351713411005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:56:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351713561797-91</Id><Topic><Title>Obama running on the strength of his I.O.U.</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1351713403465</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:56:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep... it's Called China. Obama Sold his Soul and America's Future to China with His Doubling of America's Debt in Four Years!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351713561797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:59:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351713843524-92</Id><Title>Here comes the landslide</Title><Msg>Voters have figured out that President Obama has no message, no agenda and not even much of an explanation for what he has done over the past four years. His campaign is based entirely on persuading people that Mitt Romney is a uniquely bad man, entirely dedicated to the rich, ignorant of the problems of the average person. As long as he could run his negative ads, the campaign at least kept voters away from the Romney bandwagon. But once we all met Mitt Romney for three 90-minute debates, we got to know him — and to like him. He was not the monster Obama depicted, but a reasonable person for whom we could vote. As we stripped away Obama’s yearlong campaign of vilification, all the president offered us was more servings of negative ads — ads we had already dismissed as not credible. He kept doing the same thing even as it stopped working. The result was that the presidential race reached a tipping point. Reasonable voters saw that the voice of hope and optimism and positivism was Romney while the president was only a nitpicking, quarrelsome, negative figure. The contrast does not work in Obama’s favor. His erosion began shortly after the conventions when Indiana (10 votes) and North Carolina (15) moved to Romney (in addition to the 179 votes that states that McCain carried cast this year). Then, in October, Obama lost the Southern swing states of Florida (29) and Virginia (13). He also lost Colorado (10), bringing his total to 255 votes. And now, he faces the erosion of the northern swing states: Ohio (18), New Hampshire (4) and Iowa (6). Only in the union-anchored state of Nevada (9) does Obama still cling to a lead. In the next few days, the battle will move to Pennsylvania (20), Michigan (15), Wisconsin (10) and Minnesota (16). Ahead in Pennsylvania, tied in Michigan and Wisconsin, and slightly behind in Minnesota, these new swing states look to be the battleground. Or will the Romney momentum grow and wash into formerly safe Democratic territory in New Jersey and Oregon? Once everyone discovers that the emperor has no clothes (or that Obama has no argument after the negative ads stopped working), the vote shift could be of historic proportions. The impact on Senate races could be profound. Give the GOP easy pickups in Nebraska and North Dakota. Wisconsin has been a roller coaster. Once an easy win for Republican Tommy Thompson, then a likely loss as Democrat Tammy Baldwin caught up, and now Republican again, it will probably be a third pickup. Romney’s surge in Virginia is propelling George Allen to a good lead for the first time all campaign. In Montana, Republican Denny Rehberg holds and has held for some time a small lead over Democrat incumbent Jon Tester. And, in Pennsylvania, Smith has powered his campaign to a small lead over Democrat Bob Casey Jr. The GOP now leads in these six takeaways. But it is also within easy striking distance in Ohio and Florida, where incumbents are under 50 percent and Republican challengers Connie Mack (Fla.) and Josh Mandel (Ohio) are only a few points behind. It may even be possible to entertain daydreams of Rhode Island (Barry Hinckley) and New Jersey (Joe Kyrillos) going Republican. Republican losses? Look for a giveback in Maine and possibly in Indiana and Massachusetts. In Indiana, Republican Richard Mourdock had established a 5-point lead over Democrat Joe Donnelly. But his comments about rape knocked him back to a tie. With Romney carrying the state by 15 points, however, Mourdock could still make it. In Massachusetts, Brown has been in hand-to-hand combat with Elizabeth Warren. Down by five a few days ago, he’s now tied, but the undecided usually goes against the incumbent. The most likely outcome? Eight GOP takeaways and two giveaways for a net gain of six. A 53-47 Senate, just like we have now, only opposite. Barack Obama’s parting gift to the Democratic Party.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351713843524</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:04:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351713924440-93</Id><Topic><Title>Obama running on the strength of his I.O.U.</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1351713403465</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:56:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Throw my record away. Garbage in garbage out.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1351713924440</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:05:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351714099855-94</Id><Title>Biden, the Buffoon, Does it Again... Forgets What State he is Campaigning In!</Title><Msg>Follow Andrew Kaczynski ‏@BuzzFeedAndrew Biden calls the Cleveland Plain Dealer one of the major newspapers "in this state." He is in Florida, not Ohio.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351714099855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:08:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351714173030-95</Id><Title>Republicans Have Won Every November 6th Presidential Election Since 1860</Title><Msg>Here's one more historical curiosity to observe this election cycle. Since election day was standardized in 1845 there have been 6 presidential elections held on November 6th and Republicans have won all six. That means next Tuesday, the 7th Presidential election held on this date, will either break or uphold a streak that began in 1860 with the election of Abraham Lincoln. Starting in 1792, states had a range of dates on which to conduct presidential elections, but in 1845 Congress standardized the date so it would always be the Tuesday after the first Monday in November. Since then presidential elections have been held on dates ranging from November 2nd to November 8th with each date coming up about six times in a fairly regular pattern. The date November 6th has always been a good one for Republicans: 1860 - Abraham Lincoln over Stephen Douglas 1888 - Benjamin Harrison over incumbent Grover Cleveland 1900 - William McKinley over William Jennings Bryan 1928 - Herbert Hoover over Al Smith 1956 - Dwight Eisenhower over Adlai Stevenson 1984 - Ronald Reagan over Walter Mondale Which brings us to November 6th, 2012 where it's Mitt Romney in a tight race with the incumbent Barack Obama. Will the Republicans' lucky streak hold or will Obama make history as the first Democrat to win on that date? We'll know in a week (or so). In case you're wondering, the 2016 election will be held on November 8th. It will be the 7th presidential election on this date since 1845. The prior six were evenly split with three going to Democrats (Cleveland, FDR, Kennedy) and the other three to Republicans (Lincoln, Teddy Roosevelt, G.H.W. Bush).</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351714173030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:09:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351714177519-96</Id><Topic><Title>“Don’t Ask, Don’t Tell’ is back…</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351713263467</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thousands died under Bush and you remained silent, WEASLE!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351714177519</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351714806062-97</Id><Topic><Title>Biden, the Buffoon, Does it Again... Forgets What State he is Campaigning In!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351714099855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:08:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And he's one step away from being our president. Go figure. God help us!</Msg><Username>bissell33</Username><Timestamp>1351714806062</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:20:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351715251476-98</Id><Title>Tea Party Get Own News Site... Gotta Love Grass Roots Democracy!</Title><Msg>The Tea Party gets a news site Comments (81) By DYLAN BYERS | 10/31/12 3:38 PM EDT Tea Party conservatives are getting their very own news site. The Tea Party News Network, self-described as "the only trusted news source and the antidote to mainstream media bias," is already live but will announce its launch tomorrow morning, with plans to start live video on election day. TPNN claims to have a "war room of 40-plus volunteers" who will operate out of the Venetian Resort in Las Vegas, and has established partnerships with the Talk Radio Network and radio host Rusty Humphries, who will be co-anchoring the election night coverage. "There are plenty of news websites out there, but there isn’t one that caters directly to Tea Party conservatives, providing activists with coverage and opinion that matters to them. The Tea Party News Network changes that," Todd Cefaratti, editor of the Tea Party News Network, said in a statement for the forthcoming press release. As with many right-wing news sites, TPNN puts heavy emphasis on the anti-mainstream media message: "We don’t need our supposed betters in the mainstream media telling us which stories matter or what we should think. We don’t mindlessly mimic the talking points of Washington leaders. The Tea Party movement now has a home for news it can trust." Truth be told, it's not as though Tea Party conservatives have been homeless on the web. Most right-wing news and opinion sites, including the Media Research Center and the Breitbart network, cater to those who would label themselves members of the Tea Party. But this is the first site of its scope to apply the branding and assert itself as "the voice of the Tea Party." Cefaratti is also promising to be "a vigilant watchdog on Washington’s leaders regardless of the outcome of the November election." "TPNN is not going to be just any other conservative backwater on the Internet," said Keith Urbahn, who heads the PR firm promoting the site and recently served as chief of staff to former Sec. of Defense Donald Rumsfeld. Election coverage will be co-hosted by Humphries and TPNN News Director Scottie Nell Hughes, with a particular focus on Tea Party-backed candidates like Ted Cruz, Allen West, Michelle Bachmann, and Mia Love.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351715251476</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:27:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351715273214-99</Id><Title>Obamacare exempts millions--prisoners, illegals, welfare recipients</Title><Msg>In just 14 months, Americans will be required to prove that they have federally "qualified" health insurance or face an Obamacare tax of $695 to $2,085. That is unless you are in prison, below the poverty line, or are an undocumented immigrant, according to the anti-tax group Americans for Tax Reform. When added together, those three groups total up to one-sixth of the nation's population of 314 million: 218,929 are in federal prisons, 12 million are illegals and 42 million are below the poverty line and eligible for welfare, though some fit into all three categories, according to federal reports. ATR highlighted the groups eligible from the mandate to get health insurance in a mock Internal Revenue Service form they developed to show the extra paperwork Americans will be required to fill out once the full Obamacare law kicks in, January 2014. It is based on testimony from the IRS given in September that said, "taxpayers will file their tax returns reporting their health insurance coverage, and/or making a payment." Based on other IRS requirements, ATR said that Americans will have to show that they have health insurance "qualified" by the Department of Health and Human Services. They will also have to disclose if they were covered by a qualifying plan during the year and for how long. And they could be subject to penalties and interest on unpaid Obamacare taxes for periods they were not covered.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351715273214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:27:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351715434294-100</Id><Title>Senators Again Urge Obama to Answer Key Questions about Benghazi Attack</Title><Msg>Four senators sent a letter to the White House today, urging President Obama and his advisers to answer the growing list of questions about the 9/11 attack in Benghazi, Libya, which lawmakers have posed in writing to his administration over the last month. Senators John McCain (R-Ariz.), Lindsey Graham (R-S.C.), Kelly Ayotte (R-N.H.), and Ron Johnson (R-Wisc.), the authors of the letter, explain to the president: The American people deserve to know all the facts surrounding the terrorist attack in Benghazi on September 11, 2012, that resulted in the murder of four Americans—including Ambassador Chris Stevens. Unfortunately, you and your senior administration officials have not been forthcoming in providing answers to the many questions that have emerged. On October 9, 2012, we sent a letter to the senior intelligence officials in your administration in an effort to obtain answers to these questions. More than three weeks have passed, and we still have not received a response. To make matters worse, since that original letter, we sent several subsequent letters to you or to your senior administration officials asking a number of questions, and we have failed to receive a single letter in response. The American people and their representatives in Congress need to understand what you knew about the Benghazi terrorist attack and when you knew it. We also have a right to know what steps you and your administration took—or failed to take—before, during, and after the terrorist attack to protect American lives….</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351715434294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:30:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351716191327-101</Id><Topic><Title>Shameless #$%$ Again and Again and Again and....</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351706255574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:57:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, You and Obama are a lot alike. Obama protested with great indignation at the second debate how he was "offended" by Benghazi crticism: "And the suggestion that anybody in my team, whether the Secretary of State, our U.N. Ambassador, anybody on my team would play politics or mislead when we've lost four of our own, governor, is offensive. That's not what we do. That's not what I do as president, that's not what I do as Commander in Chief." And, then the truth comes out that at least one if not several of his team, including himself, were lying to the American public. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351716191327</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351716440794-102</Id><Topic><Title>Senators Again Urge Obama to Answer Key Questions about Benghazi Attack</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351715434294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:30:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>where were these folks when Bush was president and thousands died?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351716440794</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:47:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351716754677-103</Id><Title>Today's numbers in key battleground states.</Title><Msg>Quinnipiac University, on behalf of CBS and the NY Times, stuck a dagger in Romney's Ohio hopes by showing President Barack Obama up 50-45, as well as a one-point lead in Florida and two-point lead in Virginia. Marquette University, the best pollster during the Wisconsin recall, now shows Obama winning the state 51-43. Their last poll a couple of weeks ago had it 49-48 Obama. PPP has Obama cruising in Iowa 50-45, and in Wisconsin 51-46. This is it, the stretch run, and Romney is losing ground almost everywhere.</Msg><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1351716754677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351717312395-104</Id><Title>White House Silent as Benghazi Questions Mount</Title><Msg>Last week, we alerted you to the infuriating, heart-wrenching revelation that at least three specific requests for military help from besieged Americans in Benghazi were rejected by someone in the chain of command. This decision was made despite the established fact that US officials in Tripoli, the State Department, the Pentagon and the White House were watching the horror unfold in real time, via a video feed from an unmanned drone hovering over the city. Democrats won't say if that drone was armed (and therefore capable of raining fire on the terrorists who were attacking our men and women). Why were these reinforcements refused, who specifically did the refusing, and where was the president throughout this process? These are questions being asked by US Senators, and political commentators from across the ideological spectrum. We've gotten a few answers so far. David Petraeus has emphatically denied that the CIA made this call. President Obama's Defense Secretary has hinted that the Pentagon was involved in the decision. The White House? Silence: So here's where we are: Petraeus has made clear the CIA wasn't responsible for the decision not to act. Panetta has tried to take the responsibility himself—and the White House has seemed to encourage this interpretation of events. But Panetta's position is untenable: The Defense Department doesn't get to unilaterally decide whether it's too risky or not to try to rescue CIA operators, or to violate another country's air space. In any case, it’s inconceivable Panetta didn't raise the question of what to do when he met with the national security adviser and the president at 5 p.m. on the evening of September 11 for an hour. And it's beyond inconceivable he didn't then stay in touch with the White House after he returned to the Pentagon. So the question remains: What did President Obama do that evening (apart from spending an hour on the phone with Prime Minister Netanyahu)? What did he know, and what did he decide, and what was the basis for his decisions? Petraeus has disclaimed responsibility for the decisions of September 11. Panetta has claimed responsibility for decisions that weren't his to make. Both Petraeus and Panetta have raised more questions than they've answered. The only person who can provide the answers the American people deserve is President Obama. The questions surrounding this preventable massacre still to outnumber the answers we've been given -- eight weeks after those four Americans were murdered. There are now rumors floating around that damning audio and emails have been leaked to two major media organizations.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351717312395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:01:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351717463411-105</Id><Title>Even id Obumere were tho be re-elected which is highly unlikely........</Title><Msg>......impeachment for the Benghazi coverup would be very likely.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351717463411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351717602571-106</Id><Topic><Title>Even id Obumere were tho be re-elected which is highly unlikely........</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351717463411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:04:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thousands died under Bush and you remained silent about it huh? yep just another Weasel Republican !</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351717602571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:06:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351718460853-107</Id><Topic><Title>Today's numbers in key battleground states.</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1351716754677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:52:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting fact: every location where Willard compaigns in person, he loses a little more ground. Check out this fact since his convention.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1351718460853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:21:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351718800215-108</Id><Title>They Didn't Riot Over THIS Video.....Wonder Why?</Title><Msg>It’s interesting to consider the video the street protestors didn’t riot over. More than a year ago, the Israeli satirical group, Latma, produced this video. The Israelis lampoon the Mullahs of Tehran and the flaccid response of this administration to the existential threat of Iran becoming a nuclear power. There were no recorded riots anywhere in what President Obama obligingly calls “the Muslim world” over this Israeli video. Why not? Watch the video and note the caricature of the mullah. Note his smirking and mugging for the camera. Note, too, the burka-clad Iranian damsels and their come-hither batting of their eyes. Shouldn’t the Arab Street have rioted over that one? They didn’t. And the reason they didn’t is because they knew it would do no good. The Israelis don’t quail. They don’t quiver. They don’t quake. And they never cringe. That’s why they have the Obama administration. Contrast the Obama administration’s official spokespersons—Jay Carney and Victoria Nuland—with this defiant Israeli posture, as evidenced by the Latma video. Day after day, Carney and Nuland come before the world press and grovel. There is virtually nothing that happens on the Arab Street that makes either of these capital cringers angry. For such a relentlessly pro-abortion administration, it is positively weird to see how often their spokespeople go into a fetal position. The video? Youtube "The Iranian bomb - The song"</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351718800215</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:26:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351718874426-109</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Obama Reaches 50 Percent, Leads Romney By 5 Nationally</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351718349122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:19:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351718874426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:27:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351718899994-110</Id><Topic><Title>Today's numbers in key battleground states.</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1351716754677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:52:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting fact: every location where Willard compaigns in person, he loses a little more ground. ============ Is it any wonder? Real Americans don't want a phony PLASTIC man as Pres.</Msg><Username>analgonqueen11</Username><Timestamp>1351718899994</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351719141714-111</Id><Title>Obama's Layoff Bomb</Title><Msg>The administration's bully boys don't have enough whitewash and duct tape to cover up the past, present and future devastation of the president and his economic demolition team. In June, a diffident and self-deluded President Obama claimed that "the private sector is doing fine." Last week, the private sector responded: Speak for yourself, buster. Who needs an "October Surprise" when the business headlines are broadcasting the imminent layoff bomb in neon lights? The Bureau of Labor Statistics reported last Tuesday that employers issued 1,316 "mass layoff actions" (affecting 50 workers or more) in September; more than 122,000 workers were affected overall. USA Today financial reporter Matt Krantz wrote that "(m)uch of the recent layoff activity is connected to what's been the slowest period of earnings growth since the third quarter of 2009." Some necessary restructuring is underway in response to the stagnant European economy. But more and more U.S. businesses are putting the blame — bravely and squarely — right where it belongs: on the obstructionist policies and regulatory schemes of the blame-shifter-in-chief. Last week, Ohio-based auto parts manufacturer Dana Holding Corp. warned employees of potential layoffs amid "looming concern" about the economy. President and CEO Roger Wood specifically mentioned the walloping burden of "increasing taxes on small businesses" and the need to "offset increased costs that are placed on us through new laws and regulations." Case in point: Obamacare. The mandate will cost Dana Holding Corp., which employs some 24,500 workers, "approximately $24 million over the next six years in additional U.S. health care expenses." As Ohio Watchdog blogger Maggie Thurber reported, the firm's Toledo area corporate offices laid off seven white-collar employees last Friday; company insiders told her more were on the way. They are not alone. On Tuesday, Consol Energy issued a federally mandated layoff disclosure announcing its "intent to idle its Miller Creek surface operations near Naugatuck, W.Va." The move will affect the company's Wiley Surface Mine, Wiley Creek Surface Mine, Minway Surface Mine, Minway Preparation Plant and Miller Creek Administration Group, all in Mingo County, W.Va. Despite state approval, cooperation with the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers and myriad other agencies, and a stellar safety record, Obama's EPA dragged its feet on the permit approval process. The impasse has forced layoffs of 145 Consol Energy employees that will hit at the end of the year. They are not alone. In August, Robert E. Murray, founder and CEO of Murray Energy Corporation in Ohio, blasted the White House anti-coal agenda for the layoffs and closure of his company's mine. He told Obama water-carrying CNN anchor Soledad O'Brien that "the many regulations that (Obama) and his radical appointees and the U.S. EPA have put on the use of coal, there are dozens of them and collectively by his own energy administration, have closed 175 power plants." As O'Brien barked at her guest about purported environmental objections, Murray explained that "we cannot get permits for these mines. They are delaying the issuance of permits. If you can't get the permit, you can't have the mine. ... I created those jobs, and I put the investment in that mine. And when it came time to lay the people off, I went up personally and talked to every one of them myself to lay them off. It's a human issue." And it's an innovation issue, too. As I reported in February, Obamacare's impending 2.3 percent medical device excise tax has already wrought havoc on the industry: Stryker, a maker of artificial hips and knees based in Kalamazoo, Mich., is slashing 5 percent of its global workforce (an estimated 1,000 workers) this coming year to reduce costs related to Obamacare's taxes and mandates. Covidien, a N.Y.-based surgical supplies manufacturer, recently announced layoffs of 200 American workers and plans to move some of its plant work to Mexico and Costa Rica, in part because of the coming tax hit. Mass.-based Zoll Medical Corp., which makes defibrillators and employs some 1,800 workers in the U.S. and around the world, says the medical device tax will cost the company between $5 million and $10 million a year. This July, Indiana's Cook Medical Inc. shelved plans to open five new plants because of the imminent medical device tax hit. They are not alone. The heads of Koch Industries, Westgate Resorts and ASG Software Solutions have all separately informed their employees of prosperity-undermining Obama economic politics. Left-wing groups have lambasted the executives for exercising their political free speech. But they have remained silent while the White House corruptocrats bribed federal defense contractors into delaying federally mandated layoff disclosures before the election. In a memo now being investigated on Capitol Hill, Obama promised to cover the legal fees of Lockheed Martin and other defense contractors if they ignored legal requirements to inform workers in advance about so-called sequestration cuts to the military's budget scheduled to kick in next year. Truth suppression is a time-honored Obama tactic, of course. Remember: The administration and its Democratic allies on Capitol Hill attempted to punish Deere, Caterpillar, Verizon and ATT in 2010 for disclosing how the costs of Obamacare taxes were hitting their bottom lines — even though they were simply following SEC disclosure requirements. The White House also tried to silence insurers who dared to inform their customers about how Obamacare was driving up premiums. Not this time. The administration's bully boys don't have enough whitewash and duct tape to cover up the past, present and future devastation of the president and his economic demolition team.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351719141714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:32:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351719171598-112</Id><Topic><Title>They Didn't Riot Over THIS Video.....Wonder Why?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351718800215</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:26:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Y A W W W N N N N</Msg><Username>ahkmed_the_id_homo</Username><Timestamp>1351719171598</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:32:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351719628567-113</Id><Topic><Title>Romney bought $5k of food for people to “donate” back to him at phony “hurricane” rally</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351719176159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:32:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You Libs are Truely in Full Panic Mode, eh? Trash/ Nonsense!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351719628567</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351719669122-114</Id><Topic><Title>Today's numbers in key battleground states.</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1351716754677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:52:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More independents are now supporting Romney vs. Obama. This is a clear indicator that it's Romney's advantage. Checkmate.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351719669122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:41:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351719803147-115</Id><Title>BA Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Msg>See all BA charts - all on one screen - for free. I use this free standalone lightweight tool (does not install anything on your web browser or computer - this is not an annoying browser toolbar nor an add-in). It is called Yahoo Finance 7 Ways and lets me see all charts (e.g. 1 day, 5 days, 1 month, 3 months, etc.) on the same page for any given security. Do a web search for the website RSTNL and download it from the Downloads section of that website. You can also go to the website CNET, do a search for Yahoo Finance 7 Ways in the downloads section, and download it from there.</Msg><Username>royinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1351719803147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:43:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351719939173-116</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare exempts millions--prisoners, illegals, welfare recipients</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351715273214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:27:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you mention that most unions are exempt from Obamacare? After finding out what the hell was in Obamacare they turned and fled the scene!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351719939173</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:45:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351720314737-117</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Pulling Away</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351720143224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:49:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just the Inverse... Romney is Pulling Away!! You will be Drinking Vinegar Tuesday Night.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351720314737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:51:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351720833909-118</Id><Topic><Title>Why Obama Is A Genius</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351720503679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is Nothing but an Affirmative Action Queen and a Fool. His First and Last Term Record is Worse Than Jimmy Carters and We all Know How That Turned Out, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351720833909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:00:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351722279918-119</Id><Topic><Title>Senators Again Urge Obama to Answer Key Questions about Benghazi Attack</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351715434294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:30:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just as soon as Romney releases a single COMPLETE tax return. He's a proven liar about his taxes, like when he told Mass. voters he had filed as a Mass. resident when running for Mass. governor. He can't be trusted, especially when he says, "You're going to have to trust me." Let's give him the retirement he needs to go visit his holding all over the world, but not in America (Oh. Except for his dressage horse.)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351722279918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:24:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351722305938-120</Id><Topic><Title>Romney bought $5k of food for people to “donate” back to him at phony “hurricane” rally</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351719176159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:32:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only things foul and vulgar are the things you post.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1351722305938</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:25:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351722368618-121</Id><Topic><Title>Romney bought $5k of food for people to “donate” back to him at phony “hurricane” rally</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351719176159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:32:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Considering how much money the Romney's have $5K is a very generous donation.....adjusted to my scale I will donate equally......where do I send my dollar???</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351722368618</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:26:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351722401524-122</Id><Topic><Title>Denver Dem Mayor Says Obama Losing Early Vote... The Die is Cast</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351712296771</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:38:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where are the exiting from? The post office? You guys will grasp at any straw to avoid lying awake at nights.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351722401524</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:26:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351722482124-123</Id><Topic><Title>Senators Again Urge Obama to Answer Key Questions about Benghazi Attack</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351715434294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:30:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just saw the 9/11 program on the military channel last night.......those four senators should run and hide</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351722482124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:28:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351722615451-124</Id><Topic><Title>White House Silent as Benghazi Questions Mount</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351717312395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:01:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your call has been rerouted to the FEMA help desk.....right now there's a few more pressing matters.....like helping our fellow Americans in the northeast sector of our country get back to normal</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351722615451</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:30:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351722618756-125</Id><Title>Why Obama is a slow learner</Title><Msg>Because it took him this long to realize that cooperation can actually work.Sadly it took a disaster and Governor Christie to open his eyes. Might be too little too late for him now if he loses next week. But at least he got a taste of real governing.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1351722618756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:30:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351722655022-126</Id><Topic><Title>Senators Again Urge Obama to Answer Key Questions about Benghazi Attack</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351715434294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:30:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Condi Rice just got AXED from the Repugnantcon wish list! Former Secretary of State Condoleeza Rice broke with the majority of her party last night on Fox News, as she tried to hit the brakes on the right wing’s politicization of the recent attack in Libya. Host Greta Van Susteren asked Rice directly and repeatedly about a set of emails uncovered by Reuters. In what has been dubbed “Benghazi-Gate,” the conservative media has jumped on the emails as definitive proof that the Obama administration has been lying about what it knew and when in the aftermath of the Sept. 11 attack on a diplomatic mission in Benghazi. Rice’s response was likely not what Van Susteren expected: RICE: But when things are unfolding very, very quickly, it’s not always easy to know what is really going on on the ground. And to my mind, the really important questions here are about how information was collected. Did the various agencies really coordinate and share intelligence in the way that we had hoped, with the reforms that were made after 9/11? So there’s a big picture to be examined here. But we don’t have all of the pieces, and I think it’s easy to try and jump to conclusions about what might have happened here. It’s probably better to let the relevant bodies do their work.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351722655022</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351722730057-127</Id><Topic><Title>Why Obama is a slow learner</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1351722618756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:30:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If only he had done all the Repubs wanted things would be rosy right?? Wrong, EVEN if he agreed entirely with everything they wanted - they by agreement were going to be against him.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351722730057</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:32:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351722814948-128</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Have Won Every November 6th Presidential Election Since 1860</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351714173030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a classic example of a meaningless statistic</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351722814948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:33:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351723188645-129</Id><Topic><Title>Gas Prices</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351713669495</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:01:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fill up to you hearts content.....not many miles being driven in New Jersey, eastern New York and Pennsylvania</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351723188645</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351723248904-130</Id><Title>God bless the Presdient and the people affected by the hurricane</Title><Msg>No Sept 11th on Obama's watch</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351723248904</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:40:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351723330541-131</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Pulling Away</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351720143224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:49:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be sure to tune into Fox News next Tuesday so you can see how the professionals will spin how Obama scammed the election and got himself re-elected</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351723330541</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:42:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351723336016-132</Id><Title>No Sept 11th on Obama's watch</Title><Msg>Bush got us in this mess and now repubs try the President. I am afraid of the pension raiders in Romneys camp</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351723336016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:42:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351723362761-133</Id><Title>I am afraid of the pension raiders in Romneys camp</Title><Msg>Aren't you?</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351723362761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:42:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351723402579-134</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Obama Reaches 50 Percent, Leads Romney By 5 Nationally</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351718349122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:19:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And why are you campaigning for a war criminal? Tell me again, I forgot.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351723402579</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351723733079-135</Id><Topic><Title>I am afraid of the pension raiders in Romneys camp</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351723362761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:42:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You Haven't Clue as to What You Are Posting! Pathetic Lib.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351723733079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:48:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351724055292-136</Id><Topic><Title>Senators Again Urge Obama to Answer Key Questions about Benghazi Attack</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351715434294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:30:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you bipolar?</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1351724055292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:54:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351724153540-137</Id><Title>What was this lie about jeeps going to china</Title><Msg>another romnesia moment</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351724153540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351724232353-138</Id><Topic><Title>No Sept 11th on Obama's watch</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351723336016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:42:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Four Dead Americans including our Ambassador Murdered on 9-11-2012! And Obama Denied Them Help... Let Them Die!!! Are You Really That Stupid or Acting Like Dik?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351724232353</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351724328961-139</Id><Topic><Title>No Sept 11th on Obama's watch</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351723336016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:42:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many Americans died on Sept 11 and the illegal invasion of Iraq?</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351724328961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:58:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351724443642-140</Id><Title>How many Americans died on Sept 11 and the illegal invasion of Iraq?</Title><Msg>funny how repubs forget.</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351724443642</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:00:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351725116037-141</Id><Topic><Title>How many Americans died on Sept 11 and the illegal invasion of Iraq?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351724443642</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Such drama from the ba board sissyboy..............</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1351725116037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:11:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351725246474-142</Id><Topic><Title>Senators Again Urge Obama to Answer Key Questions about Benghazi Attack</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351715434294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:30:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, he's just a turd bobbing around in the shallow end of the gene pool......................</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1351725246474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:14:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351725375427-143</Id><Topic><Title>Today's numbers in key battleground states.</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1351716754677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:52:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If we elect "Ken" we will get "Barbie" as 1st Lady.</Msg><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1351725375427</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:16:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351725804548-144</Id><Topic><Title>What was this lie about jeeps going to china</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351724153540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:55:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually Fiat is Considering Moving Production of the Jeep to Either Italy or China! For Challenged Libs Like You, Fiat is an Italian Company Who Purchased Chrysler, Who was Bailed Out by the American Tax Payers.... and Now Planning on Sending the Jobs Overseas... Great Job Obama. Romney was Right After All!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351725804548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351726822909-145</Id><Topic><Title>Why Obama is a slow learner</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1351722618756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:30:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you remember the response of Bushleague to Katrina? Tell me you weren't embarassed by his bottomless incompetence and helplessness.</Msg><Username>ahkmed_the_id_homo</Username><Timestamp>1351726822909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:40:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351726936694-146</Id><Topic><Title>BA Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>royinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1351719803147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:43:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ok so as far as I can see this is free. i just tried it and it works pretty well</Msg><Username>peelingoutsummer</Username><Timestamp>1351726936694</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:42:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351726990991-147</Id><Topic><Title>Romney bought $5k of food for people to “donate” back to him at phony “hurricane” rally</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351719176159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:32:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's so right...</Msg><Username>demfascists43</Username><Timestamp>1351726990991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351727186613-148</Id><Topic><Title>How many Americans died on Sept 11 and the illegal invasion of Iraq?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351724443642</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You of all #$%$ should talk about SISSYBOYS, eh?</Msg><Username>analgonqueen11</Username><Timestamp>1351727186613</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:46:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351727963060-149</Id><Topic><Title>God bless the Presdient and the people affected by the hurricane</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351723248904</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:40:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"No Sept 11th on Obama's watch" (except 9/11/2012, minor detail) Not much into Christmas and Easter on Obama's watch either. But lots of Ramadan celebrations. Did you notice that Obama's approach regarding the (he finally gave in and acknowledged that it was a) terrorist attack on the consulate in Benghazi, that he said he "will get who is responsible". Curious that Obama's friends in Turkey did not let us get access to the Tunisian that was a part of the attack. And the Tunisians aren't helping either. All of that "Arab Spring" support on the part of Obama is paying back in big non-existant dividends. So the "Big O" sends the FBI out to investigate three weeks after the attack. Remember the Marine Hymn, "... to the shores of Tripoli". The marines, in 1805, marched from Alexandria, Egypt to Tripoli, Libya, 520 miles via camel, averaging 20 miles per day - about the same length of time that Obama responded by finally sending in SOMEONE to do SOMETHING. This man is the Peanut Butter President. And "slow as molasses". Unless there is a photo op. Or a View op to show off his "eye candiness".</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351727963060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:59:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351728483334-150</Id><Topic><Title>Why Obama Is A Genius</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351720503679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Using the words "Obama" and "Genius" in the same sentence is a perfect example of an oblivious oxymoron.</Msg><Username>cws2012wc</Username><Timestamp>1351728483334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 20:08:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351730029314-151</Id><Topic><Title>Why Obama is a slow learner</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1351722618756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:30:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Do you remember the response of Bushleague to Katrina? Tell me you weren't embarassed by his bottomless incompetence and helplessness." Hmm.What I remember is Mayor Ray Magin and Governor Kathleen Blanco (both big Dems) sitting on their #$%$ for well over a full day before even requesting U.S. aid (which must be done for a POTUS to act). Typical Dem incompetence or lame attempt to make 43 look bad at victim's expense? I also remember upscale stores in Memphis, Houston, Jackson, Atlanta soon being sold out of big tiicket items (cell phones, entertainment gear) by illegal use of debit cards isued by FEMA. Bad Bush 43 didn't provide these to those poor folk for free.</Msg><Username>yb4itohitsfree</Username><Timestamp>1351730029314</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 20:33:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351730864694-152</Id><Topic><Title>Why Obama Is A Genius</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351720503679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's a very short season on them and a restrictive bag limit. As with the infamous three-pronged quandary.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351730864694</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 20:47:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351730869280-153</Id><Title>Romney - Genius</Title><Msg>That's why he brought Mass down to #47 in job creation.</Msg><Username>vampyrr</Username><Timestamp>1351730869280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 20:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351731208078-154</Id><Topic><Title>Romney - Genius</Title><Username>vampyrr</Username><Timestamp>1351730869280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 20:47:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are So Wrong! Did Your Union Steward Boss Tell You that Nonsense?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351731208078</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 20:53:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351731340363-155</Id><Title>Romney - Genius</Title><Msg>That's why he was able to bring Massachusetts down to position 47 in job creation - #$%$ sounds like mormon</Msg><Username>vampyrr</Username><Timestamp>1351731340363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 20:55:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351731484139-156</Id><Topic><Title>Romney - Genius</Title><Username>vampyrr</Username><Timestamp>1351731340363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 20:55:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vampyr, Redundant, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351731484139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 20:58:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351731693839-157</Id><Topic><Title>Today's numbers in key battleground states.</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1351716754677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:52:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only five days before we get to reelect O'Bama (Irish guy).</Msg><Username>vampyrr</Username><Timestamp>1351731693839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:01:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351732080132-158</Id><Topic><Title>Why Obama is a slow learner</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1351722618756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:30:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You're doing a heckuva job, Brownie."</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1351732080132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:08:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351732551273-159</Id><Topic><Title>Why Obama Is A Genius</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351720503679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CWS2012blah blah Take it easy on the words with more than 2 syllables. This will help you avoid further public humiliation.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1351732551273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:15:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351732640273-160</Id><Topic><Title>Senators Again Urge Obama to Answer Key Questions about Benghazi Attack</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351715434294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:30:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just so I understand your post, you are saying all people who run for the office of President should release their records and be as transparent as they promised 4 years ago. If I understand your post that is what you are saying.</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1351732640273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:17:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351732666966-161</Id><Topic><Title>Senators Again Urge Obama to Answer Key Questions about Benghazi Attack</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351715434294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:30:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Far worse then Watergate</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1351732666966</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351733452624-162</Id><Topic><Title>Why Obama Is A Genius</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351720503679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah,but he's not a SUPER GENIUS like Wile E. Coyote.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351733452624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:30:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351734338126-163</Id><Topic><Title>They Didn't Riot Over THIS Video.....Wonder Why?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351718800215</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:26:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Israel has a sense of humor even though they are really in serious trouble with the Arab Spring. They aren't however saying anything about Allah in this movie. They know how far they can go. The only trouble with Israel is eventually they will loose because the cards are getting stacked against them. Hopefully America will keep supporting them and Mitt Romney will win. They will be better off for another 4 years.</Msg><Username>jlrough</Username><Timestamp>1351734338126</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351736086037-164</Id><Title>Where are they now?</Title><Msg>Those "Occupy Wall Street" protestors.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351736086037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 22:14:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351736412225-165</Id><Topic><Title>Why Obama Is A Genius</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351720503679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz says "I have never encountered an "oblivious oxymoron". No doubt as there is obviously a lot you (and The Raven) have missed (except political brainwashing in public school). I have, however, encountered a few "oblivious more ons" (sp) and that would be you two.</Msg><Username>cws2012wc</Username><Timestamp>1351736412225</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 22:20:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351736642987-166</Id><Topic><Title>Smoking gun</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351736305156</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 22:18:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Obama gets re-elected - this will be the Iran Contra,Watergate,Whitewater/Monica Lewinski scandal every second term President seems to confront. America deserves better.</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1351736642987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 22:24:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351736853396-167</Id><Title>Mitt Romney's Father Marched With MLK</Title><Msg>... Barak O'bama's father followed Karl Marx . The ACORN never falls far from the tree . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351736853396</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 22:27:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351737523688-168</Id><Title>Obama's Benghazi Scandal now spinning out of control!</Title><Msg>Obama Watched Attack on Benghazi and Did Nothing to Help Them It seems that every day there is new information that is coming to light in the September 11 attack on the U.S. Consulate in Benghazi, Libya. In the latest news update, sources are saying that President Barack Obama watched much of the attack on a live broadcast as it was taking place and just sat there doing nothing to help the Americans. When you hear the latest information on how Obama failed to act to save the Americans, it could be seen to lend a little more credibility to the conspiracy theory that the attack was actually a pre-arranged kidnapping attempt set up by Obama and the Muslim Brotherhood. They were supposed to kidnap Ambassador Stevens so that Obama could exchange him for the Blind Sheik just before the election to make Obama look like a hero and allow the Muslim Brotherhood to get their Blind Sheik back. Lt. Col. Tony Shaffer, Retired Army, has told several news media that his sources that he trusts informed him that Obama was in the White House during the time of the attacks and that he watched it unfold in real time. Shaffer told Fox News: “This was in the middle of the business day in Washington, so everybody at the White House, CIA, Pentagon, everybody was watching this go down.” “According to my sources, yes, [President Obama] was one of those in the White House Situation Room in real-time watching this.” Other than placing drones overhead to watch the massacre of four Americans, the President did not issue any orders to send in anyone to help protect them. According to new information contained in the video below, there is evidence that the attack was prolonged and that some of those killed had managed to stay alive for the first six hours of the ordeal. Six hours was plenty of time for Obama to have sent a strike team to Benghazi to help defend the Ambassador and others, but he did nothing but watch.</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1351737523688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 22:38:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351738288403-169</Id><Topic><Title>Why Obama Is A Genius</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351720503679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely and obamer supporters can relax. No need reason to not spend next Tuesday at the track, casino or tavern like usual if your an obamer supporter as he has it in the bag.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1351738288403</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 22:51:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>