<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-29"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346213378079-1</Id><Title>IAM ashamed that no living entity</Title><Msg>has made it past the Earth's orbit and made it back alive since Apolllo 17 beep, beep, n bee -beep yeah team-_hozme3n</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346213378079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 00:09:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346213658280-2</Id><Topic><Title>Neil Armstrong dies . . .</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1345927443000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 16:44:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's PR dept NBC news 1st reported that Neil Young died, who many at NBC news were listening to when man 1st walked on the moon. They were bummed until VP Joe Biden told them it was the bike racer who won the Tour De Luxembourger. Astronaut Neil Young, first man to walk on moon, dies at age 82, read the NBC News headline shortly after 3 pm EST, which was tweeted out and picked up by thousands of others before it was changed. As a refresher, Neil Young is a 66-year-old rock star who is very much alive.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1346213658280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 00:14:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346213755527-3</Id><Topic><Title>IAM ashamed that no living entity</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346213378079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 00:09:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and maybe IAM Amazed you slimey bump, bump, bump I feel free the one-handed bump out of bounds I feel free....</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1346213755527</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 00:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346214577277-4</Id><Title>Only three busted off Alcatraz....</Title><Msg>their bodies never to be found....</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346214577277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 00:29:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346215230883-5</Id><Title>I remember July 19-21, 1969 like it was yesterday:</Title><Msg>beep...</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346215230883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 00:40:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346216034116-6</Id><Topic><Title>I remember July 19-21, 1969 like it was yesterday:</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346215230883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 00:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the sunny-side of the full-moon didn't answer so sent beep, beep there is no way any living being is there beep, beep, n beep beep yeah dear prudence</Msg><Username>here_comes_old_flatop</Username><Timestamp>1346216034116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 00:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346217051389-7</Id><Topic><Title>I remember July 19-21, 1969 like it was yesterday:</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346215230883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 00:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>some say longer than that but then Teddy dove and swam through the 5-knot waters repeadetdly until he lay exhausted on the banks beep... not a living enitinty has made it past the earths orbit and back since apollo 17</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346217051389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 01:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346218442557-8</Id><Topic><Title>New mileage standards would double fuel efficiency</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346207525557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 22:32:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fats, According to scientists, every celestial body (nearly all) in our solar system contains some amount of methane, from which more complex hydrocarbons, such as oil can be produced under pressure. In fact, the Cassini-Huygens mission placed a probe on Saturn's moon Titan as well as additional imaging observations of Titan by Cassini, finding rivers and lakes of methane. No plants and dinosaurs there. Imagine the scenario on earth wherein the so-called vegetation and artifacts of ancient life (the so-called "fossil" sources) were "somehow" shoved below the earth's surface in one single blow that then preserved the carbon material, followed by increasing submersion to depths of 5000 to 15000 miles down in order to pressurize and "cook" the material into oil. Given that the Amazon forest's carbon rich soil is at the very maximum six feet thick and otherwise less, not a substantial future source of oil. Consider also that as the Sahara desert creeps up upon the vegetation of surrounding land, the vegetation disappears into "dust", blown away into nothing. No “future oil” there. No trace of anything that resembled "carbon like". Like what all deserts do. You will find that it takes way more faith to believe in the mystical "fossil fuels" than that God simply placed it there for our use. The "fossil fuel" myth plays well into the hands and hearts of the "peak oil" believers and other behavior control folks that victimize the individual and feeds the wealth of the oil industry and control freak desires of governments. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1346218442557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 01:34:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346218910928-9</Id><Title>I believe we own the moon...</Title><Msg>After 19 minutes of Armstrong's testing, Colonel Aldrin joined him outside the craft. The two men got busy setting up another television camera out from the lunar module, planting an American flag into the ground, scooping up soil and rock samples, deploying scientific experiments and hopping and loping about in a demonstration of their lunar agility. They found walking and working on the moon less taxing than had been forecast. Armstrong once reported he was "very comfortable." And people back on earth found the black-and-white television pictures of the bug-shaped lunar module and the men tramping about it so sharp and clear as to seem unreal, more like a toy and toy-like figures than human beings on the most daring and far-reaching expedition thus far undertaken. after have been checking it out even if I kn ow what i know she said i know what is is like to be dead....</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346218910928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 01:41:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346221127332-10</Id><Title>198% should we get into a fighting war</Title><Msg>threre will be fewer r-money</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346221127332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 02:18:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346225335699-11</Id><Title>Definitely no pets</Title><Msg>should the bison and the great whales disasppear from this earth the the republiconned-fascists 4 bison</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1346225335699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 03:28:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346240210423-12</Id><Topic><Title>Definitely no pets</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1346225335699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 03:28:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what happens when you get bad drugs. Give it time maybe it'll get better! or not</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1346240210423</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 07:36:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346240506000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Rich Daddy Dudes</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1345984991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:43:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do these GOPigs have such an intense hatred of FREEDOM and WOMEN?</Msg><Username>Bebop_Arugula</Username><Timestamp>1346240506000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 07:41:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346240835348-14</Id><Topic><Title>The difference between Harry Reid and Willard Rmoney</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346201892952</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:58:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Boeing will cut the mustard? We will have to wait a long long time. You leftys aren't really in touch with reality, are you?</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1346240835348</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 07:47:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346241239544-15</Id><Topic><Title>New mileage standards would double fuel efficiency</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346207525557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 22:32:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess if Obama commands fuel efficincy to double, then it will just happen. What a great leader he is. No detailed planning needed just a command and it will happen. LOL</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1346241239544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 07:53:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346242217477-16</Id><Title>Why is Boeing buying back their stock, and why is the surge line still not producing 10 airplanes</Title><Msg>So Boeing is maybe, going to buy back their stock, that is because no sharholders want to owne Boeing stock and it is down 3% this year while better stocks like the apple is up 65% ytd and will have two new products out in the next two months . the apple was a 409 dollar stock at the first of this year and now is a 675 dollar stock. the boeng was a73 dollar stock at the start fo the year and is now a 71 dollar stock. well so much for the boeing pumper airplane orders and th surge line well that was supposed to happen years ago. learn to read a financial statment , the actual hole in the cost fo the 787 is 34 billion dollars and the 18 billion that boeing is going to use to buy back boenins shares would be better spent developing the 777x and the 737max, but the greedy top executives want to hold the stock price at the 71 dollar level so they can get more bonus payments. fianlly all you complainers tell me about apple stock going up 65% this year while your boeing stock went down 3% and then go ahead make my day. Boeing said its initial accounting block for the 787 is 1,100 planes, which is the number it expects to sell. It will average out production costs across those 1,100 planes. That avoids a situation where Boeing would have to account for losing money on early, slowly-built planes when it is still learning how to make them efficiently. Boeing now says it will deliver 15 to 20 of its new 787s and 747-8s this year. That's 10 fewer than Boeing's previous estimates. It also said that two-thirds of those deliveries will be the 747-8s. It didn't say why the delivery forecast was cut. So the reason is the parts are not yet made right and cannot be put together on time for the 787, and the 747-8, is a little better now, since that is the two-thirds, however the 747-8 makes much less profit than the smaller planes so once more not a good earnings report. This is Boeings way of printing money without anything to back it up. What you wanted to see was a block of 400 787 planes being used for accounting, like with the 777 This is the information investors should focus on, the usual new block of planes to set costs and profits is 400, not 1100.</Msg><Username>tammyanderson600</Username><Timestamp>1346242217477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 08:10:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346242984000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Rich Daddy Dudes</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1345984991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:43:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. Republicans are not pigs in general. A few, not all, and not nearly as many republicans are pigs as are dumbocrats. 2. Republicans love freedom. 3. Republicans love their women. That's why Republican men marry women instead of men and Republican women marry men instead of women.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1346242984000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 08:23:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346246551300-18</Id><Topic><Title>New mileage standards would double fuel efficiency</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346207525557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 22:32:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Green energy is a corrupt concept of the kooky left, and a total corrupt failure" Hmmmmmmmmm.......Romney likes it. Said he is all for it. Do you ever read what you write? If you did you would realize how utterly ignorant your posts are. Are you saying there is an endless amount of oil available?</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346246551300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 09:22:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346246714244-19</Id><Topic><Title>New mileage standards would double fuel efficiency</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346207525557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 22:32:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I lost you Bob. We got lots of oil yes We got lots of oil no choose one</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346246714244</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 09:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346246981657-20</Id><Topic><Title>The RNC of today could not blow a 10 amp fuse</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346203427018</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 21:23:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another great response from our resident third-grade poster.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1346246981657</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 09:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346249313571-21</Id><Title>MSNBC... Fair and Balanced...NOT</Title><Msg>MSNBC abandons GOP convention during every speech by a minority Published: 11:18 PM 08/28/2012 By Jeff Poor Bio | Archive | Email Jeff Poor BEVERLY HILLS, CA - AUGUST 02: (L-R) President of MSNBC Phil Griffin, host of 'The Rachel Maddow Show' Rachel Maddow, host of 'The Last Word' Lawrence O' Donnell and host of 'Hardball' Chris Matthews speak during the 'MSNBC' panel during the NBC Universal portion of the 2011 Summer TCA Tour held at the Beverly Hilton Hotel on August 2, 2011 in Beverly Hills, California. (Photo by Frederick M. Brown/Getty Images) One of the left’s favorite attacks on the Republican Party is that it is the party of old white people, devoid of diversity and probably racist. If you were watching MSNBC’s coverage of the Republican National Convention in Tampa on Tuesday night, you might believe those assertions, since missing from the coverage was nearly every ethnic minority that spoke during Tuesday’s festivities. In lieu of airing speeches from former Democratic Rep. Artur Davis, a black American; Mia Love, a black candidate for the U.S. House of Representatives from Utah; and Texas senatorial hopeful Ted Cruz, a Latino American, MSNBC opted to show commentary anchored by Rachel Maddow from Rev. Al Sharpton, Ed Schultz, Chris Matthews, Chris Hayes and Steve Schmidt. Throughout this convention, Matthews has accused the Republicans of playing dog-whistle racist politics while on scene in Tampa. It isn’t clear, however, if Matthews will hurl accusations of racism at Davis, Love or Cruz for speeches his network failed to broadca</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346249313571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346249538292-22</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC... Fair and Balanced...NOT</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346249313571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:08:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>blah blah blah did you happen to notice Fox News did the same thing.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1346249538292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346249598357-23</Id><Title>Gas Prices Close to All Time Highs.... Thanks, Obama.</Title><Msg>Hurricane Isaac and a deadly blast at Venezuela’s Amuay refinery pushed gasoline to an almost four- month high and threatened to revive a debate about energy costs in the run-up to the presidential election in November. Futures jumped yesterday in New York as Isaac forced closures of Gulf Coast refineries and reduced rates at others. That market is also reeling from an Aug. 25 explosion in Venezuela that killed at least 48 people and closed the country’s largest fuel-making plant. Futures are up 23 percent since their 2012 settlement low of $2.5501 a gallon on June 21. Retail prices for regular grade increased 0.6 cent to $3.756 a gallon yesterday, the highest level since May 7, according to AAA, the largest U.S. motoring group. Photographer: Brent Lewin/Bloomberg Prices at the pump will be the highest ever for the U.S. Labor Day holiday, AAA said yesterday. The surge reignites an issue that has pitted President Barack Obama, who has called for the elimination of billions of dollars of subsidies enjoyed by the oil and gas industry, against the presumptive Republican nominee Mitt Romney. It also spurs speculation that Obama will release supplies from the Strategic Petroleum Reserve to ease prices for consumers. “Given this administration’s belligerent rhetoric against the oil industry, it’s going to be very easy for Romney to pin the blame on Obama,” said Stephen Schork, president of Schork Group Inc., a consulting firm in Villanova, Pennsylvania. “The White House will be on the defensive. It makes an SPR release likely sooner rather than later.” Gasoline for September delivery advanced 7.68 cents, or 2.5 percent, to $3.1548 a gallon yesterday on the New York Mercantile Exchange, the highest level since April 30. Futures fell 2.87 cents, or 0.9 percent, to settle at $3.1261 today. Retail Prices Retail prices for regular grade increased 0.6 cent to $3.756 a gallon yesterday, the highest level since May 7, according to AAA, the largest U.S. motoring group. Gasoline at the pump cost $4.138 in California yesterday, $4.008 in Connecticut and $3.973 in New York.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346249598357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:13:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346249953378-24</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC... Fair and Balanced...NOT</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346249313571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:08:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, Fox, ABC, and NBC all covered the GOP speakers.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346249953378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:19:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346250132121-25</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Boeing buying back their stock, and why is the surge line still not producing 10 airplanes</Title><Username>tammyanderson600</Username><Timestamp>1346242217477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 08:10:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fred? Why did you change your handle? Yahoo find you out, eh?</Msg><Username>makboe</Username><Timestamp>1346250132121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:22:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346250240836-26</Id><Title>Obama Administration Caught Lying Again!</Title><Msg>Who are the American People going to believe? A SEAL on the actual mission or the Lying Obama Administration... Obama keeps getting caught telling lies. SEAL Book Says Bin Laden Was Unarmed, Killed Outside His Bedroom DASHIELL BENNETT 6:39 AM ET Several news outlets have finally got their hands on a copy of the new book about the raid on Osama bin Laden's Pakistan compound, and the details emerging contradict many of the earlier reports about what happened inside the house on the night the al Qaeda leader was killed. No Easy Day is set to be released September 11, but The Huffington Post's Marcus Baram picked up a preview copy in a used bookstore, which is a common way to find pre-released books. The Associated Press bought a copy as well. The book, written by ex-Navy SEAL Matt Bissonnette (under the pseudonym Mark Owen), is a first-person account of the raid on the Abbottabad compound where bin Laden had been in hiding for years. According Bissonnette's version of events, there was no extended firefight between SEAL Team 6 members and bodyguards and bin Laden himself never got the chance to confront or even see the soldiers before they killed him. Instead, he was shot in the hallway outside of his bedroom, then "disappeared into the dark room." By the time the soldiers entered, he was already dying of wounds to the head. Bissonnette says he and another team member then shot him several more times in the chest to ensure he was dead. The book also says that while there were two guns found in bin Laden's room, neither was loaded and he never had a chance to defend himself. Bissonnette even calls him a #$%$ for not being prepared to defend or kill himself. Even though bin Laden was killed without resisting, the SEAL were instructed beforehand that it was not an assassination mission and that bin Laden should have been brought back alive, if possible. Bissonnette is also critical of President Obama in his story, saying that no one on the team was a fan of the president and that they believed he and other leaders would inflate their own roles in the story. Even before the raid began, the SEALs joked about how they would help Obama get re-elected and also speculated about who would play them in the Hollywood movie. Despite their personal feelings about Obama, however, the SEALs did agree that he made the right call, saying "Although we applauded the decision-making in this case, there was no doubt in anybody’s mind that he would take all the political credit for this too.” They also complained that after a White House meeting with Obama and Vice President Joe Biden ("he reminded me of someone’s drunken uncle at Christmas dinner") the President invited them to return some other time for a beer, but that call never came.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346250240836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346250457978-27</Id><Topic><Title>The Vulture/Voucher Ticket</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346169827875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 12:03:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FACTS TO CLEAR UP THE #$%$ ABOUT JO#$%$! The economy was in “FREE FALL” as Bush was leaving! The American people were losing 8OO,OOO+ JO#$%$/Month 6,OOO,OOO JO#$%$ were lost In just 15 months under BUSH</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346250457978</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:27:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346250465130-28</Id><Title>Obama is leading America to Recovery</Title><Msg>... The other side led us into war and a recession.. !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346250465130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:27:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346250566000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Rich Daddy Dudes</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1345984991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:43:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>u r an insulting little POS and wrong 100% of the time</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346250566000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:29:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346250843438-30</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is leading America to Recovery</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346250465130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Almost 3 Straight Years the economy and JOBS has been growing 4,OOO,OOO+ JOBS ADDED in 27 months Obama Policies have helped the middle class; education, manufacturing, science and research, Medicare, debt reduction, tax rates, health care, consumer protection, college aid, energy. +4,OOO,OOO OBAMA JOB ADDITIONS 2010 TO 2012 - 6,OOO,OOO BUSH REPUB JOB L0SS 2008 &amp; 2009 _____________________ JUST THE FACTS! Bureau of Labor Statistics 1,O64,OOO JOBS ADDED IN 7 Months IN 2012 OBAMA ERA 1,84O,OOO JOBS ADDED IN 2011 OBAMA ERA 1,O27,OOO JOBS ADDED IN 2010 OBAMA ERA 4,OOO,OOO+ JOBS ADDED IN 30 MONTHS - OBAMA SUMMARY ______________ -3,6O3,OOO JOBS LOST in 2008 BUSH ERA -2,341,OOO JOBS LOST in 1st QUARTER 2009 BUSH ERA! 6,OOO,OOO or so JOBS LOST IN 15 MONTHS - BUSH SUMMARY ________________________</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1346250843438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:34:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346250845469-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is leading America to Recovery</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346250465130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd like to know your definition of a recovery , with all of the people out of work . I feel sorry for anyone who feels we have to settle for less and this is the best we can do, with all of the debt and destruction this administration has piled on us.</Msg><Username>thruston</Username><Timestamp>1346250845469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346250896726-32</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Administration Caught Lying Again!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346250240836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why should you be surprised.</Msg><Username>thruston</Username><Timestamp>1346250896726</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:34:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346250969446-33</Id><Topic><Title>The difference between Harry Reid and Willard Rmoney</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346201892952</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:58:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope you are wrong for the sake of our country.</Msg><Username>thruston</Username><Timestamp>1346250969446</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:36:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346251144000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Rich Daddy Dudes</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1345984991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:43:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES! The BA message board jihad pays us MILLIONS! Thinking of putting the money in an offshore bank account to avoid taxes, just like Mitt!</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1346251144000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346251193963-35</Id><Topic><Title>How Good is the Ryan Medicare Voucher Plan</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1346168697688</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 11:44:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you aware of all of the very bad stuff that is in the Obamacare bill that no body ever read and will affect every American in ways that they could not have imagined. You had better pray that Obamacare does not pass.</Msg><Username>thruston</Username><Timestamp>1346251193963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:39:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346251223000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Rich Daddy Dudes</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1345984991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:43:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good one</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346251223000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:40:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346251316408-37</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan, the next Veep, Hammers Obama!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1345663581000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-22 15:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wait until Ryan debates Biden. All of America will be able to separate the men from the boys and will know who lifts America up and who pulls America down.</Msg><Username>thruston</Username><Timestamp>1346251316408</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:41:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346251393872-38</Id><Topic><Title>Romney and Ryan... Soaring in the Pools...</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346197091230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 19:38:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great! Wait until all of those independents without jobs or hope of a job go to the polls. Great for Romney and Ryan.</Msg><Username>thruston</Username><Timestamp>1346251393872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346251490556-39</Id><Topic><Title>democrats diverting the issues</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1346190425955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 17:47:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People will not vote first on social issues. It is economic issues that will determine this election and even if it is social issues, women who can get abortions but cannot get jobs don't help the Democrats diverters.</Msg><Username>thruston</Username><Timestamp>1346251490556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:44:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346251527981-40</Id><Topic><Title>The RNC of today could not blow a 10 amp fuse</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346203427018</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 21:23:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Notice that the replies do not line up to the post you are repling to. They sure screwed up the format.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1346251527981</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:45:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346251658340-41</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is leading America to Recovery</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346250465130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unemployment is Higher under Obama than anytime under W. It is a fact...Google for yourself. Unemployment continues to be above 8%... Obama said he would NOT run again if Unemployment remained that high under his watch... he lied again!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346251658340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:47:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346251717384-42</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is leading America to Recovery</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346250465130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thruston - what destruction are you referring to.?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346251717384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346252141664-43</Id><Topic><Title>The Vulture/Voucher Ticket</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346169827875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 12:03:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The official 2012 Repub Party platform is a far-right fever dream, a compilation of pouting, posturing and policies to meet just about every demand from the overlapping Religious Money Worshippers, Baggers, corporate, and neo-conservative war party wings of the GOP.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346252141664</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:55:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346252585714-44</Id><Title>Republican lawmakers discriminated against minorities!!</Title><Msg>SAN ANTONIO (AP) — Stadiums and hospitals removed from the districts of black congressional members and country clubs newly drawn into those of white incumbents. A lawyer emailing "No bueno" to a Republican staffer about plans that risked leaving a paper trail and jeopardizing the legality of a voting map. Those were among the evidence a Washington federal court used to determine that Texas Republican lawmakers discriminated against minorities while drawing new political boundaries, throwing out the maps as violations of the Voting Rights Act but likely not in time to affect the November elections. The decision Tuesday by the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia is instead likely to reverberate in 2014, when some Texans could find their congressional and statehouse districts changed for the third time in five years. The long-awaited ruling was hailed as a sweeping victory by minority rights groups that sued the state after the Republican-controlled Legislature pushed through new redistricting maps last year. Texas Attorney General Greg Abbott called the decision "flawed" and vowed to appeal to the U.S. Supreme Court. "Better late than never," said Luis Vera, attorney for the League of United Latin American Citizens, one of the groups that sued the state. "It's a hell of a victory."</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346252585714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 11:03:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346253726205-45</Id><Topic><Title>Republican lawmakers discriminated against minorities!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346252585714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 11:03:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if they nominated Anne they might have a chance. Is fat #$%$ christie responsible for some of the starvation in the world? Kamakure</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1346253726205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 11:22:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346255619982-46</Id><Topic><Title>The Vulture/Voucher Ticket</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346169827875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 12:03:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have been watching MSNBC and reading the Democratic Underground way to long..... Obama is sinking in the polls!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346255619982</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 11:53:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346256407199-47</Id><Title>South Carolina offers boeing minimum wage workers and busts unions</Title><Msg>I guess that was good for us stock holders, but I thought that was a little strange to be bragging about in an election, aren't low wages the problem.</Msg><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1346256407199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 12:06:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346257433669-48</Id><Title>Sane Plan to pay down the National Debt</Title><Msg>We need a way to pay it without robbing people! The United States government imposes a Medicare tax of 2.9% on wages received by an employee and on business or farming income earned by self-employed individuals. Starting in the year 2013, Medicare taxes will be increased to 3.8% and expanded to cover both wage income and investment income for higher-income individuals. This can be increased to 4% or 5% Social Security FICA Tax Just remove the ridiculous top cap! Defense Spending Just phase in to cap it at 2.5 times what the number 2 country spends! NOTE: The number 2 Country is Communist China so surely a Capitalist System with more than double to spend should keep us safe! Cancel the tax cuts and credits recently gifted the top one percent and we should have a surplus in a few years!</Msg><Username>natsu4fun</Username><Timestamp>1346257433669</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 12:23:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346257989000-49</Id><Topic><Title>Rich Daddy Dudes</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1345984991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:43:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>waaaaaaaaaa I am demfascist the cry baby......waaaa waaa waaa</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1346257989000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 12:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346258261000-50</Id><Topic><Title>American Families ARE Getting Poorer</Title><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346168379000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 11:39:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Umm, 'cause Obama kept the Iraq war going on for no good reason, and expanded the Aghanistan war for no good reason, and maintains 1000 military bases in 130 countries for no good rason and throws $800 billion in irresponsible mad money at the military. Military expenditures are inherently inflationary because they reduce available money and credit, and they provide no useful goods and services. Our economy is in much worse shape that you'd think. If not for all that military inflationary pressure, we'd be in a deflationary spiral!</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1346258261000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 12:37:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346258398446-51</Id><Topic><Title>New mileage standards would double fuel efficiency</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346207525557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 22:32:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Burger, The point I was trying to make is that the oil is not necessarily from "fossils", just as the abundant methane on Saturn's moon Titan is not from ancient plant and animal life. Calling it "fossil fuel" gives the allusion of being finite. While the earth's molten core is primarily made of iron, according to the American Geophysical Union, studies show that carbon is present in the core, which is also abundant in the universe. That is also be true of the lower and upper mantles. A volcanic eruption also emits hydrogen sulfide. Therefore, at some level, hydrogen is in ample supply along the way. Methane consists of hydrogen and carbon. Further, geologists and energy companies are finding incredible amounts of natural gas today that is trapped underground – estimated to be good for 200 years. Thus, the natural gas price collapse of late. With that established, and the fact of methane being present in the celestial bodies throughout the solar system, here is the concept: that oil is derived not from once buried organic material but derived from some process that occurs at the interface of the core and the mantle – between the molten and the cooler, solid materials. And, likely, initially as only simple hydrocarbon compounds, methane, and ultimately, under pressure and transitional cooling, into more complex compounds that are sometimes "light, sweet oil" or "heavy, sulfur laden oil". OK, that is what “abiotic oil” is about. Your question, “are we running out or not”? I doubt it. Is it being “replenished” fast enough? Maybe, maybe not. I believe that it never had anything to do with “fossils” but that is just an opinion. The abiotic process makes way more sense to me – given the incredible unlikelihood of sufficient organic material spontaneously being buried for preservation millions of years ago – all over the planet - and then pushed to the depths necessary to impose heat and pressure and conversion to oil. Now, in my previous post, I said that I believe God put it there and for a reason. Why? He made two commands to mankind at his creation: 1) “be fruitful and multiply” (i.e., have lots of kids); and 2) “subdue the earth” (use, not abuse, the earth). The second command supports the first. So, if one believes that, how does that play with “running out of oil” which is essential to our existence today? Unless, the end is near, God knowing just how much oil is available. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1346258398446</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 12:39:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346259370679-52</Id><Topic><Title>The Vulture/Voucher Ticket</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1346169827875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 12:03:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush must have been clearing brush with all his job creator backers who didn't create a single job during his failed administration..love the republican amnesia..like we all didn't live through two wars paid on the credit card, huge jobs losses, huge job outsourcing, an unfunded drug program, an education program that was built on a lie,and didn't work, outing a CIA agent, lying to the UN, congress, and the American people.</Msg><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1346259370679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 12:56:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346259641130-53</Id><Topic><Title>New mileage standards would double fuel efficiency</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346207525557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 22:32:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Burger, The point I was trying to make is that the oil is not necessarily from "fossils", just as the abundant methane on Saturn's moon Titan is not from ancient plant and animal life. Calling it "fossil fuel" gives the allusion of being finite. While the earth's molten core is primarily made of iron, according to the American Geophysical Union, studies show that carbon is present in the core, which is also abundant in the universe. That is also be true of the lower and upper mantles. A volcanic eruption also emits hydrogen sulfide. Therefore, at some level, hydrogen is in ample supply along the way. Methane consists of hydrogen and carbon. Further, geologists and energy companies are finding incredible amounts of natural gas today that is trapped underground – estimated to be good for 200 years. Thus, the natural gas price collapse of late. With that established, and the fact of methane being present in the celestial bodies throughout the solar system, here is the concept: that oil is derived not from once buried organic material but derived from some process that occurs at the interface of the core and the mantle – between the molten and the cooler, solid materials. And, likely, initially as only simple hydrocarbon compounds, methane, and ultimately, under pressure and transitional cooling, into more complex compounds that are sometimes "light, sweet oil" or "heavy, sulfur laden oil". OK, that is what “abiotic oil” is about. Your question, “are we running out or not”? I doubt it. Is it being “replenished” fast enough? Maybe, maybe not. I believe that it never had anything to do with “fossils” but that is just an opinion. The abiotic process makes way more sense to me – given the incredible unlikelihood of sufficient organic material spontaneously being buried for preservation millions of years ago – all over the planet - and then pushed to the depths necessary to impose heat and pressure and conversion to oil. Now, in my previous post, I said that I believe God put it there and for a reason. Why? He made two commands to mankind at his creation: 1) “be fruitful and multiply” (i.e., have lots of kids); and 2) “subdue the earth” (use, not abuse, the earth). The second command supports the first. So, if one believes that, how does that play with “running out of oil” which is essential to our existence today? Unless, the end is near, God knowing just how much oil is available. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1346259641130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:00:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346261045705-54</Id><Topic><Title>South Carolina offers boeing minimum wage workers and busts unions</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1346256407199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 12:06:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually the real problem is Obama's lack of creating any Jobs for anyone, less alone, "low wages" as you post. The hard working Boeing employees in SC are very happy with their wages and even more happy to have a job! SC workers will shame the Washington workers in efficiency and Quality in short time. Obama is a job destroyer... Unemployment over 8% for over three years... Pathetic Black Unemployment at 18%... they palm to stay home this November!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346261045705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346261195822-55</Id><Topic><Title>South Carolina offers boeing minimum wage workers and busts unions</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1346256407199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 12:06:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing is in North Carolina and in their contract renewal that was signed 9 months early, Boeing agreed to keep new 737 line in Puget Sound. Also Boeing renewed 20 year lease on Boeing field.</Msg><Username>tami_sue</Username><Timestamp>1346261195822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:26:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346261200301-56</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is leading America to Recovery</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346250465130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- the fact is; - the referring destruction is Only inside the head of Republicons.!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346261200301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:26:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346261333430-57</Id><Topic><Title>New mileage standards would double fuel efficiency</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346207525557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 22:32:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama and his minions in the WH are nothing but pathological liars... Unemployment at record levels as are gasoline prices It's the Economy, Stupid, err, Obama.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346261333430</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346261925865-58</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is leading America to Recovery</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346250465130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now that's really a funny post! LMAO</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1346261925865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:38:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346262100322-59</Id><Title>Liberal Media in Meltdown as Romney Soars in the Polls!</Title><Msg>Yahoo News fires David Chalian 79 Comments (54) By DYLAN BYERS | 8/29/12 1:26 PM EDT TAMPA, Fla. -- Yahoo News has fired Washington bureau chief David Chalian after he was caught on a hot-mic during an online video broadcast today saying that Mitt Romney and his wife Ann had no problem with African Americans suffering as a result of Hurricane Isaac, a source familiar with the situation tells POLITICO. "They're not concerned at all. They're happy to have a party with black people drowning," Chalian said during the ABC News/Yahoo News webcast, in reference to the fact that the GOP convention in Tampa is taking place as Hurricane Isaac makes landfall on the north Gulf coast. The conservative media watchdog organization NewsBusters first posted audio of Chalian's remarks, but referred to him as an ABC News employee (and offered slightly inaccurate transcription). ABC News spokesperson Julie Townsend informed the organization that Chalian was with Yahoo. Chalian and Yahoo News spokesperson Kristen Morquecho did not respond to requests for comment; Townsend also did not respond to a request for comment. (ABC News, where Chalian was political director until 2010, has partnered with Yahoo News for 2012 political coverage). UPDATE (1:30 p.m.): Yahoo News confirms: "David Chalian's statement was inappropriate and does not represent the views of Yahoo!. He has been terminated effective immediately. We have already reached out to the Romney campaign, and we apologize to Mitt Romney, his staff, their supporters and anyone who was offended."</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346262100322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346262229526-60</Id><Title>Liberal Media Acting Like a bunch of Buffoons!</Title><Msg>Brian Ross Does It Again ABC Reporter Who Botched Shooter Identity MisIdentifies Yacht Flag BY: Washington Free Beacon Staff August 29, 2012 1:13 pm ABC News reported Wednesday that a group of Romney donors gathered on a yacht flying the Cayman flag. One problem: The flag is not the flag of the Cayman Islands. It is the flag of Bermuda. Among the three reporters bylined on the story is Brian Ross, who suggested on live television that the James Holmes who murdered a dozen moviegoers in July could be a Tea Party member named Jim Holmes. Ross later apologized. Update 1:31 p.m.: According to Charter World, the yacht is officially registered in the Caymans; its home port is in Fort Lauderdale. ABC reports the flag the yacht is flying is the Cayman flag; the flag is the Bermudan flag, however. It is unclear why the yacht is flying a Bermudan flag.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346262229526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:43:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346262629444-61</Id><Title>Republicans: 'This is how we feed animals'</Title><Msg>Two people were ejected from the Republican National Convention when they threw nuts at a black CNN camera woman and said "this is how we feed animals," the network said Wednesday. "CNN can confirm there was an incident directed at an employee inside the Tampa Bay Times Forum" on Tuesday, the opening day of a gala at which former Massachusetts governor Mitt Romney will accept his party's nomination to challenge President Barack Obama in November's election. "CNN worked with convention officials to address this matter and will have no further comment." Several witnesses observed the exchange, CNN reported, and convention security personnel immediately removed the two people from the forum. The convention confirmed the incident in a statement late Tuesday. "Two attendees tonight exhibited deplorable behavior. Their conduct was inexcusable and unacceptable. This kind of behavior will not be tolerated," organizers said. The incident is surely not what Republicans wanted 10 weeks out from the election. Romney has struggled to attract African American voters as well as Hispanics, and he is also on the wrong side of the gender gap, with polls consistently showing women voters preferring Obama to Romney. Current TV journalist and talk radio host David Shuster first tweeted about the incident Tuesday night. "GOP attendee ejected for throwing nuts at African American CNN camera woman + saying 'This is how we feed animals,'" Shuster posted on Twitter.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346262629444</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:50:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346262797112-62</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans: 'This is how we feed animals'</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346262629444</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:50:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Obama treats the Black community with an 18% Unemployment Rate... and that's Pathetic! They will stay home in November... tired of being taken for granted!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346262797112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346263176788-63</Id><Topic><Title>South Carolina offers boeing minimum wage workers and busts unions</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1346256407199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 12:06:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You Liberal nitwit, the second 787 Final assy line is located in Charlestown, SC! Geez, you Liberals need to investigate your Public schools.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346263176788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:59:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346263250560-64</Id><Title>Happy days are here again...</Title><Msg>at the RNC.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1346263250560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 14:00:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346263709000-65</Id><Title>Americans Getting Poorer &amp; Poorer</Title><Msg>Income DOWN &amp; don't overlook INFLATION What can you expect when you export the Money, Tech &amp; JOBS to the Commie Wage-Slaves? And then import those SLAVERY produced products? Our Government, Our Politicians DO NOTHING as they Represent the Business leaders who have the profits from the wage-slave imports to "reward" the Elected, Appointed &amp; Bureaucrats. ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Average U.S. Household Has Lost 5% in Annual Income Since Economic “Recovery” Began Back to News inShare0Monday, August 27, 2012 The rich are getting richer, and the poor really are getting poorer. According to a new report, Americans are earning less today on average than they were when the Great Recession, which began in December 2007, ended in June 2009. Using Census Bureau data, economists Gordon Green and John Coder determined that real median household income has actually fallen by 4.8% since the recession’s end. Even more surprisingly, they found that the decline since June 2009 was larger than the 2.6 percent decline that occurred during the recession. Adding them together, Green and Coder conclude that average household income has fallen 7.2% since December 2007. con't ........ http://www.allgov.com/news/top-stories/average-us-household-has-lost-5-in-annual-income-since-economic-recovery-began-120827?news=845126</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346263709000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 14:08:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346263901000-66</Id><Topic><Title>Americans Getting Poorer &amp; Poorer</Title><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346263709000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 14:08:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sentier PDF press release: http://www.sentierresearch.com/pressreleases/Sentier_PressRelease_PostRecessionaryHouseholdIncomeChange_June09toJune12_08_23_12.pdf</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346263901000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 14:11:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346264649000-67</Id><Topic><Title>Rich Daddy Dudes</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1345984991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:43:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;i'm not dependent on other people for my care and feeding either Well with the exception of the people that produce road kill from time to time. And let's not forget the free diapers that you find laying around in your trailer court.</Msg><Username>yupitsmedex2004</Username><Timestamp>1346264649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 14:24:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346267606682-68</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Media Acting Like a bunch of Buffoons!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346262229526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:43:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Liberal Media is acting like a bunch of buffoons, because they are a bunch of buffoons.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1346267606682</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 15:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346269871604-69</Id><Topic><Title>Gas Prices Close to All Time Highs.... Thanks, Obama.</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346249598357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a result of supply and demand you fool. Obama has virtually nothing to do with it. I thought you guys loved the "free market". Hypocrite ...</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1346269871604</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 15:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346270226717-70</Id><Topic><Title>Gas Prices Close to All Time Highs.... Thanks, Obama.</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346249598357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kinda like you guys blaming W for everything... "what goes around, comes around" Funny to watch your hypocrisy...</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346270226717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 15:57:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346270495827-71</Id><Title>Wow, Fox News had Larger Ratings than ABC, CNN, and MSNBC Combined</Title><Msg>... on the GOP Convention coverage Tuesday night. The true message is getting to the American People and that's a good thing!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346270495827</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 16:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346270814655-72</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Media in Meltdown as Romney Soars in the Polls!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346262100322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Corzine's motto is take what you can and give nothing back! It appears to have worked for him and it doesn't seem that Obama and Holder have much of a problem with it either. Oh yes, Wasn't Corzine a Lib politician before he became a successful crook?</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1346270814655</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 16:06:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346270977756-73</Id><Title>"Make My Day", Riding into Tampa... Destroying Obama!</Title><Msg>Clint will Poke Obama is the eye! Exclusive: Clint Eastwood Headed to Tampa for RNC Guy Benson Political Editor Aug 29, 2012 03:04 AM EST A well-placed Republican source tells Townhall that Oscar-winning director and actor Clint Eastwood will travel to Tampa, Florida to attend Mitt Romney's nominating convention this week. As the news media scrambles to identify the so-called "mystery speaker" scheduled to address GOP delegates on Thursday evening, some have speculated that the iconic Hollywood figure could fit the bill. Our source -- who spoke on the condition of anonymity -- could not confirm if Eastwood is, in fact, the intriguing "to-be-announced" speaker, but stated unequivocally that the Dirty Harry star will arrive in Florida late on Wednesday or early on Thursday, and will return to southern California on Friday. Eastwood endorsed Romney earlier this month and backed Sen. John McCain's presidential bid in 2008. He also attracted political buzz when he cut a controversial Super Bowl ad for Chrysler earlier this year, which some viewed as a tacit message in favor of President Obama. If he is the RNC mystery man, Eastwood would address Republican delegates just prior to Sen. Marco Rubio's introduction of Romney in primetime on Thursday night. Will Clint Eastwood make Mitt Romney's day? Stay tuned...</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346270977756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 16:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346271874223-74</Id><Topic><Title>New mileage standards would double fuel efficiency</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346207525557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 22:32:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>harrydokes is on auto pilot - a broken record with no one home!!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1346271874223</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 16:24:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346274846929-75</Id><Title>Obama Plays Golf While Americans Suffer...</Title><Msg>...as the UnEmployment Rate Stays Above 8% Nationally and at 18% for African Americans and Gasoline prices Soar! We need a Change in Pennsylvania Avenue... we will get the change in November. McConnell: Obama prepping for PGA, not presidency TAMPA, Fla. - Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell, who has been prosecuting a two-year case against Barack Obama's reelection, charges in his Republican Convention speech Wednesday night that the president has spent more time practicing for a golf tournament than fixing the nation's ills. "For four years, Barack Obama has been running from the nation's problems. He hasn't been working to earn reelection. He's been working to earn a spot on the PGA tour," the sometimes tart-tongued McConnell says, according to excerpts provided to Secrets. What's more, he adds, the president hasn't spelled out what he would do in a second term. "We know what the president's got on his iPod, but we don't know what he plans to do about a looming tax hike that could trigger yet another serious recession that would result in even more Americans losing their jobs. Ladies and gentlemen: America cannot afford another four years of this." The Senate leader has been rapped by Democrats for being so tough on Obama and for his early-on public call to defeat the president. But those criticisms haven't quieted the Kentucky lawmaker. In fact his convention speech steps it up a notch. "As we meet here tonight, America is suffering through an economic calamity of truly historic dimensions. Some are calling it the slowest recovery in our nation's entire 236-year history. To call this a recovery is an insult to recoveries," he says. And of the policies the president has pushed so far, McConnell says that they are out of touch with the mainstream of American life and further damaging the economy. "What this administration has in mind for America isn't a renewal, it's a great leveling out. It wants the kind of government-imposed equality that in a single generation transformed Western Europe from a place where for centuries high achievement and discovery and innovation were celebrated and prized, to a place where they have elections about whether people should have to work. Where they make promises they can't keep and write checks they can't cash." McConnell also gives a full-throated endorsement to Mitt Romney. "When Mitt Romney looks down the road, he sees a country that's ready for a comeback. I firmly believe he's the man to lead it," says McConnell. On Tuesday, convention keynote speaker New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie was criticized by some for not giving a similar strong endorsement of Romney.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346274846929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 17:14:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346277896000-76</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346266842000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 15:00:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True enough, but Obama kept the wheels spinning in the ditch by keeping bloated military budgets and continuing illegal, stupid wars.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1346277896000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346281861557-77</Id><Topic><Title>How Romney Keeps Lying Through His Big White Teeth</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346280266430</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:44:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Racist!</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1346281861557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 19:11:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346282375995-78</Id><Title>High Unemployment and Soaring Gasoline Prices will Doom Obama!</Title><Msg>Obama should have kept his word and not run for a second term with these outrageously HIGH Unemployment rates! Obama and his Administration are nothing but a bunch of liars... that's all Liberals have to run on, eh? The African American Unemployment rate is at 18%... they will stay home in protest this November!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346282375995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 19:19:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346282599336-79</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Ladies Say Never Mind Wage Equity and Birth Control Access</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346280034829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:40:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, the African American Community wants to know why under Obama the Unemployment rates for Blacks sits at 18%... way,way higher than under W.... Obama has FAILED American and his African American Community</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346282599336</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 19:23:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346282747000-80</Id><Topic><Title>American Families ARE Getting Poorer</Title><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346168379000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 11:39:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So if 5% of GDP is negligible, then why are you so uptight about social programs that actually make the world a better place? You're a hypocrite.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1346282747000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 19:25:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346282810162-81</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346279210566</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:26:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama will get crushed in November as Libs watch in horror as Obama's lead dwindles! Unemployment at record Highs as well as Gasoline Prices....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346282810162</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 19:26:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346283190317-82</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan and the GOP's New "Dog Whistle Politics"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346283012855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 19:30:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Snore... no credits or anything.. Dik, you are a flaming Liberal Idiot! Mitt and Paul will Crush Obama and the Buffoon, VP</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346283190317</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 19:33:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346285532638-83</Id><Topic><Title>8-27 status</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346165825412</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 10:57:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a 777 was delivered on the 28th. two 737's were delivered on the 29th Tomorrow and Friday should have a number of deliveries. Cathay Pacific 747 had a customer flight yesterday.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346285532638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:12:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346285730208-84</Id><Title>McCain Hammers Obama on Foreign Policy...Leaks,</Title><Msg>Obama has to be squirming to hear such truths, inconvenient truths, about his pathetic, shamefull lack of leadership! Slams Obama on his leaks of National Security Leaks for personal gain and his impotent response to Iran! The ineffective Obama and his Buffoon VP will swirl down the toilet in November! Obama has been one big turd! Time to flush the trash.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346285730208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346285801137-85</Id><Topic><Title>New mileage standards would double fuel efficiency</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346207525557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 22:32:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you're that enthusiastic about Obama's planned increase to 54miles/gal., why don't you purchase a scooter to get you around town?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1346285801137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:16:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346286321928-86</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Media Acting Like a bunch of Buffoons!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346262229526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:43:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm getting the feeling that our illegal immigrant president won't be talking about the real issues that Americans are calling for at the DNC because of the list of speakers that will be there to speak. I don't think #$%$h-s will be talking about jobs and the economy.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1346286321928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:25:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346286357606-87</Id><Topic><Title>McCain Hammers Obama on Foreign Policy...Leaks,</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346285730208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:15:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We heard the War Drums Loudly Pounded by McCain and will not give up our Medicare and Social Security "assistance" to pay for the Cost Plus Iran and Syria War the Neocons want!</Msg><Username>natsu4fun</Username><Timestamp>1346286357606</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:25:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346286452474-88</Id><Title>Obama is a Shameful Lying President!</Title><Msg>SEAL tells 60 Minutes book is for honor, not politics inShare 3More Watch the Segment » (CBS News) A retired Navy SEAL who was present at the killing of Osama bin Laden tells Scott Pelley in a 60 Minutes interview that his book about the raid is not a political statement, rather it is timed to commemorate the 9/11 attack and give credit to the hundreds of people whose work made the mission a success. The former SEAL Team 6 member, who uses the pseudonym Mark Owen, will appear in his first interview on 60 Minutes, Sunday Sept. 9 at 7:00 p.m. ET/PT. As a security measure, CBS News will not identify "Owen" in any reports about his account of the raid; his face and voice were disguised for his 60 Minutes interview. His book about the raid, "No Easy Day," will be available next week. The following is an excerpt that appeared on the CBS Evening News with Scott Pelley: He calls himself Mark Owen. That's not his real name. We've disguised him and will keep his name confidential for his own safety. Owen was on the helicopter that crashed in bin Laden's compound. He was the second man in the room when bin Laden was shot, he took the photographs of the body that were never released. But Owen told us the story is not about him -- it's the story of hundreds of Americans who spent years gathering intelligence, planning and training of the SEALs, Owen says, "We just took care of the last 40 minutes." We built what we believe is the most accurate model of bin Laden's compound ever constructed. Owen told us, before the mission, a full size replica of the compound was built in the United States for training and there was a dress rehearsal for the top brass including the chairman of the joint chiefs, Admiral Mike Mullen, and Admiral Eric Olsen, head of Special Operations Command. Scott Pelley: How did that rehearsal go? Mark Owen: It was fine. This is nothing new to us. The part that was new was all the VIPs sitting there watching. One of the things that I like after the fact was-- I remember Admiral Mullen coming by and talking to each one of us and then Admiral Olsen as well. And I thought that was cool that, you know, they walked by, shook each of our hands, and said, "Hey, are you guys ready? Can you guys pull this off?" And I'm pretty sure to a man we all said, "Yes, absolutely." Scott Pelley: How long was it before you got the call to go? Mark Owen: We had a week off in Virginia Beach. And when I say "off," it wasn't completely. But we had a week-- a week off at home-- conducted one more rehearsal, day of training on the life-size mock up. And then we got the word that we were going. Owen's book was to be released on the anniversary of 9/11, but the release has been moved up to next week. There's been criticism that the book is timed to influence the election. Mark Owen: My worry from the beginning is, you know, it's a political season. This book is not political whatsoever. It doesn't bad mouth either party, and we specifically chose September 11th to keep it out of the politics. You know, if these-- crazies on either side of the aisle want to make it political, shame on them. This is a book about September 11th, and it needs to rest on September 11th. Not be brought into the political arena, because this-- this has nothing to do with politics. When word of the book was announced last week, a few news organizations discovered Mark Owen's real name and published it. As a result, he's a marked man -- in hiding -- probably for the rest of his life. We will not reveal his true nam</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346286452474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346286564116-89</Id><Topic><Title>New mileage standards would double fuel efficiency</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1346207525557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 22:32:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>King "O" says it's so, so it must be so right simple minded DIM one? And even though the King declares it will save the middle class $1 per gallon in petrol, never mind the $5K difference in purchase price of said auto right? Effin #$%$!!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1346286564116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:29:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346286661095-90</Id><Topic><Title>McCain Hammers Obama on Foreign Policy...Leaks,</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346285730208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:15:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are probably to ignorant to know that Obama has America deeply involved in Syria and Iran. Geez, you Libs are really Ignorant and Stupid!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346286661095</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:31:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346286883857-91</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is a Shameful Lying President!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346286452474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:27:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shameful? Lying? "Say it ain't so...Typical DIM Modus Operandi to lull their DIM voters votes!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1346286883857</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346286936453-92</Id><Title>Navy</Title><Msg>The U.S. Navy will supply Australia with the ALQ-99 jammer pods it needs for its future Boeing EA-18G fleet, Flight Global reports. Australia is converting 12 of its 24 Boeing F/A-18F Super Hornets into the electronic attack Growler configuration. The Navy says that it expects to transition its forces to the Next Generation Jammer that is currently being developed.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346286936453</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:35:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346286961240-93</Id><Title>Shame on Barak Hussein Obama!</Title><Msg>Obama Honored Fallen SEALs By Sending Their Parents a Form Letter Signed By Electric Pen Posted by Jim Hoft on Wednesday, August 29, 2012, 10:31 AM On August 6, 2011, 30 US service members were killed when a CH-47 Chinook helicopter they were being transported in crashed in Wardak province, Afghanistan. It was the deadliest single loss for U.S. forces in the decade-long war in Afghanistan. 17 members of the elite Navy SEALs were killed in the crash. Yesterday, Karen and Billy Vaughn, parents of Aaron Carson Vaughn, spoke at the Defending the Defenders forum sponsored by the Tea Party Patriots outside the RNC Convention in Tampa. Karen brought a copy of the form letter they were sent following their son’s death. It’s a form letter. It was signed by an electric pen. That’s not all. Karen Vaughn reached out to the parents of the other SEALs killed in that crash. Their letters were all the same. Form letters – signed by an electric pen. Here’s a closer look at the letter sent to the parents of Chief Petty Officer Nicholas H. Null. It’s the same form letter. After the deadliest single loss of US forces in Afghanistan, Barack Obama sent out form letters</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346286961240</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346287030416-94</Id><Topic><Title>Shame on Barak Hussein Obama!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346286961240</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DIMS know no shame!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1346287030416</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:37:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346287161289-95</Id><Title>F15 radar support contract</Title><Msg>Boeing [NYSE: BA] has received an $85 million Performance-Based Logistics (PBL) contract for continued support of U.S. Air Force F-15 mechanically scanned and Active Electronically Scanned Array (AESA) radars. The new PBL contract replaces three previous support contracts with one overarching agreement.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1346287161289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:39:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346287168922-96</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Media in Meltdown as Romney Soars in the Polls!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346262100322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Last time I watched the LameStream Media Walter Cronkite was still anchoring CBS News.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1346287168922</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:39:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346287169401-97</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Media in Meltdown as Romney Soars in the Polls!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346262100322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Last time I watched the LameStream Media Walter Cronkite was still anchoring CBS News.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1346287169401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:39:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346287241890-98</Id><Title>Results of Decades of Socialist Democratic Run Cities!</Title><Msg>CHICAGO TEACHERS UNION GIVES 10-DAY STRIKE NOTICE BY TAMMY WEBBER ASSOCIATED PRESS US VIDEO BUY AP PHOTO REPRINTS MULTIMEDIA INTERACTIVE: BECOMING A TEACHER IN MID-CAREER SURVEY OF COLLEGE FUNDRAISING (PDF) AP POLL: PUBLIC EDUCATION REPORT ON LOAN OPTIONS FOR COMMUNITY COLLEGE STUDENTS (APRIL 17, 2008) AN ALTERNATIVE TO SPECIAL EDUCATION LATEST NEWS POLICE: 100-YEAR-OLD DRIVER HITS 11 NEAR LA SCHOOL RECORDS SHOW TROUBLED LIFE FOR ACCUSED MD. SHOOTER FAMILY OF ALLEGED SHOOTER "HORRIFIED" POOR MAINE KIDS' MISSING SCHOOL SUPPLIES FOUND CAMPUS SENIOR EVENTS DEEMED OFFENSIVE TO HISPANICS CHICAGO (AP) -- The Chicago Teachers Union issued a 10-day strike notice Wednesday, saying teachers in the nation's third-largest school district are ready to walk off the job for the first time in 25 years. Union President Karen Lewis said contract talks with the Chicago Board of Education, which have been under way since November, have not yet touched on some issues that teachers are most concerned about, including wages. She said job security and teacher evaluations also are issues. The notice means the soonest teachers could strike is Sept. 10, but it doesn't mean a strike will definitely happen. Lewis said no strike date has been set, and the union would continue negotiating until there is a contract, even if there is a strike. "This is a difficult decision for all of us to make," Lewis said. "But this is the only way to get the board's attention and show them that we are serious about getting a fair contract which will give our students the resources they deserve." Some of the district's 400,000 students have already started school; the rest begin Tuesday. The last Chicago teachers strike was in 1987 and lasted 19 days. The most recent contract expired in June, when 90 percent of the more than 26,000 union members voted to authorize a strike if a contract was not reached over the summer. Lewis claims the public schools administration "seems determined to have a toxic relationship with its employees," saying teachers have been belittled and demoralized. She pointed out that a previously negotiated raise was canceled and changes have been made to the way teachers are evaluated. Chicago Public Schools CEO Jean-Claude Brizard issued a statement saying students "cannot afford to be removed from the classroom" just as they're starting a new longer day, and said the district will meet every day with the union to try to avoid a strike. The school district has offered teachers a four-year contract with raises of 2 percent a year, which school board spokeswoman Becky Carroll said would cost $160 million. Lewis has repeatedly said the raise offered by the board is not acceptable. The district also wants the union to agree to a joint committee to come up with a new system to pay teachers, other than automatic raises based on seniority. The district said that doesn't mean pay raises would necessarily be based only on merit. "It could take a lot of forms; we have not even talked about it," Carroll said. The board last week authorized spending $25 million in the event of a strike, which Carroll said would help ensure the tens of thousands of students who rely on the schools for two meals a day are fed and have a safe place during the day. Much of the teachers' frustration has centered on Mayor Rahm Emanuel, who rescinded a 4 percent raise last year and then tried to go around the union in his push for a longer school day by asking teachers at individual schools to waive the union contract to work more hours. The Illinois Educational Labor Relations Board subsequently blocked Emanuel's negotiations with schools. He still was able to lengthen the school day for children to 7 hours, starting this fall, without the union's approval. The Board of Education agreed to hire almost 500 new teachers so it wouldn't have to pay current teachers more to work longer hours. But class size, pay and job security remain top concerns for teachers, the union said. "We will have a contract, and it will come the easy way or the hard way," Lewis said. "If our members are on the picket line, we will still be at the negotiating table trying to hammer out an equitable agreement."</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346287241890</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:40:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346287305895-99</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Media Acting Like a bunch of Buffoons!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346262229526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:43:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's no act ima...that's how DIMS naturally operate!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1346287305895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:41:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346290828581-100</Id><Title>Made in Kenya</Title><Msg>Made in Kenya Raised in Indonesia Invaded Hawaii Stolen Identification Impersonating President Only those with something to hide do not provide the truth.</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1346290828581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 21:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346291903961-101</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Media Acting Like a bunch of Buffoons!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346262229526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:43:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are not acting ! its simply their normal mode of IN -operation</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1346291903961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 21:58:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346293618258-102</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is a Shameful Lying President!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346286452474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:27:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not only that Obama lies about things. He never tells the truth about anything. You can count on anything he says to be false. If he ever told the truth it would just be a coincidence.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1346293618258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 22:26:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346294139611-103</Id><Topic><Title>Shame on Barak Hussein Obama!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1346286961240</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obama just doesn't have what it takes to be a leader. He just talks. Says nothing worth listening to, and he doesn't even mean anything he says anyway.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1346294139611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 22:35:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346294486266-104</Id><Topic><Title>I noticed Obamas Jobs Team is supporting Romney</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1346285355906</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:09:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are going to need a job in a few months when they get kicked out of Washington, so I suppose they don't really want the Obama recession economy.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1346294486266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 22:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346295475458-105</Id><Topic><Title>New Orleans Hurricane and flooding.</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1346277905254</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:05:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To be honest I was waiting for some horror stories about blacks suffering because Indians like Bobby don't like blacks.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1346295475458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 22:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346295788611-106</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 332, Romney 206</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346278217273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:10:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The next 16 years, 8 with Mitt &amp; 8 with Ryan in the white house are going to be real hard on you.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1346295788611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 23:03:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346296172422-107</Id><Title>Condo was great tonight</Title><Msg>No teleprompter</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1346296172422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 23:09:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346296608770-108</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 332, Romney 206</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_007</Username><Timestamp>1346278217273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:10:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is the greatest. The greatest POS.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1346296608770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 23:16:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346296989675-109</Id><Topic><Title>Made in Kenya</Title><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1346290828581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 21:40:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, O will go down in the history books as a very unusual president of the USA. A total con man.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1346296989675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 23:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346297140000-110</Id><Title>Wage Cuts Hit Millions of U.S. Workers</Title><Msg>by Patrick Martin According to a report by the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, released Friday, millions of American workers who lost their jobs after the Wall Street crash of 2008 have failed to find work, while millions more have gone back to work only after taking substantial wage cuts. According to the BLS, some 12.9 million workers were displaced from their jobs between January 2009 and December 2011. The BLS study focused on those who had lost jobs they had held for at least three years, who comprised just under half the total, some 6.1 million workers. Of these 6.1 million workers, 27 percent were still unemployed but looking for work, while 17 percent have stopped looking for work, effectively dropping out of the labor force. Of the 56 percent who had found new jobs, slightly more than half took jobs that paid less than their old jobs. For those who took new jobs with pay cuts, the majority lost 20 percent or more compared to their previous wages, on top of the loss of earnings due to part-time work or reduced overtime. con't ....... http://www.globalresearch.ca/index.php?context=va&amp;aid=32523</Msg><Username>skeptically99</Username><Timestamp>1346297140000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 23:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>