<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353906896269-1</Id><Topic><Title>Dufus Obama cut drilling on government land to hike gas prices to pay for Green Energy one bankruptcy at a time filling the pockets of his friends and supporters</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1353899247675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 22:07:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well he had to help Buffet- who bought B&amp;N railroad which bought tank cars to ship oil from canada to texas- and the pipeline would have cut into that game- ditto for new oil in the U.S And of course solar power needs an immediate backup as does wind- which after hosing the coal companies, leaves . . gas ..</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1353906896269</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 00:14:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353910850671-2</Id><Topic><Title>Dufus Obama cut drilling on government land to hike gas prices to pay for Green Energy one bankruptcy at a time filling the pockets of his friends and supporters</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1353899247675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 22:07:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please note that the first oil refinery to be built the US in 30 years is going to get started this spring in Utah. It is going to be built by the Indians. I wonder who and how the financing for the project is going to be handled? Don't suppose that the former head of the Bureau of Indian affairs, who just happens to be a Indian from Utah, had anything to do with it. Have the proper environmental impact studies been conducted? Where are all the flower snifters and tree huggers who always file ecologic litagtion to stop such projects now?</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1353910850671</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 01:20:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353912211853-3</Id><Topic><Title>China lands fighter jet on new carrier in show of force</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1353861201934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 11:33:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For Tech, According to the Navy’s own statement (in the Fleet Response Plan), the “surge” is to be handled by two carrier groups that augment the six that are to be deployed. But looking back historically on our military activities: the Iraq war ended in 2011. And there is the eleven-year-old war in Afghanistan that is still going on. How do those activities, in the same region, drive the eleven (soon ten) carrier group to exhaustion? Even if two carriers were taxed beyond normal, that doesn’t account for the rest of the fleet. Here is what I think is going on. Obama made the decision in 2011/2012 to bring as many carriers into repair/maintenance/overhaul as possible (and unnecessarily), putting them into the shipyards for simultaneous work in order to jack up the employment numbers – regardless of the effect on readiness – to further his re-election. This is shown by the early RCOH’s of USS Roosevelt, Lincoln, and Truman. Perhaps, you have a different take. Enterprise, CVN-65 Commission: 1961 Overhaul: Decommission in 2013 Status: Retired Nimitz, CVN-68 Commission: 1975 Planned RCOH: 2001/complete Status: Unavailble, return for repair Dwight D. Eisenhower, CVN-69 Commission: 1975 Planned RCOH: 2000/complete Status: Incremental availability, two month break Carl Vinson, CVN-70 Commission: 1983 Planned RCOH: 2009/complete Status: Unavailable, at Homeport Theodore Roosevelt, CVN-71 Commission: 1986 Planned RCOH: 2013/in progress Status: Unavailable Abraham Lincoln, CVN-72 Commission: 1989 Planned RCOH: (2014)/early, in progress Status: Unavailable George Washington, CVN-73 Commission: 1992 Planned RCOH: (2017) Status: 7th Fleet Ops John C. Stennis, CVN-74 Commission: 1995 Planned RCOH: (2020) Status: 5th fleet Ops Harry S. Truman, CVN-75 Commission: 1998 Planned RCOH: (2023), done early in 2012 Status: Unavailable Ronald Reagan, CVN-76 Commission: 2003 Planned RCOH: (2028) Status: Unavailable, DPIA George H.W. Bush, CVN-77 Commission: 2009 Planned RCOH: (2034) Status: Unavailable, DPIA BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1353912211853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 01:43:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353912812578-4</Id><Topic><Title>Bush got us in this recession</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351202338355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:58:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Wu what was it that Bush did exactly that caused the recession?</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1353912812578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 01:53:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353914564697-5</Id><Topic><Title>Google Search: Intertial Mass Suspension</Title><Username>dotcomsale</Username><Timestamp>1353883196058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:39:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad "intertial" isn't a real word.</Msg><Username>the_original_spaz</Username><Timestamp>1353914564697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 02:22:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353917257896-6</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA Contract Status- Anyone have an update?</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1352917990179</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 13:33:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually he was quite successful at turning gold into lead.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1353917257896</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 03:07:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353923156502-7</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA</Title><Username>bobbyb336</Username><Timestamp>1353535932208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 17:12:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If people can't take it, then maybe they shouldn't dish it out.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1353923156502</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 04:45:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353927341802-8</Id><Title>How much does Boing pay for orders cancled due to late delivery ?</Title><Msg>How much does Boeing pay customers who cancle their 787 orders due to is was 3 years late. It seems to me carries could cancle the orders and get cash. Then in two years buy a new Boeing or and Air Bus.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1353927341802</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 05:55:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353940732269-9</Id><Topic><Title>Dufus Obama cut drilling on government land to hike gas prices to pay for Green Energy one bankruptcy at a time filling the pockets of his friends and supporters</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1353899247675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 22:07:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>North America has more oil than all Arab countries combined ever had or will have and we have 300 years of natural gas. The #$%$ who tried to sell us on peak oil (UN and World Bank) need to be ignored going forward. USA is the world's reserve currency and it is tied to oil/gas and now that the USA/NA has more oil/gas than anyone else, our currency will continue to be the world's reserve currency. Obama is just a puppet and will not be allowed to jeapordize this advantage. Wind turbines are falling out of favor worldwide as Vestas and others are tanking and cutting jobs. The big winner will be solar. I say this because already in India the installed price of solar is 50 cents a watt. Here in the USA at 50 cents/watt, I could install solar (with battery storage to be off grid), for around $4,000.00 pay off my investment in 4 years of energy savings and enjoy 26 years of free electricity. Solar will be very appealing to conservatives and libertarians because it frees them from having someone else controlling their energy and paying an energy tax. Al Gore is a brilliant scam artist because he stole money selling useless carbon credits to people too dumb to know they weren't helping the environment. If Bernie Madoff had participated in the legal fraud of selling useless carbon credits he would be a hero too instead of being in jail. Lastly the USA can tell the Arab world and these other oil #$%$ bags like Chavez to F themselves as we are headed towards becoming energy independent by 2020. The CIA has closed its climate change desk as fears of foreign instability in oil producing nations will soon not be a concern to the USA. The only threat to America's energy independence is the progressive left nuts.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1353940732269</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 09:38:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353941369776-10</Id><Title>News Flash for the Wrong Wing Republican Party Finks</Title><Msg>Thanksgiving was still two weeks away when the Republican Party, to its evident shock, found itself stuffed, trussed, roasted, and ready to be served with all the trimmings. This was not the menu that the Party’s nominees, donors, and operatives had looked forward to. It was emphatically not the feast they had been primed to expect by their vulpine cheerleaders in the island universe of the illiberal media. romney beats obama, handily, Michael Barone trumpeted a few days before the election in the Examiner, Washington’s conservative giveaway daily. (The Chicago Tribune, back in ’48, had at least left out the “handily.”) “I think it’s this: a Romney win,” Peggy Noonan assured her Wall Street Journal blog readers the day before the polls opened. (“All the vibrations are right,” she explained.) Also on Election Eve, Dick Morris, a Fox News “analyst” reputed to be a pollster, promised “a landslide for Romney.” The same prediction—not just a win, a landslide—was bruited from the sinkholes (Glenn Beck) to the summits (George F. Will) of the right’s intellectual sierra. News flash: the President won, handily. With late returns still trickling in, his popular-vote margin now exceeds four million,</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1353941369776</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 09:49:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353941958295-11</Id><Title>sleep, and libdems.</Title><Msg>I use to worry about libdems being able to sleep at nite knowing they were taking down their country, and supporting so many lies. But Carville releaved my worries. He says dumb libdems sleep well since their lack of intelligence has their brains half a sleep all day long.</Msg><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1353941958295</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 09:59:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353945555655-12</Id><Title>Same losers still posting on BA board</Title><Msg>Get a life</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1353945555655</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:59:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353946990515-13</Id><Topic><Title>China lands fighter jet on new carrier in show of force</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1353861201934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 11:33:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Congressional testimony this summer: "We're not good to go right now," Vice Adm. Kevin McCoy, head of Naval Sea Systems Command, told the HASC readiness subcommittee. And he told the committee that things may well get worse in the near term before they get better. His colleague, Vice Adm. William Burke, deputy chief of naval operation for readiness, conceded under questioning that the last decade of high operational tempo does worry the service. The biggest concern: "potential overuse of our platforms." Simply put, the Navy's ships may be wearing out much more quickly than expected because they are being used much more than originally planned. From 2011, Defense News: According to statistics released by Rep. Randy Forbes, the Virginia Republican who chairs the House Armed Services Readiness Subcommittee, 22 percent of Navy ships didn’t pass their inspections in 2011. In 2007, just 8 percent of ships were rated as carrying junk equipment or insufficient spare parts. And more than half the Navy’s deployed aircraft — the F/A-18 Hornets, the jamming EA-18G Growlers, the P-3C Orion surveillance plane — aren’t ready for combat. The Navy’s surface fleet goes into the water banged up. Its aircraft carriers, frigates, destroyers spend nearly 40 percent of their deployment time with “at least one major equipment or systems failure,” according to a chart Forbes released at a hearing on Tuesday. That can include “anti-air defenses, radar, satellite communications, or engines.” Let’s not forget that even the new ships are disintegrating. And the demand on the Navy is huge. Consider the last year at sea. U.S. Navy ships and aircraft performed support missions for Iraq and Afghanistan. They helped with disaster relief after Pakistani floods and a Japanese tsunami/earthquake. They fought Somali pirates and spearheaded an ongoing war in Libya. From KomoNews Nov 23: The Navy said Wednesday it will temporarily shrink its aircraft carrier presence in the Persian Gulf area from two to one because of a mechanical problem with the USS Nimitz. The Nimitz was scheduled to deploy in January to relieve the USS Dwight D. Eisenhower, but that will be put off until summer in order to complete repairs to its propulsion system. The problem was discovered while the ship was doing pre-deployment maneuvers. As a result, the Navy made the unusual decision to bring the Eisenhower home to Norfolk, Va., in December and resurface its flight deck so it can go back to the Gulf area in February and remain for four months. In announcing the moves, the Navy said none are related to the conflict between Israel and the Hamas militants in Gaza - or any other security threats or contingency planning. They said it reflects wear and tear on the carrier fleet, which has been under enormous strain during more than 11 years of war. EOD</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1353946990515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 11:23:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353947212344-14</Id><Topic><Title>Dufus Obama cut drilling on government land to hike gas prices to pay for Green Energy one bankruptcy at a time filling the pockets of his friends and supporters</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1353899247675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 22:07:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watched a History channel program on how much the earth is worth. All the three top precious metals platinum, gold and silver ever mined or are known/thought to exist comes to less than $15 trillion dollars. That is less than our national debt. Hyper-inflation is the only way the debt can be paid/serviced.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1353947212344</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 11:26:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353951929900-15</Id><Topic><Title>Same losers still posting on BA board</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1353945555655</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:59:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get a job,loser.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1353951929900</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 12:45:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353952082362-16</Id><Topic><Title>Dufus Obama cut drilling on government land to hike gas prices to pay for Green Energy one bankruptcy at a time filling the pockets of his friends and supporters</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1353899247675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 22:07:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actuall dufuss, the price of gas is down. How does that fit into your (and rush's) idiotic model?</Msg><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1353952082362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 12:48:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353954687641-17</Id><Topic><Title>Same losers still posting on BA board</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1353945555655</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:59:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>God bless the President and the USA. The people who are suffering due to Sandy need our help. Not the hate the losers seem to live in</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1353954687641</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 13:31:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353954804134-18</Id><Title>SPEEA and Boeing</Title><Msg>Get a deal done now</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1353954804134</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 13:33:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353957352445-19</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA and Boeing</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1353954804134</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 13:33:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wu, All in due time they will$$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1353957352445</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 14:15:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353962731067-20</Id><Title>6500% PROFIT on TADF possible in the next 45 days. Contracts Announcement Any day Now</Title><Msg>TADF has 5 pending contract bids with the Department Of Defense. And if TADF gets just one approval or two approvals. TADF will make many traders millionaires, it TADF is bought in the millions at current price level. Department Of Defense approves new contracts end of year, so investors and traders are loading up. Fast entry price range 0.0004 to 0.0016. TADF is a LONG BUY for me.</Msg><Username>undervaluedstock</Username><Timestamp>1353962731067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 15:45:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353963649519-21</Id><Topic><Title>6500% PROFIT on TADF possible in the next 45 days. Contracts Announcement Any day Now</Title><Username>undervaluedstock</Username><Timestamp>1353962731067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 15:45:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The company only has two (2) full-time employees. What happens if one decides to call in sick? LOL</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1353963649519</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 16:00:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353966731239-22</Id><Topic><Title>Same losers still posting on BA board</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1353945555655</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:59:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Speaking for yourself" is a good step towards making progress in your therapy.</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1353966731239</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 16:52:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353973062853-23</Id><Topic><Title>Dufus Obama cut drilling on government land to hike gas prices to pay for Green Energy one bankruptcy at a time filling the pockets of his friends and supporters</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1353899247675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 22:07:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Four steps up one step back isn't what I consider going down.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1353973062853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 18:37:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353973158222-24</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Sub Contractor In Big Trouble!! Again!!</Title><Username>freedomrings510</Username><Timestamp>1353879917882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:45:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes this is a bad company to keep!</Msg><Username>dasani_williams</Username><Timestamp>1353973158222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 18:39:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353978064761-25</Id><Title>Obama doubling down on multiple failures</Title><Msg>4 years wothout a Federal Budget. 16.4 trillion in government debt. This debt at this rate could balloon to 21 trillion in debt after another 4 years of democrat control of Washington. Plus, Bernanke has permission to fire up the printing presses to continue the devaluation of the dollar. Gasoline could reach $9./ gallon by 2016. Businesses won't hire as long as Obama continues to issue more rules and regulations over the private sector. This will lead America to another 4 years of economic stagnation. The democrat course for economic growth will continue to fail until policy changes are made at the Federal Level. Obama and Entitlement Voters will bring down Capitalism if new drastic measures aren't implemented from Washington to safeguard Capitalism. The majority of dependent Americans can't expect to have their piece of the economic pie increased from the top 1% of taxpayers without the Progressive Experiment in Ponzism collapsing the entire economy. GDP will tumble and more economic hardships will prevail if those on government handouts continue to increase in America. These humble thoughts are brought to you courtesy of sdmiller</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1353978064761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 20:01:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353979871512-26</Id><Topic><Title>Marxist Professor claims Stalin committed no crime</Title><Username>spartacus8463</Username><Timestamp>1353976023042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 19:27:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are nutcases in all walks of life. To see one all you have to do is look in the mirror.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1353979871512</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 20:31:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353981137754-27</Id><Topic><Title>Marxist Professor claims Stalin committed no crime</Title><Username>spartacus8463</Username><Timestamp>1353976023042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 19:27:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really are dumb, aren't you freedumber? Next thing you'll be saying is that Stalin wasn't jewish.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1353981137754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 20:52:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353981243980-28</Id><Title>Where The Buffalo Roam</Title><Msg>What Republicans Are Really Up Against: Population Density Richard Florida and Sara Johnson Numerous theories have been offered recently not just for Mitt Romney's stunning defeat by Barack Obama, but for the apparent decline of the Republican electoral coalition. Many emphasize the diverse demographic coalition — of women, ethnic minorities, and gays — that came together behind the president, while others stress the well-executed ground game and state-of-the-art analytic techniques used by the Obama campaign. America's increasingly diverse demographic makeup may well have created a long-term advantage for Democrats. Republicans had better change their stripes and address these new realities if they want to be relevant and competitive again. As our own Sommer Mathis noted the morning after the election, county-level election results show that cities are very, very blue. "The math of assuming cities will go to Democrats and thus not bothering to craft a message aimed at the people who live there is just a losing game going forward for Republicans," she wrote. "And it's only going to get worse as urban populations increase and become more concentrated." After examining a series of electoral maps, Emily Badger also concluded that electoral power is "concentrated in those blue-black patches, one of which strings all the way from southern Connecticut to Washington, D.C. These are the places where people live densely together, where they require policies and an ideology that Republicans lately have not offered." We're not the only ones that have pointed to the increasingly important electoral role of cities. In their prescient 2004 book The Emerging Democratic Majority, John Judis and Ruy Teixeira argued that a new Democratic majority would be centered in both an increasingly diverse electorate and the new knowledge- and service-based economies of what they dubbed urban "ideopolises." Several years ago, Tom Davis, the former Republican congressman from Northern Virginia, speculated that Republicans were becoming more vulnerable in urban centers because, as he put it, economic development works, meaning as communities become more developed they attract more highly educated and cosmopolitan populations that tend to vote Democratic. National Journal's Ronald Brownstein has shown how creative class counties have trended increasingly Democratic over the past couple of decades. As Dave Troy puts it, the key factor in this year's election is even simpler — it's all about density. Troy, a founder of several software companies, recently plotted the county-level election results against population density (see the graph below). His conclusion was striking: "98% of the 50 most dense counties voted Obama. 98% of the 50 least dense counties voted for Romney." The graph shows a clear "crossover point" in terms of density where counties turn blue and Democratic, as he explains: At about 800 people per square mile, people switch from voting primarily Republican to voting primarily Democratic. Put another way, below 800 people per square mile, there is a 66% chance that you voted Republican. Above 800 people per square mile, there is a 66% chance that you voted Democrat. In a second graph (above), he added red states and blue states, as well as key cities, to his analysis. Based on this he notes two key facts. First, red states have very few cities, and second, the ones they do have vote overwhelmingly for Democrats. He points out that most big cities in red states voted blue. The two exceptions — Salt Lake City and Oklahoma City — had low densities, with only about 1,000 people per square mile, or less than suburban Maryland. He points out that red states seem to "simply run out of population at about 2,000 people per square mile." Given the logic of economic development and urbanization, he argues that "red states are just underdeveloped blue states," noting that: "As cities continue to grow in red states, those cities will become more blue, and ultimately, those states will become more purple, and then blue." The Republicans are becoming a party of anti-progress, which is ultimately what is costing them so dearly. The issue cuts far deeper than identity politics and turns on ideology and policy positions which are "simply not compatible with the global urban future. If that's the case, an Hispanic candidate running on the same old Republican platform will simply not resonate." The crux of the Republican problem is not the changing ethnic and demographic makeup of America, but their being at odds with the very logic of urbanism and economic development.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_888</Username><Timestamp>1353981243980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 20:54:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353981418268-29</Id><Title>Where The Buffalo Roam</Title><Msg>What Republicans Are Really Up Against: Population Density Richard Florida and Sara Johnson Numerous theories have been offered recently not just for Mitt Romney's stunning defeat by Barack Obama, but for the apparent decline of the Republican electoral coalition. Many emphasize the diverse demographic coalition — of women, ethnic minorities, and gays — that came together behind the president, while others stress the well-executed ground game and state-of-the-art analytic techniques used by the Obama campaign. America's increasingly diverse demographic makeup may well have created a long-term advantage for Democrats. Republicans had better change their stripes and address these new realities if they want to be relevant and competitive again. As our own Sommer Mathis noted the morning after the election, county-level election results show that cities are very, very blue. "The math of assuming cities will go to Democrats and thus not bothering to craft a message aimed at the people who live there is just a losing game going forward for Republicans," she wrote. "And it's only going to get worse as urban populations increase and become more concentrated." After examining a series of electoral maps, Emily Badger also concluded that electoral power is "concentrated in those blue-black patches, one of which strings all the way from southern Connecticut to Washington, D.C. These are the places where people live densely together, where they require policies and an ideology that Republicans lately have not offered." We're not the only ones that have pointed to the increasingly important electoral role of cities. In their prescient 2004 book The Emerging Democratic Majority, John Judis and Ruy Teixeira argued that a new Democratic majority would be centered in both an increasingly diverse electorate and the new knowledge- and service-based economies of what they dubbed urban "ideopolises." Several years ago, Tom Davis, the former Republican congressman from Northern Virginia, speculated that Republicans were becoming more vulnerable in urban centers because, as he put it, economic development works, meaning as communities become more developed they attract more highly educated and cosmopolitan populations that tend to vote Democratic. National Journal's Ronald Brownstein has shown how creative class counties have trended increasingly Democratic over the past couple of decades. As Dave Troy puts it, the key factor in this year's election is even simpler — it's all about density. Troy, a founder of several software companies, recently plotted the county-level election results against population density. His conclusion was striking: "98% of the 50 most dense counties voted Obama. 98% of the 50 least dense counties voted for Romney."</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_888</Username><Timestamp>1353981418268</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 20:56:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353981712646-30</Id><Title>Where The Buffalo Roam</Title><Msg>What Republicans Are Really Up Against: Population Density Richard Florida and Sara Johnson Numerous theories have been offered recently not just for Mitt Romney's stunning defeat by Barack Obama, but for the apparent decline of the Republican electoral coalition. Many emphasize the diverse demographic coalition — of women, ethnic mino rities, and ga ys — that came together behind the president, while others stress the well-executed ground game and state-of-the-art analytic techniques used by the Obama campaign. America's increasingly diverse demographic makeup may well have created a long-term advantage for Democrats. Republicans had better change their stripes and address these new realities if they want to be relevant and competitive again. As our own Sommer Mathis noted the morning after the election, county-level election results show that cities are very, very blue. "The math of assuming cities will go to Democrats and thus not bothering to craft a message aimed at the people who live there is just a losing game going forward for Republicans," she wrote. "And it's only going to get worse as urban populations increase and become more concentrated." After examining a series of electoral maps, Emily Badger also concluded that electoral power is "concentrated in those blue-black patches, one of which strings all the way from southern Connecticut to Washington, D.C. These are the places where people live densely together, where they require policies and an ideology that Republicans lately have not offered." We're not the only ones that have pointed to the increasingly important electoral role of cities. In their prescient 2004 book The Emerging Democratic Majority, John Judis and Ruy Teixeira argued that a new Democratic majority would be centered in both an increasingly diverse electorate and the new knowledge- and service-based economies of what they dubbed urban "ideopolises." Several years ago, Tom Davis, the former Republican congressman from Northern Virginia, speculated that Republicans were becoming more vulnerable in urban centers because, as he put it, economic development works, meaning as communities become more developed they attract more highly educated and cosmopolitan populations that tend to vote Democratic. National Journal's Ronald Brownstein has shown how creative class counties have trended increasingly Democratic over the past couple of decades. As Dave Troy puts it, the key factor in this year's election is even simpler — it's all about density. Troy, a founder of several software companies, recently plotted the county-level election results against population density (see the graph below). His conclusion was striking: "98% of the 50 most dense counties voted Obama. 98% of the 50 least dense counties voted for Romney."</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_888</Username><Timestamp>1353981712646</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 21:01:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353982194300-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obama doubling down on multiple failures</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1353978064761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 20:01:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unionism took Hostess down for the count. NO JOBS! Everyone loses! Thousands of former employees now without work in a weakening economy. Unionism and Communism, way to go Comrades! Unions have taken greed to new levels! May your Christmas Gifts be filled with coal!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1353982194300</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 21:09:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353983161880-32</Id><Topic><Title>Marxist Professor claims Stalin committed no crime</Title><Username>spartacus8463</Username><Timestamp>1353976023042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 19:27:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You crack me up. The "Stalin is Jewish" is on par with the birthers. Zero credibility, zero basis in fact, and spouted by those who have close to a zero brain.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1353983161880</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 21:26:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353984221498-33</Id><Topic><Title>Rice is just going to do whatever Obama tells her. Lie cheat and steal, even kill and let the Muslims sodomize the Ambassador</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1353983449515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 21:30:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The world sees your problem. Another black woman in a position of authority. Get some help. Your life can be good but the first step is admitting you have a problem.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1353984221498</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 21:43:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353984691428-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obama doubling down on multiple failures</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1353978064761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 20:01:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama: "Why take responsibility for the economy when I can conveniently blame George for another 4 years? I believe the Media could go along with that."</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1353984691428</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 21:51:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353986707512-35</Id><Topic><Title>Rice is just going to do whatever Obama tells her. Lie cheat and steal, even kill and let the Muslims sodomize the Ambassador</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1353983449515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 21:30:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least he's not a fake and a liar like you are, little Chrissy . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1353986707512</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 22:25:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353987908114-36</Id><Topic><Title>Rice is just going to do whatever Obama tells her. Lie cheat and steal, even kill and let the Muslims sodomize the Ambassador</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1353983449515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 21:30:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which Jumbotsca_ski wrote this one?: "Our Disaster-N-Chief 17-Mar-11 10:32 pm A man who looks so much like a chimp should not be Prez. It's as simple as that . Y.T. Jumbojetski"</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1353987908114</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 22:45:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353987952853-37</Id><Topic><Title>Marxist Professor claims Stalin committed no crime</Title><Username>spartacus8463</Username><Timestamp>1353976023042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 19:27:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The board communists won't like your facts about Stalin, their hero.</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1353987952853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 22:45:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353988002890-38</Id><Topic><Title>Rice is just going to do whatever Obama tells her. Lie cheat and steal, even kill and let the Muslims sodomize the Ambassador</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1353983449515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 21:30:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did dJumbot write this one?: Re: Bin Ladenn is dead! 3-May-11 01:50 am "I don't know for sure, but it could have something to do with the facts: Fact 1.) Fish eat corpses . Fact 2.) J e w s eat fish . Y.T. Jumbojetski?</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1353988002890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 22:46:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353992155299-39</Id><Topic><Title>Same losers still posting on BA board</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1353945555655</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 10:59:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wu if we weren't spending all that money on obama care, obama motors, obama solar, obama gun running,etc, we could have bought you a shovel to get all that muck out and a big 32 oz Slurpee - ops forgot, big gov won't let you big apple guys buy a slurpee. Keep drinking the Kool Aid dude</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1353992155299</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 23:55:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>