<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-24"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353745795379-1</Id><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Msg>November 22, 2012 Grand Old Planet By PAUL KRUGMAN Earlier this week, GQ magazine published an interview with Senator Marco Rubio, whom many consider a contender for the 2016 Republican presidential nomination, in which Mr. Rubio was asked how old the earth is. After declaring “I’m not a scientist, man,” the senator went into desperate evasive action, ending with the declaration that “it’s one of the great mysteries.” It’s funny stuff, and conservatives would like us to forget about it as soon as possible. Hey, they say, he was just pandering to likely voters in the 2016 Republican primaries — a claim that for some reason is supposed to comfort us. But we shouldn’t let go that easily. Reading Mr. Rubio’s interview is like driving through a deeply eroded canyon; all at once, you can clearly see what lies below the superficial landscape. Like striated rock beds that speak of deep time, his inability to acknowledge scientific evidence speaks of the anti-rational mind-set that has taken over his political party. By the way, that question didn’t come out of the blue. As speaker of the Florida House of Representatives, Mr. Rubio provided powerful aid to creationists trying to water down science education. In one interview, he compared the teaching of evolution to Communist indoctrination tactics — although he graciously added that “I’m not equating the evolution people with Fidel Castro.” Gee, thanks. What was Mr. Rubio’s complaint about science teaching? That it might undermine children’s faith in what their parents told them to believe. And right there you have the modern G.O.P.’s attitude, not just toward biology, but toward everything: If evidence seems to contradict faith, suppress the evidence. The most obvious example other than evolution is man-made climate change. As the evidence for a warming planet becomes ever stronger — and ever scarier — the G.O.P. has buried deeper into denial, into assertions that the whole thing is a hoax concocted by a vast conspiracy of scientists. And this denial has been accompanied by frantic efforts to silence and punish anyone reporting the inconvenient facts. But the same phenomenon is visible in many other fields. The most recent demonstration came in the matter of election polls. Coming into the recent election, state-level polling clearly pointed to an Obama victory — yet more or less the whole Republican Party refused to acknowledge this reality. Instead, pundits and politicians alike fiercely denied the numbers and personally attacked anyone pointing out the obvious; the demonizing of The Times’s Nate Silver, in particular, was remarkable to behold. What accounts for this pattern of denial? Earlier this year, the science writer Chris Mooney published “The Republican Brain,” which was not, as you might think, a partisan screed. It was, instead, a survey of the now-extensive research linking political views to personality types. As Mr. Mooney showed, modern American conservatism is highly correlated with authoritarian inclinations — and authoritarians are strongly inclined to reject any evidence contradicting their prior beliefs. Today’s Republicans cocoon themselves in an alternate reality defined by Fox News, Rush Limbaugh and The Wall Street Journal’s editorial page, and only on rare occasions — like on election night — encounter any hint that what they believe might not be true. And, no, it’s not symmetric. Liberals, being human, often give in to wishful thinking — but not in the same systematic, all-encompassing way. Coming back to the age of the earth: Does it matter? No, says Mr. Rubio, pronouncing it “a dispute amongst theologians” — what about the geologists? — that has “has nothing to do with the gross domestic product or economic growth of the United States.” But he couldn’t be more wrong. We are, after all, living in an era when science plays a crucial economic role. How are we going to search effectively for natural resources if schools trying to teach modern geology must give equal time to claims that the world is only 6.000 years old? How are we going to stay competitive in biotechnology if biology classes avoid any material that might offend creationists? And then there’s the matter of using evidence to shape economic policy. You may have read about the recent study from the Congressional Research Service finding no empirical support for the dogma that cutting taxes on the wealthy leads to higher economic growth. How did Republicans respond? By suppressing the report. On economics, as in hard science, modern conservatives don’t want to hear anything challenging their preconceptions — and they don’t want anyone else to hear about it, either. So don’t shrug off Mr. Rubio’s awkward moment. His inability to deal with geological evidence was symptomatic of a much broader problem — one that may, in the end, set America on a path of inexorable decline.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353749685044-2</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA</Title><Username>bobbyb336</Username><Timestamp>1353535932208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 17:12:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Making a 110K a year...surely you can afford to stay out for a while, when BA off loads the engineering to Russian or China. We would probably get the dispositions back quicker via email, then we would using the standard medium. Bottom line. The IAM gets an early contract because they (IAM) are more important. If the IAM (and many of your SPEEA engineering) would stop #$%$ up the airplane, BA wouldn't need engineering or would have miminal amount such that, BA can contract them out accordingly. NOTE: The design on all existing models has alreay been determined. BTW: I have weathered 4 strikes as an IAM member and yes, I have a 4 year degree.SPEEA loves to piggy back off of the IAM contracts. Now that they (IAM) have settled long ago, SPEEA is left out in the cold, fending for themselves. There is your leadership hard at work.</Msg><Username>trujrnyfan</Username><Timestamp>1353749685044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 04:34:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353754276145-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is going to put us backon Grayhoud !</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1353666036832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 05:20:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok, .... you can walk.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1353754276145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 05:51:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353754943778-4</Id><Topic><Title>November deliveries</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1353534964229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 16:56:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the update.</Msg><Username>mrstock52</Username><Timestamp>1353754943778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 06:02:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353755715221-5</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA</Title><Username>bobbyb336</Username><Timestamp>1353535932208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 17:12:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, I can stay out indefinitely. While I'm not old enough to retire by Boeing's standard, I'd be just fine if I never worked another day in my life. I'm financially independent. So it doesn't matter what the #$%$ Boeing does. "Bottom line. The IAM gets an early contract because they (IAM) are more important." Well Mr. More Important, you'd better go look in the mirror because during the time I've worked for Boeing your numbers have plummeted. Your population has gone right off the end of a cliff. You guys are Boeing's b#tch, as evidenced by how few of you are left. "If the IAM would stop screwing up the A/P ..." But no matter how hard you try, you can't. Can you? You guys are constantly drilling holes in the wrong location, leaving tool marks in the skin and tools in the fuel tanks and elsewhere. I know. I read the reports. "NOTE: The design on all existing models has alreay been determined." Note: Without us on the job you can build (and park) all the A/Ps you like. You just can't deliver any of 'em. Without us on the job, you have no way to get the A/P back into conformity with the design and no way to get it certified it. Seems the FAA is a little "touchy" about that kind of thing. Sorry. "... yes, I have a 4 year degree." Then why are you working as a grease monkey? What'd you do? Major in a field that you can't making a living from? ROFL "SPEEA is left out in the cold, fending for themselves." You know as well as I that the IAM and SPEEA have always negotiated their contracts separately. You're just being a #$%$ bag, which is apparently your natural state.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1353755715221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 06:15:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353758868094-6</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already pandering to the mid-west creationists! How'd that work out this past election, Marco?</Msg><Username>opiespa</Username><Timestamp>1353758868094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 07:07:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>21</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353765746203-7</Id><Topic><Title>US Troops in Afghanistan Enjoy Thanksgiving Meals...</Title><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1353600961776</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 11:16:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, you are correct, it wasn't.</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1353765746203</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 09:02:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353774116647-8</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very well said. Their swing to the anti-scientific/rational mindset is the primary reason I left the Republican party because I don't want this country to become a scientific backwater without any hope of competing in the modern world. What a lot of the right wingers on this board don't realize is how dependent companies like Boeing are on federally supported scientific and engineering research as the foundation for their products.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1353774116647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:21:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>23</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353786452018-9</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING SPEEA AND PENSION GAMES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1353529856687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 15:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmm, got my attention with this one since I plan on retiring next year. When I run the pension calculator starting in Feb. I see some non-linearity in the month to month but not as much as you say and there is always an increment from month to month, usually around .6% going up to .65% in the summer months. Also, when I asked for a benefit estimate it came out to $200/mo more than the on line calculation did so they might normalize the variation. Per the SPEEA course on retirement I really won't know until I get the first check but the estimates get more accurate as you get further into the process. From where I sit it doesn't look worth it to work another 6 months to get the extra increment.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1353786452018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:47:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353788541345-10</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING SPEEA AND PENSION GAMES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1353529856687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 15:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the words of otters... mangement offers are crapola keep the SPEAA faith</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1353788541345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:22:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353790448116-11</Id><Title>The Bell of Doom</Title><Msg>during footbasll games across channels collegiate and pro rings for the RWNJ's</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353790448116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:54:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353793173861-12</Id><Topic><Title>Does the Boeing airplane delivery number mean anything, how about the 5 year dividend and stock pric</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1353649028179</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 00:37:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The humiliation of ongoing delays in the delivery of the Boeing Co. (NYSE: BA) 787 continues to dog the huge manufacturer.. It puts Boeing in the best light possible while avoiding its flaws. Boeing hopes that as it trumpets its track record of innovation, that the 787 delays will melt away, at least as far as customers and investors are concerned. It has not worked , Bloomberg reported that:Chief Financial Official Gareth Evans said today at a press briefing that Boeing , shareholders have suffered as well. It is part of a pattern that has many of those who hold Boeing shares underwater, Over the past five years, Boeing’s stock is off about 25% Boeing has decided to adopt a marketing campaign that failed to turn investor and public eyes away from its troubles, as Thanksgiving is about delivery of turkeys maybe we should get another report from the guy who constantly tells us on the Boeing message board that Boeing deliveries are and then lists them. Too bad that does nothing for stock price . The stock price does tell investors that Boeing management is not good, unless you count promises and not actual promised cost and delivery dates. Boeing has delivered 38 787-8 in the last 42 months It would appear it would be cheaper for Boeing to hire some real management instead of paying mangers to leave, Boeing paid Jim Albbaugh 57 million to leave the company, Scott Carson steps aside, enter Jim Albaugh, while the PR is that Boeing is makinga sweeping management shake-up the reality is the bench is full of weak talent from the CEO down, friends, brothers and in-laws seldom make good leaders. Skill, knowledge and ability are the key qualities needed to manage Boeing . So how many airplanes has Boeing delivered this month or better yet how many turkey no profit 747 and 787 have been delivered this thanksgiving month.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1353793173861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:39:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353793344632-13</Id><Topic><Title>The Bell of Doom</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353790448116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:54:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did somebody ring the field artillery</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353793344632</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:42:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353793492987-14</Id><Topic><Title>The Bell of Doom</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353790448116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:54:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thnx a lot signal corp 7 has intercepted this i mean, might intercept this.... go</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353793492987</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 16:44:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353794492765-15</Id><Title>Unequivocally, the RWNJ Senate must verbalize their filibusters on C-Span</Title><Msg>and then via you.tube et al for what it is, what they are, and what it is worth... imho</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1353794492765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 17:01:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353795587830-16</Id><Title>The reason why RWNJ's are not put into Solent Green</Title><Msg>don't taste good and leave afterburn...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353795587830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 17:19:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353795841670-17</Id><Title>Good vibrations the song in my dreams last night and fatyrs which smell like turkey</Title><Msg>on the slopes of Copper Mountain biathalon backwards, upside down HGood Vibrations777</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353795841670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 17:24:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353797456801-18</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING SPEEA AND PENSION GAMES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1353529856687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 15:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I havent been to the SPEEA course on retirement- but I'm sure the so called teacher - matt - is ab0ut 70 percent clueless on the pension games. consider that he pushed the 50 cents/month fee on your BA 401k-VIP-FSP(now gone ) for access to a ING furnished software... SPEEA being one of only three unions to do so- IAM turned it down. And Helped word it so loose that it applies to ALL former bargaining unit members that still had funds in the boeing plans. Now the amount is trivial - but unless you are at least a year from your 60th birthday - the software is NOT useable. Add to that the ripoff rates/fees ING uses for other than the grandfathered choices, and it ism not a pretty picture oran endorsement of the jerks ( including el speea presidente ) who foisted that on everyone. And the initial number games as to percentages, plus the foobar wording of the SS issues in SPEEA proposal is further proof of diminished capacity to read or even be aware of the legal documents involved. The ONE good feature of the seminars is that some may take an interest in the numbers And BTW your view of the .6 rate increase/month and the normalized comment is not supported by any portion of the legal plan documents wherein the calculations that matter are covered. Keep in mind that one gets a single point calculation, and there is NO such normalization.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1353797456801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 17:50:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353799429434-19</Id><Topic><Title>Good vibrations the song in my dreams last night and fatyrs which smell like turkey</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353795841670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 17:24:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hit the off button.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1353799429434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 18:23:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353802814643-20</Id><Title>Coacaine and two-beer eyes</Title><Msg>heck the wrestiling team has won more Time Fades Away</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353802814643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 19:20:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353803835103-21</Id><Title>estimated prophet</Title><Msg>lyrics</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353803835103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 19:37:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353805216813-22</Id><Title>the 1972-75 okland A's wore funny shoes</Title><Msg>green and white gold mr, october over the fence in right field for threre players wh e\wung dung low</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353805216813</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 20:00:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353809638895-23</Id><Title>Warning: a couple three doctorate(s)</Title><Msg>triangulation theorem</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353809638895</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 21:13:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353811344985-24</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING SPEEA AND PENSION GAMES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1353529856687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 15:30:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for the non believers re speea and Ing and 50 cent fee . . this can be found on the Boeing site page 195 of the Boeing VIP summary Plan document Summary of VIP and FSP Plan Change SPEEA (Professional, Technical, and Wichita Engineering Units) This Update summarizes a change from a Letter of Understanding that affects your savings plan(s) and updates your summary plan description(s). The effective date of this change is March 1, 2011. *****The change in this Update will apply to you if you are an employee, or former employee, of The Boeing Company represented, or formerly represented, by the Society of Professional Engineering Employees in Aerospace (“SPEEA”)—Professional, Technical, or Engineering Units. ****** This Update is for your information and is being provided to you as required by Federal law. No action on your part is required. The change in this Update applies to the following plans: n The Boeing Company Voluntary Investment Plan (VIP) (Plan 002). n The Boeing Company Employee Financial Security Plan (FSP) (Plan 003). ING Advisor Service* Effective March 1, 2011, you can use the new ING Advisor Service if you are a participant in the VIP or FSP. ING Advisor Service offers personalized, objective investment advice two ways: n Use the Personal Online Advisor on Boeing Savings Plans Online through Boeing TotalAccess and/or speak with an ING Investment Advisor Representative by calling the Boeing Savings Service Center through Boeing TotalAccess, or n Enroll in the Professional Account Manager program and have a professional manage your account for you.** * Your account will be assessed a monthly fee of $0.50 per month (if you have both a VIP and FSP account, only one monthly fee applies). This fee applies to all participants eligible for ING Advisor Service. ** You will pay a monthly fee if you enroll in the Professional Account manager program. The fee is based on your total account balance. The annualized fee is 0.4% on the first $50,000 of your account balance, then 0.3% on the next $50,000, 0.2% on the next $50,000, and 0.1% on balances over $150,000. Additional information on the ING Advisor Service will be sent in the future.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1353811344985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 21:42:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353815542047-25</Id><Title>might have to answer to the coca-cola company in 1964</Title><Msg>shoot tghe lock off you doofus in 1962 well, bam</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353815542047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:52:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353818091593-26</Id><Topic><Title>might have to answer to the coca-cola company in 1964</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353815542047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:52:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mean people 2nd grade teach ode to joy</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353818091593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 23:34:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353819231005-27</Id><Topic><Title>Good vibrations the song in my dreams last night and fatyrs which smell like turkey</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353795841670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 17:24:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zermatt Kirzbuhel Garmisch Zugspitze Innsbruck Mt. Bachelor Whistler Tahoe</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1353819231005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 23:53:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353819507287-28</Id><Topic><Title>Good vibrations the song in my dreams last night and fatyrs which smell like turkey</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353795841670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 17:24:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mount Rosa August Sue from IBM Frankfurt could thanky gopd ;lmighty save d my life sorta..</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1353819507287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 23:58:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>