<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349842880901-1</Id><Topic><Title>Thew best stories of 1962 imho...the Gemini missions</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349839375466</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:22:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>about Johnny U. and the baltimore little horsies from baltimore lest us oakland raider host'in ewes best stories from 1962 imho the 707/727 nada da mix imho</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349842880901</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:21:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349844232471-2</Id><Topic><Title>Thew best stories of 1962 imho...the Gemini missions</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349839375466</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:22:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we will not and continue to promise NOT to thermonuclear again without reason mittens cannot and will not make such a promise letalone make a budget deficit neutral or else he would have won the nobel prize in economics already I mean d\how stoopid is teamhozemen and all the rwnj's et al whose entire wit falls in a can of tuna with room lerftover</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349844232471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:43:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349845411866-3</Id><Title>A liberal, a conservative and a moderate walk into a bar...</Title><Msg>The bartender says, "Hi, Mitt."</Msg><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1349845411866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:03:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349846415908-4</Id><Title>ALL we need is five Mormon first born sons</Title><Msg>is that too much to ask for war...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349846415908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:20:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349847121111-5</Id><Topic><Title>Thew best stories of 1962 imho...the Gemini missions</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349839375466</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:22:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why da #$%$ do ewes need color tv to watch the flintstones on nbc in the future during friday primetime</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349847121111</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:32:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349867631423-6</Id><Topic><Title>ALL we need is five Mormon first born sons</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349846415908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:20:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You lie like Myth Rmoney.</Msg><Username>bottomline5182</Username><Timestamp>1349867631423</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349869426038-7</Id><Topic><Title>ALL we need is five Mormon first born sons</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1349846415908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:20:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fourmore You are a Religious Bigot!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349869426038</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349870149411-8</Id><Title>Obama Finally Admits Benghazi Lies... There was No Protest at All</Title><Msg>Obama and His Administration will be Throughly Embarrassed and Exposed as Liars today During the Congressional Hearings. Shame on Obama for Trying to Politicize the Murder of Our Ambassador and Former SEALs.... Obama's First Knee Jerk Decision was to Lie, Lie, Lie about the Lack of Security After Repeated Requests for Additional Security. Obama Goes in November... Clinton and Rice Should Already Be Gone!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349870149411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:55:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349872152083-9</Id><Title>Why are Democrats so hateful and vulger?</Title><Msg>Is it because it take an uncivilized mind to be a thief and a socialist?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349872152083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:29:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349872996729-10</Id><Title>Obama syas He wants Everyone to Have a "Fair Shot."</Title><Msg>....but if you use that "fair shot" to actually accomplish something and you become successful then he and his fellow socialists/Marxists want you punished........unless you happen to be one of his big campaign donors......in which case he will redistribute the earnings of hard working tax payers to you.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349872996729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:43:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349873263886-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Finally Admits Benghazi Lies... There was No Protest at All</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349870149411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:55:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just more proof Obama doesn't care about protecting Americans any more than Stalin cared about to 20 million Russians. It's power he is addicted to and we need to send him back to Chicago and put him in rehab..</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349873263886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:47:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349873638738-12</Id><Title>Another Story the ObamaMedia Largely Ignores</Title><Msg>You’re going to have to go to a recognized conservative newspaper of cable television network to hear about this one. It’s a voter suppression story the left loves – and if the left loves it, you probably aren’t going to hear about it. Oh … to be sure .. the ObamaMedia will have kittens if someone tries to make sure that people in this country who cast votes are legally entitled to cast those votes … THAT the media will eagerly cite as evidence of voter suppression. The REAL voter suppression is going on right now on military bases around this country and around the world. It’s the military vote that’s being suppressed. It’s a plain, clear and obvious as it can be. The Obama Administration does not want our men and women in the military to vote --- or to have their votes counted. Simple as that. There’s a reason, of course. Obama knows that the military vote is not going his way. Polls show that some 66 percent of active-duty military personnel intend to vote for Romney. Only about 26 percent say they will vote for Obama. It gets even more damaging when you look at the reasons for these votes. No … the military’s support of Romney is not based on issues of national security. The two top reasons given by these soldiers are the economy and the character of the candidates. OK .. into the WayBack machine. We’re heading back to Florida in the year 2000; right after the close Florida vote threw the Bush/Gore race into turmoil. As soon as it became clear that there was going to be a recount the Democrat Party --- now see if you remember this – the Democrat Party recruited hundreds of Democrat lawyers from around the country and flew them to Florida. When these lawyers hit the ground in Florida they had one specific set of marching orders. They were told to head straight to their assigned voting districts across Florida and, once they arrive, they were to make sure that as many military votes were not counted --- that’s NOT counted --- as possible. They were to go over each and every military absentee ballot they could get their hands on and challenge them on any plausible grounds they could dream up. The message was clear – the Democrats did not want the military votes counted. As it was in 2000, so it is in 2012. After the 2008 election it was discovered that only 20 percent of the 2.6 million military voters had their votes actually counted. Congress passed the MOVE Act. The Military and Overseas Voter Empowermnent Act. This act mandated that military absentee ballots be sent to servicemen 45 days prior to Election Day. That deadline expired weeks ago. Our soldiers are complaining they never got their ballots. The MOVE act also required offices on every military installation be opened to help military personnel vote. The Washington Times tried to contact these offices on many military bases. In half the attempts they couldn’t find the office. There’s much more to these stories. Evidence of outright fraud and suppression. Some ballots were sent to military personnel with wrong dates – ballots that would have been sent back too late to count. It’s clear … Obama is moving to suppress the military vote. See if you can find the story in your local paper, or on a broadcast TV news show. The only way it will get there is when it’s too late to do anything about it, or when public outrages forces the coverage.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349873638738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349873655331-13</Id><Title>Obama Finally Admits Benghazi Lies... There was NO Protest</Title><Msg>Obama and His Administration will Be Exposed as Liars Today During the Congressional Hearings. Obama Purposely Lied to The American People and to the World to Cover Up our Ambassador's Plea for Additional Security... Security Denied by Obama! As a Result, an Ambassador and Former SEALs are Dead! From the Beginning, Obama's Knee Jerk Reaction was to Lie, Lie, Lie... Politicize the Deaths of Our Ambassador and SEALs. Obama Goes in November... Clinton and Rice Should Already be Gone!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349873655331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:54:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349873944605-14</Id><Title>Obama's Auto Bailout in Peril</Title><Msg>Do you remember how many times Democrats touted during the Democrat National Convention that Obama “saved the auto industry”? We had an audio montage of at least a dozen different speakers using some variation of that line … including Obama himself! What if I told you that it’s possible that the entire 2009 auto bailout could unravel? This is not some sort of wishful thinking or conspiracy theory. It’s happening in our court system as well speak. Creditors who were pushed out of the GM bankruptcy have taken their case to court. The particulars are pretty hairy, but here’s what it boils down to: “Even if the trial doesn’t come down to a redo of the entire 2009 restructuring deal, GM could be forced to come up with $1 billion or more to compensate the unsecured creditors at a time when its stock price is languishing and it is lobbying to get the U.S. government to sell its remaining stake in the auto maker.” It’s unlikely that the case will be resolved before the election, but if this were truly the case, then about the only talking point Obama would have left would be that he “got bin Laden,” even though all he really did was get out of the way. Way to go, Mr. President!</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349873944605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:59:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349874694190-15</Id><Title>This is Funny - Team Obama has raised almost $1 billion …</Title><Msg>......yet, they are screaming it is the Republicans who are trying to buy this election. From the campaign that raised $181 million last month, $947 million total. Drew – We’re about to get hit with an avalanche of negative ads. Romney-allied outside groups have already lined up more than $23 million in television spending for this week alone. That’s been the other side’s strategy from the beginning: slamming the airwaves with ads trashing the President and his record. Drew, I’ll be blunt: They are trying to buy this election, and we’re the only ones who are standing in their way. Don’t wait any longer to take ownership of this campaign. Can you chip in $5 or more right now to help? We’ve worked too hard to slow down now. We need to bear down these last 29 days, because Governor Romney and his allies aren’t going to play fair or take it easy on us. Take it from their own adviser: “We’re not going to let our campaign be dictated by fact-checkers.” We need to keep fighting and get the back of the guy who’s got ours — will you chip in today? Thanks. Let’s keep this up. David Axelgrease</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349874694190</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349874777153-16</Id><Topic><Title>Turning Medicare into a Voucher Program</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349796717254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:31:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ultimate aim of the Vulture/Voucher ticket is complete elimination of medicare and social security.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1349874777153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:12:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349874940571-17</Id><Title>“Vote Obama: He didn’t cancel Big Bird, just the Benghazi consulate security.”</Title><Msg>“Vote Obama: He knows how small the PBS subsidy is, but he can’t get the national debt correct to the nearest six trillion – even when he’s the guy who spent it.” Give it a week or so, and, in a grand harmonic convergence of Democrat talking points, Big Bird will be dating Sandra Fluke.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349874940571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:15:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349875273688-18</Id><Title>Environmentalists advocate ignoring the constitution</Title><Msg>In order to implement their green agenda: “What people don’t understand is sometimes we have to step outside the boundaries of the Constitution to get things done.” Environmentalists want to ban hydraulic fracturing in Las Vegas, N.M., and the surrounding county and they don’t plan to let the United States Constitution stop them. “What people don’t understand is sometimes we have to step outside the boundaries of the Constitution to get things done,” Paula Hern, a board member with Community for Clean Water Air and Earth, told the ABQ Journal. “Laws are made to protect corporations and we need laws that protect Mother Earth – earth, air and water.” Hern was defending a “community rights ordinance” banning fracking that the Las Vegas (N.M.) City Council passed but the mayor refused to sign. “The way it reads, it will supersede everything – our city charter, state and federal laws,” said Mayor</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349875273688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349875469666-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Auto Bailout in Peril</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349873944605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:59:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Plagarizing p r i c k the least you could do is give Boortz credit when you steal his work</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349875469666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:24:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349875723138-20</Id><Title>As Romney said, Obama just picks the losers …</Title><Msg>… a plant that got $150 million in taxpayer money to make Volt batteries is putting workers on furlough and has yet to produce a single battery. If this is how you want your tax money spent then you are probably one of the 47% that doesn't pay taxes.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349875723138</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:28:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349876046062-21</Id><Title>Unreal: State Department Now Saying They Never Blamed Video for Libya Attack</Title><Msg>In its latest line of excuses, the State Department is now saying officials never blamed violence in the Middle East, particularly the attack on the U.S. Consulate in Libya, on a YouTube video. The State Department denied Tuesday it ever concluded that the deadly consulate attack Sept. 11 in Libya was an unplanned outburst prompted by an anti-Islam movie. FLASHBACK: The Obama administration used that explanation for more than a week after assailants killed the U.S. ambassador to Libya and three other Americans. Most notably, the U.S. ambassador to the United Nations, Susan Rice, said in several TV interviews five days after the attack that it appeared to be "spontaneous" violence spinning out of protests of the film.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349876046062</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:34:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349876365951-22</Id><Title>obvious harry dokes and mir are the same person</Title><Msg>and that is a fact Hey MIR....give us some free tickets to paradise............ok Eddie Money?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349876365951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349876781682-23</Id><Title>repub darrell issa cut budgets for security at embasy</Title><Msg>multiple budget cuts...they cut down on funding..vigorously..to keep taxes low on mega-rich...and now these hypocrits are blaming anyone in sight.....read the news..mega rich get richer at expense of sembasy and soldiers</Msg><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1349876781682</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349877241888-24</Id><Topic><Title>BA Is Looking Good! BA Is Looking Good!</Title><Username>moody.cobb41</Username><Timestamp>1349872383039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:33:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent. I will check it out now.</Msg><Username>blake.maxwell60</Username><Timestamp>1349877241888</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:54:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349877431025-25</Id><Topic><Title>repub darrell issa cut budgets for security at embasy</Title><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1349876781682</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So obama felt that Big Bird was more important than an embassy? Obama still funded Big Bird</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1349877431025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:57:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349877906029-26</Id><Title>Wynn On Obama: "I'll Be Damned If I Want To Have Him Lecture Me"</Title><Msg>On the Tuesday broadcast of the nightly Nevada political program "Ralston Reports," Steve Wynn, CEO of Wynn Resorts sat down with host Jon Ralston to discuss the presidential election. Wynn, an outspoken critic of President Obama, didn't hold back in his latest criticism of the incumbent president seeking a second term. "I'll be damned if I want to have him lecture me about small business and jobs. I'm a job creator. Guys like me are job creators and we don't like having a bulls-eye painted on our back," Wynn said about Obama to Ralston. An excerpt of the interview is below. WYNN: I've created about 250,000 direct and indirect jobs according to the state of Nevada's measurement. If the number is 250,000, that's exactly 250,000 more than this president, who I'll be damned if I want to have him lecture me about small business and jobs. I'm a job creator. Guys like me are job creators and we don't like having a bulls-eye painted on our back. The president is trying to put himself between me and my employees. By class warfare, by deprecating and calling a group that makes money 'billionaires and millionaires who don't pay their share.' I gave 120% of my salary and bonus away last year to charities, as I do most years. I can't stand the idea of being demagogued, that is put down by a president who has never created any jobs and who doesn't even understand how the economy works. Wynn on a scrapped business plan: "I'm afraid of the president. I have no idea what goofy idea, what crazy, anti-business program this administration will come up. I have no idea. And I have to tell you Jon that every business guy I know in the country is frightened of Barack Obama and the way he thinks."</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349877906029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:05:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349877981289-27</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Democrats so hateful and vulger?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349872152083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you mean to imply that YOU are civlized? That would be a hoot!</Msg><Username>alan_gonquin_is_queer</Username><Timestamp>1349877981289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:06:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879313240-28</Id><Topic><Title>Wynn On Obama: "I'll Be Damned If I Want To Have Him Lecture Me"</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349877906029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:05:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'm a business guy..run and own a diabetes clinic....love obama......the guy who runs costco thinks the same..and starbucks,etc.......wynn is looking out for his class..they started this class warfare..we will beat them with it.</Msg><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1349879313240</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:28:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349879322962-29</Id><Title>CEO to Workers: You'll Likely Be Fired If Obama Is Re-elected</Title><Msg>David Siegel, the owner of Westgate Resorts, sent a surprising email to his employees Monday. It said that if President Barack Obama wins re-election and raises Siegel's taxes, he will have to lay off workers and downsize his company — or even shut it down. "If any new taxes are levied on me, or my company, as our current President plans, I will have no choice but to reduce the size of this company," he wrote. "Rather than grow this company I will be forced to cut back. This means fewer jobs, less benefits and certainly less opportunity for everyone." In a version of Romney's "47 percent" remarks, Siegel added that "people like me who made all the right decisions and invested in themselves are being forced to bail out all the people who didn't. The people that overspent their paychecks suddenly feel entitled to the same luxuries that I earned and sacrificed 42 years of my life for." The points are ones that have often been made during this election. But what makes the letter surprising is the source. David Siegel is the man who, together with his wife, Jackie, built the largest new house in America, known as "Versailles." His story first appeared in my book, "The High-Beta Rich." It then made it to the big screen with documentary film "The Queen of Versailles." They became symbols of outsized spending, debt and real estate in America. But when the company started buckling under $1 billion in debt during the crisis, the Siegels' home went into foreclosure and was put up for sale. They cut back on the jet, took the kids out of private school and gave up some of their staff. (Read more: Social Media's Billion-Dollar Rollercoaster) So why is David Siegel — a man who defined excess and debt in the 2000s — now saying that debt and spending are ruining the country? I asked David and during a phone interview last night, and he told me that this was about his workers, not himself. He said his own finances have vastly improved. He has paid off all of his major lenders. "I have enough money for the rest of my life and enough to leave a good inheritance for our kids." He said the loan for Versailles is paid off and he's resuming construction on the home. "The elevators are going in and they're preparing to put in the marble." The deal with Versailles' lenders, he went on, worked out "better than I imagined," since he was allowed to go nine months without making any interest payments on the loan. Jackie has several offers for a new reality TV show "which we're in the process of ranking and evaluating," Siegel said. He has learned his own painful lesson from the debt crunch. "We cut back, we're lean and mean. That's what the rest of the country has to do." Siegel said he's not acting out of self interest, but for the interest of his workers. While Westgate has never been more profitable, the company has 5,000 fewer workers than in 2007. He said that if Obama is re-elected and imposes Obamacare and higher taxes, he may just have to let more of his remaining 7,000 workers go. He said he might even shut down the company. (Read more: Why Larry Ellison Needs a $4 Billion Loan) "The combination of Obamacare and taxes would be a disaster," he said." I would probably just call it a day and that would be a disaster." Siegel stressed that he wasn't out to intimidate his workers into voting for Romney. "I can't tell anyone to vote," he said. But he wants to make sure his workers made an informed choice. "I want my employees to be educated on what could happen to their future if the wrong person is elected." Below is the full email that Siegel sent to his employees Monday. (Siegel admitted to me that he used a similar email circulating on the web as "the basis" of his own email). Subject: Message from David Siegel Date:Mon, 08 Oct 2012 13:58:05 -0400 (EDT) From: [David Siegel] To: [All employees] To All My Valued Employees, As most of you know our company, Westgate Resorts, has continued to succeed in spite of a very dismal economy. There is no question that the economy has changed for the worse and we have not seen any improvement over the past four years. In spite of all of the challenges we have faced, the good news is this: The economy doesn't currently pose a threat to your job. What does threaten your job however, is another 4 years of the same Presidential administration. Of course, as your employer, I can't tell you whom to vote for, and I certainly wouldn't interfere with your right to vote for whomever you choose. In fact, I encourage you to vote for whomever you think will serve your interests the best.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1349879322962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:28:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879445054-30</Id><Topic><Title>obvious harry dokes and mir are the same person</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349876365951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Skunked (Pepe' LePew) aka burger_barn (booger boy) you are always looking for someone else to pay your way. You stink and that is a fact.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1349879445054</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:30:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879541886-31</Id><Topic><Title>Wynn On Obama: "I'll Be Damned If I Want To Have Him Lecture Me"</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349877906029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:05:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how much do you think billionaire wynn will make and save if romney wins??..i mean quoting wynn on this is stupid..of course he's for romney...HE'S A BILLIONAIRE!!</Msg><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1349879541886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:32:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879550462-32</Id><Topic><Title>Wynn On Obama: "I'll Be Damned If I Want To Have Him Lecture Me"</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349877906029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:05:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how much do you think billionaire wynn will make and save if romney wins??..i mean quoting wynn on this is stupid..of course he's for romney...HE'S A BILLIONAIRE!!</Msg><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1349879550462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:32:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880721181-33</Id><Topic><Title>Wynn On Obama: "I'll Be Damned If I Want To Have Him Lecture Me"</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349877906029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:05:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Based on hwaerddd Multiple Responses, You Poked Him the Eye Good!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349880721181</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:52:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349881428457-34</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Democrats so hateful and vulger?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349872152083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is that vulgar private schooling working for you?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349881428457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:03:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349881493834-35</Id><Topic><Title>obvious harry dokes and mir are the same person</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349876365951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have never asked nor had anyone pay my way fishbreath. Why don't we meet up to discuss our differences??</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349881493834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:04:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349881691503-36</Id><Topic><Title>The Radical Homosexuals infiltrating the United States Congress have a plan:</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349881085211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:58:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, like Romney and Ryan you want to minimize another 10% of the population because you don't believe in what they do or feel? I say we outlaw the Republican agenda to eliminate hate from this country. Republicans seem to hate most Americans and prove it every time they open their mouths.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349881691503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:08:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349881901795-37</Id><Title>Sesame Street to Obama: Big Bird ad doesn't fly!!</Title><Msg>How funny -- now even Big Bird is anti O'Bummer! Story on MSNBC so it has to be true!</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349881901795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:11:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882162822-38</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Auto Bailout in Peril</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349873944605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:59:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the least you could do is give Boortz credit when you steal his work" said one of the board dumbcrats -- most of whom, after stealing authors' work, NEVER give the authors credit for writing the actual story.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349882162822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:16:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349882269390-39</Id><Title>big surprise</Title><Msg>jooish billionaire david siegal supports romney and the romney tax cuts...this fine american even threatens to lay people off if obama wins...a fine , real american....a regular guy..a romney guy..a billionaire</Msg><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1349882269390</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882441760-40</Id><Topic><Title>obvious harry dokes and mir are the same person</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349876365951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you not ask MIR for "some free tickets to paradise" which I suppose for you would be to the Kent Bathhouse.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1349882441760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:20:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349882759275-41</Id><Title>Obama Personal Friend of VP Debate Moderator? Debate Already Tainted! ABC Panicked!</Title><Msg>ABC News scrambles to downplay Obama’s attendance at VP debate moderator’s wedding 12:10 AM 10/10/2012 Josh Peterson Tech Editor President Barack Obama was a guest at the 1991 wedding of ABC senior foreign correspondent and vice presidential debate moderator Martha Raddatz, The Daily Caller has learned. Obama and groom Julius Genachowski, whom Obama would later tap to head the Federal Communications Commission, were Harvard Law School classmates at the time and members of the Harvard Law Review. After TheDC made preliminary inquiries Monday to confirm Obama’s attendance at the wedding, ABC leaked a pre-emptive statement to news outlets including Politico and The Daily Beast Tuesday, revealing what may have been internal network pressure felt just days before Raddatz was scheduled to moderate the one and only vice-presidential debate Thursday night. Both Politico and The Daily Beast jumped to ABC and Raddatz’s defense. The Huffington Post, a liberal news outlet, joined them shortly thereafter, while calling “unusual” ABC’s attempt to kill the story before it gained wide circulation....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349882759275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:25:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349883319561-42</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Personal Friend of VP Debate Moderator? Debate Already Tainted! ABC Panicked!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349882759275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that anything like Mr. Justice Scalia dining with oil company executives the night before making a big decision for big oil?</Msg><Username>bronx_bomber_fan2009</Username><Timestamp>1349883319561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:35:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349885158525-43</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Personal Friend of VP Debate Moderator? Debate Already Tainted! ABC Panicked!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349882759275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Is that anything like Mr. Justice Scalia dining with oil company executives the night before making a big decision for big oil? " So, Mr. dumbocrat, why don't you tell us about that "big decision."</Msg><Username>parkplacebob</Username><Timestamp>1349885158525</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:05:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349885466972-44</Id><Title>Biden; time for Payback!!</Title><Msg>for dis'n America's #1 boss - Biden's gonna rib Ryan a new one... and yea, crazy uncle Joe is crazy enough to do it... !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349885466972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:11:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349886394754-45</Id><Topic><Title>obvious harry dokes and mir are the same person</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349876365951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I understand you are slightly mentally deficient but I believe you missed the sarcasm. First of all this imposter is not close to the original Mir, whom had a command of the English language this fake obviously lacks.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349886394754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:26:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349886721909-46</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Auto Bailout in Peril</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349873944605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:59:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GM Probablly will have File for Bankruptcy Again... this Time the Union and Union Retires will Take in the Shorts</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349886721909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:32:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349887052263-47</Id><Topic><Title>Biden; time for Payback!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349885466972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually Joe is too crazy to do it, even with the moderator of the debate on his side. Ryan has the facts on his side and most people are now able to smell the democrat's spin machine from miles away. The poor insane leftys are going to fail....again!</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1349887052263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:37:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349887243045-48</Id><Title>Gallup Likely Voter Poll Results -- Romney 49% / O'Bummer 47%</Title><Msg>Bye, bye, barack!</Msg><Username>parkplacebob</Username><Timestamp>1349887243045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:40:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349887399335-49</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Personal Friend of VP Debate Moderator? Debate Already Tainted! ABC Panicked!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349882759275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or for Justice Thomas wife being a lobbyist for Citizens United group?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349887399335</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:43:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349887623710-50</Id><Title>Massive job losses coming through out the Country if obama the clown is re-elected !!!</Title><Msg>So go ahead and vote yourself out of a job !! I don't make this up folks ! obama the clown is holding your pink slips in the back room or you would know this for fact. So good luck.</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349887623710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:47:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349887774976-51</Id><Topic><Title>Massive job losses coming through out the Country if obama the clown is re-elected !!!</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349887623710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:47:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No proof, no article to support your Bull just some d-head saying stupid things and expect everyone to believe it.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349887774976</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:49:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349888023535-52</Id><Title>There will be no massive job losses unless republican congress makes them</Title><Msg>The President signs bills that pass through congress. He does not write the bills. However, the republican party has stalled any bill that would make Obama look good. They pass unilateral bills in the House that they know won't pass in the Senate. They have voted 30 times to revoke the Affordable Care Act, knowing it would not pass the Senate. They have written dozens of bills on abortion and depriving women of reproductive health care knowing it would go nowhere. Who is at blame for this mess???? THE REPUBLICAN PARTY IS THE BLAME</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349888023535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:53:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349888079932-53</Id><Topic><Title>Massive job losses coming through out the Country if obama the clown is re-elected !!!</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349887623710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:47:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, go ahead don't believe me and vote for obama the clown then, but i'm estimating 2 to 5 million full time jobs to be lost.</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349888079932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:54:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349888166433-54</Id><Topic><Title>Massive job losses coming through out the Country if obama the clown is re-elected !!!</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349887623710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:47:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So who are you no one cares what you think</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349888166433</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:56:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349888376410-55</Id><Topic><Title>There will be no massive job losses unless republican congress makes them</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349888023535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:53:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your lost !! In the real world job are created by regular folks like you and me not the communist Govenment. You'll see !!</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349888376410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:59:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349888626127-56</Id><Topic><Title>Massive job losses coming through out the Country if obama the clown is re-elected !!!</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349887623710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:47:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, You'll see ! Oh how is the Communist thing going in Venezuela .</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349888626127</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:03:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349888990431-57</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Personal Friend of VP Debate Moderator? Debate Already Tainted! ABC Panicked!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349882759275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why didn't you answer the first question? "Or for Justice Thomas wife being a lobbyist for Citizens United group?' Wow, I didn't know that Clarence's wife is a Supreme Court member!!</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349888990431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:09:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349889228866-58</Id><Topic><Title>There will be no massive job losses unless republican congress makes them</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349888023535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:53:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps you can tell us just how many "jobs" bills that the House passed that never were even brought up for a vote in the Senate -- courtesy Happy Harry Reid. What was Harry afraid of -- perhaps a yes vote in the Senate -- forcing O'bummer's hand to either sign a "jobs" bill or to veto it and be proven to be the fraud that we all know he is.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349889228866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349889369407-59</Id><Topic><Title>Biden; time for Payback!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349885466972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans using facts - are we talking about the same Republicans on this earth..?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349889369407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:16:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349889577169-60</Id><Topic><Title>Massive job losses coming through out the Country if obama the clown is re-elected !!!</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349887623710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:47:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't get me wrong, I won't be happy about this. It will be a very sad event Alot of good people will be hurt.</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349889577169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:19:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349889701331-61</Id><Title>Tuesday 10-9 activity</Title><Msg>LAN Air 767 flown back to Everett, Wa. after painting at Portland. Air China 777 flown to Portland for painting. Flydubai 737 first flight American Airlines 737 first flight. Aeromexico 737 first flight. Hebel Airlines 737 first flight. Air India 787 flown from Fort Worth to Charleston, S.C. after painting. Lion Air 737 Delivered. ANA 787 had taxi test. Bad weather prevented first flight but it may fly today (10-10)</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1349889701331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:21:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349889945055-62</Id><Topic><Title>Biden; time for Payback!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349885466972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe Biden is a Well Recognized Buffoon... Even Obama is Scared of What the Buffoon may Say... Can't Wait for Ryan to Make the Moderator Dis-Qualifer Herself at the Beginning of the Debate... Ryan will Control the Debate and the Moderator! She is Dirty.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349889945055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:25:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349890733285-63</Id><Topic><Title>Tuesday 10-9 activity</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1349889701331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:21:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Appreciate the updates.</Msg><Username>mrstock52</Username><Timestamp>1349890733285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:38:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349890821938-64</Id><Topic><Title>Biden; time for Payback!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349885466972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Joe Biden is a Well Recognized Buffoon... Even Obama is Scared of What the Buffoon may Say... After all it WAS Joe that "outed" Barack's gay mariage stance -- the one that's now hurting Obama with Black churchgoers. Barack would have preferred to keep it a "secret" until November 7.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349890821938</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349890848910-65</Id><Topic><Title>BA Is Looking Good! BA Is Looking Good!</Title><Username>moody.cobb41</Username><Timestamp>1349872383039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:33:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nicceeeee, best there is in my opinion they make me money</Msg><Username>juanita.hull56</Username><Timestamp>1349890848910</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:40:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349891210847-66</Id><Topic><Title>There will be no massive job losses unless republican congress makes them</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349888023535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:53:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can call a pig a prom queen but it doesn't make it so. Those so called jobs bills did nothing but turn back environmental safety or decrease regulation that protected the public. The Republicans just called them jobs bills. More republican spin and nothing more.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349891210847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:46:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349891317367-67</Id><Topic><Title>Massive job losses coming through out the Country if obama the clown is re-elected !!!</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349887623710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:47:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please try to keep your attention deficit in check. What the heck does Venezuela have to do with anything? You can't write, you can't debate so you reflect!!!!</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349891317367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349891375614-68</Id><Topic><Title>Tuesday 10-9 activity</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1349889701331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:21:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349891375614</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349891689300-69</Id><Title>Biden, Obama's Buffoon, will Further Expose This Failed and Lying Presidency!</Title><Msg>Ryan will Crush the Buffoon Biden and Make Obama Look Like a Good Debater... ABCs Moderator Fiasco Will Make Matters Worse!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349891689300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:54:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349892125825-70</Id><Title>IMACCON If this is a done deal for Romney, why are you on this board all day playing the fool?</Title><Msg>If this is a done deal for Romney, why are you on this board all day playing the fool?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349892125825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:02:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349892252207-71</Id><Title>If Romney has it in the bag why are all you #$%$ on this board all day</Title><Msg>posting romney propaganda all day long to the more than 200 readers. No one reads this board you fools</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349892252207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:04:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349893011785-72</Id><Title>headlines today..........a billionaire ceo threatens workers jobs so he can have tax cuts from Rmoney</Title><Msg>headlines today..........a billionaire ceo threatens workers jobs so he can have tax cuts from Rmoney</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349893011785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:16:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349893115160-73</Id><Title>ABCs Moderator Fiasco Will Make Matters Worse! by IMMACOMM</Title><Msg>how does the moderator thing make things worse for Biden???</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349893115160</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:18:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349893293146-74</Id><Topic><Title>As Romney said, Obama just picks the losers …</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349875723138</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:28:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's all true about obama the clown.</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349893293146</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:21:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349893414977-75</Id><Topic><Title>Vegas Now Predicts a Romney Landslide Victory in November</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349800925542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:42:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUMP!</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349893414977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:23:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349894278435-76</Id><Topic><Title>big surprise</Title><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1349882269390</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A #$%$ blackmailer, that's what he is. Someone ought to spray him with some hot lead.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1349894278435</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349894911724-77</Id><Title>air india problem</Title><Msg>Reports indicate the hinge of an Air India 787 cargo door "disintegrated" and the door cannot be closed. Replacement parts are in transit to India. Air India instists that the hinge was not hit by anything. We will have to wiat and see what caused the "disintegration".</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1349894911724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:48:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349895816851-78</Id><Title>GALLUP: Obama Bouncing Back Already To 5-Point Lead</Title><Msg>President Barack Obama moved back to a 5-point lead over Mitt Romney, halting the Republican nominee's post-debate momentum. Obama now leads Romney 50 percent to 45 percent in Gallup's daily tracking poll. Romney had seen a big three-day post-debate move in the Gallup daily tracking poll, but today's results signal that his debate bump is beginning to level off. Earlier on Monday, Gallup released results of three days of post-debate, which showed that Romney had tied up the race with Obama in those three days of interviews. It also found that Romney was the biggest winner in the history of the presidential debates. Obama's approval rating — which has swung wildly in recent weeks — also ticked up to 51 percent, above the "safe" 50-percent threshold for an incumbent's re-election. Obama also bumped back up in the Rasmussen daily tracking poll. He is now tied with Romney after trailing by 2 points on Sunday. Read more: http://www.businessinsider.com/obama-vs-romney-gallup-poll-oct-8-results-2012-10#ixzz28vNbOFEs</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349895816851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:03:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349896403463-79</Id><Topic><Title>The 1 Percent's Cry for Justice</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1349894641638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:44:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All of the Misery has Come Under Obama's Watch... Black American Un-Employment at 13 Plus% Obama is Destroying the Middle Class and African Americans!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349896403463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:13:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349896652052-80</Id><Title>skunked again... a Fitting Moniker Gallup Still Showing Romney Ahead as of Today!</Title><Msg>New Gallup poll shows Mitt Romney vaulting into lead over President Obama Buoyed by his strong debate performance, Republican challenger has 49% to 47% lead over incumbent. Both Romney and President focus on key battleground state Ohio BY JONATHAN LEMIRE / NEW YORK DAILY NEWS PUBLISHED: TUESDAY, OCTOBER 9, 2012, 9:40 PM UPDATED: WEDNESDAY, OCTOBER 10, 2012, 7:28 AM CHARLIE NEIBERGALL/AP Republican challenger Mitt Romney surged to a 2-point lead over President Obama in latest Gallup poll. President Obama and Mitt Romney descended on the key swing state of Ohio on Tuesday, facing an election turned upside down. A new Gallup poll showed Romney pulling into the lead, energizing Republicans and demoralizing Democrats — a dramatic reversal of fortunes following Obama’s disastrous debate last week. The shifting landscape raised the stakes for Thursday night’s vice presidential debate, leaving Democrats suddenly hoping Vice President Biden can turn things around. Obama and Romney stumped in Ohio with just 28 days until the election, the final day for residents there to sign up to vote.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349896652052</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:17:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349896871762-81</Id><Topic><Title>skunked again... a Fitting Moniker Gallup Still Showing Romney Ahead as of Today!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349896652052</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:17:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just posted the article is all.............. if you don't like it write the wall street journal</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349896871762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349896912504-82</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's Tax Plan Is Not Mathematically Possible</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1349894877394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:47:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Name of the Author: Lousy Marxists, Says t All, Indeed!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349896912504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:21:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349897005987-83</Id><Title>immacomm is a whining baby</Title><Msg>end of message</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349897005987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:23:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349897147727-84</Id><Title>Romney will say anything</Title><Msg>ROMNEY THE LIAR WILL SAY ***ANYTHING*** ABOUT ABORTION We all KNOW that Willard is a sociopathic liar. We all KNOW that Willard will say ANYTHING to win. But this is getting absolutely ABSURD: “There’s no legislation with regards to abortion that I’m familiar with that would become part of my agenda,” the GOP presidential candidate told The Des Moines Register’s editorial board during a meeting today before his campaign rally at a Van Meter farm. What? WHAT? The candidate of the most militantly anti-abortion party in American political history is saying this?!? The man whose VP nominee is so radical that he refuses to allow for an abortion even for a woman who has been impregnated by a rapist?!? What in the HELL is Willard talking about?!? He's gone ON RECORD as saying he'd support a "personhood" amendment to the Constiution that would not only ban every kind of abortion for any reason but would even outlaw certain kinds of birth control. And wouldn't you know it, a few hours after Willard said this, his campaign was walking it back. Read all about it in this post from Angry Black Lady. (Better put on your fireproof suit.) This is part of a pattern with Willard. First, he claimed he was pro-choice. Then, he said he had an "epiphany" about abortion and swung around to opposing it--even as he still acted in Massachusetts to undermine anti-abortion efforts. (See this posting from February and this from this past Sunday.) Then he said he would outlaw all abortions. Then he said he'd make exceptions. Then he said he wouldn't be proposing any new laws on abortion. Then his campaign contradicted him the very same day. What's going on here? It's Romney the Liar doing what comes naturally--saying anything to win, no matter how fraudulent, no matter how dishonest.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349897147727</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:25:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897221001-85</Id><Topic><Title>immacomm is a whining baby</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349897005987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:23:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And he's dumb as roadkill too.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1349897221001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897228079-86</Id><Topic><Title>A liberal, a conservative and a moderate walk into a bar...</Title><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1349845411866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:03:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I'll have a 3 Virgin Mary's." he replied.</Msg><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1349897228079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897244033-87</Id><Topic><Title>IMACCON If this is a done deal for Romney, why are you on this board all day playing the fool?</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349892125825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reason iamaccom-ie spends all day on this finance board is Trailer Park life is very dull. iamaccom-ie using his many IDs breaks up the ennui by parrotting republiwhoppers the repub propaganda media apparatus tells him. iamaccomie's dull propaganda soaked "brain" is receptive to lies and deceptions because it is a total vacuum..</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1349897244033</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:27:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897253065-88</Id><Topic><Title>Romney will say anything</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349897147727</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:25:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Skunk... You Sound Really Nervous... Drink a Beer or Take Something, Geez......</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349897253065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:27:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897277975-89</Id><Topic><Title>A liberal, a conservative and a moderate walk into a bar...</Title><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1349845411866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:03:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>correction: "I'll have a 3 Virgin Marys." he replied.</Msg><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1349897277975</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:27:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349897309430-90</Id><Title>who done it, Lybia ambassador attack</Title><Msg>I suppose it would be fair to ask, what part in this did Hillary's senior adviser, ms Huma Abedin, play in this entire fiasco. She was connected and related to the Egypt Brotherhood. She would have know the risk and what was up. Did she act to keep the security detail small to assist the terrorist? Why hasn't Hillary and UN amb. Rice been fired yet?</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1349897309430</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:28:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897335987-91</Id><Topic><Title>IMACCON If this is a done deal for Romney, why are you on this board all day playing the fool?</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349892125825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>roger that</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349897335987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:28:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897391530-92</Id><Topic><Title>immacomm is a whining baby</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349897005987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:23:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hurting, Little Man, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349897391530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:29:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897394213-93</Id><Topic><Title>A liberal, a conservative and a moderate walk into a bar...</Title><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1349845411866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:03:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't there a drink called Smith?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349897394213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349897708477-94</Id><Title>Brave Black Actress Defies Racist Democratics / Socialists...</Title><Msg>CNN's Piers Morgan and Liberals are Racist... Actress Stacey Dash On Receiving Racist Hate For Supporting Romney Actress Stacey Dash talks about Romney and the recent Twitter backlash. Dash says she has heard from the Romney campaign but has heard nothing from the Obama campaign. "As a country, this is my choice. This is the man I want to lead my country. It's my right as an American citizen, it's my constitutional right to have my choice to who I want to vote for for president. And I chose him not by the color of his skin, but the content of his character," the actress told CNN's Piers Morgan.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349897708477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349898209761-95</Id><Title>Free Obama Phones Foreign Made. Why is Obama Outsourcing American Jobs?</Title><Msg>Slim Pickings: World’s Richest Man Gets Richer Supplying ‘Obamaphones’ to Poor By Perry Chiaramonte Published October 10, 2012 "The world's richest man"- Carlos Slim (AP) A Mexican telecom mogul who holds the title of world's richest man, and one of President Obama's top donors are both getting even richer from the U.S. government program that supplies so-called "Obamaphones" to the poor. Carlos Slim, who has an estimated net worth of $70 billion, owns a controlling stake in TracFone, which makes $10 per phone for each device it provides to poor Americans. The company, whose president and CEO is Frederick “F.J.” Pollak, also makes money from extra minutes and data plans it sells to subscribers who get phones and service through the government's Lifeline program. The program, which began in the mid-1980s, has exploded in the past four years after being expanded from supplying landlines to the poor to providing cellular phones. “I’m not against a company making a profit. If they are making money off lifeline, the blame goes to the federal government for creating the program." - Rep. Tim Griffin (R-AR) The phones came into the national spotlight after a viral video surfaced on YouTube in which a Cleveland, Ohio, woman praised the president, saying he needed to be re-elected because he gives out free phones. “Everybody in Cleveland, every minority, got an Obama phone. Keep Obama as president. He gave us a phone. He gonna do more,” the woman said in the video. Slim’s Movil America owns TracFone and recently snapped up service provider Simple Mobile for $100 million. TracFones and Simple Mobile service are huge players in the Lifeline program through the company's “SafeLink Wireless” brand. TracFone had 3.8 million subscribers through the federal program as of late 2011.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349898209761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:43:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349898567424-96</Id><Topic><Title>air india problem</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1349894911724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:48:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So which plant was this made at?</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1349898567424</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:49:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349898702014-97</Id><Topic><Title>Free Obama Phones Foreign Made. Why is Obama Outsourcing American Jobs?</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349898209761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can not beat free phones and free minutes. I read some folks have a dozen or more phones.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1349898702014</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:51:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349898716522-98</Id><Topic><Title>If Romney has it in the bag why are all you #$%$ on this board all day</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349892252207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:04:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because, Skunk, We are Putting the Peddle to the Metal... we want a Romney Landslide... and it's Looking Good! PS Seems you Read My Posts, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349898716522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:51:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349898810119-99</Id><Topic><Title>If Romney has it in the bag why are all you #$%$ on this board all day</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349892252207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:04:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If nobody reads this post you must have typed this or you are seeing things.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1349898810119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:53:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349898884406-100</Id><Title>BA gets $2B DOD contract for C-17 support</Title><Msg>ST. LOUIS, Oct. 10, 2012 /PRNewswire/ -- Boeing [NYSE: BA] will continue assuring the worldwide availability of C-17 aircraft, which provide vital military and humanitarian airlift capability, through a $2 billion follow-on contract it recently received from the U.S. Department of Defense.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1349898884406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:54:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349900038723-101</Id><Title>Obama's Carefully Scripted Fairy Tale has Come to an End! Exposed!</Title><Msg>The Debate Last Wednesday Exposed the President Who Has No Clothes... Naked, Scared, Lost! Even Bill Clinton said of Hussein, "The Biggest Fairy Tale I've Ever Seen"</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349900038723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:13:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349900640060-102</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's Tax Plan Is Not Mathematically Possible</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1349894877394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:47:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dik, You are stupid to Fall for the Joke... Pathetic!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349900640060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349901090251-103</Id><Title>LMAO the left-wing lunatics talking about what's Mathematically Possible</Title><Msg>Liberal always have been mathematically challenged they've never figured out what happens when your outflow is bigger than your income.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349901090251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:31:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349901324484-104</Id><Topic><Title>LMAO the left-wing lunatics talking about what's Mathematically Possible</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349901090251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:31:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals are Stupid... Ideologically Confined to the Dust Bin of History! Marxism is History... Millions Upon Millions Killed in the Failed Experiment.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349901324484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:35:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349901619025-105</Id><Title>ABC in Full Panic Mode! Obama Personal Friend with VP Moderator!</Title><Msg>Biased Media Exposed Again... Can't Wait to See How Paul Addresses the Moderator She will be On the Defensive!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349901619025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:40:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349901643081-106</Id><Title>We are the nation's Job Creators</Title><Msg>Rich people like myself are the ones that overwhelmingly create most new jobs. Yet the disaster-n-chief can't figure out why they aren't expanding and creating jobs when he is threatening and demonizing anyone who can create jobs. Community organizers see themselves as dragon slayers of the straw men they set up and demonize. This country desperately needs to pass the fair tax in order to stop the the erosion of property right by Marxists like Obama</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349901643081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:40:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349901930039-107</Id><Topic><Title>We are the nation's Job Creators</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349901643081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:40:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul, err, Dik How is the "Blue Wall" Standing, eh? You are an Idiot Dik, Paul or Whoever!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349901930039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:45:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349902108486-108</Id><Topic><Title>The Radical Homosexuals infiltrating the United States Congress have a plan:</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349881085211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:58:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wouldn't be paranoid if I said,"It's a GD conspiracy," would I?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1349902108486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:48:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349902213039-109</Id><Topic><Title>We are the nation's Job Creators</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349901643081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:40:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At Least you can Count to 100... Not Bad for a Liberal Fool!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349902213039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:50:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349902878709-110</Id><Topic><Title>The Radical Homosexuals infiltrating the United States Congress have a plan:</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349881085211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:58:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wouldn't be paranoid if I said,"It's a gd conspiracy," would I?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1349902878709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:01:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349903149634-111</Id><Topic><Title>We are the nation's Job Creators</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349901643081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:40:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People who Know, know Mir.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349903149634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:05:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349903187582-112</Id><Topic><Title>Mother of slain Navy SEAL Rips Roney To Pieces</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1349902931200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:02:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here we Go Again... Obama Politicizes the Deaths of an American Diplomat and Former SEALs.... How Low can Obama Go to Get Re-elected, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349903187582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349903747463-113</Id><Title>American Voters Divorcing Obama! Death Spiral, Flat Spin!</Title><Msg>Hey, Obama we’re just not that into you -- why voters are divorcing the president By Dr. Keith Ablow Published October 10, 2012 AP According to the latest Gallup poll, Mitt Romney has leapt from a significant deficit to a 2-point lead in the wake of his widely lauded Presidential debate performance. He is simultaneously closing in on Obama’s lead in several swing states. This dramatic change may turn out to be even more meaningful when viewed through a lens that properly values the psychological power of incumbency. A shift by the electorate away from an incumbent president has more in common with divorce than it does with opting against a second date. When Americans bond with a president for more than three years, the decision to back a different candidate often comes only after much soul-searching and an extreme level of discomfort. When real disappointment sets in, and voters finally voice their intention to support the challenger, their decision can be permanent. They may be saying that the relationship is, finally, beyond repair—that there is no going back. In my practice, marriages rarely end over a single event or disappointment. But, one event can, indeed, represent a breaking point when dissatisfaction has been simmering for months or years. The first presidential debate was such an event. For the sake of metaphor, think of any friend who has called you and, after a tumultuous, but passionate, relationship, finally, finally, come to the realization that her husband isn’t the man she thought he was—at all. Millions of voters may now have packed their bags and moved out, after a whirlwind romance with President Obama and a relatively short marriage marred by unemployment, constant arguing, name-calling, signs he never much liked them, anyhow , and one of those terrible nights... - It isn’t that her husband hasn’t failed her before; he has. But something happens to crystallize her intent to move on—a particularly harsh comment from him, a single and obvious lie (one too many). And when she announces she is leaving, and you hear resolve, rather than wistfulness, in her voice, you know she is not turning back. She isn’t making a show of packing her bags; she’s moving out. Finally. Well, millions of voters may now have packed their bags and moved out, after a whirlwind romance with President Obama and a relatively short marriage marred by unemployment, constant arguing, name-calling, signs he never much liked them, anyhow (at least not the patriotic ones), and one of those terrible nights (debate night) when (in those words that any man who has gravely disappointed a woman has heard) he “had nothing to say for himself.”</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349903747463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:15:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349903850456-114</Id><Title>Are You a Union Moocher?</Title><Msg>Alot of union folks are taken in by their union propaganda. They don't realize they have become union moochers. A union moocher is someone who takes more out of the company than he puts in. You can spot a union moocher by how he carries on. He pats himself on the back for getting the company once again above water and just at contract renewal time he unites with his fellow moochers to put a hole in the company thereby sinking the company with debt once again. This pattern is a recurring syndrome. Its up to you! End the vicious cycle and don't be a union moocher.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1349903850456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349904085322-115</Id><Topic><Title>Are You a Union Moocher?</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1349903850456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Union Member Robots Don't Realize the Union Bosses take the Workers Money and Spend on Themselves... Union Bosses Laugh All the Way to the Bank with Member's Dues....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349904085322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349905296510-116</Id><Topic><Title>Are You a Union Moocher?</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1349903850456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People laugh at you for a million reasons. So what's your point.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1349905296510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:41:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349906278992-117</Id><Topic><Title>Mother of slain Navy SEAL Rips Roney To Pieces</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1349902931200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:02:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is fair for the Seal's mother to desire her son's memory to not be part of politics. Unfortuntely, she just did: "He shouldn't make my son's death part of his political agenda. It's wrong to use these brave young men, who wanted freedom for all, to degrade Obama." With a little more focus on the facts, understandably clouded by grief, she would come to realize that a different outcome for the embassy and its occupants and defenders might have ensued had it not been for the apparent negligence of the Obama Adminstration.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1349906278992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:57:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349906525111-118</Id><Topic><Title>Mother of slain Navy SEAL Rips Roney To Pieces</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1349902931200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:02:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's what we like about you, Bob -- you are so forgiving!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1349906525111</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:02:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349908050274-119</Id><Topic><Title>Mother of slain Navy SEAL Rips Roney To Pieces</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1349902931200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:02:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, we can certainly forgive Obama, but it is appropriate to not forget his negligence when it comes time to vote in November. By the way, Chris, do a search on "Bulky" or "Blob", then look at what others have said to me, and then look at my responses. From that you can judge.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1349908050274</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349908922785-120</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is holding up Warn Notices for the vote...how many families just going to be dumped on the street</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349907243136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:14:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Companies issue WARN notices, you idiot, not the President.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1349908922785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:42:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349909139442-121</Id><Topic><Title>Are You a Union Moocher?</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1349903850456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats kinda like idiots like MBFIELD who parrot the ideas of the Tea Party, which is made up of idiots just like MBFIELD. Kind of a vicious circlejerk.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1349909139442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:45:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349910430270-122</Id><Topic><Title>Mother of slain Navy SEAL Rips Roney To Pieces</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1349902931200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:02:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I leave judging to you.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1349910430270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:07:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349910887164-123</Id><Topic><Title>Vegas Now Predicts a Romney Landslide Victory in November</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349800925542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:42:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Going to happen!</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349910887164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:14:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349910936116-124</Id><Topic><Title>Massive job losses coming through out the Country if obama the clown is re-elected !!!</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349887623710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:47:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes sir.</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349910936116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:15:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349911296252-125</Id><Topic><Title>Mother of slain Navy SEAL Rips Roney To Pieces</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1349902931200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:02:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Criticizing policy mistakes is fair game. Pretending for the sake of political theater that he was deeply and personally affected by the death of an individual he once shook hands with is just plain crass. Read or listen to the mother's own words on the Ross &amp; Burbank blog at KIRO-FM Seattle: But Barbary Doherty questions Romney's account of the meeting and his motives for recounting the story on the stump. "If Mitt Romney met him and was so moved by him, I'm just wondering why someone from his office never called to see what they could do and I have never received a note of condolence from anybody in that party," she said. Doherty said her son never mentioned meeting Romney, saying it most likely "wasn't too meaningful." She's not the only one questioning Romney's account. A close friend of Doherty's told The Ron and Don Show Glen had a much different recollection of the meeting. "He said it was very comical," Elf Ellefsen said in an interview with producer Libby Denkman. , "Mitt Romney approached him ultimately four times, using this private gathering as a political venture to further his image. He kept introducing himself as Mitt Romney, a political figure. The same introduction, the same opening line. Glen believed it to be very insincere and stale." Ellefson said Romney's use of Doherty for his campaign "makes him sick."</Msg><Username>barking_dogmas</Username><Timestamp>1349911296252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:21:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349911498182-126</Id><Topic><Title>Mother of slain Navy SEAL Rips Roney To Pieces</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1349902931200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:02:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sure ain't just a woofin about that, Chris ;-P</Msg><Username>barking_dogmas</Username><Timestamp>1349911498182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:24:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349912871712-127</Id><Topic><Title>Mother of slain Navy SEAL Rips Roney To Pieces</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1349902931200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:02:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cop out. You are sensitive because of our last exchange. Here is what you said and how I saw it: You suggested to me that I should "put down my Bible", read something (which I did just for you, though I skimmed it as it was too long) that clearly was of a belief of Deism which denies the person and purpose of Jesus as well as the authority of the Bible as the Word of God. And, you also dismissed the Apostle John's Book of Revelation as being no more "revealing" than the Book of Mormon or the Koran. I responded that you have now given me an idea of your belief system. It is possible that you were, as they say, "pulling my leg". But that did not come out that way. Taking for granted that you were telling me what was true to your beliefs, I could only conclude that you deny the authority of Jesus as Savior, because it is only in the Bible, the document that you told me to "put down", where that is conveyed. It is really an all or nothing proposition. No fence posting. You became angry as a result of my statement, accusing me of arrogance. Yet it was you that gave away your thoughts and position. Did I somehow read you wrong? You may be angry that I even said anything, but it is my position that I am in the same theater with everyone else and, on occasion, it is my responsibility, according to the Bible, to warn the others of the fire - that is, hell fire. Interestingly, if you were "born again", you would understand and actually appreciate my motive. We are on this earth relative to eternity for the equivlent of a vapor that appears for a little while and then vanishes away. At our age, we know that more than we did when we were youngsters.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1349912871712</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:47:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349914192795-128</Id><Topic><Title>Mother of slain Navy SEAL Rips Roney To Pieces</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1349902931200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:02:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You guys are way over the top in criticism of Romney. He said nothing but kind words for the slain Navy Seal. The story is odd, but so what? But, in case you feel that he is simply lying, and I can't prove it one way or the other, here are some facts: 1. The account takes place at Christmastime, where it is then very cold back east, and way warmer in San Diego. 2. Romney has a house in San Diego (i.e., La Jolla). 3. The Navy Seal training is at the Coronado Naval Amphibious Base which is in San Diego 4. Romney demonstrated at the first debate in which Obama tanked big time that he has an excellent memory. The facts point to the account as being plausible.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1349914192795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:09:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349917457086-129</Id><Topic><Title>The Radical Homosexuals infiltrating the United States Congress have a plan:</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349881085211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:58:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have to have a pretty sharp eye to spot a g-a-y-w-a-d in congress. "Yeah man,he's ok. Oh boy,he's a limp wrister!" It's when they get into the Department of Education that I start to worry!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1349917457086</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349918041684-130</Id><Topic><Title>Vegas Now Predicts a Romney Landslide Victory in November</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349800925542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:42:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe Romney will win over Obama about as easily as I crush peanuts in their shells!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1349918041684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:14:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349918078397-131</Id><Topic><Title>Mother of slain Navy SEAL Rips Roney To Pieces</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1349902931200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:02:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No matter, it was still crass.</Msg><Username>barking_dogmas</Username><Timestamp>1349918078397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:14:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349920984287-132</Id><Topic><Title>Are You a Union Moocher?</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1349903850456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing Co revenue per employee: $400,320 net income per employee: $23,000 I'm on the high end of the Union scale and Boeing is making a net profit of 12% off of me. Of course companies like Apple that use a large fraction of semi-slave labor does better</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1349920984287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:03:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349921990174-133</Id><Topic><Title>We are the nation's Job Creators</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349901643081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:40:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mir(de) is telling another whopper. There is no middle class that DEMANDS things and if Mir(de) was an actual business person he would know this. It's apparently fun for folks to impersonate others, but in this case Mir(de) is a transparent liar.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1349921990174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349922829344-134</Id><Topic><Title>Are You a Union Moocher?</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1349903850456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MBfield is delusional this time, even worse than usual. Perhaps if he could find a good union job he wouldn't be so jealous. Fat chance on that ever happening.</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1349922829344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:33:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>