<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-12"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355314676106-1</Id><Title>North Korea's New Leader Burnishes Credentials With Rocket</Title><Msg>North Korea slaps Obama’s face for the third time. Thank you sir may I have another. http://www.cnbc.com/id/100302990</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1355314676106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 07:17:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355316333349-2</Id><Topic><Title>Deduct SPEEA Union Workers Pay</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1355236052422</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 09:27:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice concept big problem. You would penalize almost every large company in the U.S. From Auto to Zippo Lighters. Remeber the big bad UAW allowing cars to be built in Canada and Mexico. So much for American Auto workers</Msg><Username>yankeefan629</Username><Timestamp>1355316333349</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 07:45:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355323095910-3</Id><Title>lets hold $76.00 then^^^^^^^^</Title><Msg>If the $76.00 holds all day then we will see $80.00 VERY SOON$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1355323095910</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 09:38:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355323174782-4</Id><Topic><Title>Strong rumor out of Chicago: Boeing purchasing land in Michigan for 3rd major assembly location</Title><Username>yb4itohitsfree</Username><Timestamp>1355321962434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 09:19:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BEWARE - That's a VIRUS infested site. You should go to PRISON!</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1355323174782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 09:39:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355323447172-5</Id><Topic><Title>Strong rumor out of Chicago: Boeing purchasing land in Michigan for 3rd major assembly location</Title><Username>yb4itohitsfree</Username><Timestamp>1355321962434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 09:19:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? Makes sense. Michigan is now a right to work state. The Detroit area has been devistated by unionism. Property is dirt cheap. Michigan now ranks 3rd in attracting high tech jobs that are good paying jobs. Michigan use to be 19 th in salary level with Detroit city having lots of millionaires, lots of attractions to the city, now unionism has turned it buttugly. A wasteland with homes going for $1,000. Now it is 40th in salary, and Detroit driving the state to bankruptcy. Those that want to work have left the state for other right to work states. The population is 1/2 what it once was. Good to see the state coming back.</Msg><Username>sayfu32</Username><Timestamp>1355323447172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 09:44:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355325003768-6</Id><Topic><Title>Strong rumor out of Chicago: Boeing purchasing land in Michigan for 3rd major assembly location</Title><Username>yb4itohitsfree</Username><Timestamp>1355321962434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 09:19:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Right to Work" -- is that anything like "Citizens United", in the sense that it's an egregious misnomer?</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1355325003768</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:10:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355325272252-7</Id><Title>Climate hero says, "Hurricane Sandy cannot be attributed to climate change."</Title><Msg>From the Huffington Post. On December 7, President Bill Clinton appeared in Silicon Valley and talked at length about climate change, referring to Berkeley scientist Dr. Richard Muller as "a hero of mine." In a Fresh Dialogues interview, Muller agreed to share his reaction to the hero worship and answer some climate change questions. You may recall Dr. Muller, the self-described "former skeptic" who frequently emphasized the fallibility of research on global warming and was funded by the Koch Foundation. Last summer, after thorough research with the Berkeley Earth project, he announced his dramatic conversion in an op-ed in the New York Times. Now he concludes that global warming is happening, and that humans are essentially responsible for all of the warming in the last 250 years. I happened to be sitting next to Dr. Muller last week, and although he was whisked backstage by some big secret service staffers after Clinton's speech, he agreed to answer a few Fresh Dialogues questions by email about his research and how he feels about hero worship by number 42. You might be surprised to learn three things about Dr. Muller: 1. He says Hurricane Sandy cannot be attributed to climate change. 2. He suggests individually reducing our carbon footprint is pointless -- we need to "think globally and act globally," by encouraging the switch from coal to gas power in China and developing nations. He's a fan of "clean fracking." 3. He says climate skeptics deserve our respect, not our ridicule. Muller said he hopes that Berkeley Earth will be able to coordinate with the Clinton Foundation on their mutual goal of mitigating global warming.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355325272252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:14:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355325814106-8</Id><Topic><Title>Climate hero says, "Hurricane Sandy cannot be attributed to climate change."</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355325272252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:14:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only way to change global warming that takes place around the globe all the time is to change the temperature of the sun. Any of you libs know how to do that? Otherwise we do have technology to cleanup the coal burning, and are utilizing it. And natural gas? Libs in this country obstruct the supply. Libs are the problem, not fossil fuel utilization.</Msg><Username>sayfu32</Username><Timestamp>1355325814106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:23:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355326857357-9</Id><Topic><Title>Climate hero says, "Hurricane Sandy cannot be attributed to climate change."</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355325272252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:14:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't have a clue. People who actually have to live with fracking in their vicinity are extremely upset about the damages it is causing. Water supplies are being rendered non-potable for generations to come, and humans and livestock are showing signs of disease, just so that you can live the high life here and now. And to 'ell with the future and your grand-grandchildren, eh?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1355326857357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:40:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355327769504-10</Id><Title>Dreamliner pr will never be what we had hoped.</Title><Msg>The plane is going on 4 years behind in production. The plane has new issues every month. Boing will never get them out the door at the rated needed. BA is selling the planes now at half cost. BA will not get it down enough to make money. Boeing is used to deals the the millitary and can run costs up 500 percent and nobody cares.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1355327769504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:56:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355328002810-11</Id><Topic><Title>There's Not A Single Spending Cut That Republican Voters Support</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355255229055</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 14:47:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>theres an old saying; thouest does not know own #$%$ from hole in the ground !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355328002810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:00:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355328066262-12</Id><Topic><Title>No Government program</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1355270590848</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 19:03:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and checkn should go away on a honeymoon together. You fit like two peas in a pod. Can't say which one of you is more stupid and ignorant -- it's a toss up.</Msg><Username>demfascists45</Username><Timestamp>1355328066262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:01:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355328270967-13</Id><Title>Republicanism is a disease...</Title><Msg>its true, Republicanism is a disease... but its curable !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355328270967</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:04:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355328314173-14</Id><Topic><Title>Climate hero says, "Hurricane Sandy cannot be attributed to climate change."</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355325272252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:14:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A salient comment and I think scientist are beginning to recognize that things other than CO2 are problematic. Jason Box and Drew Shindell (a lead IPCC author) both Arctic experts, now are convinced that most of the Arctic/Greenland ice melt is due to black carbon that has reduced the albedo of ice significantly and this leads to more absorption of the Sun's radiation thus increasing ice melt in essence changing the temperature of the Sun. Scientist have drilled deep into Eastern Antarctic glaciers and found that they are not melting at the base as they had assumed and predicted. The ICESAT satellite data indicates that the ice mass balance in the Antarctic overall has been increasing by 49Gt/year since 2002 so ice melt is only happening at the North Pole. There is a proposal on the table to reduce the Sun's energy locally using water to manufacture more clouds, in the Arctic only so as not to effect any other area of the planet, to overcome the albedo loss to stop Greenland Ice loss. That would be the end of Sea level rise from Greenland ice melt and the ice mass being gained in the Antarctic would mean sea level reduction. So while we can't change the temperature of the Sun we can change the temperature effects of the Sun.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355328314173</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:05:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355328693914-15</Id><Title>I Love it when i wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Msg>woo hoo !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355328693914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:11:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355329568069-16</Id><Topic><Title>Climate hero says, "Hurricane Sandy cannot be attributed to climate change."</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355325272252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:14:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I share your concerns about dirty fracking and Professor Muller must also because he specifically mentioned "clean fracking". Is there such a thing as "clean fracking? Yes according to a new review from MIT where the IEA reports it can be made clean. _________________________________________________________________ But according to the IEA report, that doesn’t seem to be the problem in most cases. Fracking usually takes place hundreds of meters below aquifers, and it’s easy to stop the propagation of fractures. Cracking the rock requires high pressures. Stop applying the pressure, and the rock fracturing stops. However, some fracking sites are relatively near to the level of drinking water, and the IEA suggests it might make sense to ban the procedure at such locations. The IEA says the contaminated water is most likely the result of producers building substandard natural-gas wells, which are lined with metal casings and cement to keep the natural gas from contaminating aquifers. But in some cases, producers have done a poor job of cementing, allowing channels for natural gas to form. “Whenever there was a gas leakage, it came out because the cement was not well done,” says Franz-Josef Ulm, a civil and environmental engineering professor at MIT. That problem could be solved by cementing properly and then carefully monitoring the well’s integrity. “When it comes to cementing, the solutions are out there. The question is whether they are being applied,” Ulm says. _______________________________________________________________________ Like anything else the degree of safety is dependent on the degree of safety and caution applied. If Boeing didn't employ caution with established SOPs to ensure safety, flying would be leathal and unsafe. The same applies to fracking and the risks are not much different between flying and fracking IMO, and as long as safe procedures are put in place the risk can be reduced to the level of the risk of flying.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355329568069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:26:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355330590355-17</Id><Topic><Title>Climate hero says, "Hurricane Sandy cannot be attributed to climate change."</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355325272252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:14:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$. The EPA even had to change their view on the fracking damage to the water supply. With egg on their face, they retracted their earlier view that damage was being done to the water supply! Even Democrat Governors are welcoming the industry for the revenue it is creating. You libs just create baseless hysteria amongst the ignorant masses.</Msg><Username>sayfu32</Username><Timestamp>1355330590355</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:43:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355333604551-18</Id><Topic><Title>Climate hero says, "Hurricane Sandy cannot be attributed to climate change."</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355325272252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:14:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is the V-22 Osprey program an example of caution with established SOPs to ensure safety? Is the BP oil spill in the Gulf an example of caution with established SOPs to ensure safety?</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355333604551</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 12:33:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355333732590-19</Id><Topic><Title>Republicanism is a disease...</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355328270967</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:04:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Con-version therapy at a young age ?</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1355333732590</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 12:35:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355335021028-20</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke the Chairman said a month before the election Obamas policies do not support a recover now</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1355333306001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 12:28:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what executive order is that?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1355335021028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 12:57:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355335341541-21</Id><Title>South Carolina, Almost Heaven</Title><Msg>Well hush my mouth and call me Cornpone, It's the lil' ole south. I can't wait to get my new job.</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1355335341541</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:02:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355335937257-22</Id><Title>There was no law suit by Obama against Sinclair.</Title><Msg>You are ignorant. The law suit was between Sinclair and a man known as Daniel Parisi. Sure, Sinclair claims to have had sex with Obama but has no proof but there was never a liber suit brought by Obama. It was brought by Parisi because Sinclair claimed that Parisi had been paid to falsify. Parisi had no evidence that his Sinclair's claim was false so the suit was dropped. However, the suit NEVER involved Obama. Now if I could find that in 5 minutes why do you keep pressing this vicious lie?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1355335937257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:12:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355336043104-23</Id><Title>Suit never involved Obama</Title><Msg>You are ignorant. The law suit was between Sinclair and a man known as Daniel Parisi. Sure, Sinclair claims to have had sex with Obama but has no proof but there was never a libel suit brought by Obama. It was brought by Parisi because Sinclair claimed that Parisi had been paid to falsify lie detector tests. Parisi had no evidence that his Sinclair's claim was false so the suit was dropped. However, the suit NEVER involved Obama. Now if I could find that in 5 minutes why do you keep pressing this vicious lie?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1355336043104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:14:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355336565245-24</Id><Title>Boeing Re-training workers to say" Welcome to MacDonalds"</Title><Msg>Cuz they're gonna need it !!!!!!</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1355336565245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:22:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355336684601-25</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke the Chairman said a month before the election Obamas policies do not support a recover now</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1355333306001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 12:28:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The American(USA) version of the Soviet era gulags?</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355336684601</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:24:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355336758434-26</Id><Title>Just read mitt won the lie of the year award</Title><Msg>for his Jeep ad. How appropriate.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1355336758434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:25:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355336879154-27</Id><Topic><Title>Suit never involved Obama</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1355336043104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:14:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lying is all he has.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1355336879154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:27:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355337074061-28</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when i wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355328693914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:11:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When I wake up Obama is still an illegal immigrant committing the biggest fraud in American history. Sheriff Arpaio is right about your illegal immigrant president. Obama also has a sordid past that his supporters are not willing to acknowledge,even to themselves. America could do much better. Although I don't support Hillary I will admit that Hillary would have been a much better choice as president. At least Hillary is not radicalized like Obama.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1355337074061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:31:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355337362246-29</Id><Topic><Title>BA could possibly end up being the stock to monitor this week.</Title><Username>bullockderrick124</Username><Timestamp>1355318230872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 08:17:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>track record so goooooooooooood.</Msg><Username>kirkraymond625</Username><Timestamp>1355337362246</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:36:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355337900018-30</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when i wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355328693914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:11:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary, Obama, Bill? They all come from the same school! Don't try differentiating one from the other. They are all the same!</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355337900018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:45:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355338052739-31</Id><Topic><Title>Climate hero says, "Hurricane Sandy cannot be attributed to climate change."</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355325272252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:14:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First let me say that I am no arguing that fracking in any manner is good. It must be done safely and according to the expert scientists that study the science, fracking can be done in a safe manner just like flying can be done in a safe manner. Do disagree with me on this? If so then I need to hear your specific reasons why you disagree with the majority of scientists. Next you chose to offer false equivalence when you cite the Gulf oil spill to compare to fracking. A more appropriate comparison would have been to examine the the fracking that has already being done to access geothermal energy as described at last years AGU meeting. Are you against geothermal fracking for clean energy and are you making claims against it too? __________________________________________ EnergyTomorrow Blog In the news: Projects are advancing that use hydraulic fracturing to crack “hot rocks” thousands of feet below the earth’s surface and turn them into geothermal energy-producing zones. Some say it could start a revolution in electricity generation. Certainly, this map from the Energy Department’s National Renewals Lab, posted on the EnerGeo Politics blog, suggests there’s lots of hot-rock energy beneath the United States – especially in the West: The blog highlights one geothermal fracking venture – linking to this article by E&amp;E Greenwire that describes how highly pressurized water can fracture hot rocks, through which water later can be pumped, heated and reclaimed for electricity generation: "AltaRock will inject 24 million gallons of water at roughly 46 degrees Fahrenheit into these hot rocks to build a large network of small cracks. If all goes according to plan, the company will be able to circulate water through the rock and suck it out of newly drilled wells, scalding hot and ready for use in an eventual power plant." Even though it’s geothermal energy, this version of hydraulic fracturing has opponents – who sound and act like those who oppose fracking to develop clean-burning natural gas. In Oregon, where AltaRock plans operations, some are complaining despite a wealth of field experience that shows fracking is safe. E&amp;E quotes Linda Christian, the Bureau of Land Management project manager: “It perplexes me. No matter how much information you give people, if their minds are made up, their minds are made up.” ______________________________________________________ And when a closed mind is made up that mind finds it easy to dismiss scientific evidence that fracking can be done safely.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355338052739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:47:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355338132013-32</Id><Topic><Title>Climate hero says, "Hurricane Sandy cannot be attributed to climate change."</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355325272252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:14:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should read, "If not then I need to hear your specific reasons why you disagree with the majority of scientists."</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355338132013</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:48:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355338332260-33</Id><Topic><Title>There was no law suit by Obama against Sinclair.</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1355335937257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:12:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do a search for the "Down low club" to learn more about Obama's membership in this fagot club!</Msg><Username>tomfranklin96753</Username><Timestamp>1355338332260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:52:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355338513102-34</Id><Topic><Title>Climate hero says, "Hurricane Sandy cannot be attributed to climate change."</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355325272252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:14:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess those that gave me a thumbs down rating would rather see Greenland continue to melt and the people in the Maldive drown. :-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355338513102</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:55:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355339842278-35</Id><Topic><Title>Climate hero says, "Hurricane Sandy cannot be attributed to climate change."</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355325272252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:14:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are supporting the bogus notion that man has caused global warming the legitimate scientific comminuty has given you a thumbs down. At one point there were over 600 scientists around the globe that said it was a bogus notion.</Msg><Username>sayfu32</Username><Timestamp>1355339842278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 14:17:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355341361852-36</Id><Topic><Title>Climate hero says, "Hurricane Sandy cannot be attributed to climate change."</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355325272252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:14:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I only support science and truth. 600 seems very low to me. There's more than 600 in the Russian Academy of Sciences alone. :-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355341361852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 14:42:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355341411554-37</Id><Title>Bernanke on economic growth</Title><Msg>Bernanke says today that he has lowered economic growth predictions....that unemployment will stay above 6,5% through 2015 !! HAHAHA But you libs ddin't like Bush's economic growth out of a recession that grew to 4.5% GDP for a record length of time, and unemployment dropped to 4.5% throughout that time frame? Pain and misery throughout Obama's tenure, while Bush brought us out of a ression in less than 9 mo. with his tax cuts.</Msg><Username>sayfu32</Username><Timestamp>1355341411554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 14:43:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355342120859-38</Id><Topic><Title>Just read mitt won the lie of the year award</Title><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1355336758434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:25:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Multiple outfits granted this dubious award.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1355342120859</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 14:55:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355342236664-39</Id><Topic><Title>Suit never involved Obama</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1355336043104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:14:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Checkn finds a goofy weirdo homophobic story related to his latent homesexual tendencies, latches on, repeats 25,000 times trying to make it true. Poor lad. Imagine living inside that brain.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1355342236664</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 14:57:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355342349220-40</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when i wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355328693914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:11:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Enjoy the next four years..!!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355342349220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 14:59:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355342583809-41</Id><Topic><Title>Republicanism is a disease...</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355328270967</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:04:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... something more potent that kills cancer !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355342583809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 15:03:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355343713262-42</Id><Topic><Title>Republicanism is a disease...</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355328270967</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:04:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's what the socialist elite tell you about Republicans? They also tell you that you are stupid. That you can't take care of yourself, and never will be able to. They invite you ontol the govt plantaition, care for you, and you feed at the govt trough. Of course you have to agree to vote for them, and give up many individual freedoms, but you are more than happy to do that.</Msg><Username>sayfu32</Username><Timestamp>1355343713262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 15:21:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355344045236-43</Id><Topic><Title>South Carolina, Almost Heaven</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1355335341541</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:02:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I sail into Charleston harbor every summer. I love the city. From what I undersand everyone at Boing is not happy. The 787 is jacked up so everyone is #$%$ off. You can get weed just like Washington state that has it legal.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1355344045236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 15:27:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355348122918-44</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when i wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355328693914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:11:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be sure too because I'm going on welfare starting tommorrow and you're going to enjoy paying for it. Thank You</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1355348122918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:35:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355348493774-45</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Re-training workers to say" Welcome to MacDonalds"</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1355336565245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:22:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe but it will be done in Chinese. Note that the Chinese are trying to buy AIG and it aircraft purchasing leasing dept. One of the biggest buyers of Boeing airplanes and heavily into Boeing's retirement packages. Learn how to bow to the Chinese officials when they tour the plants checking up on their property.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1355348493774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:41:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355350251842-46</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when i wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355328693914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:11:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey buttlicker... thanking your master is a start.... Ive always been paying for your welfare lovin #$%$... !!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355350251842</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 17:10:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355353878053-47</Id><Topic><Title>There was no law suit by Obama against Sinclair.</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1355335937257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:12:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How old are you, wimp? That's second-grade trash coming out of your facehole.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1355353878053</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 18:11:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355354834474-48</Id><Topic><Title>to a Libturd balancing one owns check book is as foreign as a GOP</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1355353833822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 18:10:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Easy there, tiger.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1355354834474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 18:27:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355354883313-49</Id><Topic><Title>The GOP is dying</Title><Username>spartacus778899</Username><Timestamp>1354884997085</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 07:56:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Genna/Gerbil ID hybrid ..Its not about ad homiens about human weakness...there is enough of that to go around for ANY political persuasion. ITs about saving the rule of law and specifically the Bill of Rights and everything Thomas Jefferson and the founding fathers stood for...in short its about liberty and ideals and principles...somthing you DON'Tunderstand...and perhaps never well. You can go back to your regularly scheduled programming and making a lame attempt at being trendy and kool.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355354883313</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 18:28:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355355071892-50</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke on economic growth</Title><Username>sayfu32</Username><Timestamp>1355341411554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 14:43:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tax cuts for the wealthy? How do you libtards come up with that story line? Bush gave back 10% of the taxes paid for federal taxes to ANYONE that paid federal taxes. If Joe working Blow paid in $1,000 for federal taxes he got back $100. Very simple, not for the rich, for ANYONE that paid in. And why? Bush and the GOP thought it would stimulate the economy. That folks gettting a rebate would invest it. How'd it work?....created the longest, and strongest economic boom in American history!!!!!!! Govt Tax coffers overflowed! Unemployment dropped to 4.5% and GDP grew to 4.5% for 5 2 straight mo's. Now how is that tax cuts for the rich? Please tell us how you come to that false bunch of libtard #$%$.</Msg><Username>sayfu32</Username><Timestamp>1355355071892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 18:31:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355355385584-51</Id><Title>Obama supports Eugenics in Africa</Title><Msg>Yep...its hip and liberal and trendy to support Undeclared Unprovoked aggressive wars. If Obama wins a Peace PRize then they are "loving" bombs Yep...its hip and trendy to claim Obama loves African Americans cause AFTER ALL...HE is half black...and the Liberal blacks such as Jamie Foxx can prance around and laugh and say "We are winning" You phonies havent won ANYTHING...In fact Obama, through his Globalist Eugenics Boss's at places like the Rockefeller Foundation and Annenberg foundation are actively involved in Killing africans in the ancestral home of Blacks....keep on living on Fantasy island boys. ------------------------------------- “Population stabilization, the true meaning behind family planning is evident in the World Bank and UN Population Fund’s push against sovereign nations to reduce their populations by rule of the “global consensus” which dictates human rights policy by deeming some fit to live and others not… [T]he best way to achieve population stabilization is to coerce the nation’s citizens that they freely choose abortion and not having a child at all as part of an acceptable societal norm.” “By 2020, [eco-fascist] Melinda Gates hopes to extend the use of forced sterilization through manipulation of foreign governments to further the scheme of preventing 80 million of “unwanted pregnancies” in places like Africa, India and Southeast Asia. Gates believes she can prevent 40% of people who would otherwise have been born, thereby justifying family planning as a scheme to make women healthier who have “families are more successful and their communities are more prosperous.” Read the entire article here… This is the true agenda of liberals, progressives, globalists and eco-fascists like Gates and Vermont’s Peter Shumlin and #$%$ Bill McKibben who continue to push the defunct theory of global warming aka climate change on an unsuspecting, uncritical public. Human engineers (eugenicists), claim that overpopulation is the cause of the world’s ills and as such, any means necessary are justified to bring people under control. These are power hungry madmen and women.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355355385584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 18:36:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355355808004-52</Id><Topic><Title>The GOP is dying</Title><Username>spartacus778899</Username><Timestamp>1354884997085</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 07:56:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats probably because all the money was taken, used to give the wealthy republican base their tax cuts for the past twenty five years. They knew since the 1960s that the baby boomers were going to retire in full force around now, but instead of feeding the surplus for those heavy years when 76 million baby boomers were going to retire and need to collect social security, they dipped into the social security piggy bank and used it for all their own selfish goals. Now there is nothing left and guess what, they are now trying to kill the programs even though many individuals put into it for years. If we let them get away with this one, we are really stupid.</Msg><Username>flyininmytaxi</Username><Timestamp>1355355808004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 18:43:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355356230272-53</Id><Topic><Title>Obama supports Eugenics in Africa</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355355385584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 18:36:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where did this come from loony bird? World Net Daily or one of the other idiot-based paranoid rags you read? No wonder you got booted from the Air Force on a section 8.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1355356230272</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 18:50:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355356611613-54</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke on economic growth</Title><Username>sayfu32</Username><Timestamp>1355341411554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 14:43:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds about right. It was nice of him to keep this news to himself until after the election and nice to see that he left himself room in to revise it upward in 2016 right before the next election when magical thinking will again promote the idea that a 20 trillion deficit and increased government programs are turning things around and we need to stay the course. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355356611613</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 18:56:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355359153218-55</Id><Topic><Title>The GOP is dying</Title><Username>spartacus778899</Username><Timestamp>1354884997085</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 07:56:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone who thinks in terms of a "Genna/Gerbil ID hybrid" can never hope to be taken for sane.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1355359153218</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 19:39:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355359888939-56</Id><Topic><Title>Obama supports Eugenics in Africa</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355355385584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 18:36:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would gladly post a link...but in the NEW Yahoo board mechanics, posting links is forbidden. Proof is forbidden. Be proud</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355359888939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 19:51:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355360714968-57</Id><Topic><Title>The GOP is dying</Title><Username>spartacus778899</Username><Timestamp>1354884997085</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 07:56:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whatever you say Nowarrantneeded... I shoot I score...har har har</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355360714968</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 20:05:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355361489112-58</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Re-training workers to say" Welcome to MacDonalds"</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1355336565245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:22:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? Seems unlikely ... You seem to be the one who needs re-training. You can't even spell McDonald's correctly.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1355361489112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 20:18:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355362570605-59</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke the Chairman said a month before the election Obamas policies do not support a recover now</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1355333306001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 12:28:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is opening up closed prisons maybe because of this!?: Next 9/11: Iran’s Death Squad is Here! Wednesday, December 12, 2012 Iran has infiltrated a team of Quds Force terrorist leaders into the United States to attack from within in 2013, according to a source. The source within the office of Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, the supreme leader of the Islamic regime, said the team is to create instability in America through terrorism should the U.S. fail to accept the regime’s illicit nuclear program, increase sanctions, confront Iran militarily or intervene in the Syrian civil war. Members of the team, no more than 10 Quds Force officers, each lead cells totaling about 50 terrorists already in the U.S. The source is risking his life not only to reveal the terror operation but to warn that Iran is pursuing its nuclear bomb program around the clock from several secret sites. Details of the terror plot, meant to disrupt the West, have been passed on to U.S. officials, who are taking countermeasures.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1355362570605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 20:36:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355363006330-60</Id><Title>SPEEA HOW COME</Title><Msg>Why don't the local media let the people know what the average wage is for SPEEA? Do you know its 90,000K or more my guess a year I just thought I would let that out. Like they do for the IAM. Do you guys think there over paid?</Msg><Username>bobbyb336</Username><Timestamp>1355363006330</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 20:43:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355363334429-61</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Re-training workers to say" Welcome to MacDonalds"</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1355336565245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:22:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't see why you really care about misspelling of a word you got the point you replied to the question. Me myself don't really care about misspellings because I'm not paid to spell correctly and call me lazy for not hitting the backspace key to correct the spelling or clicking spell check who cares.</Msg><Username>bobbyb336</Username><Timestamp>1355363334429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 20:48:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355363742311-62</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Re-training workers to say" Welcome to MacDonalds"</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1355336565245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:22:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your problem is more than finding the backspace. Sheesh.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1355363742311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 20:55:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355366110177-63</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA HOW COME</Title><Username>bobbyb336</Username><Timestamp>1355363006330</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 20:43:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>actually the media has including Boeing and SPEEA However for an overall average of the 20,000 ( rounded) SPEEA members and feepayers, the secret number can be found on the speea site and the section called dues. Monthly Dues are set every year in Jan as being 85% of the average hourly rate. Dues for 2012 are $ 38.47 doing the extremely difficult math involves dividing 38.47 by .85 getting $ 45.25 per hour average wage ( techs AND profs ) assuming the standard 2080 hours per year then multiply 45.25 times 2080 and the secret number is ...... TA DAAAAAAAAAAA $ 94,138/year Dividing by 12 months/year = $ 7844/month. but lets keep it a secret just between us !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1355366110177</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 21:35:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355366334385-64</Id><Topic><Title>JOB SECURITY IN 2012 OR STRIKE</Title><Username>bobbyb336</Username><Timestamp>1260424255000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2009-12-10 00:50:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>remove head from posterior - IAM contract is still in force - they cannot strike this year or next year does your mommy know you are using the computer ???</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1355366334385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 21:38:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355368767922-65</Id><Topic><Title>The GOP is dying</Title><Username>spartacus778899</Username><Timestamp>1354884997085</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 07:56:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep. Crazy.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1355368767922</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 22:19:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355369030851-66</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when i wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1355328693914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:11:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In determining why you "love it" that the kenyan is president ...what principle is involved ? Do you love it that the united states is poorer economicaly ? Do you love it that we have been at war longer then any period in history ? Do you love it that the country is de facto bankrupt ? Do you love it that the kenyan has signed more executive orders (therby rendering congress irrelevant) then all oteher presidents combined ? Do you love it that he has committed over a dozen impeachable offenses ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355369030851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 22:23:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355369522129-67</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA HOW COME</Title><Username>bobbyb336</Username><Timestamp>1355363006330</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 20:43:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is actually widely reported. There are these things called "newspapers" which consist of little tiny bits of "ink" printed on a type of "paper." Folks sometimes "read" them to learn stuff, such as average wages for our SPEEA brethren. If you are this overwhelmlingly jealous of SPEEA wages, simply show up at Boeing with your long resume and announce you would like to make your very own ninety grand. Make sure to take your Yahoo posts with you so they'll hire you right now.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1355369522129</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 22:32:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355371393509-68</Id><Topic><Title>Obama supports Eugenics in Africa</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355355385584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 18:36:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOU OUGHT TO KNOW !!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355371393509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 23:03:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355372132179-69</Id><Topic><Title>Obama supports Eugenics in Africa</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355355385584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 18:36:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK ....IF YOU INSIST TRY THIS: GOOGLE: Saynsumthn’s Blog OBAMA EUGENICS IN AFRICA</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1355372132179</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 23:15:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355373122643-70</Id><Title>Unions Threaten Civil War</Title><Msg>From what I saw they threw punches like girls.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1355373122643</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 23:32:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355373758996-71</Id><Topic><Title>Strong rumor out of Chicago: Boeing purchasing land in Michigan for 3rd major assembly location</Title><Username>yb4itohitsfree</Username><Timestamp>1355321962434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 09:19:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hear Michigan is considering using eminant domain to clear nearly 1,000 acres SW of Detroit for BA at a bargain price and pay for a heated runway. If true, I hope big labor is happy that it has shot itself in the foot. Less dues = less $ for corrupt dem politicians.</Msg><Username>yb4itohitsfree</Username><Timestamp>1355373758996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 23:42:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>