<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-27"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348718960681-1</Id><Title>Sandra Fluke was quite correct and not just a fluke....</Title><Msg>In her assessment of womens's struggles and for women being to able to speak before the RWNJ sobbing Boehner House</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1348718960681</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 00:09:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348724459563-2</Id><Topic><Title>Sandra Fluke was quite correct and not just a fluke....</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1348718960681</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 00:09:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She is 30 plus years old, professional student, never had a much of a job, and killed more boners than Helen Thomas but wants to spends $1000 a month of my money on BC - a real lib pin up girl. What happened to that last pin up girl of yours Cindy Sheehan?</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1348724459563</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 01:40:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348728579810-3</Id><Topic><Title>Do one of you Romney clowns want to make a 10,000 dollar bet on the outcome?</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348671959206</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:05:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This from the one who wouldn't even show up for a 1K bet? And yes, I know you didn't!! Oh, that's right you couldn't be downtown Everett because you work, Har Har. Yet you are on this board all day long. Hmm, doesn't compute, one would think you don't work! BTW, do you even have 10K? I think I'll put my money on the retired banker. I'm thinking he has some serious resources to back his bet. You had your chance, now go away! Also, kindly don't respond, as I won't see it. {PLONK}</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1348728579810</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 02:49:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348731104541-4</Id><Topic><Title>Sandra Fluke was quite correct and not just a fluke....</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1348718960681</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 00:09:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did i say #$%$ nixon too</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1348731104541</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 03:31:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348731538629-5</Id><Topic><Title>Do one of you Romney clowns want to make a 10,000 dollar bet on the outcome?</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348671959206</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:05:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would like to bet 10,000 shares of BA that the RWNJ's don't have seven cents combined on this messageboard by name/ID</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1348731538629</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 03:38:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348732135601-6</Id><Topic><Title>Do one of you Romney clowns want to make a 10,000 dollar bet on the outcome?</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348671959206</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:05:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>september rookies wearing a wet suit they pulled out of the surf like some flotsam and jetsam BA 777 until y'all die</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1348732135601</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 03:48:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348733067493-7</Id><Topic><Title>Do one of you Romney clowns want to make a 10,000 dollar bet on the outcome?</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348671959206</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:05:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pretty much every interior window of a six story US premier dorm was shattered one October evening that is why they keep asking me to donate some more money and wild Bill, the 5th yr.senior... when all I could do was help to make the one-handed bump legal in (two person) volleyball... sorta like is what is gonna happen agian to Mitt</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1348733067493</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 04:04:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348734475707-8</Id><Topic><Title>Sandra Fluke was quite correct and not just a fluke....</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1348718960681</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 00:09:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>like an angel standing in a shaft of light uh oh knocking on the golden door rising up to paradise rainbows end doiwn that highway #$%$ho ann rmonoey me and victoria are thick Q.E. III shine... raw data</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1348734475707</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 04:27:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348735860866-9</Id><Topic><Title>Sandra Fluke was quite correct and not just a fluke....</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1348718960681</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 00:09:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>by the end of the 4th grade we are gonna need some better girls to sink our teeth into whenever that was</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1348735860866</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 04:51:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348737154610-10</Id><Title>This board is full of CRAZY Liberals</Title><Msg>that will either meltdown or go POSTAL when Romney wins!!!! It will be fun to watch.</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1348737154610</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 05:12:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348737230867-11</Id><Title>The NUTJOB and WACKO Left</Title><Msg>are well represented here by the KENT RAVEN and his aliases.</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1348737230867</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 05:13:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348742734930-12</Id><Topic><Title>BA wins $1.9B navy contract for P-8A 737's</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348706210932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the update.</Msg><Username>mrstock52</Username><Timestamp>1348742734930</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 06:45:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348743524070-13</Id><Title>Corporate America Sweats as US Nears Fiscal Cliff</Title><Msg>Top U.S. executives have less confidence in the business outlook now than at any time in the past three years - and a key reason is fear of gridlock in Washington over the fiscal deficit and tax policy. The uncertainty, coupled with slowing demand in Asia and Europe, is forcing corporate leaders to postpone decisions on major investments and hiring, and hurting sales of everything from textbooks to telephone lines. "If we don't deal with the fiscal cliff and don't deal with predictability on taxes for both citizens and business, with the rest of the world in a struggling state, this is really bad for us," John Chambers, CEO of network equipment maker Cisco Systems [CSCO 18.575 -0.09 (-0.48%) ], told Reuters on Tuesday. Some 34 percent of U.S. CEOs plan to cut jobs in the United States over the next six months, up from 20 percent a quarter ago, according to a Business Roundtable survey released on Wednesday. Only 30 percent plan to raise capital spending, compared with 43 percent previously. The group's index of CEO confidence fell to its lowest point since the third quarter of 2009, when the United States had just emerged from its worst recession in 80 years. The main culprit is the fiscal cliff — Washington's self-imposed year-end deadline to agree on a plan to shrink the federal budget or trigger $600 billion in spending cuts and higher taxes that were put in place last summer. The sharpest pain would be felt by the defense and healthcare sectors, which face direct funding cuts. But any resulting slowdown could send shockwaves across the economy. Another survey, by Deloitte, found that chief financial officers' view of business prospects had also darkened in the current quarter. Some 80 percent of U.S. CFOs surveyed by the consultancy said the economy had stalled or was about to stall. AT&amp;T [T 38.08 0.02 (+0.05%) ] CEO Randall Stephenson said orders have slowed for new phone lines as corporations hire fewer workers. "Businesses are taking action now in anticipation of January," Stephenson told investors last week. The worries aren't limited to the private sector. Officials from companies as varied as heavy-equipment maker Caterpillar [CAT 86.95 -0.06 (-0.07%) ], retailer Home Depot [HD 59.17 -0.55 (-0.92%) ] and Bank of America [BAC 8.815 -0.11 (-1.23%) ] have raised concerns about what could happen on Dec.31. Both Republicans and Democrats have suggested a more likely outcome may be a delay, in which lawmakers agree to shift their deadline into early or even mid-2013. Executives warn that failure to compromise on the budget could undermine an unsteady world economy, which is also coping with Europe's debt crisis and slowing China growth. "No recovery next year in the U.S. or in Europe (is) now forecast," Greg Hayes, chief financial officer of United Technologies [UTX 78.53 -0.24 (-0.3%) ], told investors last week. "That assumes we don't fall off this fiscal cliff, which could be devastating to the U.S. economy, probably the world economy."</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1348743524070</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 06:58:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348746814109-14</Id><Title>American Awakening</Title><Msg>Polling has Obama ahead in swing states by double digits.</Msg><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1348746814109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 07:53:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348749983301-15</Id><Title>US Durable Goods Orders Drop Worst Since Recession</Title><Msg>New orders for long-lasting U.S. manufactured goods in August fell by the most in 3-1/2 years, pointing to a sharp slowdown in factory activity even as a gauge of planned business spending rebounded. The Commerce Department said on Thursday durable goods orders dived 13.2 percent, the largest drop since January 2009, when the economy was in the throes of a recession. Orders for July were revised down to show a 3.3 percent increase instead of the previously reported 4.1 percent gain. Economists polled by Reuters had expected orders for durable goods -- items from toasters to aircraft that are meant to last at least three years -- to fall 5 percent. Last month, the drop in orders reflected weak aircraft and automobiles demand. Boeing received only one aircraft order in August, down from 260 in July, according to information posted on the plane maker's website. Transportation equipment tumbled 34.9 percent after racing ahead 13.1 percent in July. Excluding transportation, orders fell 1.6 percent after dropping 1.3 percent the prior month. Economists had expected this category to rise 0.3 percent after a previously reported 0.6 percent fall. But shipments of these goods, which are used to calculate equipment and software spending in the gross domestic product report, fell 0.9 percent after declining 1.1 percent in July. The wea kness su ggested third-quarter economic growth would probably not improve much from the April-June's 1.3 percent annual pace. Manufacturing, which has been the main driver of the recovery from the 2007-09 recession, has been hit by turbulence from sluggish domestic and global demand. Fears that the U.S. Congress could fail to avert a "fiscal cliff" -- the $500 billion or so in expiring tax cuts and government spending reductions set to take hold in 2013 -- have also left businesses with little incentive to boost production.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1348749983301</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 08:46:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348753099749-16</Id><Topic><Title>Some think the QTR ends on the Sunday the 30th</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1348714862973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 23:01:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When does the sixpence end?</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1348753099749</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 09:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348753400636-17</Id><Topic><Title>American Awakening</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1348746814109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 07:53:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One only needs to look at who is our current president to realize how stupid America has become.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1348753400636</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 09:43:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348755219577-18</Id><Title>Swing State Daily Tracking: Obama 46%, Romney 46%</Title><Msg>The full Swing State tracking update offers Rasmussen Reader subscribers a combined view of the results from 11 key states won by President Obama in 2008 and thought to be competitive in 2012. The states collectively hold 146 Electoral College votes and include Colorado, Florida, Iowa, Michigan, Nevada, New Hampshire, North Carolina, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Virginia and Wisconsin. If you do not already have a Rasmussen Reader account, subscribe now. Platinum Members have access to detailed demographic information. In the 11 swing states, the president earns 46% of the vote, and Mitt Romney is supported by 46%. Four percent (4%) are not sure, and five percent (5%) are undecided. The candidates have been tied or in a near tie every day but one for the past three weeks. In 2008, Obama won these states by a combined margin of 53% to 46%, virtually identical to his national margin.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1348755219577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:13:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348757155823-19</Id><Title>au-fish is a bet welcher</Title><Msg>But that has nothing to do with Boeing news so I won't say it more than a few more times</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348757155823</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:45:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348762353335-20</Id><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick or Dance</Title><Msg>Obamacare is a disaster that will cost the dems the election, people don't like it or understand it "Obamacare is a massive tax increase over the next 10 years that will fall largely on middle-class families; it steals more than $700 billion from Medicare to pay for the expanded coverage under ObamaCare; the unelected Independent Payment Advisory Board will ration and control Medicare costs and services without the say of doctors and patients; the Department of Health and Human Services is granted virtually unfettered powers, like the contraception mandate. Obamacare is bad policy. It was over 2,700 pages of complex rules and regulations passed behind closed doors with backroom deals -- exactly the opposite of what Obama promised when he campaigned in 2008." Bill Bennett</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1348762353335</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:12:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348762757034-21</Id><Title>NAACP worker sentenced to prison for voter fraud</Title><Msg>An NAACP executive sits in prison, sentenced for carrying out a massive voter fraud scheme. In … April a Tunica County, Miss., jury convicted NAACP official Lessadolla Sowers on 10 counts of fraudulently casting absentee ballots. Sowers is identified on an NAACP website as a member of the Tunica County NAACP Executive Committee. Sowers received a five-year prison term for each of the 10 counts, but Circuit Court Judge Charles Webster permitted Sowers to serve those terms concurrently, according to the Tunica Times, the only media outlet to cover the sentencing.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348762757034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348763440824-22</Id><Topic><Title>NAACP worker sentenced to prison for voter fraud</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348762757034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:19:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More Evidence Liberals Have to Cheat to Win!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348763440824</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:30:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348763455254-23</Id><Topic><Title>NAACP worker sentenced to prison for voter fraud</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348762757034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:19:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt Romney voted for Scott Brown in the special Massachusetts election to fill the seat of the late Ted Kennedy (D-MA). He listed his residence as the unfinished basement of his son's home in Belmont, MA. Whether the elder Romneys were legal residents of Massachusetts at the time is unknown. If he released his Massachusetts taxes for the same year he released his federal taxes, we would know. We do know that he also had a home in New Hampshire. Why might he want to live in New Hampshire? Because New Hampshire has no capital gains or income taxes. So, the Mittster parked some of his money in the Cayman Islands, some in Switzerland, and parked himself in New Hampshire, all to avoid taxes. Nonetheless, Mitt allegedly voted in the Scott Brown election. Ann probably did too. To release his 2010 Masschusetts tax returns would settle the question about whether he committed voter fraud. And, we all know how deeply concerned Republicans are about voter fraud, don't we?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348763455254</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348763671718-24</Id><Topic><Title>NAACP worker sentenced to prison for voter fraud</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348762757034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:19:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pathetic... Drinking the MSNBC Coolaid Again, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1348763671718</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348764055500-25</Id><Topic><Title>NAACP worker sentenced to prison for voter fraud</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348762757034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:19:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I find it hard to believe Ann and Mitt were staying in their sons basement, OH please this guys just another crook, but since it`s Mitt you go silent on the subject LOL you wanna know why Republicans will loose big this year, BECAUSE THEY ARE DISHONEST.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348764055500</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:40:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348764307878-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama with a 50-point lead!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_002</Username><Timestamp>1348763091747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:24:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AWESOME! Now do any of our resident RWNJs seriously believe Mitt the Twit can WIN?</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1348764307878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:45:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348764497778-27</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick or Dance</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1348762353335</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:12:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I feel your pain... LOL :))</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1348764497778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:48:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348764731536-28</Id><Topic><Title>Obama with a 50-point lead!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_002</Username><Timestamp>1348763091747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:24:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dnn't get complacent. Be sure to register your vote.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348764731536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:52:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348764851744-29</Id><Topic><Title>NAACP worker sentenced to prison for voter fraud</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348762757034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:19:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ten absentee ballots would not be "massive" fraud, not if there are 100s of thousand or even millions of ballots being counted. The most massive case of voter fraud in US history put Bushleague in the White house in 2000. It was not an election, it was a selection.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1348764851744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:54:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348765531193-30</Id><Topic><Title>NAACP worker sentenced to prison for voter fraud</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348762757034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:19:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fraudulent voter registration in Massachusetts carries a penalty of $10,000 and up to five years in jail. And the law in Massachusetts is pretty clear about the residency requirements needed to vote in the state. The state defines residence as "where a person dwells and which is the center of his domestic, social, and civil life." Using that definition, Karger spent some time interviewing Belmont residents, including members of the Romneys' local Mormon Temple, where they’d been regulars, and asked people when they’d last seen the the former Massachusetts governor or his wife around town. The local fishmonger told Karger, "They flew the coop. They moved to California. I haven’t seen Mrs. Romney in over two years, and she used to come in here all the time." Likewise, churchgoers used to worshiping with the Romneys told Karger that they also hadn't seen the Romneys in a couple years. Yet the Romneys continued to vote in Massachusetts, including in the January 2010 special election to fill Ted Kennedy’s Senate seat. Karger says he even received personal confirmation from Ann Romney about the couple's living arrangments. In April, Karger says he ran into her in Las Vegas at a meeting of the Republican Jewish Coalition, where Mitt was speaking. According to Karger, Ann told him they are living in California.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348765531193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:05:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348766220867-31</Id><Title>Republican Job Creation</Title><Msg>During the 2010 mid-terms the GOP campaigned fiercely on the platform of job creation and, as a result of such promises, the GOP gained the majority in the House of Representatives. As the new Speaker of the House, John Boehner made the welcome claim that the primary goal of the Republican Party was to increase employment in the U.S. His exact words were: "We're going to have a relentless focus on creating jobs." There are those who choose to place the blame for high unemployment on Mr. Obama's shoulders, but keep in mind that it's the House that enacts legislation and controls the governmental purse-strings, not the President. The Stimulus package passed by the Democrats in 2009 helped the economy but would have been more effective if the GOP hadn't limited it to little more than a package of more useless tax breaks for the rich. So How many jobs has the house created the last two years? What are they doing today? Oh vacation guess jobs will have to wait.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348766220867</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:17:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348766618049-32</Id><Topic><Title>American Awakening</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1348746814109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 07:53:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America is not buying what Mittford is selling. BTW, what is Mittford selling? I know what the repubs are selling, but Mittford can't seem to stay on any message for more than an hour or two.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348766618049</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:23:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348766787773-33</Id><Topic><Title>American Awakening</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1348746814109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 07:53:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>90 million eligible Americans aren't going to vote at all.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1348766787773</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348767069617-34</Id><Topic><Title>American Awakening</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1348746814109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 07:53:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fivethirtyeight seems to agree with you: Unlike many recent days, when Mr. Obama’s national polls were slightly less euphoric than his swing state surveys, Wednesday’s national polls seemed to support the notion that Mr. Obama has a clear lead in the race. The Gallup national tracking poll gave Mr. Obama a six-point lead among registered voters, close to his high mark on the year in that survey. The online tracking poll conducted by Ipsos gave him a six-point lead among likely voters. Another online tracking poll, from the RAND Corporation, put Mr. Obama’s lead at roughly seven and a half percentage points, his largest of the year in that poll. And a national poll for Bloomberg produced by the pollster J. Ann Selzer, who has a strong track record, put Mr. Obama six points ahead. The exception was the Rasmussen Reports tracking poll, which gave Mitt Romney a two-point lead among likely voters. (This was in the version of the poll that included voters who leaned toward a candidate, which is the one that FiveThirtyEight uses for all surveys.) What to think of the Rasmussen poll? Their surveys usually have a Republican lean, but it seems to have gotten stronger in the last few weeks. It has also been stronger in some years than others. Rasmussen got reasonably good results in years like 2006 and 2008 when their polls were close to the consensus. However, their polls were the least accurate of the major polling firms in 2010</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1348767069617</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:31:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348767634081-35</Id><Title>september deliveries may pop</Title><Msg>With only three days to go (not including Sunday) in September, deliveries total is 42.including only 27 737's. Why 737' deliveries are so low is anyones guess since the production rates have increased. There must be a flightline somewhere that is filling up with 737's coming out of the factory. But the 787 deliveries have jumped .to new highs and several more should ship before month end. We should also see some 747 deliveries as well. The new delivery center is almost complete at Paine Field. The noise today about the EU sanctions demands against Boeing is just that, noise, since the WTO recognizes that Airbus received more than 3 times the subsidy that they attribute to Boeing. October 24 is the BA earnings announcement Shareholders are watching this closely. The stock has not done well since it hit a high of 78+ many months ago. Deliveries are key to increasing the revenue and profit and with it, an increase in stock price.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348767634081</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:40:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348768771376-36</Id><Topic><Title>American Awakening</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1348746814109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 07:53:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some 13 of its [Rasmussen's] polls missed by 10 or more points, including one in the Hawaii Senate race that missed the final margin between the candidates by 40 points, the largest error ever recorded in a general election in FiveThirtyEight’s database, which includes all polls conducted since 1998.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348768771376</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:59:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348769035861-37</Id><Topic><Title>American Awakening</Title><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1348746814109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 07:53:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you compare it to his predecessor we must all be Einsteins.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1348769035861</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:03:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348770659894-38</Id><Topic><Title>First 3 on my ignore list</Title><Username>paquoz</Username><Timestamp>1171662249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2007-02-16 16:44:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>barbara_anne_hollinqsworth! I've MISSED you sweetheart! where ya been?</Msg><Username>al_qaeda_sunrise</Username><Timestamp>1348770659894</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:30:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348770824624-39</Id><Topic><Title>september deliveries may pop</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348767634081</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:40:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Make that 43 planes delivered. They delivered a 767 yesterday that I just noticed.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348770824624</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:33:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348771254017-40</Id><Topic><Title>NAACP worker sentenced to prison for voter fraud</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348762757034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:19:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you hate freedom?</Msg><Username>r_all_christians_morons</Username><Timestamp>1348771254017</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348772096298-41</Id><Topic><Title>september deliveries may pop</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348767634081</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:40:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Make that 44 planes delivered. They delivered another 737 this morning (9-27).</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348772096298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:54:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348772615018-42</Id><Topic><Title>NAACP worker sentenced to prison for voter fraud</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348762757034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:19:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rockstar is unbelievably ignorant.....I'm sure someone has to tell him when to breath. You can't legally avoid federal taxes by parking some of your money in the Cayman Islands, some in Switzerland, and parking yourself in New Hampshire. And it ain't illegal to avoid state or country capital gain taxes where there are no capital gain taxes. Rockstar is a kool-aid gulping victim of left-wing dogma and propaganda.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348772615018</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:03:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348772864409-43</Id><Title>Liberal Terified of TEA Party</Title><Msg>.....nothing scares the left-wing lunatics like people saying "we're Taxed Enough Already." It sends shivers down their spine and makes their hair stand straight up.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348772864409</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:07:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348773002922-44</Id><Topic><Title>NAACP worker sentenced to prison for voter fraud</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348762757034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:19:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it is illegal to Vote in Massachusetts if you are living in California and or New Hampshire, the Romeny`s have houses in these two states but choose to stay in his sons Basement in Mass.? how much ignorance does it take to believe that?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348773002922</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:10:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348773165243-45</Id><Title>Oh Boy: Horrible New Economic Numbers Released, Double-Dip Recession Coming?</Title><Msg>As you digest these figures, keep in mind that we were already experiencing the worst economic 'recovery' since the Great Depression -- featuring "feeble growth, exhausted consumers, a jobs hole and shrinking paychecks." And now there's this: New orders for manufactured durable goods in August decreased $30.1 billion or 13.2 percent to $198.5 billion, the U.S. Census Bureau announced today. This decrease, down following three consecutive monthly increases, was the largest decrease since January 2009 and followed a 3.3 percent July increase. Excluding transportation, new orders decreased 1.6 percent. Excluding defense, new orders decreased 12.4 percent. Transportation equipment, down following four consecutive monthly increases, had the largest decrease, $27.8 billion or 34.9 percent to $51.9 billion. Nondefense new orders for capital goods in August decreased $18.5 billion or 24.3 percent to $57.7 billion. Shipments decreased $1.2 billion or 1.7 percent to $69.5 billion. Unfilled orders decreased $11.9 billion or 2.0 percent to $580.5 billion. Inventories increased $1.5 billion or 0.9 percent to $171.9 billion. Defense new orders for capital goods in August decreased $4.1 billion or 40.1 percent to $6.1 billion. Shipments decreased $0.1 billion or 1.7 percent to $8.1 billion. Unfilled orders decreased $2.0 billion or 1.2 percent to $165.6 billion. Inventories increased $0.4 billion or 1.8 percent to $21.4 billion. In case you've forgotten (and how could you? The president mentions this every five minutes), January 2009 was during the teeth of the crisis, when our economy was in severe recession. We're moving backwards, not "forward." A few additional notes from Ed Morrissey: Unfilled orders — the “backlog” on which every manufacturer relies for continuity and security — also dropped by 1.7%, the largest drop since December 2009 ... Inventories, however, rose by 0.6%, which indicates that demand is perhaps even worse than this report would indicate. Meanwhile, as Katie notes, our economic growth rate has been revised downward from an already pathetic, stagnation-level number. The government had originally estimated that GDP grew by a measly 1.7 percent in the second quarter. In its final assessment, that figure has slumped to 1.25 percent:</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348773165243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348773443500-46</Id><Title>Voters Expect Economy to Improve With Romney as President</Title><Msg>The latest Rasmussen Reports national telephone survey finds that only 34% of Likely U.S. Voters think the economy is likely to get better if President Obama is reelected and Democrats regain full control of Congress, marking little change from early July when the two sides ran nearly even. By comparison, 43% now believe the economy is likely to improve if Romney wins and the GOP is in charge of Congress. That’s up seven points from 36% in the previous survey. Sixty-two percent (62%) are more pessimistic about the economic impact if the president and his party in Congress win the election, with 41% who expect the economy to get worse and 21% who say it will stay about the same. Fifty-two percent (52%) paint a similar picture if the Republican challenger wins and the GOP takes over Congress.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348773443500</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:17:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348773475305-47</Id><Topic><Title>Oh Boy: Horrible New Economic Numbers Released, Double-Dip Recession Coming?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348773165243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why has the GOP house which was took control of the majority 2 years ago done nothing to create jobs and send legislation to the President to be signed? what are they spending their time doing ?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348773475305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:17:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348773669508-48</Id><Title>Carney: We Didn't Lie About Libya, We Just Had Different Facts At the Time</Title><Msg>Does Carney even have a clue what a FACT is?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348773669508</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:21:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348773784120-49</Id><Topic><Title>Voters Expect Economy to Improve With Romney as President</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348773443500</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:17:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who cares what polls say, do some flipping history Republicans are a disaster!! they hold back wages , want to take more benefits away and basically pay you peanuts to work more hours so some rich guy makes more profits he can stick in his offshore bank account. Republican policies are a huge part of why this country is in the shape it is in now.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348773784120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:23:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348773833505-50</Id><Topic><Title>NAACP worker sentenced to prison for voter fraud</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348762757034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:19:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You got us. Excuse us all to heck. 10 votes.........major outcry coming from all over. Excuse me but this happened in 2011.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1348773833505</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:23:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348774334773-51</Id><Topic><Title>september deliveries may pop</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348767634081</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:40:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>make that 46 total deliveries. They just delivered another two 737's.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1348774334773</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348774480435-52</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Job Creation</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348766220867</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:17:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They didn't create any jobs, but they did vote to repeal Obama care 33 or 34 times. That was a very useless way to waste Tax Payer money ( at about $2M per vote ). So who is it that is out of fresh ideas?</Msg><Username>vtguru56</Username><Timestamp>1348774480435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:34:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348774944456-53</Id><Title>GOP's female politicians look more feminine...but so do male Democrat Politicians</Title><Msg>If a new academic study is to be believed, Republican women politicians look more feminine than their Democratic counterparts. The study, by two UCLA researchers, found that female politicians with what are described as stereotypically feminine features tended to be Republicans, and the reverse was also true for Democratic women. GOP women rated, on average, twice as stereotypically feminine as Democrats. In fact, the authors said the correlation was so strong that undergraduates were regularly able to guess someone's party affiliation just by the way she looked. "I suppose we could call it the 'Michele Bachmann effect,'" said Kerri Johnson, an assistant professor at UCLA and the study's senior author, said in a statement announcing the research — a reference to the well-known GOP congresswoman from Minnesota. When it came to men, however, male Democratic politicians were also more feminine, the study found. But the researchers said that was not as revealing a finding since they have many members like Barney Frank, Bill Nelson and Harry Reid The study is to be printed in the peer-reviewed Journal of Experimental Social Psychology.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348774944456</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348775124292-54</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Job Creation</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348766220867</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:17:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The house also passed several budgets of which Democrats refused to bring up for a vote in the Senate. So, who are the REAL obstructionists?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348775124292</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:45:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348775268950-55</Id><Topic><Title>GOP's female politicians look more feminine...but so do male Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348774944456</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so what you are saying there is the GOP has lost it and has to dig real deep these days to come up with new ways to make fun of other people that don`t agree with them?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348775268950</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:47:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348775502673-56</Id><Topic><Title>Our debt will enslave a generation and bring down our country</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1348623396229</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:36:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The strategy "Starve the Beast" (aka the 2 Santa Claus approach) is a Republican creation. And this is the primary cause of the Debt growing. As I recall, the budget was balanced before a republican named George W. Bush took control. And screwed it up. And what is Romney's plan? Spend a lot more on defense ( good for Boeing ), give a bunch of tax cuts ( to corp, wealthy ), and then some how magically balance the budget ( and hopefully reduce the debt ). Problem is that there isn't enough to cut from the budget to do that, unless you are going to stop pay Social Security Benifits. Of course, he would have to keep charging SS tax. Explain how you give tax cuts, spend more on defense, and balance the budget. Or is your arguement really just more Tea Bagger FEAR MONGERING?</Msg><Username>vtguru56</Username><Timestamp>1348775502673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:51:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348775606841-57</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Job Creation</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348766220867</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:17:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What specifically did the house do to attempt to create jobs?</Msg><Username>vtguru56</Username><Timestamp>1348775606841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348775900372-58</Id><Title>Everett seeks branch campus from WSU, not UW</Title><Msg>At last a real university close by. Not the self promoting high priced diploma mill (UW aka University of Weyerhaeuser). Search the topic for the article.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1348775900372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:58:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348776016390-59</Id><Topic><Title>Our debt will enslave a generation and bring down our country</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1348623396229</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 21:36:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot to mention that the deficit was declining and $260 billion and unemployment was 4.2% before Democrats took control of both houses in 2006. BTW Clinton had a Republican Congress that brought him kicking and screaming to that balanced budget that he now likes to brag about.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348776016390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:00:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348776357261-60</Id><Topic><Title>GOP's female politicians look more feminine...but so do male Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348774944456</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UCLA is an extremely liberal University. I'm sure they just couldn't avoid the facts found in their study.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348776357261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:05:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348776700362-61</Id><Topic><Title>GOP's female politicians look more feminine...but so do male Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348774944456</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean as strong and powerful as Lindsey Graham?</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1348776700362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:11:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348778086744-62</Id><Topic><Title>GOP's female politicians look more feminine...but so do male Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348774944456</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, GOP women know what it takes to the votes of GOP men. Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1348778086744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:34:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348778153306-63</Id><Topic><Title>GOP's female politicians look more feminine...but so do male Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348774944456</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: Yes, GOP women know what it takes to win the votes of GOP men.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1348778153306</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:35:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348778630634-64</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Job Creation</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348766220867</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:17:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If jobs and the economy are such critical issues to Republicans why is the house on Vacation and still to this day not enacted any legislation? they even filibustered the Farm bill last week these guys are pathetic, hope they get voted out for doing nothing but hoping for the worse to happen. just like the lame Propaganda repeaters on Yahoo.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348778630634</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:43:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348779129874-65</Id><Title>Why will Liberals vote for more debt?????</Title><Msg>.....is it so they won't have to get a job or is it they never think they should have to pay back what they borrow?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348779129874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:52:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348779582461-66</Id><Title>WSJ: The more we learn, the more Benghazi looks like a gross security failure...</Title><Msg>In his United Nations speech on Tuesday, President Obama talked about the September 11 attack on the U.S. consulate in Libya and declared that "there should be no doubt that we will be relentless in tracking down the killers and bringing them to justice." What he didn't say is how relentless he'll be in tracking down the security lapses and intelligence failures that contributed to the murders. Let's say there's some doubt about that. None of the initial explanations offered by the White House and State Department since the assault on the Benghazi consulate has held up. First the Administration blamed protests provoked by an amateurish anti-Islam clip posted on YouTube. Cue Susan Rice, the U.N. Ambassador and leading candidate for Secretary of State in a second Obama term: "What happened initially was that it was a spontaneous reaction . . . as a consequence of the video, that people gathered outside the embassy and then it grew very violent." Administration officials also maintained that the diplomatic missions in Libya and Egypt, the site of the first attacks this September 11, were properly defended and that the U.S. had no reason to prepare for any attack. "The office of the director of National Intelligence has said we have no actionable intelligence that an attack on our post in Benghazi was planned or imminent," Secretary of State Hillary Clinton said last week, calling the security measures in place there "robust." Cell phone video footage and witness testimony from Benghazi soon undercut the Administration trope of an angry march "hijacked" by a few bad people. As it turned out, the assault was well-coordinated, with fighters armed with guns, RPGs and diesel canisters, which were used to set the buildings on fire. Ambassador Chris Stevens died of smoke inhalation. Briefing Congress, the Administration changed its story and said the attacks were pre-planned and linked to al Qaeda. You'd think this admission would focus attention on why the compound was so vulnerable to begin with. But the Administration wants to avoid this conversation. The removal of all staff from Benghazi, including a large component of intelligence officers, would also seem to hinder their ability to investigate the attacks and bring the killers to justice. Journalists have stayed on the case, however, and their reporting is filling in the Administration's holes. On Friday, our WSJ colleagues showed that starting in spring, U.S. intelligence had been worried about radical militias in eastern Libya. These armed groups helped topple Moammar Ghadhafi last year but weren't demobilized as a new government has slowly found its legs. As we've noted since last winter, the waning of American and European interest in Libya could have dangerous consequences. Deteriorating security was no secret. On April 10, for example, an explosive device was thrown at a convoy carrying U.N. envoy Ian Martin. On June 6, an improvised explosive device exploded outside the U.S. consulate. In late August, State warned American citizens who were planning to travel to Libya about the threat of assassinations and car bombings.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348779582461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:59:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348779891938-67</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: The more we learn, the more Benghazi looks like a gross security failure...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348779582461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libya is a dangerous place everybody knew that , even the folks that got killed their, so it was a Terrorist attack , what is screaming about it on a message board going to change. in 9-11-01 thousands of Americans were killed on American soil because of a lack of leadership and a Terrorist attack yet all you want to do is forget all about that huh? and point fingers, you folks are comical.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1348779891938</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:04:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348780476194-68</Id><Topic><Title>How the GOP Thought Leaders Created Mitt in the First Place -</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_002</Username><Timestamp>1348780128246</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:08:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post... I like this line: =The root of the campaign's fundamental dishonesty, which is what has led to its incoherence in the first place, is the fact that the Republican primary electorate forced Romney to renounce the only real achievement he has as an elected politician — the Massachusetts health-care reform. Once you find you have to lie about all the good you did, what does the rest of it really matter?=</Msg><Username>mr_mortadella</Username><Timestamp>1348780476194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:14:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348780728729-69</Id><Topic><Title>Repackaging Mitt as a Compassionate Conservative? It’s Too Late</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_002</Username><Timestamp>1348779893158</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:04:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bears repeating: =What we're seeing in Ohio isn't a new Mitt Romney. It's a newly-packaged Mitt Romney. The real Mitt Romney is the one we saw on the videotape last week. And no amount of re-taping can disguise the package's true contents=</Msg><Username>mr_mortadella</Username><Timestamp>1348780728729</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:18:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348782736375-70</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: The more we learn, the more Benghazi looks like a gross security failure...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348779582461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rock, "Libya is a dangerous place everybody knew that , even the folks that got killed their, so it was a Terrorist attack , what is screaming about it on a message board going to change." The value of the message board notwithstanding, the importance of the message is that, one that does need screaming, is that President Obama has proven to be negligent and dishonest and simply must be sent on his way. As Clint Eastwood said, 'When someone isn't doing the job, we've got to let him go'. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1348782736375</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:52:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348785418890-71</Id><Topic><Title>Repackaging Mitt as a Compassionate Conservative? It’s Too Late</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_002</Username><Timestamp>1348779893158</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:04:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In other words, you don't care how tightly you have to pinch your nose to ignore the stench when you vote for Romney, because your only criterion for a candidate is that he runs against Obama. You deserve Mittens, but hopefully REAL Americans are going to save you from yourself.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1348785418890</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 18:36:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348786406833-72</Id><Topic><Title>Obama screws up the whole world and he wins Unemployment surging in 47 states. gas doubled, 45% on Welfare</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348785571128</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 18:39:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe everyone on your street knows you, and no one wants to set you off.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1348786406833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 18:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348787132542-73</Id><Topic><Title>Obama screws up the whole world and he wins Unemployment surging in 47 states. gas doubled, 45% on Welfare</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348785571128</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 18:39:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HERE LIBTARD, GOT TO DO EVERYTHING FOR YOU The 2012 Index of Dependence on Government By William W. Beach and Patrick Tyrrell February 8, 2012 Print PDF Download PDF Share Facebook Twitter Email More Abstract: The great and calamitous fiscal trends of our time—dependence on government by an increasing portion of the American population, and soaring debt that threatens the financial integrity of the economy—worsened yet again in 2010 and 2011. The United States has long reached the point at which it must reverse the direction of both trends or face economic and social collapse. Yet policymakers made little progress on either front since the 2010 Index of Dependence on Government was published. Today, more people than ever before—67.3 million Americans, from college students to retirees to welfare beneficiaries—depend on the federal government for housing, food, income, student aid, or other assistance once considered to be the responsibility of individuals, families, neighborhoods, churches, and other civil society institutions. The United States reached another milestone in 2010: For the first time in history, half the population pays no federal income taxes. Related to these disturbing trends, publicly held debt continued its amazing ascent without any plan by the government to pay it back. As if those circumstances were not dire enough, the country is about to witness the largest generational retirement in world history by a population that will depend on currently bankrupted pension and health programs. The 2012 Index of Dependence on Government highlights the gathering fiscal storm clouds. Unsustainable increases in dependent populations predate the recent recession—and continuing economic morass—and have continued to rise since the economy collapsed in 2008 and 2009. There is one silver lining to those clouds: A few policymakers and independent public policy groups have advanced plans for restoring fiscal balance in Washington. Among them is The Heritage Foundation. Heritage calls its fiscal plan Saving the American Dream. The Heritage plan reforms and funds those government programs that matter most to people who need the government’s help, and it frees the private sector to create the millions of jobs that will dramatically reduce the growth of dependence on government. Virtually no issue so dominates the current public policy debate as the future financial health of the U.S. government. Americans are haunted by the specter of enormously growing mountains of debt that suck the economic and social vitality out of this country. Only the intrepidly stagnant and jobless economic recovery garners more attention, and many are beginning to believe that even that sluggishness is tied to the nation’s growing burden of publicly held debt.[1] Of course, the roots of the problems produced by the great and growing debt lie in the spending behaviors of the federal government. Annual deficits far greater than the government’s revenue are fueling explosive levels of debt. One such significant area of rapid growth is those programs that create economic and social dependence on government. The 2012 publication of the Index of Dependence on Government marks the tenth year that The Heritage Foundation has flashed warning lights about Americans’ growing dependence on government programs. For a decade, the Index has signaled troubling and rapid increases in the growth of dependence-creating federal programs, and every year Heritage has raised concerns about the challenges that rapidly growing dependence poses to this country’s republican form of government, its economy, and for the broader civil society. Index measurements begin in 1962; since then, the Index score has grown by more than 15 times its original amount. This means that, keeping inflation neutral in the calculations, more than 15 times the resources were committed to paying for people who depend on government in 2010 than in 1962. In 2010 alone, the Index of Dependence on Government grew by 8.1 percent. The Index variables that grew the most were: ■Housing: 13 percent ■Health Care and Welfare: 13.1 percent ■Retirement: 3.1 percent. The increase from the previous Index means that the Index has now grown by 60.7 percent just since 2001. One of the most worrying trends in the Index is the coinciding growth in the non-taxpaying public. The percentage of people who do not pay federal income taxes, and who are not claimed as dependents by someone who does pay them, jumped from 14.8 percent in 1984 to 49.5 percent in 2009. This means that in 1984, 34.8 million tax filers paid no taxes; in 2009, 151.7 million paid nothing.[2] It is the conjunction of these two trends—higher spending on dependence-creating programs, and an ever-shrinking number of taxpayers who pay for these programs—that concerns those interested in the fate of the American form of government. Americans have always expressed concern about becoming dependent on government, even while understanding that life’s challenges cause most people, at one time or another, to depend on aid from someone else. Americans’ concern stems partly from deeply held views that life’s blessings are more readily obtained by independent people and that growing dependence on government erodes the spirit of personal and mutual responsibility created through family and civil society institutions. These views help explain the broad public support for welfare reform in the 1990s. This ethic of self-reliance combined with a commitment to the brotherly care of those in need appears threatened in a much greater way today than when this Index first appeared in 2002. This year, 2012, marks another year that the Index contains significant retirements by baby boomers. Over the next 25 years, more than 77 million boomers will begin collecting Social Security checks, drawing Medicare benefits, and relying on long-term care under Medicaid. No event will financially challenge these important programs over the next two decades more than this shift into retirement of the largest generation in American history. It is not only financial tests that these programs will face. Certainly, financial challenges will be great over the next several decades, given that none of these “entitlement” programs can easily meet its obligations even now. Doubling the number of people in retirement will constitute a massive growth of the population largely dependent on government programs in the United States, and a potentially ruinous drain on federal finances. Perhaps the most important aspect of the boomer retirement is its dramatic reminder of the rapidly growing dependence on government in the United States. There was such a rapid growth in dependence in 2010 that the twin concerns—how much damage this growth has done to the republican form of government, and how harmful it has been to the country’s financial situation—has deepened significantly. Not only did the federal government effectively take over half of the U.S. economy and expand public-sector debt by more than all previous governments combined, it also oversaw a second year of enormous expansion in total government debt at the federal level. Much of that growth in new debt can be traced to programs that encourage dependence. Chart 2 illustrates how 70.5 percent of federal spending now goes to dependence-creating programs, up dramatically from 28.3 percent in 1962, and 48.5 percent in 1990. Many Americans are expressing increasing frustration at this fiscally grim state of affairs. Most Members of recent Congresses have known that the major entitlement programs not only need major repairs, but also that these programs are starting to drive up annual deficits and promise to produce substantial deficits in the near future. Many Americans are especially frustrated by the way Congress ignores or, at best, claims to support, comprehensive budget reform plans. Plans like The Heritage Foundation’s Saving the American Dream[3] and Representative Paul Ryan’s (R–WI) “Roadmap,”[4] which offer well-developed and reasonable blueprints for getting federal finances under control, have not been seriously debated by most Members of Congress. This absence of genuine efforts by Congress to manage the federal government’s worsening financial crisis is now worrying a number of international financial organizations, including the International Monetary Fund (IMF). On May 14, 2010, the IMF ranked the U.S. sec­ond place among countries that must reduce their structural deficit (caused in part by spending on dependence-creating programs) or risk financial calamity. The IMF predicts that U.S. public-sector debt will equal 100 percent of its gross domestic product (GDP) by 2015 unless immediate actions are taken to cut the deficits by an amount equal to 12 percent of GDP by 2014. Even woeful Greece need only cut its deficits by 9 percent of its national output. Then, on August 5, 2011, the credit rating company Standard &amp; Poor’s downgraded U.S. sovereign debt from its AAA rating to AA+.[5] This dramatic and highly controversial assessment of the federal government’s financial health was on the horizon three days earlier when Moody’s Investors Service announced its view that the prospects for the fiscal health of the central government had turned “negative.”[6] Not to be outdone, on November 28, the third big ratings agency, Fitch, also revised its outlook on U.S. credit from “stable” to “negative” (meaning there is a “slightly greater than 50% chance” that Fitch will downgrade U.S. credit from “AAA” over the next two years).[7] The IMF, the rating agencies, and many watchful citizens are right to be concerned about the growing debt and growing dependence. Programs that encourage dependence quickly morph into political assets that policymakers readily embrace. Many voters support politicians or political parties that mandate higher incomes or subsidies for the essentials of life. No matter how well meaning policymakers are when they create such aid programs, these same programs quickly spiral beyond their mission and become severe liabilities. Many countries have already passed the fiscal tipping point at which reckless growth in dependence programs has produced domestic debt crises. How far along the path to crisis is the United States? Are Americans closing in on a tipping point that endangers the workings of their democracy? Or have Americans already passed that point? Can this republican form of government withstand the political weight of a massively growing population of Americans who receive government benefits and who contribute little or nothing for them? How seriously have these federal programs eroded civil society by nullifying what were once social obligations, and by crowding out services that used to be provided by families, congregations, community groups, and local governments? To explore these questions, one must measure how much federal social programs have grown. The Index of Dependence on Government is an attempt to measure these patterns and provide data to help ascertain the implications of these trends. Table 1 contains the 2012 Index scores—from 1962 to 2010, with 1980 as the base year. As the table indicates, dependence on government has grown steadily at an alarming rate. The Fiscal Calamities Created by Growing Dependence Entitlements. The issue of dependence is particularly salient today when more and more Americans are increasing their reliance on government as they pass into retirement. Current retirees became eligible for Social Security income, as well as for health care benefits from Medicare or Medicaid, at age 65.[8] These programs currently make up 42 percent of all non-interest federal program spending. Over the next two decades, that spending will increase to nearly 62 percent of non-interest spending as 10,000 baby boomers per day retire and begin to collect benefits. Jointly, these programs will enable the government dependence of nearly 80 million baby boomers. This phenomenon is particularly troubling because most of the soon-to-be users of these programs are middle-class to upper-class Americans who do not need government support. Since eligibility for these programs is linked to age, not financial need, millionaires collect the same benefits, such as subsidized prescription drugs through Medicare Part D, as do low-income retirees. Paying for these middle-class and upper-class entitlements in the coming years will require unprecedented levels of deficit spending. Focusing on Social Security and Medicare alone, Americans face $45.9 trillion in unfunded obligations (read: new borrowing) over the next 75 years. That is more than $200,000 per American citizen—an unsustainable level of debt that is sure to slow the economy and could force even higher rates of taxation in the future. The high costs of these programs, which will be shouldered by the children and grandchildren of baby boomers, could easily lead to further increases in dependence of future generations—which would be more likely to depend on welfare during a slow economy. This snowballing of dependence—caused by automatic reliance on Social Security, Medicare, and Medicaid—could easily send the country past the tipping point of dependence, eroding civil society and endangering the functioning of democracy itself. Additionally, the growing cost illustrates the budgetary problem of allowing dependence to expand unchecked. One reason this growth will be so significant is that these programs increase on autopilot, which further perpetuates dependence, since these programs are not subject to regular debate and evaluation. Unlike nearly all other federal outlays, Social Security, Medicare, and Medicaid are mandatory spending programs that operate outside the annual budget process. This exemption entitles these programs to call on all federal revenues first, regardless of other budgetary priorities. Substantive policy reform is required if this automatic dependence is to be halted. The solution is to turn these programs into 30-year budgeted programs, subjecting the budgets to debate every five years. Other policy reforms—that emphasize independence and self-reliance—must also be part of addressing the problems inherent in these and other programs. The concept of a safety net ought to be restored to gear Social Security, Medicare, and Medicaid toward those who truly need these programs. This restoration can be accomplished by relating benefits to retirees’ income and encouraging personal savings during working years. Even though many Members of Congress and other legislators show great hesitance in reforming these badly broken programs, good reforms—that preserve the basic commitments this country has made to its retired and indigent populations—do exist. The Heritage Foundation’s Saving the American Dream plan strengthens the anti-poverty elements of these mandatory programs while also protecting them from financial ruin. Doing nothing, however, guarantees that seniors one day will find themselves largely without the benefits that currently play such an important part of their retirement plans. Growth in the Non-Taxpaying Population. The challenges that Congress faces in reforming these entitlement programs are heightened by the rapid growth of other dependence-creating programs, such as subsidies for food and housing and college financial aid, and by the growing number of Americans who incur no obligations for receiving them. How likely is Congress to reform entitlements in any meaningful way under such circumstances? Can Congress rein in the massive middle-class entitlements in an environment of fast-expanding dependence programs? In 1962, the first year measured in the Index of Dependence on Government, the percentage of people who did not pay federal income taxes themselves and who were not claimed as dependents by someone who did pay federal income taxes stood at 23.7 percent; it fell to 12 percent by 1969 before beginning a ragged and ultimately steady increase. By 2000, the percentage was 34.1 percent; by 2009, it was 49.5 percent.[9] In short, the country is now at a point where roughly one-half of “taxpayers” do not pay federal income taxes, and where most of that same population receives generous federal benefits. (See Chart 1.) This trend should concern everyone who supports America’s republican form of government. If the citizens’ representatives are elected by an increasing percentage of voters who pay no income tax, how long will it be before these representatives respond more to demands for yet more entitlements and subsidies from non-payers than to the pleas of taxpayers to exercise greater spending prudence? Section 1: The Purpose and Theory of the Index The 2012 Index of Dependence on Government is divided into four major sections. Section 1 explains the purpose of and theory behind the Index; Section 2 reviews major policy changes in five federal-program areas; Section 3 features a methodology that describes how the Index is constructed; and Section 4 discusses the Index in terms of the number of Americans who depend on government programs. The Index of Dependence on Government is designed to measure the pace at which federal government services and programs have grown in areas once considered to be the responsibility of individuals, families, communities, neighborhood groups, churches, and other civil society institutions. By compiling and condensing these data into a simple annual score (composed of the scores for the five components in Section 2), the Index provides a useful tool for analyzing dependence on government. Policy analysts and political scientists can also use the Index and the patterns it reveals to develop forecasts of trends and consider how these trends might affect the politics of the federal budget. The Index uses data drawn from a carefully selected set of federally funded programs. The programs were chosen for their propensity to duplicate or replace assistance, such as shelter, food, monetary aid, health care, education, or employment training, which was traditionally provided to needy people by local organizations and families. In calculating the Index, the expenditures for these programs are weighted to reflect the relative importance of each service (e.g., shelter, health care, or food). The degree of a person’s dependence will vary with respect to the need. For example, a homeless person’s first need is generally shelter, followed by nourishment, health care, and income. Analysts in The Heritage Foundation’s Center for Data Analysis weighted the program expenditures based on this hierarchy of needs, which produces a weighted Index of expenditures centered on the year 1980. Historically, individuals and local entities have privately provided more assistance to needy members of society than they do today. Particularly during the 20th century, government gradually offered more and more services that were previously provided by self-help and mutual-aid organizations.[10] Lower-cost housing is a good example. Mutual-aid, religious, and educational organizations long have aided low-income Americans with limited housing assistance; after World War II, the federal and state governments began providing the bulk of low-cost housing. Today, the government provides nearly all housing assistance for the poor and low-income. Health care is another example of this pattern. Before World War II, Americans of modest income typically obtained health care and health insurance through a range of community institutions, some operated by churches and social clubs. That entire health care infrastructure has since been replaced by publicly provided health insurance, largely through Medicaid and Medicare. Regardless of whether the medical and financial results are better today, the relationship between the people who receive health care assistance and those who pay for it has changed fundamentally. Few would dispute that this change has affected the total cost of health care, and the relationships among patients, doctors, and hospitals, negatively. Financial help for those in need has also changed profoundly. Local, community-based charitable organizations once provided the majority of aid, resulting in a personal relationship between those who received assistance and those who provided it. Today, Social Security and other government programs provide much or all of the income to low-income and indigent households. Nearly all the financial support that was once provided to temporarily unemployed workers by unions, mutual-aid societies, and local charities is now provided by federal income, food, and health programs. This shift from local, community-based, mutual-aid assistance to anonymous government payments has clearly altered the relationship between the receiver and the provider of the assistance. In the past, a person in need depended on help from people and organizations in his or her local community. The community representatives were generally aware of the person’s needs and tailored the assistance to meet those needs within the community’s budgetary constraints. Today, housing and other needs are addressed by government employees to whom the person in need is a complete stranger, and who have few or no ties to the community in which the needy person lives. Both cases of aid involve a dependent relationship. However, support provided by families, churches, and other civil society groups aims to restore a person to full flourishing and personal responsibility, and, ultimately, to be able to aid another person in turn. This kind of reciprocal expectation does not characterize the dependent relationship with the political system. The former relationship is essential to the existence of civil society itself. The latter is usually based on one-sided aid without accountability for a person’s regained responsibility for self and toward his community. Indeed, the “success” of such government programs is frequently measured by the program’s growth rather than by whether it helps recipients to escape dependence. While the dependent relationship with civil society leads to a balance between the interests of the needy person and the community, the dependent relationship with the government runs the risk of generating political pressure from interest groups—such as health care organizations, nonprofit organizations, and the aid recipients themselves—to expand and cement federal support. The Index of Dependence on Government provides a way to assess the magnitude and implications of the change in government dependence in American society. The Index is based principally on historical data from the Pres­ident’s fiscal year (FY) 2012 annual budget proposal.[11] The last year measured in the 2012 Index is FY 2010. The Center for Data Analysis (CDA) used a simple weighting scheme and inflation adjustment to restate these publicly available data. CDA analysts encourage replication of their work and will gladly provide the data that support this year’s Index upon request. The steps to prepare this year’s Index are described in the methodology in Section 3. Section 2: The Five Index Components CDA analysts began by reviewing the federal budget to identify federal programs and state activities supported by federal appropriations that fit the definition of dependence—providing assistance in areas once considered to be the responsibility of individuals, family, neighborhood groups, churches, and other civil society institutions. The immediate beneficiary of the program or activity must be an individual. This method generally excludes state programs; federally funded programs in which the states act as intermediaries are included. Elementary and secondary education are the principal state-based programs that are excluded under this stipulation. Post-secondary education is the only part of government-funded education included in the Index.[12] Military and federal employees are also excluded because national defense is the primary constitutionally mandated function of the federal government and thus does not promote dependence as measured by the Index. CDA analysts then divided the qualifying pro­grams into five broad components: 1.Housing 2.(a) Health Care and (b) Welfare 3.Retirement 4.Higher Education 5.Rural and Agricultural Services The following sections discuss the pace and content of policy changes in these five components. 1) Housing.[13] The Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD) was created in 1965 by consolidating several independent federal housing agencies into one presidential Cabinet department. The purpose of the consolidation was to elevate the importance of government housing assistance within the constellation of federal spending programs. At that time it was believed that the destructive riots that broke out in many cities in the early 1960s were a consequence of poor housing conditions and that these conditions were contributing to urban decay. HUD spending still largely reflects that dual mission. In any given year, about 80 percent of HUD’s budget is targeted at housing assistance, and the other 20 percent is focused on urban issues by way of the Community Development Block Grant (CDBG) program. Given the nature of these programmatic allocations, HUD budgetary and staff resources are concentrated on low-income households to an extent unmatched by any other federal department. Within the 80 percent of the HUD budget spent on housing assistance are a series of means-tested housing programs, some of which date back to the Great Depression. Typically, these programs provide low-income people, including the elderly and disabled, with apartments at monthly rents scaled to their incomes. The lower the income, the lower the rent. Traditionally, HUD and the local housing agencies provide eligible low-income households with “project-based” assistance, an apartment unit that is owned and maintained by the government. Public housing projects have historically been the most common form of such assistance, but they began to fall out of favor in the 1960s because of the rampant decay and deterioration that followed from concentrating too many troubled, low-income families in a single complex or neighborhood. Periodically, new forms of project-based programs are adopted as “reform,” which also tend to fall out of favor after several years of disappointing results. HOPE VI is the most recent form of project-based assistance, and high costs and low benefits led the George W. Bush Administration to attempt, unsuccessfully, to terminate the program in 2006. Efforts are now underway by some in the Obama Administration to increase the program’s funding. HUD also provides “tenant-based” housing assistance to low-income households in the form of rent vouchers and certificates. These certificates help low-income people rent apartments in the private sector by covering a portion of the rent. The lower the person’s or family’s income, the greater the share of rent covered by the voucher or certificate. Vouchers were implemented in the early 1970s as a cost-effective replacement for public housing and other forms of expensive project-based assistance; vouchers still account for only a portion of housing assistance because of housing-industry resistance to terminating the lucrative project-based programs. Finally, HUD provides block grants to cities and communities through the CDBG program according to a needs-based formula. Grant money can be spent at a community’s discretion among a series of permissible options. Among the allowable spending options is additional housing assistance, which many communities use to provide assistance to a greater number of low-income households. Although HUD programs are means-tested to determine eligibility, they are not entitlements. As a result, many eligible households do not receive any housing assistance due to funding limitations. In many communities, the waiting lists for housing assistance are several years—and in some cases local housing authorities no longer add new families to the list because there is simply no prospect of new applicants receiving an apartment in the foreseeable future. Recognizing that HUD housing assistance can create dependence among those who receive its benefits, some Members of Congress have attempted to extend the work requirements of the 1996 Personal Responsibility and Work Opportu­nity Reconciliation Act (PRWOR) to HUD programs. Advocates for the poor have thwarted these efforts. To date, the most that can be required of a HUD program beneficiary is eight hours per month of volunteer service to the community or housing project in which the beneficiary lives. After a mid-decade jump reflecting spending to rebuild infrastructure destroyed by Hurricanes Katrina and Rita, the housing component of the Index moderated, but in 2008 jumped significantly as the federal government added several mortgage-bailout programs to its traditional low-income, housing-assistance focus. Beginning in 2008, the federal government took over the operations of Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac and has since then spent more than $150 billion to keep them afloat and allow them to continue to provide mortgage credit to finance home sales. More than 90 percent of all single-family residential mortgage credit is now provided by these two government-sponsored, government-controlled enterprises, thereby extending dependence on federal assistance to middle-class and upper-middle-class households. 2(a) Health Care.[14] Increasing spending and enrollment in public health care programs, particularly Medicare, Medicaid, and the Children’s Health Insurance Program (CHIP), is leading to greater dependence on government. In 2010, total combined enrollment in these three programs was roughly 98 million individuals—32 percent of the entire U.S. population.[15] The three programs accounted for $793.2 billion, or 5.5 percent of GDP, in federal spending, 238 percent more than the $333.9 billion spent on these programs just a decade earlier.[16] According to the Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services (CMS), by 2020, government spending on health care will represent 50 percent of total national health expenditures.[17] In its 2011 annual report on health insurance coverage, the U.S. Census Bureau published figures that underscore the current trend toward greater dependence on government health programs.[18] The percentage of Americans in government health programs is rising faster than ever, in part due to a struggling economy, Medicaid and CHIP expansions, and a rapidly growing elderly population entitled to Medicare benefits. The consequences are greater dependence on taxpayer-subsidized coverage, and a decline in private health insurance. Medicare. Congress established Medicare in 1965 through Title XVIII of the Social Security Act. Medicare pays for health care for individuals ages 65 and above, and for those with certain disabilities. Medicare enrollment has steadily increased since its enactment due to increases in both population and individual life expectancy. In 1970, 20.4 million individuals were enrolled in Medicare.[19] By 2010, the number of</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348787132542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:05:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348787284001-74</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ: The more we learn, the more Benghazi looks like a gross security failure...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348779582461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear gregjanetommax/checkn/gedphillip In the words of Arche Bunker, STIFLE YOURSELF. You are making each and every Republican look like a mega-ultra-doofus. You will be responsible for many D votes by presenting yourself this way. STIFLE RIGHT NOW please.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1348787284001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:08:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348788294833-75</Id><Topic><Title>Obama with a 50-point lead!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_002</Username><Timestamp>1348763091747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:24:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, I know you re going to vote. I meant to say everybody should vote, early and often (as baggers fear).</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348788294833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:24:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348788445574-76</Id><Topic><Title>Why will Liberals vote for more debt?????</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348779129874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:52:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Ryan / Romney Republican plan, with it massive tax cuts for the already weathy, (according to the GAO) will increase the national debt $3.5 TRILLION dollars more than any budget proposals that Obama has proposed. So why would I vote for Romney when his budget plan will increase the deficit MORE than anything the Democrats have proposed? The Ryan/Romney budget does not even propose to balance the Federal budget until 2040!!! So why are you hammering the Dems? A New Deal Liberal Democrat, and proud of it. And yes, I WILL be ruled by fact checkers, because the truth DOES matter.</Msg><Username>gastbeer1954</Username><Timestamp>1348788445574</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:27:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348788883550-77</Id><Topic><Title>The Lead is now 53 points!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_002</Username><Timestamp>1348782712836</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:51:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the President continues on his exponential rise he will wipe out the repubs in the House and the Senate on election day.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1348788883550</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348789199457-78</Id><Topic><Title>The Lead is now 53 points!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_002</Username><Timestamp>1348782712836</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:51:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think there is a very good chance he will do just that.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1348789199457</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348794133358-79</Id><Topic><Title>Everett seeks branch campus from WSU, not UW</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1348775900372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:58:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see cg is trying to say something with his anonymous ratings.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1348794133358</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:02:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348796435274-80</Id><Topic><Title>Everett seeks branch campus from WSU, not UW</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1348775900372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:58:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong once again. Maybe it was simply another typically stupid post.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1348796435274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:40:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348799076214-81</Id><Title>Make that how many Boeing deliveries wow that means nothing to shareholders</Title><Msg>Notice how just 3 stocks of the DJ held it up today the one to discuss here is BA down, all those plane orders a certain boeing pumper claims is good and the larger EADS-company is just noise,well he needs to go to apple and notice on a up day apple is up over 2.4% while on a up day Boeing is down .21% while the main averages are up . Whats that mean, that means any shareholder of Boeing is losing their investment and not getting the huge gains that the stockmarket has posted for a few years Boeing was a 70 dollar range stock when apple was a 35 dollar stock and in the time it took to go from their last iphone to this phone apple value has gone up 700% so for `5 years the fowl has been stating the opinion , instead of getting any value, unless he is a paid Boeing union or mangment worker then the shareholders are paying him. the old person making huge on Boeing is the number one employee the CEO</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348799076214</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 22:24:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348799932126-82</Id><Topic><Title>GOP's female politicians look more feminine...but so do male Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1348774944456</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe he meant certain GOP politicians, certain fake religions, and certain magic underwear?</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1348799932126</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 22:38:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348800485081-83</Id><Title>Ready set strike Boeing SPEEA and try the outsourcing business plan sure you bet</Title><Msg>SPEEA, Boeing at loggerheads before decisive vote All signs point to a heavy rejection of Boeing's first contract offer to its white-collar engineering union when the mail-in ballots are counted Monday. A strike by engineering employees would be "a complete failure, in my mind, on both sides," Mike Delaney, left, vice president of engineering for Boeing Commercial Airplanes. Let's see, Boeing in it "wisdom" decided to try off shoring a bunch of the 787 engineering and machining. When the company was 20 billion in the hole due to the fact that they screwed up, didn’t their own engineering expert say outsourcing was a mistake and now the only thing keeping Boeing down will once more cause failure the MD managed of outsourcing as a failed business model .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1348800485081</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 22:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348801751270-84</Id><Title>A losing Coach wants a 4year contract renewal</Title><Msg>Claiming that the margin of losses is getting smaller with each game and eventually he will win one. Nice try Coach.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1348801751270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:09:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348803206195-85</Id><Topic><Title>Al Queda strikes our embassy</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348782407537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama lied Americans died</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1348803206195</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:33:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>