<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-13"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350106506376-1</Id><Title>French II - 4 quarters of A's</Title><Msg>a. tonsil hockey with Kris or Pam, as if I stand a a chance to feeling their tiny french I #$%$ too b.l. if mr paoltetti is still alive by the end of the year see. a. c. apparentlty th\e VC do not draft small tit gals who don;t tonsil hockey so well d. possibly might have not shown up to class according to the flex-rules of the time between then and now e....</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1350106506376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 01:35:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350108505112-2</Id><Topic><Title>Why Don't Democrats Ever Want to Pay for the Things they want?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349986120786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:08:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You lie like a Republican.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1350108505112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 02:08:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350109773238-3</Id><Topic><Title>The Vice Presidential Debate: Joe Biden Was Right to Laugh</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1350081718069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:41:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some excellent commentaries there on Biden vs. the patheic lying huckster... Thanks for all of them.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1350109773238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 02:29:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350114228985-4</Id><Title>they have added: She's A Woman who undertrstands</Title><Msg>to blowing up trains in 1962</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1350114228985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 03:43:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350116174302-5</Id><Title>What team are you on anyways</Title><Msg>riding bicylces over to the water fountain when they put me in first pitch got stuck in the chain link fence behind the catcher throw the baseball over the plate into the strike zone to,their best hitter easy out three Now I undersrtand...She;s A Woman</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1350116174302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 04:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350118790795-6</Id><Topic><Title>Why Don't Democrats Ever Want to Pay for the Things they want?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349986120786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:08:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or a republican who used to work at Bain Capitol</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1350118790795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 04:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350119221081-7</Id><Topic><Title>If you could magnify a RWNJ's brain about a million times</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1350071619033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:53:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look up the word "pathetic" in the dictionary......if one's not handy just look in the mirror</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1350119221081</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 05:07:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350122741887-8</Id><Topic><Title>Triumph of the Wrong: The GOP's Austerity Plan for America</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1350081289952</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:34:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and hopefully we will draft liberal wimps, like you, so that you can actually serve instead of being fat, dumb and lazy while collecting your welfare handout.</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1350122741887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 06:05:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350122826380-9</Id><Topic><Title>Why Don't Democrats Ever Want to Pay for the Things they want?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349986120786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:08:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wimpy #$%$</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1350122826380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 06:07:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350122872674-10</Id><Topic><Title>The Vice Presidential Debate: Joe Biden Was Right to Laugh</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1350081718069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:41:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who are you? The BA board proctor or BA board proctologist?</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1350122872674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 06:07:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350122933198-11</Id><Topic><Title>Why Joe won</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1350084969448</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is Big Bird your imaginary friend?</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1350122933198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 06:08:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350123005948-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why Don't Democrats Ever Want to Pay for the Things they want?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1349986120786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 16:08:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are an uneducated simpleton and getting all emotional again.</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1350123005948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 06:10:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350137728786-13</Id><Topic><Title>Wisonsin, Michigan. Pennsyvania &amp; New Harmpshire Now leaning Romney,</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1350061834404</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:10:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, the MSM is democrat biased, so if even the MSM polls say that Mitt is leading -- well it certainly is believable.</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1350137728786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:15:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350137916003-14</Id><Title>Gallup Poll Romney 49% / O'Bummer 47%</Title><Msg>Romney up another point -- O'Bummer not Rasmusson shows Romney 49% / O'Bummer 48%</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1350137916003</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:18:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350138303057-15</Id><Title>Romney up by 2% in Virginia</Title><Msg>according to real clear poltics</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1350138303057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:25:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350138360272-16</Id><Title>Romney up by 4% in New Hampshire</Title><Msg>according to real clear politics</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1350138360272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:26:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350139584394-17</Id><Topic><Title>BA Accelerated Rate of Movement... How Long can BA Last??</Title><Username>houstonhart228</Username><Timestamp>1350137564939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:12:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The site really helped me to make the profits.</Msg><Username>tristansnyder851</Username><Timestamp>1350139584394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:46:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350140038818-18</Id><Title>O'Bummer Falls Below 60% on Intrade!!!</Title><Msg>He's lost more than 20% since just before his debate with Mitt. He's going down faster than a cheap hooker on a paying customer -- or Monica on Bill.</Msg><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1350140038818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350140323388-19</Id><Topic><Title>O'Bummer Falls Below 60% on Intrade!!!</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1350140038818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:53:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even the fantasy poll has to employ some measure of reality.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1350140323388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350140381740-20</Id><Title>The ‘Moderate Mitt’ Myth</Title><Msg>The ‘Moderate Mitt’ Myth The way a presidential candidate campaigns for office matters to the country. A campaign should demonstrate seriousness of purpose and a set of core beliefs, and it should signal to voters whether a candidate shows trustworthiness and judgment. Those things don’t seem to matter to Mitt Romney. From the beginning of his run for the Republican nomination, Mr. Romney has offered to transfigure himself into any shape desired by an audience in order to achieve power. In front of massed crowds or on television, he can sound sunny and inclusive, radiating a feel-good centrism. His “severely conservative” policies and disdain for much of the country are reserved for partisans, donors and the harsh ideologues who clutter his party’s base. This polarity is often described as “flip-flopping,” but the word is too mild to describe opposing positions that are simultaneously held. The best way to judge candidates is not by the popular way they describe their plans near the end of a campaign; it is by the most divisive presentations of themselves earlier on. A candidate’s political calculations when fewer people are watching is likely to say far more about character than poll-tested pleasantries in the spotlight. That’s what is disingenuous about the “Moderate Mitt” in recent speeches and the first presidential debate. He hasn’t abandoned or flip-flopped from the severe positions that won him the Republican nomination; they remain at the core of his campaign, on his Web site and in his position papers, and they occasionally slip out in unguarded moments. All he’s doing is slapping whitewash on his platform. The immoderation of his policies, used to win favor with a hard-right party, cannot be disguised. This week, for example, in the swing state of Iowa, Mr. Romney tried to cover up his strident anti-abortion agenda. “There’s no legislation with regards to abortion that I’m familiar with that would become part of my agenda,” he told The Des Moines Register’s editorial board. But that carefully worded statement was designed to mislead, because the threat to women’s rights doesn’t necessarily come from legislation. He would cut financing for Planned Parenthood, and he has said he wants to overturn Roe v. Wade and would appoint justices who would do so. And, though he has conveniently forgotten, he does support anti-abortion legislation — what he called in a 2011 essay the Pain-Capable Unborn Child Protection Act to ban abortion when a fetus can feel pain. In 2007, he said he’d sign a bill prohibiting all abortions. He has also tried to paper over his positions on his $5 trillion tax cut, pretending it would be cost-free, and he now says he wants to cover pre-existing health conditions, though his plan does so only for those who have insurance coverage. At last week’s debate, Mr. Romney presented himself as a bipartisan leader able to work with Democrats. But that’s not how Massachusetts Democrats remember his tenure as governor, as Michael Wines of The Times reported last week. He ignored or insulted Democrats and failed to achieve most of his big-ticket proposals, like reform of the Civil Service and pension systems. His decision to support a universal health care system in 2006, long advocated by Democrats, was seen at the time as a purely political calculation, at least until Republicans rejected the idea in 2009 when President Obama proposed it. There isn’t really a Moderate Mitt; what is on display now is better described as Convenient Mitt. Anyone willing to advocate extremism to raise money and win primaries is likely to do the same to stay in office.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1350140381740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:59:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350141000434-21</Id><Topic><Title>O'Bummer Falls Below 60% on Intrade!!!</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1350140038818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:53:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blob, that's a really dumb post. Intrade is not a POLL -- it is a PREDICTION MARKET. And it has nothing to do with "fantasy." It's about putting your money where your mouth is. Clearly you don't know you're talking about. Have you been listening to Rmoney and his randroid sidekick a little too much, and that lying style is rubbing off?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1350141000434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350141237227-22</Id><Topic><Title>Romney up by 4% in New Hampshire</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1350138360272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:26:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I still don't understand it...........Romney down, you can't trust the polls - Romney ahead, break out the champagne - I don't trust you and I definitely don't trust Romney so I'll trust my own instincts and assume it'll be a tight race with the majority of the voters finally seeing the light and re-electing Obama</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1350141237227</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:13:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350143504863-23</Id><Topic><Title>O'Bummer Falls Below 60% on Intrade!!!</Title><Username>breck80424</Username><Timestamp>1350140038818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:53:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bebop, Take a tranquilizer. "POLLS are an integral part of political FORECASTING" per the WIKI. Whether it is done with someone's voice, click on a website, or a meaningless "trade" with someone's money like Intrade. Also, per the on-line dictionary: "FORCAST: to PREDICT". As far as "Intrade" being a "fantasy", its "measure" or "prediction" seems to fulfill or sate Hooz's present fantasies of Obama coming in at a landslide - unlike all of the other people based polls that presently provide a "neck and neck" prediction. So, yes, I would say that "fantasy" is an accurate description. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1350143504863</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:51:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350144257908-24</Id><Topic><Title>BA Accelerated Rate of Movement... How Long can BA Last??</Title><Username>houstonhart228</Username><Timestamp>1350137564939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:12:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can count on your money by investing in the stockmarket for better future returns.</Msg><Username>carrollraymundo473</Username><Timestamp>1350144257908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350146144842-25</Id><Title>Obama's ATF cans F&amp;F whistle blower in Denny's parking lot</Title><Msg>Where is the union fighting for their members, where is Joe Biden fighting for the working guy. They can't even do the wrong thing right. By Katie Pavlich News Editor, Townhall Special Agent Vince Cefalu has worked for the Bureau of Alcohol Tobacco and Firearms for more than 25 years. On top of successfully placing dozens of hard criminals behind bars throughout his career, Cefalu has received promotions and consistently positive evaluations. When he started raising his voice about ATF corruption and illegal wiretapping in 2005, things changed. Tuesday evening, Cefalu was asked to meet Special Agent in Charge of the San Francisco Field Division Joseph Riehl at a Denny's Restaurant near Lake Tahoe. When he arrived, he was served termination papers in the parking lot. Classy move. The exchange was secretly recorded by a confidential source. David Codrea has more: The video, shaky at times from being handheld, and with color imbalance streaking happening inadvertently in the uploading to YouTube, was recorded by a confidential source and shows Cefalu approached by two ATF management representatives including Joseph M. Riehl, Special Agent in Charge of the San Francisco Field Division, which encompasses Northern California and Nevada field offices.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1350146144842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:35:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350151157966-26</Id><Topic><Title>The ‘Moderate Mitt’ Myth</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1350140381740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney Does Look Moderate Compared to the Left Wing Socialist Obama! So, What is your Point?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1350151157966</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350151742282-27</Id><Title>Obama's Campaign Collasping Under the Perfect Storm!</Title><Msg>A Convergence of a Poor Economy, Caught Lying Over and Over Again about the Terrorist Attack in Benghazi, and Obama's Utter Defeat in the Presidential Debate has Romney Gaining Momentum in Almost all States! Romney Leads on the Swing States... Too Late for Obama as Romney has the MoJo!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1350151742282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:09:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350155677685-28</Id><Topic><Title>David Brooks syndicated columnist has it right</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1350154486861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wouldn't use the term "fix" - try "modify".........if that doesn't fit try "ruin"</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1350155677685</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:14:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350157023855-29</Id><Topic><Title>David Brooks syndicated columnist has it right</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1350154486861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe we could just have gregjanetommax fixed. :-)</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1350157023855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:37:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350158394993-30</Id><Topic><Title>David Brooks syndicated columnist article this morning has it so right</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1350149834368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:37:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you hate the English language?</Msg><Username>alan_gonquin_is_queer</Username><Timestamp>1350158394993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:59:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350158633355-31</Id><Title>Friday activity</Title><Msg>767 for DHL had first flight. 787 for China Southern had first flight. 777 for Ethiopian had first flight. 787 for ANA had first flight. 737 for Ryanair had first flight. 737 for Spicejet had first flight. 737 for Malasia was delivered. 787 for Ethiopian had a customer flight.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1350158633355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:03:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350159616604-32</Id><Topic><Title>Sir Paul McCartney, brilliant songwriter, has it right</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1350155377102</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:09:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get back Lorretta.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1350159616604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:20:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350161679859-33</Id><Title>The smartest man at Boeing is James McNerney</Title><Msg>The GE-McD management is up to the usual games. Wonder if they have already hired one of the typical anti- union firms to try the intimidation game and stay marginally within the law. Boeing may well be sticking both feet in mouth - or suffering from optical- rectitude same games you played at GE will not win you any popularity games (oh! that is right! none of us can stand you anyway!). Do not forget management...without the people who do the work..You have NO bonuses or executive pay. *slap*Boeing’s white-collar union, embroiled in testy contract negotiations with management, filed two unfair labor practice complaints Friday against the company. The Society of Professional Engineering Employees in Aerospace (SPEEA) said Monday that Boeing had attempted to harass and intimidate its members by video-taping solidarity marches and conversely by confiscating the cameras of SPEEA members and deleting their photographs of the events. The union filed the complaints at the Seattle office of the National Labor Relations Board (NLRB). unposter.Jul 16, 2012 12:56 I'm holding for 100. How is uniposter going to get to 100 when the smartest man at Boeing is James McNerney ? BTW JRCC up 30% last week on romney coal is good pump did you miss that uni-foul wait for BA to reach 100 and lose as usual</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1350161679859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:54:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350163708861-34</Id><Topic><Title>any body see Obama's homosexual agenda?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1350082484595</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U r just lying about both of these bills. Why are you so against anti discrimination bills?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1350163708861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350164338382-35</Id><Topic><Title>BA Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>kevininthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1350150975754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:56:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, I just downloaded it and I might end up using this every day now...</Msg><Username>peelingoutsummer</Username><Timestamp>1350164338382</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:38:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350166268353-36</Id><Topic><Title>The Vice Presidential Debate: Joe Biden Was Right to Laugh</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1350081718069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:41:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When a wise man has a controversy with a foolish man, The foolish man either rages or laughs, and there is no rest. (Prov 29:9)</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1350166268353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:11:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350166331594-37</Id><Topic><Title>David Brooks syndicated columnist article this morning has it so right</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1350149834368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:37:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does he hate more--English, or anybody not exactly like him? Just another semiliterate Republican homophobe racist.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1350166331594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:12:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350171435964-38</Id><Topic><Title>The Vice Presidential Debate: Joe Biden Was Right to Laugh</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1350081718069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:41:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, That was a good response, though the word that you are pointing to (Hebrew, "heh-awkh' ", transliteration) is "an expression of joy" or "satisfaction over the misfortune of an enemy or rival". I suppose you are then saying that Biden was continuously filled with joy or gloating while he was supposed to be debating. Therefore, he was not taking the debate seriously. That was my conclusion as well. But, I liked your response. Keep up the Bible reading! BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1350171435964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:37:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350172391124-39</Id><Topic><Title>The Vice Presidential Debate: Joe Biden Was Right to Laugh</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1350081718069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:41:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Various bulky persons need to concentrate on Matthew 6:1. Especially with respect to Republican hypocrisy.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1350172391124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:53:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350172617892-40</Id><Topic><Title>The Vice Presidential Debate: Joe Biden Was Right to Laugh</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1350081718069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:41:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't try. Republican hypocrites are the worst kind. They'll eventually get theirs.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1350172617892</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:56:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350172943914-41</Id><Topic><Title>The Vice Presidential Debate: Joe Biden Was Right to Laugh</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1350081718069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:41:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dem666, And what part of the Bible do you concentrate on for yourself for eternity? Imagine you are standing outside the "Gates of Heaven" seeking permission to enter. Which single verse would apply to you that you could use that would guarantee entry? Now, lest you think I am "playing with you", I am not. And, be sure that the verse you select provides a "guarantee". Unlike the tenor of the original post, I am not laughing becuse this is not at all funny. We get only one chance, after that is the judgment. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1350172943914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350173795856-42</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Campaign Collasping Under the Perfect Storm!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1350151742282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:09:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you imagine the kind of tongue lashing by the Liberal Media if George Bush Jr. had Obama's record? And the Liberals say there isn't any bias in the Media! And what would the Liberal Media say about former President Bush Jr. if the Media found out that George Bush Sr. was a Communist Marxist? They'd drag the entire Bush family to Timbuktu and back! Barak gets the royal treatment like Little Lord Fontlauroy! Just stating the facts of the situation. A Conservative President always has to work twice as hard as a Liberal President for respect from the Liberal Media.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1350173795856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:16:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350185098594-43</Id><Topic><Title>The Vice Presidential Debate: Joe Biden Was Right to Laugh</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1350081718069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:41:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is despicable when a pseudo-religious personage continuously bears false witness in favor of a political position and tries to falsely present a different image. Disgusting hypocrisy that marks a sickening % of Republicans.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1350185098594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 23:24:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350185853886-44</Id><Topic><Title>The Vice Presidential Debate: Joe Biden Was Right to Laugh</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1350081718069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:41:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dem666, Save your anger and hate breath on this one. You did not answer my question because you cannot. Listen, fella, you need Jesus. Go and read Romans 10:9,10. Also John 3:16-18. If you were to ascribe to belief (faith) as it states in those passages you would have the answer that you need. May God bless you, BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1350185853886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 23:37:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>