<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352529061649-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama wants 98% of Americans taxes cut now!</Title><Username>gin.haruko</Username><Timestamp>1352485062797</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:17:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is sad that the people who tricked you into this 1%-99% class warfare thing to get your vote are none other than part of the 1% itself (e.g., Obamas, Clintons, John Kerry-Heinz, Pelosi, Kennedy's, Hollywood celebs, etc.) -- nothing but a bunch of rich hypocrites. If they cared so much about the MIDDLE CLASS, why don't they become part of it? Even Bozo Biden parades around trying to trick people to vote for him by claiming/lying he is part of the MIDDLE CLASS, although his income is way above it. Also, if you represent a charity, which candidate would YOU like to have contribute to your cause (Note that Romney gave more percentage-wise than anyone else, as well as DOLLAR-WI$E, and note that stingy BOZO BIDEN was the cheapskate): Tax rates and charitable giving in 2011: President Barack Obama: Income: $790,000 Federal taxes: $162,000 Tax rate: 20.5 percent Charitable donations: $172,000 Percentage of income: 22 percent Republican presidential nominee Mitt Romney: Income: $13.7 million Federal taxes: $1.94 million Tax rate: 14.1 percent Charitable donations: $4 million Percentage of income: 29.35 percent Vice President Joe Biden: Income: $379,178 Federal taxes: $87,900 Tax rate: 23 percent Charitable donations: $5,500 Percentage of income: 1.46 percent Vice presidential nominee Paul Ryan: Income: $323,416 Federal taxes: $64,764 Tax rate: 20 percent Charitable donations: $12,991 Percentage of income: 4 percent</Msg><Username>mr_johnson2u</Username><Timestamp>1352529061649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 01:31:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352530880794-2</Id><Topic><Title>Will the House Stop Holding America Hostage and Let the America Progress Forward?</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1352493103440</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:31:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe it's time for a showdown. Paul Krugman: Let's not make a deal NY Times To say the obvious: Democrats won an amazing victory. Not only did they hold the White House despite a still-troubled economy, in a year when their Senate majority was supposed to be doomed, they actually added seats. Nor was that all: They scored major gains in the states. Most notably, California -- long a poster child for the political dysfunction that comes when nothing can get done without a legislative supermajority -- not only voted for much-needed tax increases, but elected, you guessed it, a Democratic supermajority. But one goal eluded the victors. Even though preliminary estimates suggest that Democrats received somewhat more votes than Republicans in congressional elections, the GOP retains solid control of the House thanks to extreme gerrymandering by courts and Republican-controlled state governments. And Rep. John Boehner, the speaker of the House, wasted no time in declaring that his party remains as intransigent as ever, utterly opposed to any rise in tax rates even as it whines about the size of the deficit. So President Barack Obama has to make a decision, almost immediately, about how to deal with continuing Republican obstruction. How far should he go in accommodating the GOP's demands? My answer is, not far at all. Obama should hang tough, declaring himself willing, if necessary, to hold his ground even at the cost of letting his opponents inflict damage on a still-shaky economy. And this is definitely no time to negotiate a "grand bargain" on the budget that snatches defeat from the jaws of victory. In saying this, I don't mean to minimize the very real economic dangers posed by the so-called fiscal cliff that is looming at the end of this year if the two parties can't reach a deal. Both the Bush-era tax cuts and the Obama administration's payroll tax cut are set to expire, even as automatic spending cuts in defense and elsewhere kick in thanks to the deal struck after the 2011 confrontation over the debt ceiling. And the looming combination of tax increases and spending cuts looks easily large enough to push America back into recession. Nobody wants to see that happen. Yet it may happen all the same, and Obama has to be willing to let it happen if necessary. Why? Because Republicans are trying, for the third time since he took office, to use economic blackmail to achieve a goal they lack the votes to achieve through the normal legislative process. In particular, they want to extend the Bush tax cuts for the wealthy, even though the nation can't afford to make those tax cuts permanent and the public believes that taxes on the rich should go up -- and they're threatening to block any deal on anything else unless they get their way. So they are, in effect, threatening to tank the economy unless their demands are met. Obama essentially surrendered in the face of similar tactics at the end of 2010, extending low taxes on the rich for two more years. He made significant concessions again in 2011, when Republicans threatened to create financial chaos by refusing to raise the debt ceiling. And the current potential crisis is the legacy of those past concessions. Well, this has to stop -- unless we want hostage-taking, the threat of making the nation ungovernable, to become a standard part of our political process. So what should he do? Just say no and go over the cliff if necessary. It's worth pointing out that the fiscal cliff isn't really a cliff. It's not like the debt-ceiling confrontation, where terrible things might well have happened right away if the deadline had been missed. This time, nothing very bad will happen to the economy if agreement isn't reached until a few weeks or even a few months into 2013. So there's time to bargain. More important, however, is the point that a stalemate would hurt Republican backers, corporate donors in particular, every bit as much as it hurt the rest of the country. As the risk of severe economic damage grew, Republicans would face intense pressure to cut a deal after all. Meanwhile, the president is in a far stronger position than in previous confrontations. I don't place much stock in talk of "mandates," but Obama did win re-election with a populist campaign, so he can plausibly claim that Republicans are defying the will of the American people. And he just won his big election and is, therefore, far better placed than before to weather any political blowback from economic troubles -- especially when it would be so obvious that these troubles were being deliberately inflicted by the GOP in a last-ditch attempt to defend the privileges of the 1 percent. Most of all, standing up to hostage-taking is the right thing to do for the health of America's political system. So stand your ground, Mr. President, and don't give in to threats. No deal is better than a bad deal.</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1352530880794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 02:01:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352530957431-3</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush -- always Bush's fault</Msg><Username>mr_johnson2u</Username><Timestamp>1352530957431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 02:02:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352533833297-4</Id><Topic><Title>I'm feeling patriotic</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1352513869058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 21:17:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may be feeling patriotic but you're sounding idiotic.</Msg><Username>ossiker</Username><Timestamp>1352533833297</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 02:50:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352534221197-5</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you telling us that Obama attacking terrorist would have hurt his campaign? Get a grip, fool.</Msg><Username>ossiker</Username><Timestamp>1352534221197</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 02:57:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352535630011-6</Id><Topic><Title>Open flys close careers</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352506044986</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:07:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So why did he have to resign? Who wouldn't want to have an affair with this DISH? She is HOT HOT HOT!</Msg><Username>vibrant_alpha_male</Username><Timestamp>1352535630011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 03:20:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352541284844-7</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, a lot of it is Reagan's fault too.</Msg><Username>shameless_commie</Username><Timestamp>1352541284844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 04:54:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352545917239-8</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We had you to tell us about it every day . What a blessing it is to have Liberals around . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1352545917239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 06:11:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352546114898-9</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Turns out Fox News was right, and you were wrong again, so who's the bumpkin now, pumpkin . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1352546114898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 06:15:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352547111948-10</Id><Title>So, I Suppose This Means No XL Pipe Line</Title><Msg>The Canadians shake their heads in disbelief, and prepare to make deals with China, industrialized nations cooperating with each other to their mutual benefit . P.S. Boeing announces lay-offs in defense and space . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1352547111948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 06:31:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352557831619-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama wants 98% of Americans taxes cut now!</Title><Username>gin.haruko</Username><Timestamp>1352485062797</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:17:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are almost right but obama is a global guy, and globally you and most Americans are the 2%.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1352557831619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 09:30:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352559355282-12</Id><Title>My Condolences to Baggers</Title><Msg>I know how much you baggers really wanted a Bokmun/ Hermanator ticket. It was unfortunate the party moneybags owners foisted Willard Mittford off on you. Dirty shame really. Truly Pathetic . Eh!</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1352559355282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 09:55:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352561500472-13</Id><Title>Boeing Corporate to hold up Philadelphia as a ................</Title><Msg>model division!!!!!! Rumours are circulating to that effect!!!!!!</Msg><Username>caveman2501</Username><Timestamp>1352561500472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 10:31:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352562385263-14</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1352559355282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 09:55:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL!</Msg><Username>demfascisls40</Username><Timestamp>1352562385263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 10:46:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352563477240-15</Id><Topic><Title>So, I Suppose This Means No XL Pipe Line</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1352547111948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 06:31:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there will be a keystone pipeline from Canada to Texas</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1352563477240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 11:04:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352565623480-16</Id><Topic><Title>Obama wants 98% of Americans taxes cut now!</Title><Username>gin.haruko</Username><Timestamp>1352485062797</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:17:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paulie, you are spinning like a spider. Still your post about tax cheats remind me of Timothy Geithner. You know that guy Obuma appointed to print all that money for him.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1352565623480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 11:40:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352568532840-17</Id><Title>It's time to protect your 401k's before its to late. Market is going a lot lower fast</Title><Msg>It's time to protect your 401k's before its to late. Market is going a lot lower fast</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1352568532840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 12:28:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352574445211-18</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1352559355282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 09:55:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course we do NOT live in a constitutional Republic. We haven't for awhile, if ever. From the days of white-male property owners to the days of corporations are people and super/pacs's Arthur Jensen: You have meddled with the primal forces of nature, Mr. Beale, and I won't have it! Is that clear? You think you've merely stopped a business deal. That is not the case! The Arabs have taken billions of dollars out of this country, and now they must put it back! It is ebb and flow, tidal gravity! It is ecological balance! You are an old man who thinks in terms of nations and peoples. There are no nations. There are no peoples. There are no Russians. There are no Arabs. There are no third worlds. There is no West. There is only one holistic system of systems, one vast and immane, interwoven, interacting, multivariate, multinational dominion of dollars. Petro-dollars, electro-dollars, multi-dollars, reichmarks, rins, rubles, pounds, and shekels. It is the international system of currency which determines the totality of life on this planet. That is the natural order of things today. That is the atomic and subatomic and galactic structure of things today! And YOU have meddled with the primal forces of nature, and YOU... WILL... ATONE! Am I getting through to you, Mr. Beale? You get up on your little twenty-one inch screen and howl about America and democracy. There is no America. There is no democracy. There is only IBM, and ITT, and AT&amp;T, and DuPont, Dow, Union Carbide, and Exxon. Those are the nations of the world today. What do you think the Russians talk about in their councils of state, Karl Marx? They get out their linear programming charts, statistical decision theories, minimax solutions, and compute the price-cost probabilities of their transactions and investments, just like we do. We no longer live in a world of nations and ideologies, Mr. Beale. The world is a college of corporations, inexorably determined by the immutable bylaws of business. The world is a business, Mr. Beale. It has been since man crawled out of the slime. And our children will live, Mr. Beale, to see that... perfect world... in which there's no war or famine, oppression or brutality. One vast and ecumenical holding company, for whom all men will work to serve a common profit, in which all men will hold a share of stock. All necessities provided, all anxieties tranquilized, all boredom amused. And I have chosen you, Mr. Beale, to preach this evangel. Howard Beale: Why me? Arthur Jensen: Because you're on television, dummy. Sixty million people watch you every night of the week, Monday through Friday. Howard Beale: I have seen the face of God. Arthur Jensen: You just might be right, Mr. Beale.</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1352574445211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 14:07:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352574691006-19</Id><Title>It was a good win. A clean win.</Title><Msg>Similar to the win of 2008. And unlike 2000 and 2004 where Bush sued Gore to stop the vote count letting the right-wing court decide an election, and irrefutable voter fraud and counting irregularities.</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1352574691006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 14:11:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352577667269-20</Id><Topic><Title>It was a good win. A clean win.</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1352574691006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 14:11:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course it was helped along here by the fact that here, as in 2008, the Republicans wanted to lose--while in 2000 and 2004 they wanted to win.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1352577667269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 15:01:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352577704014-21</Id><Topic><Title>43 Trillion dollar LAwsuit awaits Obama Whitehouse</Title><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1351854694176</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 07:11:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It’s obvious why you got so many thumbs down for your post, as follows: “…As many such as Rush Limbaugh had charged, the massive bailouts used for AIG, General Motors, Chrysler Corporation, a number of banks, even broadcasting companies, was apparently disbursed for other clandestine purposes such as slush funds for Democrat election campaigns. …” Lush Rimbow rarely identifies those in the mega-banks, or similarly sized corporations, as partners in crime. In fact these are the money centers that work in concert with the Federal Reserve to fleece the rest of the population for their own benefit. Of course, if you wish to contradict the claim, please DO post anything Rimbow has ever said that identifies these economic powerhouses as really being at the heart of virtually all current corrupt market activities. It is abundantly clear that Bimbow’s success is due, in large part, because of his continuing support for America’s largest corporations, despite their participation in that which goes against the public interest, like outsourcing. Companies, like Boeing, benefit greatly from the stirring up of international conflict, as do those behind the central banks internationally through their loan activities, backed primarily by the US population making such activities risk free (taxpayer funded along with the hidden inflation tax). Beyond that, your post was a positive one on a news story that gets far too little coverage on the lawsuit by the Spire Law Group. We can only hope that this case proceeds at enough speed to save the country from collapse.</Msg><Username>hapiwondrer</Username><Timestamp>1352577704014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 15:01:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352577822808-22</Id><Topic><Title>So, I Suppose This Means No XL Pipe Line</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1352547111948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 06:31:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw Daryl Hannah speak about it. She said the line goes all the way to the Gulf. It's not about bringing the oil to the USA--it's about bringing the oil to the world market.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1352577822808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 15:03:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352579353425-23</Id><Topic><Title>Open flys close careers</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352506044986</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:07:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bongo 52. Sabre 6.</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1352579353425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 15:29:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352583416620-24</Id><Topic><Title>So, I Suppose This Means No XL Pipe Line</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1352547111948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 06:31:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hopefully that horrible tar sand pipeline is dead for good! Most Canadians do not want the Keystone Pipe Line or tar sands oil! Famous Canadian Naomi Klein is an award-winning journalist, syndicated columnist and author of many international bestsellers and she says that opposition to the Keystone Pipeline on both sides of the border is fierce and many will lay their life on the line to stop it!</Msg><Username>gin.haruko</Username><Timestamp>1352583416620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 16:36:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352584488233-25</Id><Title>Is Mittens still going on his "Jobs Tour" ?</Title><Msg>whatever a jobs tour is...</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1352584488233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 16:54:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352585876096-26</Id><Topic><Title>So, I Suppose This Means No XL Pipe Line</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1352547111948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 06:31:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The Canadians shake their heads in disbelief, and prepare to make deals with China" That is what the pipeline is for anyway, to send Canadian oil to china, we won't get anything out of it, but all the risk from the pipeline.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1352585876096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 17:17:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352587512956-27</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's a "Peedrool?" Another lost teabagging doofus Republican old angry white Confederate States resident?</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1352587512956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 17:45:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352587662506-28</Id><Topic><Title>So, I Suppose This Means No XL Pipe Line</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1352547111948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 06:31:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good...the destruction to the boreal forest for profit is obscene</Msg><Username>opiespa</Username><Timestamp>1352587662506</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 17:47:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352587760279-29</Id><Topic><Title>So, I Suppose This Means No XL Pipe Line</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1352547111948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 06:31:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"P.S. Boeing announces lay-offs in defense and space " Mainly deadwood....VP's and directors....No one will miss them</Msg><Username>opiespa</Username><Timestamp>1352587760279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 17:49:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352590210564-30</Id><Topic><Title>So, I Suppose This Means No XL Pipe Line</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1352547111948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 06:31:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama just closed the western half of the United States to oil shale development. This guy is serious about bringing fuel prices to $6 or $7 a gallon. America is doomed under Obama!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1352590210564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 18:30:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352590847811-31</Id><Topic><Title>So, I Suppose This Means No XL Pipe Line</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1352547111948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 06:31:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mother Nature wins another!</Msg><Username>opiespa</Username><Timestamp>1352590847811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 18:40:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352592868117-32</Id><Topic><Title>Open flys close careers</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352506044986</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:07:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wrong as usual - he can be subpoened- and one way or the other- he will testify before a Congressional Committee under oath- probably in a closed meeting.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352592868117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 19:14:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352597290039-33</Id><Topic><Title>Open flys close careers</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352506044986</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:07:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don, It is a curious as follows: 1. The scandal is revealed after the election, though it was clearly known for a long time (a la the FBI and CIA security investigations). One can only assume that the President knew. 2. Broadwell was being investigated as a result of a complaint related to "harassing" emails. The FBI also indicated that they had thought that Petraeus' email account was compromised. What that might mean is that either his government or his (more sensitive) email accounts were accessed by Broadwell. To relate that to the email harassment, that means that some "private" email addresses were being used, addresses that few would have - save for the likes of Petraeus. The FBI does not start an investigation related to email without there being something fairly substantial involved. 3. Broadwell's initial contact with Petraeus was all about this book of hers. Books sales require public exposure and interest. Lots os sales means lots of money. Perhaps Broadwell purposely used these private email addresses to harass some folks for the express purpose of provoking complaints that would start an investigation and bring down Petraeus. Maybe she was spurned or maybe she simply saw his demise as an avenue to get that exposure she needed for her book sales - and thus, money. What is not likely is that she was too stupid to realize that using private email addresses, known to very few, and harassing folks would not expose her to an investigation - and lead to Petraeus and their affair. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1352597290039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 20:28:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352599759660-34</Id><Topic><Title>Open flys close careers</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352506044986</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:07:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We now know hoozdik_hertz.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1352599759660</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 21:09:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352600916684-35</Id><Topic><Title>Open flys close careers</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352506044986</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:07:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Naw- thats way too complicated - Occams razor applies 1) Broadwell was/is a climber and proud of her close relationship with Petraeus 2) She tangled with some other female ( read cat fight ) and used her friendship with Petraues as some sort of a club - ( i'll tell god on you for this . . . ) 3) said female went to fbi - being a civilian issue. In checking personal email accounts/emails came across ref to Petraeus. 4) FBI has zip control or authority over cia accounts investigations - but probably noticed a govt account in emails to from harassed female or from Broadwell 5) harassment did not reach criminal level - but at some time - FBI notified agency ( When) The rest is history However- still questions Timeline- When notify agency When notify petraeus 6) there is IMHO a strong possibility that said female harassed was with agency ? 7) another IMHO-- agency #$%$$ed that petraeus claimed video ddespite agency member in tripoli claimingm opposite - and figured its get even time Sort of like BA - the bodies you step on on the way up can trip you on the way down. ..</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352600916684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 21:28:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352601600942-36</Id><Title>Romney is a worthless loser like the rest of bloodthirsty rightwingers</Title><Msg>World will be a much better place without republicans.</Msg><Username>awesome_turk</Username><Timestamp>1352601600942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 21:40:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352602046992-37</Id><Topic><Title>So, I Suppose This Means No XL Pipe Line</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1352547111948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 06:31:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>meanwhile Obuma supporter W Buffet bought Burlington Northern- another company ordered BUCU tanker cars to ship oil from canada- north dakota to texas. Pipline would have put a major crimp in that deal and reduced long term profits. Guess which companies put in many $$ to campaign ? we've got the best congress and president our tax money can buy.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352602046992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 21:47:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352602184532-38</Id><Topic><Title>So, I Suppose This Means No XL Pipe Line</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1352547111948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 06:31:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rail-car delivery forecast for 2012 from Rail Theory Forecasts' Toby Kolstad For a very long time, rail-car orders and deliveries have followed very predictable patterns, tracking closely with well-known and long-established patterns in the economy and railroad operations. There always have been anomalies — such as the build-up of the ethanol fleet or a temporary surge in orders from a government stimulus program — but they only had a marginal impact on the total fleet numbers and either could be easily quantified for future forecasts or dismissed as one-time phenomena. However, everything changed in 2011. Orders surged as the economy sputtered during the first half of the year, driving up delivery rates at an unprecedented rate. The words of Dorothy Gale in The Wizard of Oz came to mind more than once during the past year: "Toto, I've a feeling we're not in Kansas anymore." Our initial forecast of 22,000 new-car deliveries and our formal forecast in December 2010 of 26,300 cars for 2011 compared poorly with the 44,000 cars that are now expected to be delivered this year. If only the overall U.S. economy had recovered in a similar fashion! As for 2012, the situation is still very fluid, but there should not be any retreat from the current levels of production. Deliveries may even be higher — 51,500 cars, say — if crude oil shipments continue to drive up tank-car orders. Orders for small-cube covered hoppers seem to know no limit this year, and almost 18,000 cars were ordered between June 2010 and June of this year. Even more orders were expected in the second half of 2011, and deliveries eventually could increase the overall size of the 65,000-car, small-cube covered hopper fleet by 50 percent. We didn't anticipate that hydrofracking wells for natural gas could lead to so many new rail-car orders. When they enter service, these cars eventually could lead to more than 300,000 new loads annually for railroads.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1352602184532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 21:49:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352608247058-39</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Corporate to hold up Philadelphia as a ................</Title><Username>caveman2501</Username><Timestamp>1352561500472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 10:31:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would be great if true!!!!!!</Msg><Username>av_week_reader</Username><Timestamp>1352608247058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 23:30:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>