<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-21"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356066367021-1</Id><Topic><Title>Adolf Hitler: TIME Magazine Man of the Year, 1938</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356045403007</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:16:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK Pea peepee.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356066367021</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:06:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356066865800-2</Id><Topic><Title>22 Schoolchildren Stabbed in China on Same Day As Sandy Hook</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356035776579</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:36:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes it does. It took the Chinese assailant long enough that adults were able to arrive on the scene (armed with push brooms to subdue him, I might add. How's that for lethality?) And oh yeah -- of the 22 children attacked, no one was killed.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356066865800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:14:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356066975659-3</Id><Topic><Title>Adolf Hitler: TIME Magazine Man of the Year, 1938</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356045403007</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:16:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What problem might that be, Chrissy ? Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1356066975659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:16:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356067202861-4</Id><Topic><Title>Adolf Hitler: TIME Magazine Man of the Year, 1938</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356045403007</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:16:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"right" and "wrong" are only subjective, and relative to Liberals, who are confused and mistaken about a great many things, dipstick . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1356067202861</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:20:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356068246240-5</Id><Topic><Title>Antarctic ice growing, not shrinking</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356041772104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 17:16:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Skeptic arguments that Antarctica is gaining ice frequently hinge on an error of omission, namely ignoring the difference between land ice and sea ice. In glaciology and particularly with respect to Antarctic ice, not all things are created equal. Let us consider the following differences. Antarctic land ice is the ice which has accumulated over thousands of years on the Antarctica landmass itself through snowfall. This land ice therefore is actually stored ocean water that once fell as precipitation. Sea ice in Antarctica is quite different as it is generally considered to be ice which forms in salt water primarily during the winter months. In Antarctica, sea ice grows quite extensively during winter but nearly completely melts away during the summer (Figure 1). That is where the important difference between antarctic and arctic sea ice exists. Arctic sea ice lasts all the year round, there are increases during the winter months and decreases during the summer months but an ice cover does in fact remain in the North which includes quite a bit of ice from previous years (Figure 1). Essentially Arctic sea ice is more important for the earth's energy balance because when it melts, more sunlight is absorbed by the oceans whereas Antarctic sea ice normally melts each summer leaving the earth's energy balance largely unchanged. One must also be careful how you interpret trends in Antarctic sea ice. Currently this ice is increasing and has been for years but is this the smoking gun against climate change? Not quite. Antarctic sea ice is gaining because of many different reasons but the most accepted recent explanations are listed below: i) Ozone levels over Antarctica have dropped causing stratospheric cooling and increasing winds which lead to more areas of open water that can be frozen (Gillet 2003, Thompson 2002, Turner 2009). and ii) The Southern Ocean is freshening because of increased rain, glacial run-off and snowfall. This changes the composition of the different layers in the ocean there causing less mixing between warm and cold layers and thus less melted sea ice (Zhang 2007). All the sea ice talk aside, it is quite clear that really when it comes to Antarctic ice, sea ice is not the most important thing to measure. In Antarctica, the most important ice mass is the land ice sitting on the West Antarctic Ice Sheet and the East Antarctic Ice Sheet. Therefore, how is Antarctic Land-ice doing? Estimates of recent changes in Antarctic land ice (Figure 2) range from losing 100 Gt/year to over 300 Gt/year. Because 360 Gt/year represents an annual sea level rise of 1 mm/year, recent estimates indicate a contribution of between 0.27 mm/year and 0.83 mm/year coming from Antarctica. There is of course uncertainty in the estimations methods but multiple different types of measurement techniques (explained here) all show the same thing, Antarctica is losing land ice as a whole, and these losses are accelerating quickly.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1356068246240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:37:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356068771093-6</Id><Title>Repubs sound so desperate !</Title><Msg>Poor things ... dazed confused and gasping !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356068771093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:46:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356068972583-7</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs sound so desperate !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356068771093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Love it !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356068972583</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:49:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356070394869-8</Id><Topic><Title>Antarctic ice growing, not shrinking</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356041772104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 17:16:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... and yet the ocean is not rising, proving the author (whom you copied from) to be full of Liberal . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1356070394869</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 01:13:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356071409028-9</Id><Topic><Title>22 Schoolchildren Stabbed in China on Same Day As Sandy Hook</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356035776579</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 15:36:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They were very lucky, others have not been; From "The Epoch Times", and Radio Free Asia : "There has been a spate of attacks that have targeted Chinese children in recent years. In 2010, a knife-wielding man killed nine people, including seven small children. Later, a man killed three kindergartners with a knife. Many analysts have speculated that growing social problem, anger towards the ruling Communist Party, and the widening gap between the wealthy and poor have increased tensions for ordinary Chinese. “Those who have genuine psychiatric problems [in China] aren’t getting treatment, while some political dissidents are locked up in mental hospitals by the police and the government,” former Shandong University professor Sun Wenguang told RFA ." Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1356071409028</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 01:30:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356071969549-10</Id><Topic><Title>Antarctic ice growing, not shrinking</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356041772104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 17:16:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Therefore, how is Antarctic Land-ice doing?" SCAR ISMASS Workshop, July 14, 2012 Mass Gains of the Antarctic Ice Sheet Exceed Losses H. Jay Zwally'. Jun Li', John Robbins2, Jack 1. Saba2, Donghui Yi', Anita Brenner', and David Bromwich4 Abstract During 2003 to 2008, the mass gain of the Antarctic ice sheet from snow accumulation exceeded the mass loss from ice discharge by 49 Gtlyr (2.5% of input), as derived from ICESat laser measurements of elevation change. The net gain (86 Gtlyr) over the West Antarctic (WA) and East Antarctic ice sheets (W A and EA) is essentially unchanged from revised results for 1992 to 2001 from ERS radar altimetry. Imbalances in individual drainage systems (DS) are large (-68% to +103% of input), as are temporal changes (-39% to +44%). The recent 90 Gtlyr loss from three DS (Pine Island, Thwaites-Smith, and Marie-Bryd Coast) of WA exceeds the earlier 61 Gtlyr loss, consistent with reports of accelerating ice flow and dynamic thinning. Similarly, the recent 24 Gtlyr loss from three DS in the Antarctic Peninsula (AP) is consistent with glacier accelerations following breakup of the Larsen B and other ice shelves. In contrast, net increases in the five other DS ofWA and AP and three of the 16 DS in East Antarctica (EA) exceed the increased losses. Alternate interpretations of the mass changes driven by accumulation variations are given using results from atmospheric-model re-analysis and a parameterization based on 5% change in accumulation per degree of observed surface temperature change. A slow increase in snowfall with climate wanning, consistent with model predictions, may be offsetting increased dynamic losses.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1356071969549</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 01:39:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356091119116-11</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or to put it another way ....Why are we being asked to disarm when we have an executive branch ARMING our enemies ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356091119116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 06:58:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356092200061-12</Id><Title>BA is certainly not looking fine. Understand why.</Title><Msg>Has someone looked over the articles being published? Awesome stuff that will assist any investor or trader. microcapwatcher . info/-BA</Msg><Username>whittendean435</Username><Timestamp>1356092200061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 07:16:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356094940857-13</Id><Topic><Title>Will We Forget Newtown’s Kids?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356047049387</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 18:44:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"counting on our notoriously short national attention span." Is that the same attention span that forgets an Executive Branch that gave guns to Mexican Drug Lords during Fast and Furious...? And if we have a President giving aid and comfort to our enemies...such as giving guns to AlQaeda (google it) ...WHY are we being asked to disarm ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356094940857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:02:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356095818649-14</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Article III, Section 3 of the Constitution is clear. Obama and his Administration are guilty of Treason! Aiding and abetting the Republic’s enemies is treason. Taking up arms against the Republic by a citizen is treason too. Also, in my opinion, any oath taker, law maker, or party leader, who promotes the abrogation of our Rights under the Constitution is committing treason. For example, passing laws that violate our Constitution is equal to taking up arms against the Republic. I call this law warfare. That being said, Obama can not complete his mission to destroy the strength of this Republic as long as the People bear arms. This is why Obama wants to abrogate our 2nd Amendment. I personally am not in favor of armed rebellion. However, we can appeal to our Armed Forces to follow their oath to defend the Constitution against enemies both foreign and domestic. I would start with the most loyal of the Armed Forces: The United States Marines.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356095818649</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:16:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356095883486-15</Id><Title>Will We Forget the Millions Of Innocent Babies Democrats Murder?</Title><Msg>No doubt the party of no morals and no conscience will.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356095883486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:18:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356097317234-16</Id><Topic><Title>Will We Forget the Millions Of Innocent Babies Democrats Murder?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356095883486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:18:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats have glorified the right to the barbaric slaughter of millions of innocent babies where their skulls are crushed and their brains are sucked out. They are the same party that said slaves weren't fully human and should only count as 3/5 of a person. The same party that fought a war to keep slavery legal. The same Party that started the KKK and elected a KKK Grand Wizard to the Senate. The same party that opposed civil rights in the 50s and 60s.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1356097317234</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:41:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356097747255-17</Id><Topic><Title>Antarctic ice growing, not shrinking</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356041772104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 17:16:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You just have to shake your head and laugh at the ignorance of people who have drank the Global Warming kool-aid. To find out ignorant they are fill a bowl to the brim with ice and water. When the ice melts check and see how much the water level has risen. Melting sea Ice ain't gonna make the seas rise.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1356097747255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:49:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356097848490-18</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Will Cliff Plunge Cost You</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356028579415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:36:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>makboeing, how about we cut multi million dollar handouts to wealthy farmers? Or, rebates to GE and Boeing?</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356097848490</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:50:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356098098716-19</Id><Title>Boehner Goes Down in FLAMES</Title><Msg>Leader Boehner could not get his republibagger caucus to vote for his "Plan B". They were bleeding heart concerned about his tax on their millionaire benefactor/employers.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356098098716</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:54:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356098214639-20</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs sound so desperate !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356068771093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are doooooooooomed!</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356098214639</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:56:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356098453275-21</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs sound so desperate !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356068771093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No wonder! How would you feel if the election has been affected by fraud. Dead people counted along with illegl alien votes, etc. Republicans have too many morals. That is their problem. As Rush says, you can't beat Santa Claus.</Msg><Username>fpmanchack</Username><Timestamp>1356098453275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 09:00:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356098593331-22</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs sound so desperate !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356068771093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you helping to bring Communists to take over our country. Don't you read. Try reading about Saul Alinsky!!!</Msg><Username>fpmanchack</Username><Timestamp>1356098593331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 09:03:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356098615168-23</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs sound so desperate !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356068771093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The nomination of the most breathtakingly shape-shifting and dishonest Presidential candidate in history was Act I of their self-destruction. Boehner's driving us over the fiscal cliff will be Act II.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356098615168</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 09:03:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356098699216-24</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs sound so desperate !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356068771093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you helping to bring Communism into our country? Huh, Are you???</Msg><Username>fpmanchack</Username><Timestamp>1356098699216</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 09:04:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356098794435-25</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs sound so desperate !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356068771093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too many dead, illegal people votes. No morals whatsoever.</Msg><Username>fpmanchack</Username><Timestamp>1356098794435</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 09:06:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356099142459-26</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs sound so desperate !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356068771093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love the sound of baggers whining in the morning...... It sounds like victory for the american people</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356099142459</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 09:12:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356099460705-27</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner Goes Down in FLAMES</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356098098716</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:54:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Christmas will be awful at Boehner's house. Can we all imagine the crying, the squalling, the whimpering. Gonna sound like the Romney household election night.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356099460705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 09:17:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356099866612-28</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner Goes Down in FLAMES</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356098098716</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:54:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harry &amp; obama both said they would vote it down so who cares?</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1356099866612</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 09:24:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356100191371-29</Id><Title>Rich republican women have always had abortion available</Title><Msg>I remember prior to Roe Wade when these women had to travel all the way to Sweden for their aborts but the poor women only had back alley abortionists. The anti abortionist crowd who are endowed by Gawd almighty to keep us from abortion would rather murder the poor women in the back alley than admit that women have always used abortion to avoid unwanted pregnancy for at least the past 5000 years. Must be a heady feeling to be a warrior for Gawd eh</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1356100191371</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 09:29:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356100744489-30</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner Goes Down in FLAMES</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356098098716</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:54:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fascist, it's just that I luv the smell of burning baggers in the morning!!!!</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356100744489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 09:39:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356101194759-31</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Will Cliff Plunge Cost You</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356028579415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:36:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The intransigence of the republibaggers may be an opportunity to finally crush the crazies politically. If Boehner decides to ally with Democrats and pass something reasonable -- that will leave the nut-cases with the snakey-flags standing on the street corner, along with the last surviving nonagenarians of the John Birch Society. BUH BYE</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356101194759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 09:46:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356101732299-32</Id><Topic><Title>BA is certainly not looking fine. Understand why.</Title><Username>whittendean435</Username><Timestamp>1356092200061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 07:16:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>im in</Msg><Username>hirsch.roderick</Username><Timestamp>1356101732299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 09:55:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356102848431-33</Id><Title>America Must Stop Codling the Mediocre Class</Title><Msg>President Oblamer always talks about saving the mediocre class. He wants to be a champion of mediocrity. He hopes against hope to some day be a president who rises to a high level of mediocrity. He obviously likes mediocrity because they are so malleable and easily manipulated. By punishing high achievement while rewarding and protecting mediocrity he has fundamentally transformed America into just another mediocre country. Historically, it was our nation's highest achievers that were also our greatest philanthropists giving trillions to help people escape mediocrity. High achievers like Peabody, Morgan, Carnegie, Rosenwalds, Rockefeller, Hilton, Franklin, Emerson, Ford, Colgate, Du Pont, Heinz, and Scaife made this country great through their hard work and devotion to excellence. The mediocre class lives on jealousy, envy and hatred of high achievers. That's why they are so easily manipulated. High achievers like myself, those noted above and a thousand others think it's an absurdity to think stealing from others and generations yet unborn is going to produce anything good for our posterity. It has always destroyed nations and it will destroy America as we knew it.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356102848431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:14:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356103280179-34</Id><Title>We need a Plan R or Recession Plan</Title><Msg>ASAP come January 1,2013.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1356103280179</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:21:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356103374354-35</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You better measure your words......what you have asked might get you a lot of attention and seems like some of it is deserved</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1356103374354</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:22:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356103635796-36</Id><Topic><Title>Will We Forget the Millions Of Innocent Babies Democrats Murder?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356095883486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:18:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hoozdik_hertz_333 is obviously a low intelligent victim of socialized government education and feeds from the trough of perpetual campaign rhetoric. The median age in the U.S. is 36.8 years. Since age 40 constitutes a majority by the dik's logic if everyone below 40 could and did vote to terminate the lives of everyone over 40 it would be justifiable. The success of mob rule to achieve what is immoral is not the same as justice. "Life, faculties, production—in other words, individuality, liberty, property—this is man. And in spite of the cunning of artful political leaders, these three gifts from God precede all human legislation, and are superior to it. Life, liberty, and property do not exist because men have made laws. On the contrary, it was the fact that life, liberty, and property existed beforehand that caused men to make laws in the first place."</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356103635796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:27:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356104068401-37</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of that has been created by Obama, and the left controlling the PR battle bigtime, AND the LOW INFORMATION level folks in socieity today. That plays up to the libs. Obama's campaign went totally after these low information level folks. He didn't even go after the informed public!..and won re-election. Congress is influenced by public opinion, and the GOP has to change its strategy on how to win elections. Quit basing elections of facts, and numbers while the leftists lie and strike fear. Remember OJ Simpsons murder case? They gave DNA evidence ad nausium, and put the ignorant jury to sleep. FEAR works, and there is plenty of fear to strike given the socialist direction were are headed.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356104068401</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:34:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356104265985-38</Id><Topic><Title>We need a Plan R or Recession Plan</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1356103280179</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:21:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again! Back to my striking fear in the public opinion arena. Obama's socialist agenda, and why he doesn't want to cut any spending that is the sole problem!....has to be exposed, and attacked! NO tax raises will ever put a dent in Obama's big spending, socialist agenda. Revenue is just fuel to fire up more socialist spending!</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356104265985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:37:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356104391186-39</Id><Title>I finally figured it out</Title><Msg>'T party' Repubes are Mayan Apocalysp Zombies. This is the only reasonable answer to why they have been so determined to destroy America and wont even support their own Republican leader, House Speaker Boener...</Msg><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1356104391186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:39:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356104741332-40</Id><Topic><Title>I finally figured it out</Title><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1356104391186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:39:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So your ignorant conclusion after days of figuring it out, conclude we desperately need much more govt spending, and desperately need more tax hikes? You are dumber than any Mayan ever thought of being.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356104741332</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:45:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356104885624-41</Id><Topic><Title>We need a Plan R or Recession Plan</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1356103280179</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:21:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My household has been living on a budget knowing the consequence of not adhering to it. Why can't our government do the same? Get rid of the credit card and the printing press!</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1356104885624</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:48:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356105015876-42</Id><Topic><Title>Rich republican women have always had abortion available</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1356100191371</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 09:29:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what's the problem. Rich Republican women have always be able to own big houses, drive Mercedes and wear expensive clothes too. Do you have a clue what being "rich" means?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356105015876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:50:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356106365909-43</Id><Topic><Title>I finally figured it out</Title><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1356104391186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:39:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As bushJr said' i dont care about deficits right now'. Yes he/we have spent trillions on wars /tax breaks and corporate welfare over the last decade and Most Americans realize that we have to pay these debts...That is except for the 'T' partiers, that walk around brain Dead now and during the debt ceiling fiasco in aug/2010. ...My zombie thesis is confirmed...You must be one of the newly hatched, to have the conclusions you come to in spite of any reasonable evaluation of the Facts easily identified as the issues which has driven America into the ditch leading to this fiscal cliff...GLTY sir...</Msg><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1356106365909</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:12:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356106478089-44</Id><Topic><Title>Constitutional Corruption</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356063746209</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 23:22:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point Sparty....1913 was a very bad year for the U.S. and the cause of liberty. In previous years the supreme court had ruled the income tax unconstitutional. The Democrats kept pushing for it. The Republicans finally and foolishly agreed to the proposal but only if there was a constitutional amendment to authorize it - thinking the necessary states would never approve it. They underestimated the deviousness of the Democrat propaganda machine. Of course the Democrats lied about the amendment just like they do about most laws they want impose on the electorate. They convinced the population that most people would never have to pay the income tax and only the rich would be taxed - sounds familiar huh? Never underestimate the power of jealousy and envy to cause people to be led over a cliff by the Pied Pipers promising to spend other people's money on them.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356106478089</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:14:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356106549501-45</Id><Topic><Title>We need a Plan R or Recession Plan</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1356103280179</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:21:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because your budget involves decisions made by YOU the consumer deciding on where you want to spend your money. If you want to make a contibution YOU want it to go directly to those in need as well. Obama says "you are too stupid to make good decisions with your money, WE, the big govt socialists want your money, and will spend it as we see fit." And the way they see fit is crony capitalism. Govt officials get more wealthy, and those at the bottom never see much of any of it.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356106549501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:15:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356106744708-46</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Relax. No more coffee. Unload your AR-15 and sit quietly by the front door. Someone will come for you soon.</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1356106744708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:19:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356106947670-47</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that the SAME Al-Qadea Americans are supposed to give up heir Rights and Civil Liberties for /</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1356106947670</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:22:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356107388429-48</Id><Topic><Title>A Message to the NRA's Wayne LaPierre</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356106766814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It has always been amazing to me how many NRA members are a bunch of macho wannabees. They cant join Real American organizations like the VFW, IAVA or DAV because of their youthful cowardices. 'wayne' and charlton' are prime examples.</Msg><Username>manferfish</Username><Timestamp>1356107388429</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:29:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356107515931-49</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs sound so desperate !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356068771093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356107515931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:31:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356107618012-50</Id><Title>Secession is far Preferable to Overthrow of an Abusive Government</Title><Msg>A couple of weeks ago, I reviewed Loyola University (MD) professor of economics, Thomas DiLorenzo's The Real Lincoln, a book that presented abundant evidence that most of the Founders took the right of state secession for granted. Despite that evidence, some readers concluded differently. Let's consider an alternative to secession in response to federal government encroachment on our liberties. Suppose Congress enacted the Federal Clean Thoughts Act (FCTA) and President Obama signed it. Under its provisions, before books and newspaper reports could be published, and before television and radio programs could be broadcasted, prior approval of their "fitness" would have to be obtained from the Federal Clean Thoughts Commission. Several parties bring a lawsuit before the U.S. Supreme Court charging FCTA is a violation of the First Amendment; however, the U.S. Court finds that under the Constitution's "general welfare clause" the law is constitutional. What do Americans do? Do we accept the tyranny, pick up the sword or do we think about state secession again? I would hope that the response of my fellow Americans wouldn't be: "Williams, the law is the law. The Court has said FCTA is constitutional and our job is to obey." What's clear in this scenario is that the legislative, executive and judicial branches of government are joined with one another to undermine our constitution and destroy our liberties. Do we allow the federal government to determine the scope of its own powers? Should we accept whatever Congress, the White House and the Courts say is constitutional? Not according to Alexander Hamilton, who in Federalist Paper 28 said, "The State governments will, in all possible contingencies, afford complete security against invasions of the public liberty by the national authority." One response to federal encroachment is for state governments to declare federal laws that have no constitutional authority null and void and refuse to enforce them. While the U.S. Constitution provides no specific provision for nullification, the case for nullification is found in the nature of compacts and agreements. Our constitution represents a compact between the states and the federal government. As with any compact, one party does not have a monopoly over its interpretation nor can one party change it without the consent of the other. Additionally, no one has a moral obligation to obey unconstitutional laws. That's not to say there isn't a compelling case for obedience to unconstitutional laws: the brutal force of the federal government to coerce obedience. While Congress hasn't yet enacted such a flagrant violation of the First Amendment, most of what Congress does, with U.S. Supreme Court and White House sanction, represents constitutional encroachments of varying degrees. You say, "Williams, explain that." Article I, Section 8 of our Constitution enumerates (lists) those powers delegated to Congress. The Tenth Amendment says, "The powers not delegated to the United States by the Constitution, nor prohibited by it to the States, are reserved to the States respectively, or to the people." That clearly says that powers not delegated to Congress by Article I, Section 8 belong to the people and the states. In violation of both the letter and spirit the federal government imposes unconstitutional and costly mandates covering the gambit from education and land usage to how much water can be used to flush toilets. I wonder when a governor and his state legislature will summon the courage to declare some of these federal laws null and void and refuse to enforce them. Of course, Washington might respond by not sending back money the citizens pay in federal taxes. Then the potential of ugliness arises because the state can establish a mechanism to withhold the money its citizens send to Washington. Walter E. Williams</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356107618012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:33:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356108413857-51</Id><Title>Do States Have the Right to Secede?</Title><Msg>Since there was only a remote possibility that we could successfully negotiate with Congress, the Courts and White House to obey the U.S. Constitution, I speculated that liberty could only realized by a unilateral declaration of independence - namely, part company. Quite a few readers criticized the idea, calling secession unconstitutional. Let's look at it. On March 2, 1861, after seven states had seceded and two days before Abraham Lincoln's inauguration, Senator James R. Doolittle (WI) proposed a constitutional amendment that said, "No State or any part thereof, heretofore admitted or hereafter admitted into the Union, shall have the power to withdraw from the jurisdiction of the United States." Several months earlier Representatives Daniel E. Sickles (NY), Thomas B. Florence (PA) and Otis S. Ferry (CT) proposed a constitutional amendment to prohibit secession. Here's my no-brainer question: would there have been any point to offering these amendments if secession were already unconstitutional? I'm guessing, no. But there's more evidence. The ratification documents of Virginia, New York and Rhode Island explicitly said that they held the right to resume powers delegated should the federal government become abusive of those powers. There's more evidence. At the 1787 constitutional convention a proposal was made to allow the federal government to suppress a seceding state. James Madison, the father of our constitution, rejected it saying, "A Union of the States containing such an ingredient seemed to provide for its own destruction. The use of force against a State would look more like a declaration of war, than an infliction of punishment and would probably be considered by the party attacked as a dissolution of all previous compacts by which it might be bound." Professor Thomas DiLorenzo, in his revised The Real Lincoln, provides abundant evidence in the forms of quotations from our Founders and numerous newspaper accounts that prove that Americans always took the right of secession for granted. Plus, secession was not an idea that had its origins in the South. Infuriated by Thomas Jefferson's Louisiana Purchase, in 1803, the first secessionist movement started in New York, Massachusetts, Connecticut and other New England states. Every single bit of evidence shows that states have a right to secede. There's absolutely nothing in the Constitution that prohibits secession. What stops secession is the brute force of a mighty federal government, as witnessed by the costly War of 1861. Only one thing good came out of that war. It eliminated slavery. It's had a devastating legacy for future generations of Americans in that since the issue of secession was brutally settled, the federal government is free to run roughshod over the safeguards envisioned by the Framers, namely the Ninth and Tenth Amendments. There's little to suggest that the same brutality wouldn't be encountered if secession were tried again, as one writer cautioned: if New Hampshire seceded, massive troops along with today's deadly modern military equipment would be on its soil before lunch. Walter E. Williams</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356108413857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:46:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356108759553-52</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Will Cliff Plunge Cost You</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1356028579415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 13:36:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vas Mir If I were a rich man, Ya ha deedle deedle, bubba bubba deedle deedle dum. All day long I'd biddy biddy bum. If I were a wealthy man. I wouldn't have to work hard. Ya ha deedle deedle, bubba bubba deedle deedle dum. If I were a biddy biddy rich, Yidle-diddle-didle-didle man. Dedicated to all baggers!</Msg><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1356108759553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:52:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356108802015-53</Id><Title>Fiscal destruction AGAIN from Hypocrit Repube Tpots</Title><Msg>Americans and Worldwide Investors are losing $Millions/$Billions because of a few selfrightous 'T' partiers representing their 1% benefactors against the rest of America. Mr Obama offered 1.5 trillion in spending cuts including everything from 'meals on wheels' for seniors to medicare/medicade/social security cuts and didn't even touch Defense spending, but that wasn't good enough...Yet these 'T'partiers cant even make their own plan or offer. They just kill any attempts at salvaging efforts to pay debts They championed and supported when it was their turn to govern. Now we are all heading over the Cliff AGAIN, which will cause huge financial damage...AGAIN...Brilliant</Msg><Username>manferfish</Username><Timestamp>1356108802015</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:53:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356108911181-54</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have we traveled so far down the road to tyranny a person can't even ask a question about statements in our declaration of independence without fear of being visited by government thugs?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356108911181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:55:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356109178718-55</Id><Title>Boehner: What? Me Worry?</Title><Msg>After getting shellacked by his own caucus John Boehner contended Friday that he was not worried about his future as speaker of the House The final stage of terminal illness..........acceptance..</Msg><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1356109178718</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:59:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356109342916-56</Id><Topic><Title>Rich republican women have always had abortion available</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1356100191371</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 09:29:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ziiiiiing.........point flying over the Dik's head. It's murder no matter who does it. If only rich people can afford to hire hit men to eliminate people they don't like should the government provide funds to the poor so they can hire hit men?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356109342916</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:02:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356109433448-57</Id><Topic><Title>Do States Have the Right to Secede?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356108413857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:46:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where does the Federal government get its money?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356109433448</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:03:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356109758198-58</Id><Topic><Title>Rich republican women have always had abortion available</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1356100191371</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 09:29:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vas mir: "Dear God, you made many, many poor people. I realize, of course, that it's no shame to be poor. But it's no great honor either! So, what would have been so terrible if I had a small fortune?" If I were a rich man, Ya ha deedle deedle, bubba bubba deedle deedle dum. All day long I'd biddy biddy bum. If I were a wealthy man. I wouldn't have to work hard. Ya ha deedle deedle, bubba bubba deedle deedle dum. If I were a biddy biddy rich, Yidle-diddle-didle-didle man. I'd build a big tall house with rooms by the dozen, Right in the middle of the town. A fine tin roof with real wooden floors below. There would be one long staircase just going up, And one even longer coming down, And one more leading nowhere, just for show. I'd fill my yard with chicks and turkeys and geese and ducks For the town to see and hear. And each loud "cheep" and "swaqwk" and "honk" and "quack" Would land like a trumpet on the ear, As if to say "Here lives a wealthy man." If I were a rich man, Ya ha deedle deedle, bubba bubba deedle deedle dum. All day long I'd biddy biddy bum. If I were a wealthy man. I wouldn't have to work hard. Ya ha deedle deedle, bubba bubba deedle deedle dum. If I were a biddy biddy rich, Yidle-diddle-didle-didle man. I see my wife, my Golde, looking like a rich man's wife With a proper double-chin. Supervising meals to her heart's delight. I see her putting on airs and strutting like a peacock. Oy, what a happy mood she's in. Screaming at the servants, day and night. The most important men in town would come to fawn on me! They would ask me to advise them, Like a Solomon the Wise. "If you please, Reb Tevye..." "Pardon me, Reb Tevye..." Posing problems that would cross a rabbi's eyes! And it won't make one bit of difference if i answer right or wrong. When you're rich, they think you really know! If I were rich, I'd have the time that I lack To sit in the synagogue and pray. And maybe have a seat by the Eastern wall. And I'd discuss the holy books with the learned men, several hours every day. That would be the sweetest thing of all. If I were a rich man, Ya ha deedle deedle, bubba bubba deedle deedle dum. All day long I'd biddy biddy bum. If I were a wealthy man. I wouldn't have to work hard. Ya ha deedle deedle, bubba bubba deedle deedle dum. If I were a biddy biddy rich, Yidle-diddle-didle-didle ma</Msg><Username>majac_op</Username><Timestamp>1356109758198</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:09:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356110299862-59</Id><Topic><Title>Will We Forget the Millions Of Innocent Babies Democrats Murder?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356095883486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:18:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals want your guns but they're ok with abortion! Give me a break!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1356110299862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:18:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356110307179-60</Id><Title>delivery number jumps</Title><Msg>Six 787's were delivered on the 20th. Customers were ANA, Air India, JAL, LOT, Qatar and United. Total plane deliveries so far are 48 for December. 30 737's. 2 747's. 2 767's. 6 777's. 8 787's.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1356110307179</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:18:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356110691404-61</Id><Title>deliveries increase</Title><Msg>Six 787's were delivered on the 20th. Customers were ANA, Air India, JAL, LOT, Qatar and United. Total plane deliveries so far are 48 for December. 30 737's. 2 747's. 2 767's. 6 777's. 8 787's.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1356110691404</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:24:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356111538804-62</Id><Topic><Title>Do States Have the Right to Secede?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356108413857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:46:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In NJ we pay in more then we get back,unlike some states that get double of what they pay in.If obama stiffs nj on the sandy 60 bil thats needed to rebuild we should secede.They could'nt fork it over fast enough to New Orleans....</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1356111538804</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:38:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356111576730-63</Id><Title>Ob ama Gives Guns to Terrorists and Drug Cartels and wants to........</Title><Msg>....confiscate the guns of law abiding Americans. Tyranny on the march.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356111576730</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:39:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356111613123-64</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And an assault rifle would hel[ you fix that how?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356111613123</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:40:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356112283162-65</Id><Title>The natural progress of things is for liberty to yield and government to gain ground.</Title><Msg>Thomas Jefferson. Makes you wonder why Democrats want government to grow so much. Must be a hatred for liberty.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356112283162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:51:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356112303156-66</Id><Topic><Title>We need a Plan R or Recession Plan</Title><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1356103280179</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:21:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, sure. But when the 1981-model car you need to drive to work every morning suddenly throws pistons through the hood and you don't have $24,000 in the bank, CREDIT can be a real Godsend, can't it? For a government, an equivalent situation might be when people who are different than you kill a lot of Americans and you need to go to war to look like a "decider" but you don't have a couple billion bucks to spare, then the ol' credit card is a real help, too.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356112303156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:51:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356112375645-67</Id><Topic><Title>Will We Forget the Millions Of Innocent Babies Democrats Murder?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356095883486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:18:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>= ________________ is obviously a low intelligent victim of socialized government education ..." Care to tell me again how you convert temperatures back and forth between F° and C° ? I found that quite entertaining. I suspect you learned more about entertaining than math wherever you went to school. And then tell us all again how trickle-down econ works. Thanks.</Msg><Username>wonderdoc</Username><Timestamp>1356112375645</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:52:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356112593534-68</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs sound so desperate !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356068771093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To arms! The commies are coming! The commies are coming!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356112593534</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:56:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356112825300-69</Id><Topic><Title>Will We Forget the Millions Of Innocent Babies Democrats Murder?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356095883486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 08:18:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores! Trickle down econ will start to work when hell hits 0 degrees Celsius.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356112825300</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 13:00:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356112909147-70</Id><Topic><Title>The natural progress of things is for liberty to yield and government to gain ground.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356112283162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:51:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He said that just after he'd boffed one of his black slaves. Now, there was liberty for you!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356112909147</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 13:01:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356112997094-71</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>phantomfield would have made a good little Nazi because after all Hitler and the National Socialist party of Germany (Nationalsozialistische Deutsche Arbeiterpartei) was democratically elected. Although they only murdered 6 million Jews the American Democrats have killed over 40 million innocent babies.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356112997094</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 13:03:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356113140162-72</Id><Topic><Title>The natural progress of things is for liberty to yield and government to gain ground.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356112283162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:51:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps but according to Democrats that slave was only 3/5 human.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356113140162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 13:05:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356113352270-73</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a pretty sick puppy, do you know that?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1356113352270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 13:09:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356114219629-74</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs sound so desperate !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356068771093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The republican rubes have been abandoned by every one of their heros. Palin, Rawmoneyn nugent the draft dodger, batsh1t, arpaio, trump, and even rush turned out to be a felonious drug addict.</Msg><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1356114219629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 13:23:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356114229521-75</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs sound so desperate !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1356068771093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 00:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans have morals? LOL</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1356114229521</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 13:23:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356114399625-76</Id><Topic><Title>Secession is far Preferable to Overthrow of an Abusive Government</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356107618012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:33:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YAAAAWWWWNNNNNNN You never tire of that maudlin garbage, do you?</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1356114399625</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 13:26:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356114546484-77</Id><Topic><Title>Secession is far Preferable to Overthrow of an Abusive Government</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356107618012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:33:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think that ANYONE would stop the red states from seceding this time. Just go.</Msg><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1356114546484</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 13:29:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356114690757-78</Id><Topic><Title>Do States Have the Right to Secede?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356108413857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:46:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mir tries to recover from his recent "convert C to F" treatise by referring to an 1861 constitutional amendment proposal. Ya can't make this stuff up.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1356114690757</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 13:31:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356115825227-79</Id><Topic><Title>Do States Have the Right to Secede?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356108413857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:46:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama hopes a state tries, and then he can expand the powers of his big, centralized, socialist govt even more. And to the guy who said states will accept fed funds, and not secede?...states tried to lower the failed stimulus bill they knew would fail by turning down the federal money Obama wanted to jam down their throats. When some said they didn't want it Obama threatened federal action against those states. And now, a number of RED STATES are taking the debt problem into their own hands, and have balanced their books very nicely on their own....and why folks in huge debt BLUE states are fleeing to those RED STATES to lower their tax burden, and get out from having to pay for the huge debt in their BLUE state. Businesses as well in order to be profitable, and be able to hire more workers.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356115825227</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 13:50:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356117008591-80</Id><Topic><Title>Secession is far Preferable to Overthrow of an Abusive Government</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356107618012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:33:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BLUE state folks who PERSONALLY will be forced to pay back their massive debt created by their liberal legislatures are hoping that tax payers in other states will bail them out. Let's hope not. And the next effort by libs is expected to be an "escape tax". A heavy tax on those planning on moving to a more responsible governed RED STATE, and try to affoid their tax burden. The population of Michigan is now half it once was due to the mass exodus of folks wanting work, and getting out from under the massive tax burden being imposed on them. Talk about a downward spiral created by lbieralism.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356117008591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:10:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356117754578-81</Id><Title>48 planes delivered so far.in DEcember</Title><Msg>30 737's. 2 747's 2 767's 6 777's 8 787's. 6 787's were delivered on 12/20. 1 each on 12/7 and 12/14.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1356117754578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:22:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356118147102-82</Id><Title>Why Are Liberals so Fearful of Liberty and Independence?</Title><Msg>Is it because they just can't grow a pair? Or is it because they feel security in hiding their weakness behind the brute force of forced collectivism and mob rule?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356118147102</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:29:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356119050620-83</Id><Topic><Title>Secession is far Preferable to Overthrow of an Abusive Government</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356107618012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:33:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not surprisingly, most of the states that receive more money from the federal government than what they pay into the system are "red" states. Pot, meet Mr. Kettle.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1356119050620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:44:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356119244229-84</Id><Topic><Title>48 planes delivered so far.in DEcember</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1356117754578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:22:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does that mean more recalls and groundings?. Don't get sucked in. if you have profits take them. . I'm sold today GL to ya . I can sleep with a smile on my face.</Msg><Username>tosellornot</Username><Timestamp>1356119244229</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:47:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356119297860-85</Id><Title>Why Are Blue Stes Lossing Population?</Title><Msg>Why are people leaving them in droves for red states.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356119297860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:48:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356119409524-86</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your comment is insane. Believing in American values like free democratically held elections and fundamental human rights as found in the Constitution of the United States and the Bill of rights thereto is the opposite of being a Nazi.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1356119409524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:50:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356119499624-87</Id><Topic><Title>A Message to the NRA's Wayne LaPierre</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356106766814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Four people shot on a highway in Pennsylvania today. I guess we need an armed policeman in every school AND on every highway now.</Msg><Username>bfamidon</Username><Timestamp>1356119499624</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:51:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356119889067-88</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good question rover. Our Declaration of Independence says the time to overthrow our government is "when a long train of abuses and usurpations, pursuing invariably the same Object evinces a design to reduce them under absolute Despotism." For you victims of socialized government education, Despotism is a form of government in which a single entity rules with absolute power. That entity may be an individual, as in an autocracy, or it may be a group such as a political party or an oligarchy. The word despotism means to "rule in the fashion of a despot" and does not necessarily require a singular "despot", an individual.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356119889067</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:58:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356120049942-89</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are Blue Stes Lossing Population?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356119297860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:48:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typos - Why Are Blue States Losing Population? Just in case their are any victims of socialized government education that couldn't tell.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356120049942</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 15:00:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356120407191-90</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are Liberals so Fearful of Liberty and Independence?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356118147102</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:29:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They can't control you who are too stupid to govern yourselves. Control.</Msg><Username>sparrowgt</Username><Timestamp>1356120407191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 15:06:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356120558480-91</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are Liberals so Fearful of Liberty and Independence?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356118147102</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:29:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahhhh.....thanks.....so it's because liberals are too stupid to live in freedom and they hate people who aren't.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356120558480</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 15:09:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356120593732-92</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are Blue Stes Lossing Population?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356119297860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:48:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I answered that one. Who wants to see their standard of living reduced to abject poverty? Who wants to be burdened with paying back the massive govt debt created by liberals who will never pay it down, just spend the money they get via tax receipts to create bigger and bigger debt removing more and more of decent folks' freedoms in doing so?</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356120593732</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 15:09:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356120739808-93</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke said Obama's policies do not support a recovery. Libtards ignore such statements now blame him for Obama's failure</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1356110898046</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:28:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama does NOT want a recovery nor USA to retain its strength. Obama does Not like this country &amp; has said so in his books. He believes the Founding Fathers were wrong. It is now time to repay the poor, take back the wealth that was stolen from them by those who are rich. If this country goes down the drain; good enuf for it. It deserves that . Read his books, writings in college, etc. Its all there. We keep thingking he wants good for us. I believe you should listen to what people say then watch them.. Both of these parameters point this direction for Obama.</Msg><Username>sparrowgt</Username><Timestamp>1356120739808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 15:12:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356120998201-94</Id><Topic><Title>A Message to the NRA's Wayne LaPierre</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356106766814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Far from it....standard liberal pattern..jump on an emotional issue to remove more freedoms via big centralized govt. and the terrible consequences of liberal policy that gets passed, and follows. Now, after some level headed investigation we get the background on the MOTHER! She was a huge contributor to the mass murders. Took her very intelligent son who graduated early, and took college classes, but was mentally disturbed to a gun range as early as 9 yrs. old to learn to shoot well the stockpile of weapons and ammo she had accumulated as a kooky survivalist! She was assigned to her kid as his therapist when she needed mental consoling herself!! And a teacher? How was she allowed in the school when an FBI check is required? But what will we here from the liberal press? ..about the mother?..or just the need for gun control?</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356120998201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 15:16:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356122515724-95</Id><Topic><Title>America Must Stop Codling the Mediocre Class</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356102848431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's funny. I've never seen Bill Gates, Warren Buffet or any other true "high-achievers" post here. True "high achievers" don't waste their time posting on an Internet message board, to total strangers no less, droning on and on about how high, mighty and wealthy they are. Your constant obsession with money and wealth betrays the painful truth. You have neither ... and are apparently unable to cope with the reality that is your life. Perhaps you should consider some counseling. They may even be able to prescribe something to help with your affliction. Good luck.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1356122515724</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 15:41:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356122756522-96</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke said Obama's policies do not support a recovery. Libtards ignore such statements now blame him for Obama's failure</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1356110898046</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:28:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why should it take Ben to convince anyone that Obama's centralized, big govt, big tax payer spending approach is good for the economy? FDR did it, and it produced a terrible economy for a decade? GW BUSH did just the opposite, promoted the private sector investment not spending a taxpayer dime, and it immediately created a record growth economy that lasted the longest in USA history! Europe has done what Obama has done, and look at the debt, and personal suffering in Europe. Are we committed to the fact that the majority of USA citizens are stupid?</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356122756522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 15:45:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356122978109-97</Id><Topic><Title>America Must Stop Codling the Mediocre Class</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356102848431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"how high, mighty and wealthy" is Mir? I don't recall him saying. CTTOI why are you so jealous of Mir? He's always been one of the best posters on this board for years. H</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356122978109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 15:49:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356123015207-98</Id><Topic><Title>Who's fault is it now, Bohner I mean didn't he say Obama was lying Obama is after the</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1356120657690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 15:10:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The dirt poor live in back alleys, and in dung made huts in Venezuela voting for Chavez the same as the majority voted for Obama in the USA. The numbers of dirt poor just increase in numbers having to live, and feed at the govt trough on the govt plantation. It is a win, win for the left....until all the workin stiffs tax revenue runs out, and we go deeep in debt. And it looks like we is there!</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356123015207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 15:50:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356123122181-99</Id><Topic><Title>America Must Stop Codling the Mediocre Class</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356102848431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"how high, mighty and wealthy" is Mir? I don't recall him ever saying. Why are you so jealous of him? Does his words of truth cut you to the bone. I think so.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356123122181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 15:52:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356123488078-100</Id><Topic><Title>America Must Stop Codling the Mediocre Class</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356102848431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His words have no truth. Only doofus-speak. Proven when he "explained" how to relate F to C.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1356123488078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 15:58:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356123648085-101</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Time to Overthrow Our Government?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1356050057016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:34:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, I believe we're real close! Liberal media is the propaganda arm of the government so they must go too. Let's not forget to reign in the Hollywood elites. This mushy affair they have going with Obama is unamerica and downright q-u-e-r!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1356123648085</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 16:00:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356125307575-102</Id><Topic><Title>A Message to the NRA's Wayne LaPierre</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356106766814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe Heston served in WWII as a staff sargent on B-25s. Don't know about Wayne.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1356125307575</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 16:28:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356125640955-103</Id><Topic><Title>A Message to the NRA's Wayne LaPierre</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356106766814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Folks gunned down in our big cities everyday...why no concern from the left?...1/2 doz or so in democrap town, Chicago everyday. .. Democrap central. Why no concern? Another weapon, a Fast and Furious provided weapon to gun dealers by Obama at a border, murder scene just lately. Why no news, and concern about it?</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356125640955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 16:34:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356125718979-104</Id><Topic><Title>Right-wing author, the "Daily Show" host has helped "drive [God] out of our society"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1355963975117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 19:39:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>~~~ 2. Gin, While the teachings of the Taliban may be different from strict Islam, as they are "radicalized", the Koran and Islam are nevertheless the antithesis of the Bible and Christianity. They are polar opposites.~~~--- You missed my point! I was not promoting any religion! I was stating that the main problem with any religion is that it's original good teachings get twisted and word crafted into evil teachings that benefit whoever is twisting and word crafting the original meanings! Example: The Christian Coalition claims to be non-partisan. The Christian Coalition passes out “voter guides” in churches and yet is granted tax exempt status. It clearly supports a radical conservative agenda and is associated with Christian fundamentalism. It is yet another group that believes that America should be a Conservative Christian state. They are a threat to the Constitution!</Msg><Username>gin.haruko</Username><Timestamp>1356125718979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 16:35:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356126244374-105</Id><Topic><Title>A Message to the NRA's Wayne LaPierre</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356106766814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes he did. That was when he was a Democrat, however :-) But everyone is free to change their stands on political issues; and no one should talk smack about a great American like Heston. (I'm not sure anyone WAS.) Following the assassination of Senator Robert F. Kennedy in 1968, Heston and actors Gregory Peck, Kirk Douglas and James Stewart issued a statement calling for support of President Johnson's Gun Control Act of 1968.[27][28] He opposed the Vietnam War during its course (though he changed his opinion in the years following the war)[29] and in 1969 was approached by the Democratic Party to run for the U.S. Senate. He agonized over the decision and ultimately determined he could never give up acting.[30] He is reported to have voted for Richard Nixon in 1972, though Nixon is unmentioned in his autobiography.[31] By the 1980s, Heston opposed affirmative action, supported gun rights and changed his political affiliation from Democrat to Republican.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356126244374</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 16:44:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356126509711-106</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are Liberals so Fearful of Liberty and Independence?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356118147102</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:29:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cry me a river, fairy godfather.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356126509711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 16:48:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356126682337-107</Id><Topic><Title>The natural progress of things is for liberty to yield and government to gain ground.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356112283162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 12:51:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are saying that Democrats wrote the U.S. Constitution, then I agree the GOP has never done squat for the common man.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356126682337</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 16:51:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356128357092-108</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>correct...TSA and now State Troopers will go in your pants and anal cavities because AlQaeda is hiding there....but lets approve of Barry giving them guns in Benghazi</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356128357092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:19:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356128477088-109</Id><Topic><Title>A Message to the NRA's Wayne LaPierre</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356106766814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you concerned about your President giving guns to AlQaeda in Libya or Syria ? ..or Mexican Drug lords at the border ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356128477088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:21:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356128715301-110</Id><Topic><Title>Do States Have the Right to Secede?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356108413857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:46:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>walter Williams the creetin product of James Mellon University--- er James Mason University which is of course funded by the Mellons and the Kochs- to spread their view of troooth as they see fit. Just think young people in their late teens who are unable to think for themselves go to this school and are indoctrinated in the most acid vitriol of the lunatic right before they even make it to their twenties. A lot of these kids are rendered useless to society by this right wing poison and spend their days attacking our Western Civilization and ripping off the economy in true republican fashion</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1356128715301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:25:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356129161288-111</Id><Topic><Title>Do States Have the Right to Secede?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356108413857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:46:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course there may be nothing in the constitution to prevent secession but there is nothing in the constitution to prevent the remaining states and their congress along with the president to mount a military attack on these states and force them to not secede. Of course that was 1861- today the majority of the old Union states might want to expel the states of the old Confederacy from the Union and there is nothing in the constitution to prevent it. Hey lets get cracking and get rid of these loser states- let them go the h....ll</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1356129161288</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:32:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356129346214-112</Id><Topic><Title>Celebrate the Greatest Gift Ever Given to Mankind</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356128485169</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:21:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks.....What is your price projection for gold and Silver for 2013 ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356129346214</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:35:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356129460009-113</Id><Topic><Title>Do States Have the Right to Secede?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356108413857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:46:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you have something to say about Walter William' observation of history or are you just angry that that he actually backs up his comments with facts instead of spewing left-wing Marxist kool-aid?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356129460009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:37:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356129687322-114</Id><Topic><Title>America Must Stop Codling the Mediocre Class</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356102848431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I don't recall him ever saying." Then either you have a very selective memory or you haven't been paying attention. He constantly posts about how superior he is to everybody else. Jealous of him is the last thing I am. He's an arrogant, pompous, wind bag whose self-esteem is so frail that he needs to prop it up by running others down. I'd NEVER want to be anything like him. As for his words cutting to the bone ... That's a laugh. Nothing could be further from the truth. Let me guess. Mushrooms?</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1356129687322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:41:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356130201962-115</Id><Topic><Title>America Must Stop Codling the Mediocre Class</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356102848431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mediocrity generally has a clue. Obama catered to the clueless. Told them complete falsehoods, and they shook their heads "yes", tell us more. Obama never mentioned how he would govern just told lies, and struck fear in the ignorant. Like "There he goes again (Romney) wanting to return us to what got us in this mess in the first place." Total lie, Obama, and the left got us into this mess, but the ignorant bought into it, and got him re-elected. Don't believe me?...ask James Carville.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356130201962</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:50:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356130325914-116</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are Liberals so Fearful of Liberty and Independence?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356118147102</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:29:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Schools of higher learning are betraying the American way of life by vocally endorsing socialism or worse onto the student body. They set the agenda for our children. The American people suffer the consequences as products of the American educational system make their way into society and politics. Each new generation more disinclined to support a nation that has been the envy of the world. The greatest nation the world has ever seen is struggling with an alternative to perfection that has been forced upon it.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1356130325914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:52:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356130344843-117</Id><Topic><Title>Celebrate the Greatest Gift Ever Given to Mankind</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356128485169</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:21:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hard to do these years without being attacked by a liberal aethist attacking you as a Christian, rightwing, radical extremist.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356130344843</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:52:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356131257929-118</Id><Topic><Title>48 planes delivered so far.in DEcember</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1356117754578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:22:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>8 787 each lossing 116,000 ,2 747 at a loss so stockholders lost 1 million dollars 2 767 that is very littel profit, 6 777 a little more profits so the heritage 767 Union designed is the last revenue producer and with the fail on the engine that will be another money loser</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1356131257929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:07:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356131402674-119</Id><Topic><Title>48 planes delivered so far.in DEcember</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1356117754578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:22:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing gains year to date in stock price 3.8% BAC yeard to date gain 103% you decide any shareholder of Boeing stock who reads about deliveries is following a failure report look at the stock price</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1356131402674</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:10:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356131510495-120</Id><Title>Boeing buys more land in South Carolina....Bye Bye Left Coast Losers !!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>You Left Coast Losers better brush up on your "Welcome to McDonalds" greeting ! lololololololololol In ten years the biggest product made in dope smoken' Seattle will be a 24oz. cafe latte.</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1356131510495</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:11:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356131598560-121</Id><Topic><Title>BEST NEWS OF 2012</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1356130601286</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:56:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like Pauline didn't get her partridge in a pear tree that she wanted. So, like a typical Dim, she blames the rich for her mediocre life of want. Poor, poor, Dim Pauline!!!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1356131598560</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:13:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356131718341-122</Id><Topic><Title>Extremists</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356131567685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:12:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do they rage with hate when you remind them that more government means less freedom? BINGO...We have a winner!!!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1356131718341</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:15:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356131791017-123</Id><Title>Boeing corporate raiders</Title><Msg>Genius. This is the new America Boeing grants Bonuses and stock options for the top brass, pink slips and blame for the working class. This trend is from the right-wing think tanks and pundits who demonize union members as freeloaders and thugs. It has been a decades-long project, and it’s been incredibly successful. Of course, union scolds never pause to ask why Boeing executives, love to underfund pension funds — that is, to fail to live up to the contracts the with employees in the first place. In this way, private equity operators of Boeing are stuffing companies with debt, squeezing fees and profits into the right executive pockets, and shafting patsies like Boeing shareholder’s, wage employees. When Condit purchased MD , he did not know he purchased a corporate raider company, the few who post here all the time in Boeing Executive defense don’t get it, the Boeing company is being raided. First the massive amount of Boeing held land was sold, . , then the work was outsourced, or moved to a right to work state, and the goal is to bleed Boeing dry then move on.. Boeing will be sucked dry for bankruptcy, which is another technique to pass on Boeing worker pensions to the taxpayer . . All this corporate insider raiding is covered with , . all the bluster about Union’s as characterized as the moochers off society, one group is habitually ignored the executive moochers.. This is the new America:. The reality is not quite so simple — from the Wall Street Journal, no less — consider all the hype surrounding the Hostess company union had crippled and forced Hostess out of business. The truth is that Hostess executives, after their workforce had already taken pay cutbacks or pay freezes, while the Hostess executives had diverted employee retirement funding payments, so payments it was supposed to make to the employee pension fund went into other accounts! The American taxpayer will fund the hostess blue collar workers pensions and the executives move on to retirement or to work for another company to corporate raid it into bankruptcy. The days of the corporate raider have shifted from the Icahn’s and skipped this middle man and gone directly to the Boeing BOD, as worked by the CEO of Boeing company. This is the game plan from Chicago for Boeing , it's the business plan per MD bankruptcy experts, they learned on their own company first, and now are applying this to Boeing, it is so simple to . Condit is very happy with his slice and retired. Year to date Boeing has come on now up to 3.8% gain for the year, Bank of America is up 103% for the year. Analysts predict stock buy back will not help boeing ratings, while a famous analyst predicts BAC is set to blast off for next year humm maybe forget all those costly 787 that are sold at a 116000.00 loss per plane and the 747 that are all sold at a loss and look at the stock price divident raise 10% humm tax was 15% now about 50% so factor in the 103% gain for BAC to the 3.8% gain for BA and then make the right choice dead cat bounce stock BA or good gainer at low price with high volume BAC !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1356131791017</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:16:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356131947869-124</Id><Topic><Title>A Message to the NRA's Wayne LaPierre</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356106766814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would you please retreat into your Sir Paul blowup doll already and let the "sane" adults handle these matters already?</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1356131947869</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:19:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356132046433-125</Id><Topic><Title>A Message to the NRA's Wayne LaPierre</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1356106766814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who said we are not concerned with it? Silence is golden to you Dims isn't it Pecker?</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1356132046433</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:20:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356132747834-126</Id><Topic><Title>America Must Stop Codling the Mediocre Class</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356102848431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you know I am not Bill Gates, or Warren Buffet? Both are bigtime liberals by the way like most billionaires are, and contribute to the Democrat Party for selfish reasons. The benefit from crony capitalism.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356132747834</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:32:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356132891332-127</Id><Topic><Title>Extremists</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356131567685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:12:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same reason communists accept communism. There govt has convinced them they are stupid, and can't make good decisions by themselves...they need big govt. and are satisfied working for the govt much of the year....if they work.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356132891332</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:34:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356133553908-128</Id><Title>Can Politicians Really Spend Your money better than you can?</Title><Msg>If you answered Yes, you're an idiot. Maybe they can spend it faster but better?.....they've got the country $16 trillion dollars in debt. Why would any sane person want to give them more of their money?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1356133553908</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:45:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356134060879-129</Id><Topic><Title>Celebrate the Greatest Gift Ever Given to Mankind</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356128485169</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:21:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a bonafide whackjob...</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1356134060879</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:54:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356134586876-130</Id><Topic><Title>Extremists</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356131567685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:12:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>= There govt = Cute! Where did ya learn the Teabonics? Here in this forum?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1356134586876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 19:03:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356134589004-131</Id><Topic><Title>Celebrate the Greatest Gift Ever Given to Mankind</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356128485169</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:21:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am heavily invested in all metals. Gold Silver lead and Brass. Jim Rogers, one of the worlds leading commodity investrs thinks All will go up in value with Gold going over $2000 by the end of 2013. Silver breaching the legendary 50 dollar mark....but not before a brief period of deflation in the first part of 2013. I've been preaching about the Federal Reserve on here for years so that is no surprise.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356134589004</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 19:03:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356134792669-132</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing buys more land in South Carolina....Bye Bye Left Coast Losers !!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1356131510495</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:11:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope. We'll be just fine. As for you, not so much, which is readily apparent from your angry, envious post ... Have a nice day! : )</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1356134792669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 19:06:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356135076975-133</Id><Title>Eric Holder’s Sympathy For the Devil</Title><Msg>I am almost bored hearing about how the Obama White House is going to use executive orders to impose some kind of gun control. Stop threatening and do it, already! Let the struggle begin. But sometimes the news gets interesting. For example, recently Eric Holder tried to get us all to feel sorry for the impoverished agents of the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms, and Explosives. When discussing options, Reuters reports “Those options will have to include a ‘strong and robust’ Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives, the chronically under-funded agency that enforces federal gun laws, he said.” Poor, poor, BATFE! So weak and frail! So much in need of funds so they can do so much good… Seriously? The BATFE’s body count is already strong and robust. Ruby Ridge involved other jackbooted agencies, but the BATFE was a major player. And then there was Waco and the David Koresh cult. They insisted on a grand siege rather than simply arresting Koresh when he was out jogging. Their self-serving decision, along with other bad decisions, led to the incineration of women and children. Two years later, to the day, we had the bombing of the Federal Building in Oklahoma City. Mysteriously, the BATFE were warned not to show up for work. After the blast, while people were trapped and suffering and dying, time and again medical personnel had to leave the wreckage and abandon those they were helping because a “new explosive” had been discovered. It is likely those explosives were actually materials the BATF had been illegally storing in the building and wanted to move so they wouldn’t get in trouble. But why am I digging up scandals from back in the nineties? The most incredible aspect of Eric Holder’s statement is his shameless pretense that the BATFE needs to be made “strong and robust” in the context of their most recent scandal. Strong and robust to succeed at what? Do they need to become strong and robust enough to sell hundreds of weapons to Mexican drug cartels so that they can be used to murder Americans and Mexicans? They’ve already got that covered. Just how much more empowerment does Holder thinks the BATFE requires? If you want to see fewer gun deaths, a good argument could be made for eliminating the BATFE. This would, first of all, eliminate their contribution to firearm deaths. Even if we need a federal domestic police force, that doesn’t prove we need several of them. We have the Federal Bureau of Investigation and the Department of Homeland Security. How does a third distinct agency give Americans protection? It just creates confusion. I find it completely amazing that Holder can simply shrug off the BATFE’s lethal crimes—crimes that seem to implicate himself—and use the deaths of innocent children to portray the agency as a solution and not a problem. Another question: does Holder think talking up the BATFE makes most Americans feel safe and secure? If I were a gun merchant, I would consider such rhetoric the best advertising I could possibly get.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356135076975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 19:11:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356135233991-134</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TSA is sticking their hands down your wifes pants in public because they are trying to find Alqaeda in our underwear..... Not even Nazi Germany did that....if we don't draw a line in the sand soon, its all gone</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356135233991</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 19:13:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356135741679-135</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama employed the Muslim Brotherhood lobbyist to organize an investigation of the Benghazi murders. The guy had access, and many times to the White House.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356135741679</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 19:22:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356137269754-136</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing buys more land in South Carolina....Bye Bye Left Coast Losers !!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1356131510495</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:11:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You tell us Redneck! LOL</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1356137269754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 19:47:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356137279977-137</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Holder’s Sympathy For the Devil</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356135076975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 19:11:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't believe that wigging out ever bores you, spart.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356137279977</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 19:47:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356138428991-138</Id><Topic><Title>Can Politicians Really Spend Your money better than you can?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1356133553908</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:45:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Evidently liberals realize they are too stupid to spend their own money aqnd would rathe some politician spend it for them.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1356138428991</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 20:07:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356138473806-139</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney....</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1356134792825</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 19:06:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear Sir Paul Thanks for the sane posts. You counteract at least 5000 of spartapoo's rantings. Keep up the fine work.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1356138473806</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 20:07:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356138966107-140</Id><Topic><Title>Extremists</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356131567685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:12:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great post</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356138966107</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 20:16:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356139119645-141</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Holder’s Sympathy For the Devil</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356135076975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 19:11:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the article: "Their (BATF and FBI) self-serving decision, along with other bad decisions, led to the incineration of women and children." ....didnt I just say that the other day...and didn't some #$%$ in denial say it never happenned ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356139119645</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 20:18:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356139542678-142</Id><Topic><Title>Celebrate the Greatest Gift Ever Given to Mankind</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356128485169</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:21:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chris_genna2 - You sound like a real wack job with a very big chip on your shoulder. No one forces anyone to worship anyone. All they do is ask for a little respect and time to say a prayer or space to express their faith. Your holier than thou Democrat Party did the same thing when they had a Catholic Cardinal say a payer at their convention. You anti religious nut jobs should be asking where are all the Atheist hospitals, cancer clinics, schools, universities, disaster relief, shelters for the homeless and orphanages. About all you kooks do is make sure places that kill babies are well funded. Once you Godless perverts do half as much as Churches and Synagogs have done maybe some one will take you for something other than a whining nut job.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1356139542678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 20:25:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356140499381-143</Id><Topic><Title>America Must Stop Codling the Mediocre Class</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356102848431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mir_roguns - you're one of the few posters on here that ever make sense. I can't understand what most of them are doing on a finance board.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1356140499381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 20:41:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356140606640-144</Id><Topic><Title>America Must Stop Codling the Mediocre Class</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356102848431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ask your little imaginary pal Mir about C vs F. HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1356140606640</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 20:43:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356140836624-145</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney....</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1356134792825</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 19:06:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Totally agree. Sir Paul nailed it.</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1356140836624</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 20:47:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356141113760-146</Id><Topic><Title>Tonight is Crab Night at the Petroleum Club</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356133022275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:37:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's poultry night at the supermarket. All the ladies are entitled to a free goose.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1356141113760</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 20:51:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356142637068-147</Id><Topic><Title>Can Politicians Really Spend Your money better than you can?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1356133553908</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:45:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Politicians might spend a libtard's money better than they could and Heather is obviously spending Sir Paul's money better than he could.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1356142637068</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:17:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356142962535-148</Id><Title>U.S. Space contract extension</Title><Msg>ALBUQUERQUE, N.M., Dec. 20, 2012 -- Boeing [NYSE: BA] will continue to provide engineering and scientific support for U.S. space situational awareness under an Innovative Research and Optical Site Support (IROSS) contract extension from the Air Force Research Laboratory (AFRL). Under the 18-month, $67 million extension, Boeing Directed Energy Systems will provide engineering support, conduct research, and maintain and enhance telescope and electro-optical systems at the Starfire Optical Range in New Mexico and the Maui Space Surveillance Complex in Hawaii. Boeing also is assisting with efforts to modernize major observatory systems at the Maui complex, and helping to return the systems from a period of testing and upgrades to full operational status.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1356142962535</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:22:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356143132474-149</Id><Title>space launch system PDR completed</Title><Msg>HUNTSVILLE, Ala., Dec. 21, 2012 -- Boeing [NYSE: BA] and NASA on Dec. 20 completed the Preliminary Design Review (PDR) for the Space Launch System (SLS) core stage and avionics, validating the design of the rocket that will send humans beyond low Earth orbit to places like the moon, an asteroid and ultimately Mars. The PDR is a comprehensive review that demonstrates that the design meets all system requirements within acceptable risk constraints, establishing approval for proceeding with detailed design. The first mission in 2017 will be an un-crewed loop around Earth's moon, to be followed by a crewed mission.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1356143132474</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:25:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356143784085-150</Id><Topic><Title>America Must Stop Codling the Mediocre Class</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356102848431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 10:14:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thus, you are out of place and should look elsewhere.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356143784085</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:36:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356143867211-151</Id><Topic><Title>Celebrate the Greatest Gift Ever Given to Mankind</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356128485169</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:21:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bless you, my pseudo-learned son.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356143867211</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:37:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356143952533-152</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing buys more land in South Carolina....Bye Bye Left Coast Losers !!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1356131510495</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:11:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This comment shows just how uneducated folks are on the "EAST" coast. What is the "LEFT COAST"??? Never heard the WEST coast termed as "LEFT". Perhaps you were attempting to be funny using the term "Left" as in Boeing "left" for SC? In any case - unlike SC, McDonald's workers here make twice what they make over there. We'll be asked to move to SC if they decide to move as we all know there are not enough educated people over there. Only thing they good at is spittin n burpin.</Msg><Username>ev3044</Username><Timestamp>1356143952533</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:39:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356143962021-153</Id><Topic><Title>WHY is President Barry giving Assault Weapons to Al-Qaeda (Confirmed)?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356049251554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 19:20:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you get turned down for a job at TSA?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356143962021</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:39:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356144293331-154</Id><Topic><Title>Celebrate the Greatest Gift Ever Given to Mankind</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356128485169</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:21:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Make everyone else? Who does that? Obama attacked the Catholic Church to where the Catholic Church sued Obama, then he supports Muslims in everyway possible, from supporting their Mosque at the 9-11 sight, and not even willing to identify who the Muslim terrorists are that want to kil us, and who we are at war with. You are a bad joke.</Msg><Username>smalltowndude01</Username><Timestamp>1356144293331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:44:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356144636568-155</Id><Topic><Title>Celebrate the Greatest Gift Ever Given to Mankind</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356128485169</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:21:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who mentioned making out? Talk about being a joke -- it isn't a mosque and it's not at the site. Would you like it if someone denied you a permit to build your Catholic church on some obscure pseudo-patriotic grounds? I don't think you would. I come here for the humor, and I am almost never disappointed (unless the talk is about mowing down 6-year-olds with gunfire.)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1356144636568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:50:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356144903552-156</Id><Topic><Title>Extremists</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356131567685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:12:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Teabonics? Probably at Mir's make believe Petroleum Club, where they practice converting C to F.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1356144903552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:55:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356146718040-157</Id><Topic><Title>Extremists</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356131567685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:12:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... like your grade point average . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1356146718040</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 22:25:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356147173659-158</Id><Topic><Title>Extremists</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356131567685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:12:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably because they are bitter self proclaimed Liberals that seek to blame and punish others for their own failures and rejection by society . They clearly don't belong in the land of the free, and the home of the brave . ... and no Chrissy, being drafted way back when doesn't change that equation . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1356147173659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 22:32:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356149338363-159</Id><Topic><Title>Extremists</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1356131567685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 18:12:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Easy there, sonny. Even Djumbots can find solace this time of year. Try to jettison your feelings of failure and utter worthlessness and jealousy.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1356149338363</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 23:08:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356150175752-160</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are Blue Stes Lossing Population?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1356119297860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 14:48:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Highdensity of ugly women</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1356150175752</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 23:22:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>