<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351742406304-1</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney's Father Marched With MLK</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1351736853396</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 22:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt marched in support of Vietnam war while avoiding the draft. Sounds just like Mitt. "The photo was also mentioned by the Boston Globe in 2008, with a partial image of the event clipped from a newspaper front page. The paper wrote in its definitive series on the former governor that, "Among the long hair and ragged clothes of his classmates, Romney stood out both for his smart appearance and his ardent support of the war.""</Msg><Username>gerbilfood4me</Username><Timestamp>1351742406304</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 00:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351743267355-2</Id><Topic><Title>Senators Again Urge Obama to Answer Key Questions about Benghazi Attack</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351715434294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:30:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Benghazi is turning into grounds for impeachment. " - was Regan impeached for his dealings in Nicaragua........</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351743267355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 00:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351743513597-3</Id><Topic><Title>Why Obama Is A Genius</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351720503679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anybody who supports Obama is a socialist - a gambler - a low life and a drunk or drug abuser is that right??? Come Nov 6th - you gonna see how many of those types vote in the presidential election....glad I'm one of his supporters</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1351743513597</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 00:18:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351744615169-4</Id><Topic><Title>What was this lie about jeeps going to china</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351724153540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:55:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No they are not. The are considering restarting production in China. Production in the US remains. They are moving nothing. You and Mitt are FOS.</Msg><Username>gerbilfood4me</Username><Timestamp>1351744615169</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 00:36:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351745596083-5</Id><Topic><Title>You have no Fact Jack... factcheck dot org</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351743792479</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 00:23:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Missed a point "Sept. 14: Clinton spoke at Andrews Air Force Base saying "deploring — and I quote — ‘an act of ugly terror.’ ” and told the father/mother of one of those killed - " WE will arrest the guy who produced the video " ( that caused all this ) A proveable lie. And of course Jolting joe Biden who said to the father - did your son always have ba***** the size of cueballs ? ' And Obuma could NOT and did NOT look the father in the eye as he shook his hand and said I'm sorry " And then ObUma claimed he gave immediate orders to protect ... So if true- then either Panetta or the chairman of Joint chiefs decided to NOT do anything ??? Somebody is lieing !</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1351745596083</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 00:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351748336426-6</Id><Topic><Title>You have no Fact Jack... factcheck dot org</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351743792479</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 00:23:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not to mention the TV ads run on Muslim TV with Hilary apologizing for the youtube video. I can almost see the terrorist looking at each other saying "what video?". In some bizarre way I can understand the terrorists, but our governments actions after are totally insane. Just imagine if obama was pres on Dec 8th 1942, he would have blamed Pearl Harbor on Charlie Chan movies.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1351748336426</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 01:38:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351748425720-7</Id><Topic><Title>What was this lie about jeeps going to china</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351724153540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:55:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama also told us that the bailout of the auto industry did cost the taxpayer one cent yet we the taxpayers lost $1.3 billion dollars on the Chrysler bailout.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351748425720</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 01:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351751220630-8</Id><Topic><Title>Senators Again Urge Obama to Answer Key Questions about Benghazi Attack</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351715434294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:30:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is a good thing that Obama has not actually closed Gitmo. There is room for him at this point.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351751220630</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 02:27:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351753597731-9</Id><Title>(Just a couple of) the Obama Administration's accomplishments:</Title><Msg>Every now and again, the other side likes to claim President Obama doesn't have a record to run on. They're wrong. Here's a taste of why: 1. The first bill President Obama signed was the Lilly Ledbetter Fair Pay Act, to help women fight back when they don't get equal pay for equal work. 2. His Recovery Act supported millions of jobs and helped to stave off a second Great Depression. 3. He pushed for and won middle-class tax cuts that benefitted every American worker, and saved the typical family $3,600 in taxes over the last four years. 4. President Obama rescued the auto industry, and now GM and Chrysler are healthier than they've ever been. The American auto industry has added nearly a quarter of a million jobs since June 2009 -- and they most likely wouldn't exist right now without President Obama's leadership. 5. He doubled funding for Pell Grants, helping to make college more affordable for nearly 10 million families. 6. His student loan reform ended billions in subsidies to banks serving as middlemen and reinvested those savings directly into students. 7. The President established the American Opportunity Tax Credit, worth up to $10,000 over four years of college. 8. His Race to the Top Initiative helped spur nearly every state to raise academic standards. 9. His tax cuts, social-welfare programs, and economic policies lifted nearly 7 million Americans above the federal poverty line in 2010. 10. President Obama has signed 18 tax cuts for small businesses since taking office. 11. We've seen 5.2 million new private-sector jobs over the last 31 months. 12. The unemployment rate is at the lowest level since President Obama took office. 13. Health care reform -- passed after decades of failed attempts by every previous President -- provides affordable health coverage to every American and will lower premiums by an average of $2,000 per family by 2019. 14. Obamacare expanded access to lifesaving preventive care such as cancer screenings and immunizations with no out-of-pocket costs for 54 million Americans. 15. Obamacare ends insurance discrimination against the 129 million Americans with pre-existing conditions. 16. Because of Obamacare, over 3 million more young adults have health insurance today than would if the new law hadn't passed. 17. The parents of over 17 million children with pre-existing conditions no longer have to worry that their children will be denied coverage. 18. President Obama has ordered the overhaul of federal government regulations to make them smarter, practical, and more efficient. Just a fraction of these commonsense initiatives will help save businesses $10 billion in the next five years alone. 19. His historic investments in clean energy have helped more than double the amount of electricity we obtain from wind and solar sources and helped increase biofuel production to its highest level in history. 20. President Obama is doubling fuel efficiency standards, which will save drivers more than $8,000 at the gas pump, not to mention lessen the impact of automobiles on our environment. 21. President Obama has taken unprecedented action to address climate change, reaching historic international agreements to curb carbon emissions, and taking action here at home to reduce carbon pollution from our vehicles and promote clean energy production. 22. He has taken historic action to protect our environment -- signing one of the largest expansions of protected wilderness in a generation and putting in place standards to reduce toxic air pollution that will save thousands of lives. 23. President Obama fought for and won landmark Wall Street reform that reins in the abuses that led to the financial crisis and ends the era of taxpayer bailouts and "too big to fail." 24. Wall Street reform created the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau, the nation's first federal agency focused solely on consumer financial protection -- and the Bureau is already protecting families from unfair and abusive financial practices from Wall Street banks and shadowy corners of the financial industry. 25. As part of President Obama's commitment to transparency, the White House has posted its visitor records online for the first time ever. 26. President Obama's all-of-the-above approach to energy has helped cut the United States' dependence on foreign oil to its lowest level in 20 years. 27. President Obama responsibly ended the war in Iraq. 28. He announced a plan to end the war in Afghanistan and transition security responsibility to the Afghan people. 29. President Obama sent the largest security assistance package to Israel in history and funded the Iron Dome system, which is protecting Israeli homes and schools from rocket attacks. 30. President Obama rallied the international community to implement the toughest sanctions on Iran in history. 31. Through the President's historic increases in Veterans Affairs funding, he has expanded and improved healthcare and job training access for our returning veterans. 32. President Obama negotiated the New START Treaty with Russia to reduce the number of nuclear weapons in both countries. At the same time, he also secured commitments from dozens of other countries to lock down nuclear materials. 33. His administration naturalized 11,146 military service members as U.S. citizens in 2010; more than in any year since 1955. 34. President Obama set a bold new plan for the future of NASA space exploration, using the skill and ability of the private sector for short trips to the International Space Station, while building a new vehicle for exploration of distant space, and doing everything in his power to support the economy on Florida's Space Coast. 35. President Obama recognizes that tourism is one of America's largest economic engines; he's worked to encourage international visitors to come here, maintaining our security while keeping millions of Americans in good, paying jobs. 36. He has affirmed his personal support of marriage equality, directed the Justice Department to stop defending DOMA in federal courts, and took the practical and compassionate step of extending hospital visitation rights to same-sex partners. 37. He fought for and won the repeal of Don't Ask, Don't Tell, allowing gay and lesbian members of the military to serve openly for the first time in history. 38. When Congress failed to fix our broken immigration system, his administration did everything in its power to improve it, streamlining the legal immigration process and announcing a policy that lifts the shadow of deportation from hard working young immigrants brought to the U.S. as children. 39. Oh, and he gave the order to send troops in after Osama Bin Laden -- and has decimated al-Qaeda's senior leadership.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351753597731</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 03:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351754184106-10</Id><Title>"Storm Surge" -- LOL</Title><Msg>Obama's lead on intrade jumps up to 37.2 percent points. He's making Willtard look like a groping fool, desperately staging embarassing and mistimed photo ops... distributing cans of food, COME ON. Is that the best he can do?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351754184106</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 03:16:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351754391895-11</Id><Topic><Title>You See Victims, Romney Smells “Opportunity” - And This Guy Wants to be MY President !</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351743010322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 00:10:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a miserably pathetic campaign Willtard is running! Has he lost control? Or is he just a #$%$ leader?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351754391895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 03:19:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351761544955-12</Id><Title>Romney Versus the Automakers</Title><Msg>When General Motors tells a presidential campaign that it is engaging in “cynical campaign politics at its worst,” that’s a pretty good signal that the campaign has crossed a red line and ought to pull back. Not Mitt Romney’s campaign. Having broadcast an outrageously deceitful ad attacking the auto bailout, the campaign ignored the howls from carmakers and came back with more. Mr. Romney apparently plans to end his race as he began it: playing lowest-common-denominator politics, saying anything necessary to achieve power and blithely deceiving voters desperate for clarity and truth. This started months ago when he realized that his very public 2008 stance against the successful and wildly popular government bailout of G.M. and Chrysler was hurting him in the valuable states of Ohio and Michigan. In February, he wrote an essay for The Detroit News calling the bailout “crony capitalism on a grand scale” because unions benefited and insisting that Detroit would have been better off to refuse federal money. (This ignores the well-documented reality that there was no other cash available to the carmakers.) When that tactic didn’t work, he began insisting at the debates that his plan for Detroit wasn’t really that different from President Obama’s. (Except for the niggling detail of the $80 billion federal investment.) That was quickly discredited, so Mr. Romney began telling rallies last week that Chrysler was considering moving its production to China. Chrysler loudly denounced it as “fantasies,” saying it was only considering increasing production in China for sale in China, without moving a single American job. “I feel obliged to unambiguously restate our position: Jeep production will not be moved from the United States to China,” Chrysler’s chief executive, Sergio Marchionne, said in a statement. “Jeep assembly lines will remain in operation in the United States and will constitute the backbone of the brand. It is inaccurate to suggest anything different.” In fact, 1,100 new jobs will be added in Toledo to produce a new generation of Jeep. The Romney campaign ignored the company, following up with an instantly notorious ad saying President Obama “sold Chrysler to Italians who are going to build Jeeps in China.” If the false implication wasn’t clear enough, the campaign put out a radio ad on Tuesday saying “Barack Obama says he saved the auto industry. But for who? Ohio or China?” What happened, the ad asks, “to the promises made to autoworkers in Toledo and throughout Ohio?” What happened was that those promises were kept. Nearly 1.5 million people are working as a direct result of the bailout. Ohio’s unemployment rate is well below the national average. G.M.’s American sales continue to increase, and Chrysler said this week that its third-quarter net income rose 80 percent. These companies haven’t just bounced back from the bottom; they are accelerating. What Mr. Romney cannot admit is that all this is a direct result of the government investment he would have rejected. It’s bad enough to be wrong on the policy. It takes an especially dishonest candidate to simply turn up the volume on a lie and keep repeating it. By doing that in a flailing, last-minute grab for Ohio, Mr. Romney is providing a grim preview of what kind of president he would be.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351761544955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 05:19:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351761624039-13</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Versus the Automakers</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351761544955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 05:19:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gotta love the last two lines: // It’s bad enough to be wrong on the policy. It takes an especially dishonest candidate to simply turn up the volume on a lie and keep repeating it. By doing that in a flailing, last-minute grab for Ohio, Mr. Romney is providing a grim preview of what kind of president he would be. \\</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351761624039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 05:20:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351764666340-14</Id><Topic><Title>You have no Fact Jack... factcheck dot org</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1351743792479</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 00:23:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you ask your war "hero" buttbuddy, the Kent Raven, to explain this to you. After all, he knows how to tell a war story or two.................</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1351764666340</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 06:11:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351764772650-15</Id><Topic><Title>"Storm Surge" -- LOL</Title><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351754184106</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 03:16:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You think something is funny about the storm surge? Why don't you go to NY or NJ and tell them what's so funny. I bet a liberal punk like you would last less than a NY minute.</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1351764772650</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 06:12:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351773758279-16</Id><Title>Media Bias Intensifying</Title><Msg>I was talking with a former newsman yesterday – a news director and news anchor. He lives way up in the frozen north, right in the middle of Obama territory. He told me that it just cannot be avoided any more – no matter how much he wanted to believe that our national press corps is truly impartial in this presidential race, the obvious blatant bias for Obama simply cannot be denied any more. The media, with exceptions, is in the tank for Obama and the news coverage has been and will be carefully calculated so as to increase the likelihood of Obama’s reelection. The clearest recent example is, of course, the lack of coverage of Obama’s malfeasance in the Benghazi situation. There’s a cover-up going on. A massive cover-up. Simply put, the documents now exist to show that Obama knew the security situation at the consulate was deteriorating. He new that additional security was being requested and denied. He knew al Qaeda was threatening to attack American interests in Libya. He knew the attack was underway within two hours. He denied the men under attack additional protection from US forces. He knew Ansar al Sharia, an al Qaeda offshoot was responsible. He knew our Ambassador was missing. He denied these Americans protection. They died. He blamed it on a video, and went to Las Vegas. You will only know the full story if you watch the hated (by the left) Fox News Channel. Another example? Let’s look at our economy. There’s a very interesting comparison of media coverage of our economy as George H.W. Bush was locked in a battle for reelection with Bill Clinton, and the current situation with Obama, a Democrat, locked in a reelection battle with Mitt Romney. We have just seen the data for economic growth in the 3rd quarter of 2012. We have similar data for the Bush 41. Here you go: Obama’s 3rd quarter election year GDP 2.0% Bush’s 3rd quarter election year GDP 2.7% Got that? The economy was growing 30% faster in Bush’s final year than it is now for Obama. So let’s look at the headlines in The New York Times for the stories detailing these GDP numbers. First … October 29, 1992. The GDP had nearly doubled to 2.7%: “GROSS NATIONAL LETDOWN” Now, last Sunday’s NYT headline on Obama’s 2.0% increase in GDP: “SLOW BUT STEADY IMPROVEMENT” Any questions? The bias is clear; and the bias exists because the media needs cover. They promoted this Obama guy right into office without any vetting. Now they realize what an abysmal failure he is, but they have to work hard for his reelection if for no other reason than to save face. The defeat of Obama would be a huge embarrassment to the national media that worked so hard to put him in office. The media would be discredited. They can’t allow that to happen. Let the bias and the hype continue. The media will pay in terms of public trust … but their man has to be reelected. NBN</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351773758279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 08:42:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351774223904-17</Id><Title>Children of the Future - Don't blame Us - you voted for Obama and Democrats</Title><Msg>Our on-coming spending, debt and entitlement crisis is the most predictable crisis in our history. If you want to understand why I think America may be screwed, consider how we tackle the following issues and which leaders will do a better job of merely mitigating the eventual disaster … The average American household’s share of federal spending is $29,691, roughly two-thirds of median household income. Federal entitlements are driving this spending growth, having increased from less than half of total federal outlays just 20 years ago to nearly 62 percent in 2012. For every $6.80 the federal government collected in taxes in 2012, it spent $10. Consequently, $3.20 out of every $10 spent was borrowed. The big three entitlements alone will absorb all tax revenues by 2048. Other spending, such as national defense or interest on the debt would have to be financed completely on borrowed money. In fiscal year 2012, Washington spent $88 billion on K–12 and vocational education, nearly triple the amount of just 10 years ago, after adjusting for inflation. Yet these huge infusions of federal funds to these state and local priorities have failed to improve educational performance. The 2012 deficit was an estimated 7.3 percent of GDP; the historical average is 2.1 percent of GDP. If current policies continue, debt held by the public will approach 90 percent of total economic output by 2022, and will be twice the size of the entire economy 25 years from now. Those are just handful of just jaw-dropping statistics from the Heritage Foundation’s Federal Spending by the Numbers – 2012. We cannot continue to elect people who believe that America’s true greatness comes from government spending, as Barack Obama has explicitly told us. It is quite the opposite …government spending is stripping America of its greatness by creating a nation of dependents and sucking dry the producers.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351774223904</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 08:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351774416475-18</Id><Title>Anyone Know Why Democraqts are Terrified of Voting on a Budget?</Title><Msg>I don't either.........maybe it's because they think budgets are too restricting. I would never vote for anyone in a party that refused to pass a budget.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351774416475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 08:53:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351774642568-19</Id><Title>Obama's Second Term</Title><Msg>What is Obama going to do more of, if he is re-elected next week? His chief advisor Valerie “ready to rule from day one” Jarrett says that Obama will “spend a lot more time traveling around the country.” Why? To keep people engaged … oh and to hold Congress accountable. Wait, what? Yup, looks like the Obama administration is already showing its cards for his (God forbid) next term. Obama’s plan will be to blame Congress. Wow, now there’s presidential leadership! Four more years! Doesn’t matter though. Moochers, parasites and leaches don’t care how much he travels; just as long as their checks keep coming.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351774642568</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 08:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351775341025-20</Id><Title>We Need Obama 4 More Years</Title><Msg>These states hard hit by Hurricane Sandy look like bombed out Europe after WW II. They will need more government help not less. Romney stands for less government help, Obama for more. In fact, these states in my opinion need a Marshall Plan for recovery. That is why in these hard times we need to re-elect Obama President. True, I support alot of Romney plans for this country. But the reality is we can't let the business savvy prosper and leave the rest of the nation beyond. We are all on one ship America, and when those on the bottom are sinking we must all lend a hand because Hurricane Sandy can come to us all.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351775341025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:09:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351776098661-21</Id><Title>Cable Shows Benghazi Consulate Not Prepared for Coordinated Attack</Title><Msg>Fox News is reporting today about a newly obtained cable showing even more damning information about the situation in Benghazi, Libya just ahead of the terrorist attack on 9/11 which left U.S. Ambassador Chris Stevens and three other Americans dead. The cable shows there was a clear concern for safety and the developing dangers of al Qaeda in the city just before the attack occurred. An emergency meeting to discuss al Qaeda's growing presence in Benghazi was held a month before the attack and it was determined the U.S. consulate could not withstand a coordinated attack should one occur. The emergency meeting came months after multiple security requests were made and denied by the State Department. Summarizing an Aug. 15 emergency meeting convened by the U.S. Mission in Benghazi, the Aug. 16 cable marked “SECRET” said that the State Department’s senior security officer, also known as the RSO, did not believe the consulate could be protected. “RSO (Regional Security Officer) expressed concerns with the ability to defend Post in the event of a coordinated attack due to limited manpower, security measures, weapons capabilities, host nation support, and the overall size of the compound,” the cable said. According to a review of the cable addressed to the Office of the Secretary of State Hillary Clinton, the Emergency Action Committee was also briefed "on the location of approximately ten Islamist militias and AQ training camps within Benghazi … these groups ran the spectrum from Islamist militias, such as the QRF Brigade and Ansar al-Sharia, to ‘Takfirist thugs.’” Each U.S. mission has a so-called Emergency Action Committee that is responsible for security measures and emergency planning. The details in the cable seemed to foreshadow the deadly Sept. 11 attack on the U.S. compound, which was a coordinated, commando-style assault using direct and indirect fire. Al Qaeda in North Africa and Ansar al-Sharia, both mentioned in the cable, have since been implicated in the consulate attack. In addition to describing the security situation in Benghazi as “trending negatively,” the cable said explicitly that the mission would ask for more help. “In light of the uncertain security environment, US Mission Benghazi will submit specific requests to US Embassy Tripoli for additional physical security upgrades and staffing needs by separate cover.” One thing is very clear: The State Department knew their personnel was in imminent danger from al Qaeda and they did nothing to protect them. The cable further dismantles the administration's bogus YouTube video argument. While the administration’s public statements have suggested that the attack came without warning, the Aug. 16 cable seems to undercut those claims. It was a direct warning to the State Department that the Benghazi consulate was vulnerable to attack, that it could not be defended and that the presence of anti-U.S. militias and Al Qaeda was well-known to the U.S. intelligence community. In a three-page cable on Sept 11, the day Stevens and the three other Americans were killed, Stevens wrote about “growing problems with security” in Benghazi and “growing frustration” with the security forces and Libyan police. The ambassador saw both as “too weak to keep the country secure.” Our men were left there to die.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351776098661</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351776292466-22</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm begining to wonder if Obama has an allergy to the truth.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351776292466</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:24:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351776418001-23</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Allergy to the truth. I think Mitt Romney has that title locked up for all time. No one has ever contradicted themselves with the volume and speed that he has. I am sure in your non-real world you are now outraged, FAUX outrage is why FAUX news has an audience.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1351776418001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:26:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351776423938-24</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now we got a number of states near devastation. It was the President who thoughtfully took the time to visit and lead a team to organize disaster relief. Did Romney stop everything to talk with the experts on what is needed for states including New York, New Jersey and Conn. No he thinks a food and clothing drive is enough and continues with his campaigning. Romney does not have a handle on the real problems of our country. His "let them eat cake" does not cut it.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351776423938</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:27:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351776551711-25</Id><Title>White House Silent as Benghazi Questions Mount</Title><Msg>Last week, we alerted you to the infuriating, heart-wrenching revelation that at least three specific requests for military help from besieged Americans in Benghazi were rejected by someone in the chain of command. This decision was made despite the established fact that US officials in Tripoli, the State Department, the Pentagon and the White House were watching the horror unfold in real time, via a video feed from an unmanned drone hovering over the city. Democrats won't say if that drone was armed (and therefore capable of raining fire on the terrorists who were attacking our men and women). Why were these reinforcements refused, who specifically did the refusing, and where was the president throughout this process? These are questions being asked by US Senators, and political commentators from across the ideological spectrum. We've gotten a few answers so far. David Petraeus has emphatically denied that the CIA made this call. President Obama's Defense Secretary has hinted that the Pentagon was involved in the decision. The White House? Silence:</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351776551711</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:29:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351776728224-26</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Versus the Automakers</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351761544955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 05:19:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is disgusting when a (pseudo) religious candidate brays a giant and filthy lie, then doubles down when publicly called on it. This Jeep business should make all Americans sick. Willard will say any thing at any time to any group on any subject, regardless of what he said yesterday and regardless of the facts. Willard knows he is telling a giant whopper here. He does know that that without Ohio, he's done so the lies come at the speed of talk.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1351776728224</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:32:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351776775043-27</Id><Title>Mitt or Barack?</Title><Msg>Tell me if you hate to watch reruns or you always try a new menu every time you eat out and I will tell you who you are voting for.</Msg><Username>zosimomaximo</Username><Timestamp>1351776775043</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:32:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351776791064-28</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumbocrats are funny......there are actually hundreds of videos showing Obama lying......you would think that if Romney is the liar they could come up with at least on video of him lying.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351776791064</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:33:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351777590997-29</Id><Title>Women claim Sen. Bob Menendez [D-NJ] paid for sex in Dominican Republic...</Title><Msg>"Two women from the Dominican Republic told The Daily Caller that Democratic New Jersey Sen. Bob Menendez paid them for sex earlier this year. In interviews, the two women said they met Menendez around Easter at Casa de Campo, an expensive 7,000 acre resort in the Dominican Republic. They claimed Menendez agreed to pay them $500 for sex acts, but in the end they each received only $100. The women spoke through a translator in the company of their attorney, Melanio Figueroa. Both asked that their identities remain obscured for fear of reprisals in the Dominican Republic. When shown a photograph of Sen. Menendez, the women said they recognized him as the man with whom they’d had sexual relations at Casa de Campo this spring. Both said they were brought to the resort with the understanding they would be paid for sex. Neither knew the identity of the man at the time. Both claimed to recognize him later as Sen. Menendez. “He called him[self] ‘Bob,’” said one. One woman said Menendez wooed her with compliments like “beautiful” before they slept together. The other woman recounted, with apparent bitterness, receiving from an intermediary only $100 of the $500 she had been promised. “He lies,” she said of Menendez. “He says one thing and does another.” What did these these women expect......for God's sake the man IS a Democrat.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351777590997</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:46:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351777904300-30</Id><Title>Democrats Already Cheating - Program Voting machines</Title><Msg>Voting machine swaps Obama for Romney MARION — Joan Stevens was one of several early voters at the polls on Monday. But when Stevens tried to cast her ballot for president, she noticed a problem. Upon selecting “Mitt Romney” on the electronic touch screen, Barack Obama’s name lit up. It took Stevens three tries before her selection was accurately recorded. “You want to vote for who you want to vote for, and when you can’t it’s irritating,” Stevens said. Stevens said she alerted Jackie Smith, a board of elections member who was present. Smith declined to comment, but Stevens says she mentioned that the machine had been having problems all day. Stevens also reported the issue to Sophia Rogers, the director of the board of elections for Marion County.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351777904300</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:51:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351777992887-31</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forget Benghazi, mistakes were made during the immediate crisis on the other side of the world. There will be plenty of investigation so these mistakes can be avoided in the future. What is more important now is the largest disaster to the nation ever. New Jersey, NY are national disaster areas. Hurricane Sandy, except for the loss of life, has done more damage and is affecting badly more lives than 9/11. The initial estimates of damage range around 50 billion. Which Presidential candidate is more prone to help the disaster states recover. The answer is the one who cares more about these states, who believes it is the role of government to help these states recover and that man is President Barack H. Obama.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351777992887</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:53:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351778113399-32</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Versus the Automakers</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351761544955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 05:19:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>err 50,000 million, which approximates the amount required to cleanup after Sandy poof gone ahkmed, err sparty, supports our lawless looter n chief and his party of death of theft</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1351778113399</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:55:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351778307926-33</Id><Title>'Hurricane Sandy Has Already Created More Jobs Than Obama Has'...</Title><Msg>......Obama is not interested in creating jobs nor does he know how.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351778307926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:58:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351778458609-34</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical of the "new" GOP, double down on your lying. There are not hundreds of video showing Obama lying, there are tons of videos where Mitt lies (I was not against the bailout, I want to privatize FEMA, his current ads about Chrysler and GM). Even better there are tons of videos where other Repubs call him liar (specifically Newt used that exact word). Truth is like science and math in the GOP world, something to be scorned and dismissed because it interferes with their party line. Much like the Taliban or Iran's government.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1351778458609</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351778966082-35</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>our coward n chief deserted heros in their time of need freedumber, chrissie or spart, inquiring minds wanna know which enemy useful idiot?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1351778966082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351779221736-36</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, kind of like Bush huh?</Msg><Username>romannorga</Username><Timestamp>1351779221736</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351779377607-37</Id><Title>Fox news keeps republicans ignorant.</Title><Msg>Fox news keeps republicans mis informed. Half truths is the same as a lie. Canada won't allow fox news to air on tv. Google it.</Msg><Username>romannorga</Username><Timestamp>1351779377607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:16:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351779411954-38</Id><Title>Benghazi - It Smelly Velly, Velly Fishy</Title><Msg>Why Obumer spike Ben Laden ball over over and over and over and over again after he say "We no spike the ball." Then turn silent like dummy with no ventriloquist over Benghazi.</Msg><Username>chinamanpro</Username><Timestamp>1351779411954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:16:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351779659655-39</Id><Topic><Title>Election over. Romney wins big.</Title><Username>locost7777</Username><Timestamp>1351778300291</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:58:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney has no chance now. More likely an Electoral Landslide for Obama. Back to Bain Capital for Mitt</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1351779659655</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:20:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351779786116-40</Id><Title>Obama more likey Mao than American U.S. president</Title><Msg>He likey communism more than freedom. Velly, velly confused man. Only thing confuse him more than than Father's Day is how to be Commander in Chief. Maybe he need start with basics like how to pronounce "corpsman" yuk, yuk yuk.</Msg><Username>chinamanpro</Username><Timestamp>1351779786116</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:23:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351780056270-41</Id><Topic><Title>Fox news keeps republicans ignorant.</Title><Username>romannorga</Username><Timestamp>1351779377607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:16:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Fox news keeps republicans mis informed." Not true. Fox news keeps republicans only somewhat misinformed whereas NBC, CNN, MSNBC, NPR, NYT, WA POST, PBS, etc. keep EVERYONE substantially misinformed about the realities of the world, letting only their skewed views get through their socialistic filters.</Msg><Username>dm60010</Username><Timestamp>1351780056270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:27:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351780209614-42</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - It Smelly Velly, Velly Fishy</Title><Username>chinamanpro</Username><Timestamp>1351779411954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:16:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Silent is what you were while thousands of Americans were killed under Bush</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351780209614</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:30:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351780635188-43</Id><Topic><Title>Fox news keeps republicans ignorant.</Title><Username>romannorga</Username><Timestamp>1351779377607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:16:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spot on, DM, spot on. Fox is where you get the truth.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1351780635188</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351780653549-44</Id><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Msg>stoning and crucifixion to follow...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351780683164-45</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - It Smelly Velly, Velly Fishy</Title><Username>chinamanpro</Username><Timestamp>1351779411954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:16:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rockstar80333 ....you velly wacky man.....silent is what you Dumbocrats were while hundreds of thousands of Americans were being killed under FDR.</Msg><Username>chinamanpro</Username><Timestamp>1351780683164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:38:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351781099908-46</Id><Title>Pew: Yup, Romney's Leading Velly, velley Big in Early Voting</Title><Msg>"In the poll, conducted Oct. 24-28, 19% of likely voters say they have already voted; that is unchanged from the same week in the 2008 campaign (Oct. 23-26, 2008). Currently, Romney holds a seven-point edge among early voters (50% to 43%); because of the small sample, this lead is not statistically significant. At this point four years ago, Obama led John McCain by 19 points (53% to 34%) among early voters." Yuk, yuk, yuk.</Msg><Username>chinamanpro</Username><Timestamp>1351781099908</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351781345256-47</Id><Topic><Title>NATE SILVER: Obama's Odds Of Winning Have Now Hit 79%</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351770783612</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 07:53:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The polls were taken before Sandy. High ranking repubs have given the President high marks for handling the situation in a Presidential, decisive leadership manner. Sandy has given Willard a major headache. Willard and his worshipful followers are desperate and flailing about, trying to distract They are pathetic. eh!</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1351781345256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:49:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351781464069-48</Id><Topic><Title>Mitts odds of losing increase!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351692553621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:09:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it keeps getting better</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351781464069</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:51:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351782096731-49</Id><Title>Willard Flip-Flops on FEMA</Title><Msg>After vociferously saying he would kill FEMA Willard has now shifted with the wind and says he didn't mean it. Send flipper back to Sea World!</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1351782096731</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:01:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351782319851-50</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Dick Hertz...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351780897115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:41:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, We Know You are a Nitwit....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351782319851</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:05:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351782975454-51</Id><Topic><Title>Election over. Romney wins big.</Title><Username>locost7777</Username><Timestamp>1351778300291</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:58:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>=... no message, no agenda and not even much of an explanation for what he has done over the past four years.= Check my post at Nov 1, 2012 3:06 AM. Nothing you say contains even a particle of truth.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351782975454</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:16:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351782975638-52</Id><Topic><Title>Nate Silver Just Offered Joe Scarborough An Election Wager For The Ages</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351771087808</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 07:58:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey willard., I'll bet you $10,000 you lose</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1351782975638</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:16:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351783036399-53</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Already Cheating - Program Voting machines</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1351777904300</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:51:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cry us a river...</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351783036399</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:17:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351783375333-54</Id><Topic><Title>Willard Flip-Flops on FEMA</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1351782096731</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:01:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I stand by what I said, whatever it was." - Willard</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1351783375333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:22:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351783443838-55</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Dick Hertz...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351780897115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:41:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you campaigning for a war criminal? Have y9u no sense of decency, sir?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351783443838</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:24:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351783515640-56</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351781487217</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:51:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People who like people who like war crimes. There's your Democratic party.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351783515640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:25:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351783660747-57</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh so suddenly when his ox gets gored, phantom goes socialist.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351783660747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:27:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351783711554-58</Id><Topic><Title>NATE SILVER: Obama's Odds Of Winning Have Now Hit 79%</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351770783612</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 07:53:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This morning Nate Silver raised President Obama to over 300 electoral votes. That last debate really sank Willards ship.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1351783711554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:28:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351784005790-59</Id><Topic><Title>Fox news keeps republicans ignorant.</Title><Username>romannorga</Username><Timestamp>1351779377607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:16:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You truly are very mis informed. Go back and call rush limbaugh, he'll get ya going the wrong way. He's the worst thing in the republican party. The most hateful man in America.</Msg><Username>romannorga</Username><Timestamp>1351784005790</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:33:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351784110463-60</Id><Topic><Title>Nate Silver Just Offered Joe Scarborough An Election Wager For The Ages</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351771087808</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 07:58:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll raise it $100,000.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1351784110463</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:35:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351784462919-61</Id><Topic><Title>Fox news keeps republicans ignorant.</Title><Username>romannorga</Username><Timestamp>1351779377607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:16:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Canada thing is not true and never has been.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1351784462919</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:41:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351784511180-62</Id><Topic><Title>We Need Obama 4 More Years</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351775341025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:09:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shouldn't our tax dollars pitch in to help states like New Jersey, NY and Conn recover from the worst natural disaster that has hit our nation. President Obama thinks so and so do I.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351784511180</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:41:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351784771868-63</Id><Topic><Title>We Need Obama 4 More Years</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351775341025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:09:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do too, phantomfield.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1351784771868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351785081150-64</Id><Title>No Matter How Much You Shakey, Kicky and Dancey,,,,,,,,</Title><Msg>Obumer and his commie minions are on their way out. This is America.....if you want commie government.....plenty of other countries to go to. If you likey freedom vote Obumer out of office.</Msg><Username>chinamanpro</Username><Timestamp>1351785081150</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:51:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351785622719-65</Id><Title>Hi! I Chinaman pro.</Title><Msg>I No likey Dumbocrats and Obumer. Mitt Romney will win cuz still more Americans likey freedom and U.S. constitution than like socialist/commie government likey Obumer want. But I gotta admit, still alotta stupid blind people who no can see commie policies like Obummer's. If Obumer ever had to actually work for living he might learn something.</Msg><Username>chinamanpro</Username><Timestamp>1351785622719</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:00:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351785945286-66</Id><Title>New Chrysler cars named after Mitt Romney!</Title><Msg>Jeep Binder Double Down Dodge Chrysler 47 PT Loser</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351785945286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351785975836-67</Id><Title>I feely Sorry for Dick Hertz</Title><Msg>....he sound likey he velly, vellly gay guy.....prolly grow up but never able grow a pair.</Msg><Username>chinamanpro</Username><Timestamp>1351785975836</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:06:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351786079782-68</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is it that you think Obama has done? Basically, Mr. Eye Candy has made a few photo ops and written some checks. He did not hold back the oceans, the main destructive force of Sandy, as he had promised resulting from when he got elected: "This was the moment when the rise of the oceans began to slow, and our planet began to heal." He was pompous back then and he is pompous now. In four years he will continue to be pompous. The question is do the voters want the same pompous windbag as President or an experienced and successful leader, manager and businessman who knows how to make things happen? Obama out - Romney in.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351786079782</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:07:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351786100540-69</Id><Title>Economy is doing great under Obama</Title><Msg>I don't trust Romney with my pension</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351786100540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:08:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351786298802-70</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - It Smelly Velly, Velly Fishy</Title><Username>chinamanpro</Username><Timestamp>1351779411954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:16:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whatever happened 60 years ago is not even part of of the topic and if you were around than most likely you would of supported it! now back to the thousands killed under Bush , why don`t you folks scream and yell as much about the thousands killed during his 8 years instead of turning 4 guys killed by terrorist in Libya into a political issue , pretty flipping disturbing and unpatriotic in my book.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351786298802</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:11:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351786443519-71</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>businessman, could you name a businessman who has been a successful President in the history of the US?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351786443519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:14:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351786508834-72</Id><Topic><Title>Economy is doing great under Obama</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351786100540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:08:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Un-Employment Numbers to be Released Tomorrow Will Disappoint ... Fair Math has The Rate Up to 7.9 or 8.0... Yep, Obama's Economy is Doing Just "Fine"</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351786508834</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:15:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351787112092-73</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice try, but those were not mistakes. They were purposeful actions take by Obama that made the Libyan personnel vulnerable. The real question is why did he want to do that. The possibilities are endless.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1351787112092</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351787329510-74</Id><Topic><Title>Economy is doing great under Obama</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351786100540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:08:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, The economy is doing just fine in China. Here in the US it's not so good.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1351787329510</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351787514324-75</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The president and his entourage did nothing by going to New Jersey except to get in the way. It was a photo op.........nothing more.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351787514324</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:31:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351787525642-76</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only faux-noise dittoheaded repugs try to politicize Benghazi, same for global climate change... they are truly twisted</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1351787525642</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:32:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351787709536-77</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"could you name a businessman who has been a successful President in the history of the US?" Let's say that I cannot. But the founding fathers were not only lawyers, they consisted also of businessmen. Now, let's look at Romney: in addition to being a successful Governor, he was manager of the 2002 Winter Olympics and a corporate leader. In the cases of Gov. of Massachusetts and Manager of the Olympics, he presided over elimination and resolution of deficits and debts. As a businessman, despite all of the negative commentary, that has also been preeminently successful, creating personal wealth that is reported to be $250 million. Obama made a few million dollars on his books about himself. Obama came into office having done NOTHING in his entire career. And, he has done nothing positive since he has been in office - save for the over stated killing of bin Laden. Let's kick him out and give him a plaque for that and call it even. The American public owes this man nothing.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351787709536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:35:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351787953860-78</Id><Topic><Title>Fox news keeps republicans ignorant.</Title><Username>romannorga</Username><Timestamp>1351779377607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:16:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fox is where you get the truth, like Chrysler is moving JEEP to China because of Obama...hahaha, only a complete dolt would say that, or believe it... in other words Mittens and all his dittoheaded dunderhead Fuax Noise supporters</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1351787953860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:39:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351788038369-79</Id><Title>ELEVATOR SHOES FOR ALL 787 MANAGERS!!!!</Title><Msg>That is the Rumour!!!!!</Msg><Username>caveman2501</Username><Timestamp>1351788038369</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:40:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351788110033-80</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama and his Administration have Been Caught in Documented Lies and is Struggling to Come Clean! Their Latest Answer to the Press on this Subject Is a Terse "No Comment" What is Obama Hiding from the American People?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351788110033</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:41:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351788190946-81</Id><Topic><Title>New Chrysler cars named after Mitt Romney!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351785945286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yugo broke</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1351788190946</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351788197600-82</Id><Topic><Title>New Chrysler cars named after Mitt Romney!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351785945286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's the new Chevy model... the GOP ' God Intended ' ask Richard Mourdock for a test drive !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351788197600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:43:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351788408783-83</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reason that the conservatives and other seekers of truth desire to highlight what happened at Benghazi NOW is that, after 6 November, it will be too late to hand Obama his pink slip. What will likely happen after Nov 6, should this man continue to occupy the White House, is that he will be impeached. The Republicans are likely to maintain control of the House and they do the impeaching. It will happen, you can plan on it. If the Senate is maintained by the Democrats, that may end the process - unless some Democrats come to their senses, but Obama will be a lame duck at the START of his second term.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351788408783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351788656499-84</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bb - you sound so desperate !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351788656499</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:50:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351788711393-85</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps they could be like a wimpy repug... who claim it's not a lie if you believe it was true,,, not in our wildest dreams did we ever think that they would use the rioting over the anti-isalm video as a ruse to hastily organize an attack of our consualte on the anniversary of 9/11...and it would be true,,,, because ambassador stevens would not have gone there... Only wimps and repugs try tp politicize Benghazi, global climate change (100 year storms every other year now says the governor of NY), and relief aid to massive disaster areas...</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1351788711393</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351788949509-86</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you are such seekers of truth why do you buy the GOP garbage lies so easily?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351788949509</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:55:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351788972606-87</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where were his waders , bullhorn, and Mission Accomplished banner like duhbya, or his stack of spam cans like Willtard... sorry, but Obama very presidential, and assurative...to those suffering and in need... even the R blimp Christie praised him highly</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1351788972606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:56:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351789079759-88</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I businessman and his policies created the Great depression 90 years ago Carter was a Business man too along with Bush and we know how Successful they were as Presidents , Romeny will be like Failure on steroids</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351789079759</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:57:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351789602909-89</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, the Repugnantcons are known for reducing the extreme measure of impeachment to a cheap political trick. Someone should shove your religious pomposity up your ...</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351789602909</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 13:06:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351789867002-90</Id><Topic><Title>Answer the quesions Mr. President</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351775698977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:14:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing more than concern for storm victims. The presidency is SUPPOSED to be a bully pulpit, remember? Like Saint Ronald said. Which commander in chief sent three naval vessels to the area to act as floating helicopter operations centers? You DO remember helicopters, don't you?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351789867002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 13:11:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351789894358-91</Id><Topic><Title>New Chrysler cars named after Mitt Romney!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351785945286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe Isuzu, an amusingly upbeat liar/former spokesperson for Japanese car mfger Isuzu, making ever-more mendacious claims about Isuzu vehicles and capping them off with the tagline "You have my word on it." endorses Rawmoney.</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1351789894358</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 13:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351790279655-92</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hopefully Lyin' Ryan will lose his house seat along with losing his Rawmoney ticket spot. These holier-than-thou religious zealot liars and hypocrites must go! Madchelle Bachmann getting the boot by voters too!</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1351790279655</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 13:17:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351790629077-93</Id><Topic><Title>27839913</Title><Username>locost7777</Username><Timestamp>1351782831814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The desperation of the ultra-right is getting just comical at this point.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351790629077</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 13:23:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351790997969-94</Id><Topic><Title>Media Bias Intensifying</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351773758279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 08:42:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big talk from a message board hate-monger.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351790997969</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 13:29:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351791128586-95</Id><Topic><Title>"Storm Surge" -- LOL</Title><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351754184106</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 03:16:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're MUCH funnier when you're simply irrelevant than when you let your rage consume you.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351791128586</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 13:32:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351793064346-96</Id><Title>Let's hear it for ...</Title><Msg>... a commander in chief who isn't satisfied to just fly over and look down at the disaster. Let's hear it for Obama, who appeared for what fish brains calls a "Photo Op" with Chris Christie. How unlike Romney's "Photo Op" of accepting canned goods he bought from "concerned Repugnantcons" so he could ship them to "New Jersey, I think it was" where the American Red Cross, (who can't afford the time it would take to organize and distribute them) will direct them to the nearest open food bank -- before they get on with actually HELPING people.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351793064346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351793754551-97</Id><Title>‘GOP bloodlust’ over Benghazi</Title><Msg>Geraldo Rivera slammed the politicization of the attack in Benghazi, firing off a series of tweets while hunkered down at home in Edgewater, N.J., during Hurricane Sandy. Rivera, the Fox News contributor and "Geraldo at Large" host, criticized the controversy being pushed by some conservatives. It's "clear no C130 gunships were available," Rivera tweeted. "Criticize coverup [but] saying White House watched [and] did nothing to help is a lie." Rivera called the "GOP bloodlust" surrounding the Obama administration's handling of Libya "insincere," "desperate" and reminiscent of the political firestorm surrounding the "Fast and Furious" gun-walking scandal that rocked the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives in 2011. The "real" question regarding Benghazi, Rivera tweeted, is this: "Did Obama spin to retain Bin Laden killer mystique?" To suggest the four U.S. consulate workers killed in Benghazi "could have been saved," Rivera added, is a "cruel myth."</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351793754551</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:15:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351793919416-98</Id><Topic><Title>Media Bias Intensifying</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351773758279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 08:42:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow............a whole story based on the concrete evidence of "I was talking with a former newsman yesterday – a news director and news anchor." Well I talked to God yesterday and he said Obama will be president for another term. So there!!!!!!</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351793919416</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:18:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351793968100-99</Id><Topic><Title>Let's hear it for ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351793064346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am with you on this Chris. hip hip hooray</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1351793968100</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:19:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351794613280-100</Id><Topic><Title>We Need Obama 4 More Years</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1351775341025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:09:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When the money starts flowing for disaster releif i'll beleive it...You can't even get gas in NJ..</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1351794613280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:30:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351795839317-101</Id><Topic><Title>Let's hear it for ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351793064346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hear Hear!!!</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1351795839317</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:50:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351796049211-102</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd gladly help with that!</Msg><Username>barking_dogmas</Username><Timestamp>1351796049211</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:54:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351796168053-103</Id><Topic><Title>Early voting</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351795789102</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:49:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Man the Repukes are smoking some serious weed! LMAO</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1351796168053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:56:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351796195182-104</Id><Topic><Title>Let's hear it for ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351793064346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aye! Governor Christie's nice words to Obama was the kiss of death for romney's grand campaign. I can imagine the fury in the romney camp! Kamakure</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351796195182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351796387703-105</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HMMM CNN REPORTS On Friday, President Obama was asked directly by Denver's KUSA-TV's Kyle Clarke whether our forces were denied backup during the attack. The president dodged the first question. Clark followed up, "Were they denied requests for help during the attack?" "Well, we are finding out exactly what happened," the president responded. "I can tell you, as I've said over the last couple of months since this happened, the minute I found out what was happening, I gave three very clear directives. Number one, make sure that we are securing our personnel and doing whatever we need to." This is different from what the president said in his Rose Garden speech on September 12, when he mentioned nothing about securing personnel the evening of the attack, or what he said to "The View" or Univision in the weeks after the attack. GOES ON</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1351796387703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:59:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351796701772-106</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>COMMENT BY MYSELF IF oBUMa gave such an order as he claims- then panetta and a few generals are lying when they said they did not respond cuz they were not sure what was happening Or do you believe that when the CIC gives such an order- the military- cia- state dept says well we dont think we should do that- so we will just watch as oBUMa goes to bed for his big day in vegas ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1351796701772</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:05:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351796828203-107</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351781487217</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:51:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's drone strikes kill women and children in countries with which we are not at war. He's claiming the right to kill anyone, anywhere, any time, for any reason or no reason--even American citizens. He bombs a house and then half an hour later he bombs it again to kill the rescue workers. He's a war criminal and he should be in jail.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351796828203</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:07:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351798317024-108</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shakey, Kicky and Dancey,,,,,,,,</Title><Username>chinamanpro</Username><Timestamp>1351785081150</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:51:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go Chinaman go! Go like a pro!</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351798317024</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:31:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351798519728-109</Id><Title>Uh O......OHIO: R 49% O 46%...</Title><Msg>GOP pollster: Romney up in Ohio, closing the gap in Wisconsin By Cameron Joseph - 11/01/12 12:29 PM ET Mitt Romney has the lead in Ohio and trails narrowly in Wisconsin, according to a new poll for the group Citizens United. Romney leads Obama by 49 to 46 percent in Ohio, according to the poll, and trails Obama in Wisconsin by 49 to 47 percent, according to polling first obtained by The Hill. Partisan polls should be viewed with some skepticism, and both polls put Romney in a better position than most publicly available data has shown. Obama has a small but steady lead in most Ohio polls, and a slightly wider lead in Wisconsin. The polls also show Senate GOP candidates in better shape in the two states than recent public polling has suggested. Ohio state Treasurer Josh Mandel (R) leads Sen. Sherrod Brown (D-Ohio) by 50 to 45 percent in the poll, and former Wisconsin Gov. Tommy Thompson (R) edges Rep. Tammy Baldwin (D-Wis.) by 47 to 45 percent. Recent public polling has shown Brown with a comfortable lead and Baldwin holding a narrow lead over Thompson.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351798519728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:35:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351799153386-110</Id><Topic><Title>Uh O......OHIO: R 49% O 46%...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351798519728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:35:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nm</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1351799153386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:45:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351799345131-111</Id><Topic><Title>Uh O......OHIO: R 49% O 46%...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351798519728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:35:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A "GOP Pollster" Yeah, that's credible when no other polls agree with it. Enjoy fantasy land.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1351799345131</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:49:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351799671742-112</Id><Topic><Title>Uh O......OHIO: R 49% O 46%...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351798519728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:35:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harrydope, The usual lies and #$%$ from the idiot corner. Name one thing Obama has done, or has said he would do, to limit gun rights or ownership. He got an F from the Brady Center numbnuts. Just of one the multitude of GOP lies, it's what they do because believing in facts, science, or math will get you called a RINO.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1351799671742</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:54:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351799762264-113</Id><Topic><Title>Uh O......OHIO: R 49% O 46%...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351798519728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:35:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do you get this crap? No matter who wins, nobdy is going to take any guns away unless maybe someone is mentally unstable - which is probably what you're afraid of.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1351799762264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:56:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351799885490-114</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the past two years, House Republicans have continued to deprioritize the security forces protecting State Department personnel around the world. In fiscal year 2011, lawmakers shaved $128 million off of the administration's request for embassy security funding. House Republicans drained off even more funds in fiscal year 2012 -- cutting back on the department's request by $331 million.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1351799885490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:58:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351800257439-115</Id><Title>Obama Still Lying to America Again About al Qaeda</Title><Msg>At a campaign event today in Wisconsin, President Obama once again misled the country about the status of the terrorist group al Qaeda. "Al Qaeda has been decimated," he said to the crowd. This statement is simply not true. Recently, "al Qaeda is on the run" was dropped from Obama's campaign trail stump speeches due to the fallout over the 9/11 attack in Benghazi which was carried out by al Qaeda terrorists. That move by the campaign doesn't change the fact that al Qaeda has not been "decimated" and is not "on the run" as President Obama suggested to the American people for months. In Libya alone, al Qaeda has had a strong presence, especially in the Benghazi area, since the beginning of this year. Congressional testimony given by State Department officials both on the ground in Libya and in Washington revealed U.S. Ambassador Chris Stevens and other officials repeatedly requested more security for the consulate in Benghazi and all of their requests were denied. In July, Stevens received a death threat from al Qaeda on Facebook and even sent a request for more security on 9/11, the day he was killed. While the State Department denied more security, they did increase the amount of "hardship" pay officials in Benghazi received.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351800257439</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351800586132-116</Id><Title>Will We Still Have Time to Impeach Obama</Title><Msg>after Obama loses the election will there be enough time to impeach him before we send him packing back to Chicago in January?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351800586132</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:09:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351800717450-117</Id><Title>Campaigning Much More important to Obama than doing his job.</Title><Msg>.....he's stopped playing golf to campaign.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351800717450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:11:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351802350260-118</Id><Topic><Title>Will We Still Have Time to Impeach Obama</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351800586132</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:09:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Daniel Ellsberg says Obama deserves to be impeached.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351802350260</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:39:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351802422616-119</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Dick Hertz...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351780897115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:41:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you campaigning for a war criminal? Have you no sense of decency, sir?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351802422616</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:40:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351802986666-120</Id><Topic><Title>UAW Charges Romney With Profiteering From Auto Bailout</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351802320423</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a Bunch of Union BS.... More of Dik's Blue Nonsense, eh?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351802986666</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:49:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351803395228-121</Id><Title>Anger Building in NYC... Obama's Katrina, eh?</Title><Msg>Nerves are Fraying... Fights and Rioting next. Blue State Libs Will be Out of Control by this Weekend!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351803395228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351804240284-122</Id><Title>GOP Suppress Congressional Research Service Report. Summary: "Tax cuts don't work"</Title><Msg>"The results of the analysis suggest that changes over the past 65 years in the top marginal tax rate and the top capital gains tax rate do not appear correlated with economic growth. The reduction in the top tax rates appears to be uncorrelated with saving, investment, and productivity growth. The top tax rates appear to have little or no relation to the size of the economic pie. However, the top tax rate reductions appear to be associated with the increasing concentration of income at the top of the income distribution. As measured by IRS data, the share of income accruing to the top 0.1% of U.S. families increased from 4.2% in 1945 to 12.3% by 2007 before falling to 9.2% due to the 2007-2009 recession. At the same time, the average tax rate paid by the top 0.1% fell from over 50% in 1945 to about 25% in 2009. Tax policy could have a relation to how the economic pie is sliced—lower top tax rates may be associated with greater income disparities."</Msg><Username>windyhorn</Username><Timestamp>1351804240284</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:10:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351804263066-123</Id><Topic><Title>Anger Building in NYC... Obama's Katrina, eh?</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351803395228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:56:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More fabrication. GOP Gov. of NJ and mayor of NY both say different, publicly and adamantly. Let's see, who should we believe, the GOP elected leaders or the liar and idiot who calls himself imaccon. Tough call, if your IQ is in single digits. Easy call if you are smarter than that.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1351804263066</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:11:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351804537633-124</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351781487217</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:51:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It sounds as if you are on the side of the terrorists. Freedom, security, liberty, and even justice all have costs. Obama is one of the good guys. Perhaps your so-called 'innocents' should not hang around with the bad guys.</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1351804537633</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:15:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351804642806-125</Id><Topic><Title>I would not be buying here</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351797221614</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which Willard are you talking about? He has taken both sides of this issue, in line with 100% of his other positions or statements.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1351804642806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:17:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351805014563-126</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351781487217</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:51:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your tires must be bald, considering the traction you're getting with this "War criminal" hogwash. Obama has never invaded a country that never did us any harm.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351805014563</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:23:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351805070347-127</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Repug lying global climate change deniers are sure they have "undenialble evidence against the Obamantor" Benghazi is so laughable that it is almost insane on their parts. They are gonna be even crazier come Tuesday NEXT.</Msg><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351805070347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:24:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351805119696-128</Id><Topic><Title>Campaigning Much More important to Obama than doing his job.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351800717450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:11:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's more than Boxarox ever did after 9/11.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351805119696</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:25:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351805223477-129</Id><Title>Hi, my name is Dik Dipopolis</Title><Msg>....but people call me dippy for short....I'm a Democrat of course and some people think that's why people call me dippy. Whateva. Obama is my hero. He's skinny and black and I think it's pretty coll that a skinny black man who never had a real job could become president of the united states.</Msg><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1351805223477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:27:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351805236513-130</Id><Topic><Title>Uh O......OHIO: R 49% O 46%...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351798519728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:35:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dream on. Any gun owner who thinks Obama wants to take away his guns should put one of his to his left ear and aim for his right ear. He won't hit anything vital.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351805236513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:27:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351805303060-131</Id><Topic><Title>Let's hear it for ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351793064346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ain't it great to live in a free country? Ain't that freedom of speech thing wunnerful?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351805303060</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:28:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351805391358-132</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ONLY applicable word in your post, Don, is "If ..." Even then it's a smallish mole hill.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351805391358</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:29:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351805413533-133</Id><Topic><Title>Campaigning Much More important to Obama than doing his job.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351800717450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:11:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are one confused hairydope, quoting the lying joe-the-plumber who didn't even have a contractors license. I want to see how Obamacare plays out before even considering repealing it. So far so good. Probably gonna get better with time, especially when compared to the status quo of 30M uninsured, skyrocketing costs yet record profits by the health insurance comanies, denial of coverage, dropped coverage...etc, etc, etc,</Msg><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351805413533</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:30:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351805463344-134</Id><Topic><Title>Media Bias Intensifying</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351773758279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 08:42:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351805463344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:31:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351805623974-135</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would have thought an upstanding Christian zealot like Bulk would be lobbying for stoning Obama rather than simply impeaching him.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351805623974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:33:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351805649728-136</Id><Topic><Title>Uh O......OHIO: R 49% O 46%...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351798519728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:35:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Any gun owner who thinks Obama wants to take away his guns should put one of his to his left ear and aim for his right ear. He won't hit anything vital." Chris, you need to make yourself clearer. An initial read of your post suggested something that would undoubtedly be true, but then I realized you were talkling about the gun owner's ears, not.......LOL</Msg><Username>cws2012wc</Username><Timestamp>1351805649728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:34:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351805799935-137</Id><Topic><Title>Media Bias Intensifying</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351773758279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 08:42:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's second term GDP, + 3% Bush's secnd term GDP, -8% Rmoney is just more Boosh! and, where are 'the documents' proving what Obama knew about Benghazi We have the documents that Boosh knew about 9/11! We have the documents that Boosh knew there were no WMD's in Iraq! That is the real RWNJ media bias.</Msg><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351805799935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:36:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351805860840-138</Id><Title>New Poll: No need for Democrats Wasting their time Voting</Title><Msg>I took the poll myself. I polled 12 other guys that live in the project and 11 of the 12 guys say they're for Obama even if they aren't going to waste their time voting for him. The one guy that didn't like Obama isn't on welfare so he don't count anyway. So if Obama is so far ahead my recommendation is no to waste your time and welfare money going to the vote cause Obama he gonna win anyway. Stay home, have a nice glass of Thunderbird and reduce your carbon footprint by not having on of those scary vans pick you up. Those things remind me of something taking people to work.</Msg><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1351805860840</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:37:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351806010816-139</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Michael Bloomberg endorses President Barack Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351805714519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:35:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bloomberg made the right endorsement!</Msg><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1351806010816</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:40:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351806713986-140</Id><Topic><Title>Let's hear it for ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351793064346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the last few decades of US history, no other president, or candidate for president has ever been so out of touch with reality and "you people" as is Willtard. Amazing -- one would almost have to think he's an idiot.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351806713986</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:51:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351806790309-141</Id><Topic><Title>Let's hear it for ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351793064346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"She also asked residents to refrain from gassing up their vehicles. The city's emergency vehicles need gas and it's in short supply, Zimmer said. "Don't go to gas stations," she pleaded. "Conserve." Non-residents are not permitted to drive into the city, unless they are bringing supplies or volunteering with the relief effort, Zimmer confirmed. Zimmer praised the city's public-safety departments, Gov. Chris Christie and President Obama for their help getting the city back to normal."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351806790309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:53:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351807102139-142</Id><Title>Voters are abandoning 14% taxes and dressage horsies for all...</Title><Msg>why, what is wrong with a grand vision like that...</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1351807102139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351807236414-143</Id><Title>New Yorkers Rude Just because Obama Won't Help them.</Title><Msg>Just look at these headlines Gas Shortages May Not End for Another Week... Fear Turns to Frustration, Anger... Fistfights, Guns Drawn... Fuel scramble... Some Siphoning From Cars! 'I'm pretty pissed'... Troopers deployed to gas stations... CON ED: 'Vast Majority' Won't Have Power Until Nov. 11... Stars throw extravagant Halloween party despite destruction... Commuter Delays Rage... NYC Official: Red Cross 'Absolute Disgrace'... What do they expect Obama to Do? Maybe if Doomberg and Coumo would offer to give him some good campaign photo ops we would be able to help them. Some people just aren't sophisticated enough to understand how this works. You scratch my back and I'll give you tax payer's money......they should have noticed how all those green energy companies did it.</Msg><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1351807236414</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351807350570-144</Id><Topic><Title>Early voting</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351795789102</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:49:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think so? I actually believe it's a form of paranoia -- Delusions of Grandeur. 06 Nov is going to be a hoot!</Msg><Username>wonderdoc</Username><Timestamp>1351807350570</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:02:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351807364627-145</Id><Topic><Title>Uh O......OHIO: R 49% O 46%...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351798519728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:35:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are posting like a crazy person that got off his meds today............too funny!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1351807364627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:02:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351807380166-146</Id><Topic><Title>Let's hear it for ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351793064346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YEEAAHHH! :)))</Msg><Username>wonderdoc</Username><Timestamp>1351807380166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:03:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351807450286-147</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too little too late... LOL! I'm lovin' it :)))</Msg><Username>wonderdoc</Username><Timestamp>1351807450286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:04:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351807538107-148</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You idiots have completely shot your wad with all the birther nonsense; your cred is ZERO.</Msg><Username>wonderdoc</Username><Timestamp>1351807538107</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351807716286-149</Id><Topic><Title>Uh O......OHIO: R 49% O 46%...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351798519728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:35:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your desperation is something to behold, it's hugely entertaining! Don't stop now.</Msg><Username>wonderdoc</Username><Timestamp>1351807716286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:08:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351807985892-150</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Desperation is always demonstrated by the form of language used. Take Chris Genna for example. He cannot formulate any form of cogent response so out comes the inflammatory and vulgar comments. He learned that in his "yellow journalism" class.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351807985892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:13:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351808161786-151</Id><Title>You just don't know where Romney stands on ANY issue</Title><Msg>That is why you can't trust him. He has no specifics on any issue. That is why you can't trust him. Only negative attacks against Obama, no campaign of his own. That is why you can't trust him. His record as a vulture capitalist while at Bain and his own banking habats overseas belies his true moral values. That is why you can't trust him.</Msg><Username>repupblicansagainstromney</Username><Timestamp>1351808161786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:16:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351808618731-152</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did he take a journalism class in China?</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1351808618731</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:23:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351808735074-153</Id><Topic><Title>Uh O......OHIO: R 49% O 46%...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351798519728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:35:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will be funny to see him go off the deep end after the election. What will he and all his aliases do if Barry loses?</Msg><Username>floydian_slips_11</Username><Timestamp>1351808735074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:25:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351809459142-154</Id><Topic><Title>New Yorkers Rude Just because Obama Won't Help them.</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1351807236414</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has Obama denied any disaster aid, like Bush did.</Msg><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351809459142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:37:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351809510638-155</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Suppress Congressional Research Service Report. Summary: "Tax cuts don't work"</Title><Username>windyhorn</Username><Timestamp>1351804240284</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:10:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you trying to say that Reality trumps Ideology?</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1351809510638</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:38:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351809644587-156</Id><Topic><Title>You just don't know where Romney stands on ANY issue</Title><Username>repupblicansagainstromney</Username><Timestamp>1351808161786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:16:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh boy...you're right on that one. We know exactly what Obama stands for because there are videos. He's for redistribution of income, for mandated socialized healthcare, higher taxes on higher achievement, more taxes on job creators, more food stamps, more welfare, higher unemployment, higher deficits, more debt, more borrowing from the Chinese, more regulations, more green energy companies and executive orders ignoring the constitution and congress. That is why we can trust Obama.</Msg><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1351809644587</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:40:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351809877401-157</Id><Topic><Title>You just don't know where Romney stands on ANY issue</Title><Username>repupblicansagainstromney</Username><Timestamp>1351808161786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:16:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot, Obama is also making Chrysler sending JEEP to China, deluded dipiyshitdem, ,,</Msg><Username>repugsareliars</Username><Timestamp>1351809877401</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:44:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351810169975-158</Id><Topic><Title>Uh O......OHIO: R 49% O 46%...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351798519728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:35:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think you should lose any sleep over "...if Barry loses" floyd. That is looking less and less likely.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351810169975</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:49:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351810293838-159</Id><Title>Media 'blackout' as Rmoney,,,er, Bush speaks in Cayman Islands</Title><Msg>Media 'blackout' as Bush speaks in Cayman Islands GEORGE TOWN, Cayman Islands (AP) — Organizers of an investment conference in the Cayman Islands say they have been forbidden from disclosing any details about a speech by former President George W. Bush in the offshore financial haven, an event spokesman said Thursday. Cayman Islands officials are proud of the British territory's role as an offshore finance center. But members of the U.S. Congress and advocates for changes in tax laws have accused corporations and wealthy individuals of using so-called financial havens to improperly avoid taxes.</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1351810293838</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:51:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351810356875-160</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Michael Bloomberg endorses President Barack Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351805714519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:35:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's all over now! joseph smith and magic underwear won.t save the great fabricator! Kamakure</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1351810356875</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351810454534-161</Id><Topic><Title>You just don't know where Romney stands on ANY issue</Title><Username>repupblicansagainstromney</Username><Timestamp>1351808161786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:16:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All Rmoney has said is that he'd do the same as Bush, but only more! Nobody wants a repeat of the Bush Great Recession, or worse,,,</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1351810454534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:54:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351810596393-162</Id><Topic><Title>Uh O......OHIO: R 49% O 46%...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351798519728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:35:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't wait to see him flip flop again on the war. If Romney wins he will be, once again, against the war. Now THAT will be funny.</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1351810596393</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:56:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351810676298-163</Id><Topic><Title>Uh O......OHIO: R 49% O 46%...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351798519728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:35:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He hasn't even posted a rational thought yet!</Msg><Username>harry_caul</Username><Timestamp>1351810676298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:57:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351810767967-164</Id><Title>Oh that Nate Silver</Title><Msg>Mr. Obama had one more terrible day in the polls, on Friday, Oct. 12, when Mr. Romney’s chances of winning the Electoral College rose to almost 40 percent in the forecast. But that was when Mr. Romney’s momentum stopped. Since then, Mr. Obama’s standing has rebounded slightly. His position in the national polls has stabilized; although the national polls continue to tell a different story about the race than the state polls do; it can no longer be said that they have Mr. Obama behind.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351810767967</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:59:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351810989058-165</Id><Topic><Title>You just don't know where Romney stands on ANY issue</Title><Username>repupblicansagainstromney</Username><Timestamp>1351808161786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:16:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>= He's explained it in too complicated terms for you libs to understand it appears.= Oh I understand all right: translated what he is saying is "y'all will get yer pie in the sky by and by." If you don't agree with that interpretation, perhaps you can give us your "compllicated" explanation.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351810989058</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:03:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351811435572-166</Id><Topic><Title>Let's hear it for ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351793064346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because Okiedokes can't spell Hoboken, pehaps you thought he was talking about the mayor of New York City. I think he was LYING about Ms. Dawn Zimmer, the mayor of Hoboken, who has not said anything negative about Obama or Christie</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351811435572</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:10:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351811575415-167</Id><Topic><Title>Uh O......OHIO: R 49% O 46%...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1351798519728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:35:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I use the word "irrelevant" and look who shows up.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351811575415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:12:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351812072677-168</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Michael Bloomberg endorses President Barack Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351805714519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:35:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Mayor Bloomberg also introduced and obtained passage of a measure to restrict soft drinks to no more than 16 ounces. Apparently, he has not heard of "refills". Nevertheless, while Chris Genna praises freedom in this country he praises freedom hating leaders such as Bloomberg and Obama. Unless it is freedom to have unfettered abortions.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351812072677</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351812181253-169</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may blather to your heart's discontent, as I spot a loss in your near future. You also spot this upcoming loss, which we can spot by your own increasing desperation, panic, sense of loss, etc. In the meantime, true Americans call Mr. Genna "Sir." He earned the Distinguished Flying Cross, as did my father. So perhaps you should get into the closet, blow out the candle, and pay attention to Matthew 6. Good riddance.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1351812181253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:23:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351812512096-170</Id><Topic><Title>Mayor Michael Bloomberg endorses President Barack Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351805714519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:35:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The endorsements for Obama keep piling up. But hey, Clint Eastwood, Meatloaf, and Ted Nugent are backing Rmoney,,,in other words, who ?, the senile, those who lost it all, and a crazed gun-toting redneck</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351812512096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:28:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351812793147-171</Id><Topic><Title>Anger Building in NYC... Obama's Katrina, eh?</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351803395228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:56:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh Course They Say That... Just Wait Until This Weekend!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351812793147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351813158806-172</Id><Title>What does Rmoney say about Benghazi...</Title><Msg>Nada,,, he is too busy collecting cans of Spam to feed to the hurricane Sandy victims, and posing for ads decrying how he saved the auto industry and it is Obama who is making Chrysler outsource JEEP to China. All the hot air about Benghazi is right-wing hate radio and the Faux Noise channel. "investigations are being conducted by both the FBI and the Accountability Review Board" said WH spokeman Carney, adding "The President is anticipating results that show us exactly what happened, who was responsible and what lessons we can learn from it in terms of how we ensure that it never happens again," Carney said.</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1351813158806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:39:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351813323385-173</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Witch Hunt</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1351780653549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>iam...666, You make me laugh. Look at Chris' post. Look at mine. Dissect the words. I stand by what I wrote and can justify it - in the closet or not. Who used vulgarity? Whatever one may have earned in the past is no "free pass" to vulgar behavior today. His medal, a case in point, is all the more reason that, while he fought for and lauds the notion of freedom, that he does not spew condemnation and "hate speech" to others for their expression of freedom - political or faith based. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1351813323385</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:42:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351813414766-174</Id><Title>Seven Romney males and none have served in the U.S military</Title><Msg>Virtually everyone served during WWII, but not Mitt's dad. Romney agitated for the Vietnam war, but didn't serve instead he fled to France. And despite Romney's support for he Iraq war, none of his privileged sons chose to serve.</Msg><Username>billsj2000</Username><Timestamp>1351813414766</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:43:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351813800342-175</Id><Topic><Title>Oh that Nate Silver</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1351810767967</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:59:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Karl Rove wants Romney to lose. Americans will be disappointed in their president no matter who he is, and it better serves the Republicans' cause if they're disappointed in a Democrat.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1351813800342</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:50:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351814138018-176</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt hits the panic button</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351813920535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:52:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More of Dik's Blue Wall Garbage... Just Shows How Concerned and Afraid the Libs are off a Romney Landslide!!!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351814138018</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:55:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351814316068-177</Id><Topic><Title>Romney compares relief efforts to cleaning up a football field</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351814205903</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dik, You Sound Panicked... Obama Will Lose Big!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351814316068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:58:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351814615013-178</Id><Topic><Title>Anger Building in NYC... Obama's Katrina, eh?</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351803395228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:56:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's the deal with capitalizing most of the first letters in all the words of your posts? Is that something you learned in home-schooling?</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1351814615013</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:03:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351814663469-179</Id><Title>Reports of Fights and Guns at Obama's Katrina Gas Stations....</Title><Msg>Rioting will Erupt Among the Libs in NYC this Weekend! Total Breakdown of Civil Order Among Libs....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351814663469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351814735722-180</Id><Topic><Title>Anger Building in NYC... Obama's Katrina, eh?</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351803395228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:56:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bloomberg is a Democrat... What a Surprise?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351814735722</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351814940980-181</Id><Topic><Title>Seven Romney males and none have served in the U.S military</Title><Username>billsj2000</Username><Timestamp>1351813414766</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:43:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But, but I Did't Enhale....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351814940980</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:09:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351816409291-182</Id><Topic><Title>Its true Obama is a Marxist</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351797109783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:11:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>= filling the pockets of his friends and supporters like Al Gore who when leaving office was worth $2M now due to Obama's Green Energy is worth $100M and not able to pick one winner. = Well if he picked Al Gore and Gore is now $98M richer, I'd say that qualifies for picking winners. LOL, you're such an incredible D O P E.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351816409291</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:33:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351816422531-183</Id><Topic><Title>Media Bias Intensifying</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351773758279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 08:42:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Media would rip the George Bush administration to shreds if Bengazigate happened on Bush's watch! But the worst scandal in American history has the Media vigilantly protecting Barak Obama from public scrutiny in the hopes of saving the President's reelection! The Media,Hollywood, and Institutions of Higher Learning have all succumed to Socialist Doctrines compliments of the Communist Manifesto for the destruction of Western Culture!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351816422531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:33:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351816548226-184</Id><Topic><Title>Its true Obama is a Marxist</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351797109783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:11:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said, and so appropriate for that illiterate IDIOT.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1351816548226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:35:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351816661065-185</Id><Topic><Title>Media Bias Intensifying</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1351773758279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 08:42:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cry me a river. You're panicking, arent't you? Not at all becoming. In fact, your whining and flailing makes you look pretty stupid.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1351816661065</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:37:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351817043168-186</Id><Topic><Title>Romney-Ryan and the Slashing of Medicaid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351816694577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post, thanks... Next Tuesday is clearly OUR day.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351817043168</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:44:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351817080526-187</Id><Topic><Title>Romney-Ryan and the Slashing of Medicaid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351816694577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Garbage as it is Obama Stealing Over $700 Billion from MediCare to Pay for His Unpopular ObamaCare!!! You have the Names Backwards, eh!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351817080526</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:44:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351817304709-188</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt hits the panic button</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351813920535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:52:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Conservative fingers jammed deep in ears (touching) while screaming "LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA"</Msg><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1351817304709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:48:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351817401210-189</Id><Topic><Title>Romney-Ryan and the Slashing of Medicaid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351816694577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has anybody mentioned the slashing of 715 billion dollars from Medicare with Obamacare,yet? Or have all the liberals conveniently forgotten this fact? Obamacare is the Liberals biggest coverup since Benghazigate! Obama has a disastrous record!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351817401210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351817492621-190</Id><Topic><Title>Romney-Ryan and the Slashing of Medicaid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351816694577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep talkin' :))</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1351817492621</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351817600855-191</Id><Title>Staten Island Residents Beg for Food and Clothes... Obama's Katrina!</Title><Msg>Libs Will be Rioting in the Streets of NYC this Weekend! What Disasterous TV Clips for Obama just Before the Election!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351817600855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:53:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351817680275-192</Id><Topic><Title>Seven Romney males and none have served in the U.S military</Title><Username>billsj2000</Username><Timestamp>1351813414766</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:43:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course they "served" their country....by trying to get others to join their religeon, and then campaigning for their Dad. Of course, they never risked coming back in a coffin..........</Msg><Username>barking_dogmas</Username><Timestamp>1351817680275</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:54:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351817927434-193</Id><Topic><Title>Romney-Ryan and the Slashing of Medicaid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351816694577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nancy Pelosi: "We have to pass the bill before we can find out what's in it!"</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351817927434</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:58:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351817946513-194</Id><Topic><Title>Seven Romney males and none have served in the U.S military</Title><Username>billsj2000</Username><Timestamp>1351813414766</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:43:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did You Serve?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351817946513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:59:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351818166939-195</Id><Title>Obama "Most Incompetent Commander in Chief" since Jimmy Carter!!!!!</Title><Msg>Obama's Coverup in Benghazi IS being Crushed by "***FOX NEWS***" and NOW CBS and ABC are being Forced to Cover the BREAKING NEWS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! And Never Forget, THIS Coverup has a "*****Body Count*****"!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!.........The REAL News Matters Breaking News on the Libya Attack: Top Administration Officials Did Not Call on Counterterrorism Agencies CBS Sources: Key Counterterrorism Task Force Not Convened During Benghazi Attack Criminal Negligence: Benghazi Gave 1-Month Warning IBD Senior U.S. Officials: State Department Never Requested Military Backup in Benghazi America, Obama..........."HIS" People and the National Press out of Washington have been LYING and Covering their #$%$ Off about what Happened in Benghazi!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Documents found in Benghazi consulate claimed “troubling” surveillance by Libyan guards; Update: Obama not participating in investigation; Report: State never requested military back-up during attack Sources: Key task force not convened during Benghazi consulate attack 'Troubling' Surveillance Before Benghazi Attack Sensitive documents found amid the wreckage of the U.S. consulate shine new light on the Sept. 11 assault that killed Ambassador Chris Stevens and three other Americans. *****Exclusive: Classified cable warned consulate couldn't withstand 'coordinated attack' By Catherine Herridge Secret Cable Revelation Blows Open Benghazi Cover-Up Story Fox News’s Benghazi bombshell: Why haven’t other media followed? Sen. Kyl: President Obama needs to answer Benghazi questions before election, Americans can decide whether they want to rehire him John Bolton, Sen. Graham Press Tunisia for Benghazi Suspect Access READ ALL about IT Where "The REAL News Matters"!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351818166939</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:02:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351818183193-196</Id><Topic><Title>Seven Romney males and none have served in the U.S military</Title><Username>billsj2000</Username><Timestamp>1351813414766</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:43:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where as Barak Obama served in the Indonesian Communist Youth Corps.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1351818183193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:03:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351818246870-197</Id><Topic><Title>‘GOP bloodlust’ over Benghazi</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351817361524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Has Blood on His Hands... Obama has Lied Repeatedly to the American Peope and the World About Benghazi... Obama is Still Lying as he Boxed Himself into a Liars Corner!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351818246870</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:04:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351818587861-198</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This White House has been Lying about Benghazi from the Beginning and NOW Fox NEWS has totally NUKED the LIE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351818587861</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:09:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351818850980-199</Id><Topic><Title>Obama "Most Incompetent Commander in Chief" since Jimmy Carter!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351818166939</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:02:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is Incompetent....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351818850980</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:14:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351818907101-200</Id><Topic><Title>‘GOP bloodlust’ over Benghazi</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351817361524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No he doesn't and no one will here squat about this once the election is over</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1351818907101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351818938979-201</Id><Topic><Title>‘GOP bloodlust’ over Benghazi</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351817361524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hear squat</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1351818938979</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:15:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351818989570-202</Id><Topic><Title>Obama "Most Incompetent Commander in Chief" since Jimmy Carter!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351818166939</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:02:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better than bush lite</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1351818989570</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:16:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351819135897-203</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Prove it!</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1351819135897</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:18:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351819239455-204</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fox News is for brain dead bumpkins to lazy to look things up for themselves. It is reality news less the reality.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1351819239455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:20:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351819446337-205</Id><Title>Charles Woods Obama's Cindy Sheehan!</Title><Msg>Looking Worse for Obama!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351819446337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:24:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351819664463-206</Id><Topic><Title>‘GOP bloodlust’ over Benghazi</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_789</Username><Timestamp>1351817361524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Geraldo is a liberal. Enough said.</Msg><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1351819664463</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:27:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351820504269-207</Id><Topic><Title>Staten Island Residents Beg for Food and Clothes... Obama's Katrina!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351817600855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:53:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Say that it anit so! lets review! 5 days of warnings to get out of the impact zone and stock up on supplies, amost 100 people dead (and counting), FEMA and 1st responders stood by and watched over 100 homes burn to the ground after the President said "I GOT THIS", fights breaking out for food, water and fuel, most mass transit shut down.. still..........etc.Sounds familiar! You can bet if a republican was in office the media and liberals would be foaming at the mouth with rage by now. Looks like the "anointed one" getting another pass for NOT DOING what he says he was going to do!</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1351820504269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351820769293-208</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check out the Videos I just Posted that IS going to BREAK this Wide OPEN!!!!!!!! Congressional HEARINGS ARE NEXT and OMG is this going to be HOT in 2013!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Read All About it Where "The REAL News Matters" "New Info -Top Counterterror Group Not Consulted During Benghazi Attack By The Obama Admin!" "SEAL father: Who denied backup during Benghazi attack?"</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351820769293</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:46:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351821148775-209</Id><Title>Many People That I Know Are Preparing For A Second Obama Term</Title><Msg>They're buying Gold... they're buying Treasuries... a couple are even considering ex-patriation as Facebook's Edwardo Saverin did when he fled to Singapore... or Apple's Steve Wozniak and his ex-patriation to New Zealand. On the mutual fund side, assets have been leaving "domestic stock" mutual funds for quite awhile now as bond funds or "emerging markets" funds are accumulating substantial assets. Meanwhile, corporations are sitting on record levels of cash... especially at overseas subsidiaries where they're avoiding America's highest-in-the-world corporate tax by keeping it out of the U.S. I've never SEEN "capital flight" of this magnitude in the U.S. I've seen it in other countries that lurched toward socialism over the decades... like Cuba or Venezuela... but I never thought it could happen HERE. Every day, Mr. Obama talks about how he's going to jack up taxes on those with investment capital (eg: the wealthy) and everyday we see signs that they are leaving "productive" investments to protect their capital from Mr. Obama's threats. The top 1% of american earners already provide 38% of all U.S. tax revenues that come from individual income taxes... and projections are that upwards of 45% of them would come from the top 1% if Mr. Obama achieves his taxation goals. Right now, the U.S. is conducting the most MASSIVE, "fiscal" stimulus in history... eg: $1.2 trillion in deficit spending. We are also conducting the most massive "MONETARY" stimulus ever... with 0% fed-funds interest rate and the over-heating printing presses of QE3... ... yet our economy is only growing at barely 2% GDP... when in the past, such huge amounts of stimulus would have our economy smoking along at 8 or 9% growth! The reason: No amount of stimulus can overcome the immense power of "capital flight" to completely neutralize a capitalist system such as ours. It's what happened in almost every country throughout history that was run by an "anti-capitalism" leader like Mr. Obama..... .... whoever thought it could happen HERE! All I can say is... next tuesday, I hope you'll all go to the polls and vote... not for yourself... but for the America that our Children will live in. Spokanimal</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1351821148775</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:52:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351821581993-210</Id><Title>Clint Eastwood has a Message that ALL Americans should Listen to!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>A Cutting Indictment on the PAST 4 YEARS and Obama.............A Very Powerful Video!!!!!!!!!!! American Crossroads: "At Stake" "The REAL News Matters"</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351821581993</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:59:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351822430726-211</Id><Topic><Title>Save the Wutang</Title><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1351569132377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 23:52:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wu, is that you jumping into the dumpster?</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1351822430726</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 22:13:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351822980254-212</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood has a Message that ALL Americans should Listen to!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351821581993</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch it. Bump it.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351822980254</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 22:23:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351823224631-213</Id><Topic><Title>Staten Island Residents Beg for Food and Clothes... Obama's Katrina!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1351817600855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:53:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But I heard him (Obama) say during his phot op in New Jersey as he hugged a grief stricken woman that "everything is O.K.".</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1351823224631</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 22:27:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351827145866-214</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Woods: WH officials 'murdered' my Son!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1351536749339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:52:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The little boy who cried wolf (peedrool) used up his credibility 5,215 screeched, irrational, whining, ridiculous, kooky posts ago. Stop besmirching the good name of your father.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1351827145866</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:32:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351827844705-215</Id><Title>Do you trust Romney with your pension?</Title><Msg>Educated people say no.</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351827844705</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:44:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351827956330-216</Id><Title>President Obama, thank you for correcting Bush's mistakes</Title><Msg>I can't trust a man who hides his taxes</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351827956330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:45:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351828046458-217</Id><Title>Bin Laden</Title><Msg>We haven't forgotten 911. Too bad we invaded Iraq and Afganistan and couldn't afford to pay for it</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351828046458</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351828149468-218</Id><Title>No 911 on Obama's watch</Title><Msg>Great job Mr. President. Oh yeah, the market did pretty good today</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1351828149468</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>