<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349670745839-1</Id><Topic><Title>Top Reasons Libs Hate Romney</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1349539939218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 12:12:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unlike obama's stand on Gitmo, 2009 immigration plan, etc or his truthful words on fast &amp; furious, youtube killed the ambassador, recovery summer, shovel ready, etc. The list is endless.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1349670745839</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 00:32:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349689280997-2</Id><Topic><Title>How many here are supporting obama the clown?</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1349548205914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:30:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give them Kent, bath house and all......................</Msg><Username>alangonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1349689280997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 05:41:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349694393471-3</Id><Title>Favorable Tax Draws Companies to Britain</Title><Msg>Leave the US and take your money with you. ============================================ At least 20 multinationals are drawing up plans to move their regional or global headquarters to Britain over the next year after government efforts to increase the competitiveness of the UK’s business tax regime. Ernst &amp; Young, the professional services firm, said the country was successfully competing with low-tax countries such as Switzerland and Singapore as a base for multinational companies. The firm told the Financial Times that the 20 planned moves it was aware of would create about 2,000 highly-paid jobs and generate several hundred millions of pounds of extra corporate, employment and consumption tax revenues. “We are seeing the UK win more often than it loses. That is a transformation,” said John Dixon, head of UK tax at Ernst &amp; Young. His comments offer welcome encouragement for the Treasury, which has widely reformed the corporate tax system after a spate of multinationals moved their tax base out of Britain in 2008. Last month, David Gauke, a Treasury minister, trumpeted Britain’s tax advantages in Washington in what the Treasury said was “an unashamed bid to promote the UK to US businesses”. He pitched to companies including Seadrill, an offshore drilling company which had said it was considering moving its management from Stavanger in Norway to London, Dubai, Singapore or Houston. Several companies have already moved global headquarters to Britain, including Aon and Lancashire Holdings, both insurers, and Ensco and Rowan, both drilling contractors, and Delphi Automotive, a vehicle component manufacturer. In August WPP, the world’s largest advertising company, announced plans to move its tax base back from Ireland. The US is the biggest source of companies considering moving to Britain for tax reasons even though the country’s Internal Revenue Service tightened its rules in June to make it harder for US companies to change their domicile. Asian and European companies — including several big companies with regional headquarters in Switzerland — are also eyeing Britain, E&amp;Y said. Singapore’s Low Taxes Lure TrafiguraAon to Relocate Headquarters to LondonOsborne Says Banks Unlikely to Quit City Mr Dixon said that publicly-announced global headquarter moves – often involving the relocation of just a small number of senior executives — were just “the tip of the iceberg”. Many more jobs were created by regional headquarter moves — often involving marketing, sales, distribution and procurement — which are frequently undertaken without publicity. Securing new headquarters would go some way to reversing Britain’s slide in inward investment, resulting from its dependence on financial services. E&amp;Y said inward investment created nearly 30,000 jobs in 2011 from 679 projects, down 7 per cent from 2010. The UK was at risk of losing its position as Europe’s top destination for foreign direct investment to Germany within two years, it said. Mr Dixon said the UK business tax regime was now “fully competitive” when benchmarked against other countries, as a result of a planned cut in the corporate tax rate to 22 per cent in two years’ time, a new tax break for patent income, new rules on foreign profits and tax-deductible interest costs. Mr Dixon said there were also “signaling benefits” from the chancellor’s Budget decision to cut the 50p top personal tax rate to 45p, describing the move as “another bit of wind in the sails”.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1349694393471</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 07:06:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349701354744-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obamas homosexual agenda</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349666363566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 23:19:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow u r still stuck in the 1930s.....time to geet with the times</Msg><Username>ivxum22</Username><Timestamp>1349701354744</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:02:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349703112236-5</Id><Title>Corruption: Exposing Barack Obama’s Illegal Foreign Campaign Money</Title><Msg>A new report obtained by Townhall from the non-partisan Government Accountability Institute [GAI] shows the Obama campaign has potentially violated federal election law by failing to prevent the use of fraudulent or foreign credit card transactions on the official Obama for America [OFA] donation webpage. For the past eight months, GAI has been investigating the potential influence of foreign online campaign donations in House, Senate and presidential elections. The report was conducted using spidering software and found thousands of foreign sites linking to campaign donation pages. The investigation was conducted with the guidance of a former U.S. attorney. GAI is led by Peter Schweizer, who recently exposed congressional insider trading in his book Throw Them All Out. “As FBI surveillance tapes have previously shown, foreign governments understand and are eager to exploit the weaknesses of American campaigns,” the report says. “This, combined with the Internet’s ability to disintermediate campaign contributions on a mass scale, as well as outmoded and lax Federal Election Commission rules, make U.S. elections vulnerable to foreign influence.” OFA seems to be taking advantage of a “foreign donor loophole” by not using CVV on their campaign donation page. When you donate online to the Obama campaign using a credit card, the contribution webpage does not require donors to enter a secure CVV number (also known as CSC, CVV2 or CVN), the three-digit securing code on the back of credit cards. This code, although not 100 percent effective, is used to ensure a person making a purchase physically possesses the card. According to the report, 90 percent of e-commerce and 19 of the 20 largest charities in the United States use a CVV code, making its use standard industry practice in order to prevent fraud. Another anti-fraud security measure includes software, better known as an Address Verification System, to verify a donor’s address matches the address on file with the credit card company. The investigation could not determine whether OFA is using this type of software to prevent fraudulent or illegal donations. Because of the lack of a CVV code requirement, the door is opened for OFA to accept robo-donations, or in other words, large numbers of small and automatic donations made online to evade FEC reporting requirements. Although it isn’t illegal to decline the use of a secure CVV credit card code for campaign donations, it is illegal to accept campaign donations from foreign sources. Campaigns are required under criminal code not to solicit, accept or receive foreign donations in any amount. The Federal Elections Commission doesn’t require campaigns to disclose the names of donors making contributions of less than $200 unless audited. In addition, FEC rules don’t require campaigns to keep records of those giving less than $50. These rules combined with the lack of a CVV numbers make it easy for campaigns to get away with taking foreign donations. According to GAI, it is the duty of the campaign to “ensure compliance with the law. Indeed, they risk criminal prosecution for the conscious failure to do so. This means that whether or not the FEC requires it to be reported, campaigns have an independent duty under the law to discover and protect against criminal campaign contributions.” Protecting against criminal campaign contributions is easily accomplished by requiring a CVV code on the campaign donation page. OFA has specifically touted its “grassroots” success by showcasing the majority of its donations coming from those giving less than $200. It appears the campaign also solicits funds for less than $200 in order to avoid having to report the name of the person making a donation under FEC rules. The GAI documents included the following email from Barack Obama to campaign supporters: Photobucket</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349703112236</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:31:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349703345171-6</Id><Title>GALLUP: 5-POINT ROMNEY BOUNCE</Title><Msg>PRINCETON, NJ -- Registered voters' preferences for president are evenly split in the first three days of Gallup tracking since last Wednesday's presidential debate. In the three days prior to the debate, Barack Obama had a five-percentage-point edge among registered voters.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349703345171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:35:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349703491587-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obamas homosexual agenda</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349666363566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 23:19:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has a lot of queer ideas.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349703491587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:38:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349704581107-8</Id><Title>Martin Luther King was a Republican and Democrats started the KKK</Title><Msg>Democrats opposed the civil rights amendment and are still angry about losing their war to keep slavery legal.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349704581107</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349708933323-9</Id><Title>Another Right-Wing Nervous Breakdown</Title><Msg>... last Friday's epic job truthers push by Fox News and the rest of the off-kilter far-right media. Without the slightest bit of evidence, Obama's media detractors suggested a truly vast conspiracy had taken hold inside the federal government in an effort to doctor the unemployment numbers and boost Obama's re-election run. Why Obama allowed the supposedly malleable economists at the Bureau of Labor Statistics to run up the unemployment rate to 10 percent in 2009 when all he had to do, apparently, was demand that they fudge the books, we may never know. But the far-fetched nonsense was thoroughly embraced by Fox News and throughout the fevered swamps....</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349708933323</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:08:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349709743182-10</Id><Topic><Title>Obamas homosexual agenda</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349666363566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 23:19:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... you have become quite the advocate of homosexuality... im guessing you'll be making a 'coming-out' announcement soon..</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349709743182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349709783856-11</Id><Topic><Title>I Urge All Americans To Vote For Barack Obama</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney55</Username><Timestamp>1349551010494</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:16:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349709783856</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:23:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349709991579-12</Id><Topic><Title>Another Right-Wing Nervous Breakdown</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349708933323</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:08:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>does your mother know you are using the computer on a school day?</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1349709991579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:26:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349710026059-13</Id><Title>Wow! Romney Up 16 points with Independent Voters... a 24 Point Awing from 2008.</Title><Msg>BATTLEGROUND POLL: ROMNEY UP 16 WITH INDEPENDENTS, UP 13 IN ENTHUSIASM by JOHN NOLTE 8 Oct 2012, 6:10 AM PDT 131 POST A COMMENT In 2008, President Barack Obama won the independent vote over John McCain by a margin of eight points, 52-44. This morning, a new Battleground Poll has Mitt Romney massacring Obama among indies by a whopping 16 points, 51-35. That's a 24-point swing among independents since 2008, a group that makes up anywhere from a quarter to a third of voters, and yet Battleground still has Obama in the lead 49-48…? But if I'm skeptical of those bottom-line numbers, our journalist overlords who have chosen to palace guard instead of question will declare me a "truther." The Battleground Poll also shows an 13 point enthusiasm gap in Romney's favor. Only 73% of Obama's supporters are "extremely likely" to vote, compared to 86% of Romney's supporters. But again, don't question Battleground's 49-48% outcome. In fact, don't question anything anymore -- or the media will question you and mock you as a "truther. " This includes questioning our government about the release of counter-intuitive unemployment statistics very helpful to the president just 30 days out from the election. Though the media hasn't yet decided it's time for a Romney Comeback Narrative, and probably never will, even if he wins -- there's no question Romney is rebounding in every national and swing state poll. Nationally, Gallup has it all tied up among registered voters -- with the president dangerously below 50 at 47%. Rasmussen uses the more reliable likely voter screen and has Romney up 49-47%. In the Real Clear Politics poll of polls, nationally Romney is only down .09%. A week ago he was down over 4 points. In Ohio, according to RCP's poll of polls, Obama's Ohio lead has shrunk to three -- Virginia has Obama only up by 0.3. Florida and Colorado are tied. The good news for Romney is that we are now seeing polls from each of these states with the GOP nominee in the lead. The bad news for Obama is that in most of these swing state polls, he is not hitting 50. Well, actually the worst news for Obama is 85% of the calls made for this new Battleground Poll were made prior to Obama humiliating himself in last week's debate. Follow John Nolte on Twitter @NolteNC</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349710026059</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:27:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349710381737-14</Id><Title>Republicans can't be Trusted</Title><Msg>the Republican leadership have nothing to offer for the economy, healthcare or foreign policy... their conspiracy theory's and acting Desperate are not qualifications to hold office...!!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349710381737</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:33:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349710456041-15</Id><Title>University of Colorado Study Continues to Point to a Romney Win!</Title><Msg>Updated election forecasting model still points to Romney win, University of Colorado study says October 4, 2012 • Social Sciences An update to an election forecasting model announced by two University of Colorado professors in August continues to project that Mitt Romney will win the 2012 presidential election. According to their updated analysis, Romney is projected to receive 330 of the total 538 Electoral College votes. President Barack Obama is expected to receive 208 votes -- down five votes from their initial prediction -- and short of the 270 needed to win. The new forecast by political science professors Kenneth Bickers of CU-Boulder and Michael Berry of CU Denver is based on more recent economic data than their original Aug. 22 prediction. The model itself did not change. “We continue to show that the economic conditions favor Romney even though many polls show the president in the lead,” Bickers said. “Other published models point to the same result, but they looked at the national popular vote, while we stress state-level economic data.” While many election forecast models are based on the popular vote, the model developed by Bickers and Berry is based on the Electoral College and is the only one of its type to include more than one state-level measure of economic conditions. They included economic data from all 50 states and the District of Columbia......</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349710456041</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:34:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349710601321-16</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans can't be Trusted</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349710381737</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama has Been an Utter Failure and have Been Caught Time after Time lying to the American People and the World!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349710601321</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:36:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349710911459-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obamas homosexual agenda</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349666363566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 23:19:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If getting with the times means learning how to bend over and spread it wide I'll pass.and be glad I'm out of school. But(t) you go and enjoy it. Is you favorite place the same as Obama's.... Ilikealickydicky?</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1349710911459</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:41:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349711241947-18</Id><Title>Obama Gives African Americans the Economic Middle Finger... Black Un-Employment at 13.4%</Title><Msg>Black middle class economically vulnerable Downturn has wiped out gains of last 30 years, Urban League says October 07, 2012|By Dawn Turner Trice, Chicago Tribune reporter Roxie King, 63, lost her job as a cardio echo ultrasound technician in 2010 and has been struggling to keep her Chicago home. (Heather Charles, Chicago Tribune) Generations of Valerie Magee's family, from her grandparents to her children, have deepened their roots in the black middle class, finding a pathway to prosperity through college education and the support of family members. But as Magee, 56, watches college tuition skyrocket and wealth and incomes plummet, she worries that college might be moving beyond her young grandchildren's grasp. So Magee, a divorced nurse administrator, recently sold her pricey south suburban Matteson home, hoping that will free her up financially to better assist her children if they need help with a future mortgage payment or tuition. "Every generation wants the next to move up at least one more rung on the ladder, not backward — never backward," she said. "My daughter and son-in-law are doing OK for now, but who knows what will happen tomorrow?" For months, the presidential candidates have been trying to court the middle class, extending offers of tax cuts, lower gas prices and better schools. The message: America does well when the middle class does well. The corollary: We feel your pain. But much less attention has been given to the black middle class, which since the recession and slow recovery has suffered massive decreases in wealth and high rates of home foreclosures. Blacks overall are experiencing a 13.4 percent unemployment rate, according to figures released Friday, much higher than the national rate of 7.8 percent. The Pew Charitable Trusts' Economic Mobility Project recently released a report projecting that 68 percent of African-Americans reared in the middle of the wealth ladder will not do as well as the previous generation. In August, the National Urban League's State of Black America 2012 report found that nearly all the economic gains that the black middle class made during the last 30 years have been wiped out by the economic downturn. "This is a very dire situation," said Valerie Rawlston Wilson, an economist with the National Urban League Policy Institute. "Even for blacks who have college degrees, we've seen a doubling of their unemployment (rate) between 2007 and 2010."...</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349711241947</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:47:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349711723875-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Gives African Americans the Economic Middle Finger... Black Un-Employment at 13.4%</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349711241947</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:47:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama serves the 1%. Just check who's his Chairman of the Fed is and his secy of the Treasury. The guy's just a pretty puppet--a little brighter and prettier than the puppet who preceded him, maybe, that's all.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1349711723875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349711794458-20</Id><Topic><Title>I Urge All Americans To Vote For Barack Obama</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney55</Username><Timestamp>1349551010494</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:16:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do we need a war criminal in the White House?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1349711794458</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349713381960-21</Id><Topic><Title>GALLUP: 5-POINT ROMNEY BOUNCE</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349703345171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:35:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How could any thinking person vote for a liar and failure like O? I'm sure the polls are skewed in O's favor, but the election results will hopefully show the real situation. Someone needs to investigate why the mainstream media is so biased toward Obama. Hopefully after the elections we will get to the truth behind the actions of the media and the financial international elite. We can see their destructive effects on America and the whole western world every day. America needs to shake these parasites off soon.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1349713381960</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:23:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349713641837-22</Id><Title>week one deliveries</Title><Msg>14 planes were delivered in week one. Seven 737's. One 747. Two 777's. Four 787's. It was a good start for the month of October. There are a number of planes which have completed first flights and those read for delivery in week two.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1349713641837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:27:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349715120170-23</Id><Topic><Title>week one deliveries</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1349713641837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:27:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great update.</Msg><Username>mrstock52</Username><Timestamp>1349715120170</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:52:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349715558974-24</Id><Title>romneytheliar</Title><Msg>If you are as determined as I am to politically destroy Willard, you REALLY, REALLY, REALLY need to check this out. It's a 200 page summary of research on Mitt Romney's life and career compiled by John McCain's campaign staff for the 2008 primary season. It was leaked earlier in the year, but I don't think it got enough play. It is absolutely and utterly DAMNING in its indictment of Willard. (Remember, McCain passed up Romney for VP in favor of Sarah Palin, of all people!) There's just so much here. Let's sample some, shall we?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349715558974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:59:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349715685071-25</Id><Title>Glad to hear Mitt wants our navy to have as many ships as we had in 1916 -</Title><Msg>however, I would bet today's battle cruisers have about 50 times (or more) the lethality of the ships of WWI. Therefore why do we need the same amount of ships????????</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1349715685071</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:01:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349715725786-26</Id><Topic><Title>romneytheliar</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349715558974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:59:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spread your stink again, Skunk.</Msg><Username>au.kingfish</Username><Timestamp>1349715725786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:02:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349715931011-27</Id><Topic><Title>Wow! Romney Up 16 points with Independent Voters... a 24 Point Awing from 2008.</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349710026059</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:27:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for your article but I was advised over a week ago not to trust polls......I suggest you jump on that train too and don't put much stake in those main stream media biased polls</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1349715931011</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:05:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349716166672-28</Id><Topic><Title>romneytheliar</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349715558974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:59:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1349716166672</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349716185141-29</Id><Topic><Title>borrow money from China to be paid for our kids and grandkids to pay for Big Bird today</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349715056937</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:50:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's fight in 2 wars and make gigantic cuts in taxes but swear up and down that won't effect our national debt......spare me &amp; big bird your pathetic logic</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1349716185141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:09:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349716324678-30</Id><Topic><Title>GALLUP: 5-POINT ROMNEY BOUNCE</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349703345171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:35:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know and I do too - when Obama wins his re-election you're gonna swear there was massive fraud and all kinds of weird conspiracies in play</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1349716324678</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:12:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349717170669-31</Id><Topic><Title>romneytheliar</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349715558974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:59:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>=Let's sample some, shall we?= Yes please. Can you post an approximate link? Thanks!</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349717170669</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:26:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349718184141-32</Id><Topic><Title>romneytheliar</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349715558974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:59:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EF-You fish</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349718184141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349718567462-33</Id><Title>Romney fibs</Title><Msg>Abortion  Romney says he changed his mind on abortion meeting with Harvard stem cell researcher – Romney claims the doctor said scientists “kill” embryos after 14 days, but doctor later said Romney “mischaracterized my position.”  Months after his “conversion,” Romney stated his commitment to upholding Massachusetts’ abortion laws and appointed pro-choice judge to state district court.  In October 2005, Romney signed bill expanding family planning services, including abortion counseling andmorning-after pill.  In December 2005, Romney “abruptly ordered his administration to reverse course … and require Catholic hospitals to provide emergency contraception medication to rape victims.”  Romney health insurance plan expanded access to abortion, required Planned Parenthood representative on state panel.  Romney endorsed legalization of abortion pill RU-486 access during his 1994 Senate race and backed federal funding of abortion, saying “I think it’s important that people see me not as a pro-life candidate.”  In 1994 and 2002, Romney confirmed his support for Roe v. Wade decision and forcefully positioned himselfas pro-choice in 1994 Senate race, saying “you will not see me wavering on that.”  Romney has refused to comment on bill pending in South Carolina legislature requiring that abortion doctors offer pregnant women option of viewing ultrasound Bain Capital  Romney spent most of his business career as CEO of private equity firm Bain Capital – as of June 2007 he maintained an investor’s stake in the company.  Bain Capital has been criticized for relentless focus on bottom line at expense of workers and jobs.  Romney describes himself as a “business legend” in his campaign ads and once said of himself: “I’m basically in the investor’s Hall of Fame.”  Bain Capital financed 1988 buyout with junk bonds issued by Drexel Burnham – when SEC filed charges against the firm and CEO Michael Milken, Bain Capital maintained their business relationship; Romney later reminisced about “the glorious days of Drexel Burnham.”  In 2004, Bain &amp; Co. received a multi-million dollar contract from the National Iranian Oil Company.  Romney sat on board of directors of Bain portfolio company Damon Clinical Laboratories, which in 1996 was fined over $100 million for Medicare fraud committed during Romney’s tenure.  Bain Capital owned company named Ampad that purchased an Indiana paper plant, fired its workers and offered to bring them back at drastically reduced salary and benefits – the firings became an issue in the 1994 Senate race when workers blamed Romney for their situation and appeared in Kennedy campaign ads.  After Romney became governor, Bain Capital teamed up with Chinese appliance maker Haier Group in 2005 in effort to purchase Newton, IA-based Maytag Corp. and send jobs overseas.  At least two Bain Capital companies – Stream International and Modus Media – focused on outsourced technical support services, expanding facilities abroad while contracting operations in the United States.  Bain Capital operated steel company called GS Industries which went bankrupt in 2001 after years of labor strife, closing a plant in Kansas City and laying off over 700 workers Economic Issues  State spending increased at well over rate of inflation under Romney’s watch, estimated at 24% - more than$5 billion – over Romney’s final three years.  Under Romney, Massachusetts dramatically underperformed the rest of the nation in terms of job growth.  Romney has been criticized by experts for failing to deliver on issues of business development and economic growth after selling himself as the “CEO governor.”  2006 report issued by quasi-public Massachusetts Technology Collaborative warned the state was losing itsgrip as leader in “innovation economy” and that tech job was alarmingly slow.  Romney left his successor to fill a budget deficit exceeding $1 billion.  Romney raised state fees and taxes more than $700 million per year, according to independent experts.  Romney raised fees by roughly $500 million in his first year alone, a figure that was highest in the nation.  Romney quadrupled gun licensing fees and raised fees on first responders, real estate transactions, the blind,golfers and many others.  Romney implemented three rounds of tax changes (which he referred to as “closing loopholes”) which increased business taxes by an estimated $400 million per year.  Massachusetts’ corporate tax climate now ranks 47th in the nation, according to the Tax Foundation. [The highlighted parts are my emphases] There is MUCH, MUCH more. But a clear picture emerges: Romney talks a good game but his words are deceptive, and his willingness to change positions for the sake of political expediency is ASTOUNDING. His hypocrisy knows no bounds, and he habitually lies about his so-called "achievements". Dive into this, and keep one thing in mid as you do: THIS ASSESSMENT COMES FROM REPUBLICANS!</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1349718567462</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:49:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349718741642-34</Id><Title>Romney Tales II</Title><Msg>The amazing Paul Krugman weighs in on one of Willard's more brazen and disgusting lies from Wednesday's debate. Excerpts: “No. 1,” declared Mitt Romney in Wednesday’s debate, “pre-existing conditions are covered under my [health care] plan.” No, they aren't — as Mr. Romney’s own advisers have conceded in the past, and did again after the debate. Was Mr. Romney lying? Well, either that or he was making what amounts to a sick joke. Either way, his attempt to deceive voters on this issue was the biggest of many misleading and/or dishonest claims he made over the course of that hour and a half. Yes, President Obama did a notably bad job of responding. But I’ll leave the theater criticism to others and talk instead about the issue that should be at the heart of this election. ******** [After pointing out that Romney's plan has nothing to do with anyone's definition of pre-existing.] What Mr. Romney did in the debate, in other words, was, at best, to play a word game with voters, pretending to offer something substantive for the uninsured while actually offering nothing. For all practical purposes, he simply lied about what his policy proposals would do. How many Americans would be left out in the cold under Mr. Romney’s plan? One answer is 89 million. According to the nonpartisan Commonwealth Foundation, that’s the number of Americans who lack the “continuous coverage” that would make them eligible for health insurance under Mr. Romney’s empty promises. By the way, that’s more than a third of the U.S. population under 65 years old. Another answer is 45 million, the estimated number of people who would have health insurance if Mr. Obama were re-elected, but would lose it if Mr. Romney were to win. Read the whole thing, and then spread the word: ROMNEY'S DEBATE PERFORMANCE WAS NOTHING BUT A PACK OF LIES DESIGNED TO DECEIVE PEOPLE.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349718741642</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349718796603-35</Id><Title>Romney the sociopath</Title><Msg>Monday, October 8, 2012A VERITABLE ***FLOOD*** OF LIES FROM ROMNEY THE LIAR All checked by PolitiFact, and all located here. Really, when you see them one after another, over 30 WHOPPERS in one place, the effect is quite stunning. (Thanks to faithful reader Bally Balldez!) Posted by Joseph at 12:40 AM No comments: Email ThisBlogThis!Share to TwitterShare to Facebook Sunday, October 7, 2012WOW!! CHECK OUT JOHN McCAIN'S OPPO RESEARCH BOOK ON ROMNEY THE LIAR If you are as determined as I am to politically destroy Willard, you REALLY, REALLY, REALLY need to check this out. It's a 200 page summary of research on Mitt Romney's life and career compiled by John McCain's campaign staff for the 2008 primary season. It was leaked earlier in the year, but I don't think it got enough play. It is absolutely and utterly DAMNING in its indictment of Willard. (Remember, McCain passed up Romney for VP in favor of Sarah Palin, of all people!) There's just so much here. Let's sample some, shall we? Abortion  Romney says he changed his mind on abortion meeting with Harvard stem cell researcher – Romney claims the doctor said scientists “kill” embryos after 14 days, but doctor later said Romney “mischaracterized my position.”  Months after his “conversion,” Romney stated his commitment to upholding Massachusetts’ abortion laws and appointed pro-choice judge to state district court.  In October 2005, Romney signed bill expanding family planning services, including abortion counseling andmorning-after pill.  In December 2005, Romney “abruptly ordered his administration to reverse course … and require Catholic hospitals to provide emergency contraception medication to rape victims.”  Romney health insurance plan expanded access to abortion, required Planned Parenthood representative on state panel.  Romney endorsed legalization of abortion pill RU-486 access during his 1994 Senate race and backed federal funding of abortion, saying “I think it’s important that people see me not as a pro-life candidate.”  In 1994 and 2002, Romney confirmed his support for Roe v. Wade decision and forcefully positioned himselfas pro-choice in 1994 Senate race, saying “you will not see me wavering on that.”  Romney has refused to comment on bill pending in South Carolina legislature requiring that abortion doctors offer pregnant women option of viewing ultrasound Bain Capital  Romney spent most of his business career as CEO of private equity firm Bain Capital – as of June 2007 he maintained an investor’s stake in the company.  Bain Capital has been criticized for relentless focus on bottom line at expense of workers and jobs.  Romney describes himself as a “business legend” in his campaign ads and once said of himself: “I’m basically in the investor’s Hall of Fame.”  Bain Capital financed 1988 buyout with junk bonds issued by Drexel Burnham – when SEC filed charges against the firm and CEO Michael Milken, Bain Capital maintained their business relationship; Romney later reminisced about “the glorious days of Drexel Burnham.”  In 2004, Bain &amp; Co. received a multi-million dollar contract from the National Iranian Oil Company.  Romney sat on board of directors of Bain portfolio company Damon Clinical Laboratories, which in 1996 was fined over $100 million for Medicare fraud committed during Romney’s tenure.  Bain Capital owned company named Ampad that purchased an Indiana paper plant, fired its workers and offered to bring them back at drastically reduced salary and benefits – the firings became an issue in the 1994 Senate race when workers blamed Romney for their situation and appeared in Kennedy campaign ads.  After Romney became governor, Bain Capital teamed up with Chinese appliance maker Haier Group in 2005 in effort to purchase Newton, IA-based Maytag Corp. and send jobs overseas.  At least two Bain Capital companies – Stream International and Modus Media – focused on outsourced technical support services, expanding facilities abroad while contracting operations in the United States.  Bain Capital operated steel company called GS Industries which went bankrupt in 2001 after years of labor strife, closing a plant in Kansas City and laying off over 700 workers Economic Issues  State spending increased at well over rate of inflation under Romney’s watch, estimated at 24% - more than$5 billion – over Romney’s final three years.  Under Romney, Massachusetts dramatically underperformed the rest of the nation in terms of job growth.  Romney has been criticized by experts for failing to deliver on issues of business development and economic growth after selling himself as the “CEO governor.”  2006 report issued by quasi-public Massachusetts Technology Collaborative warned the state was losing itsgrip as leader in “innovation economy” and that tech job was alarmingly slow.  Romney left his successor to fill a budget deficit exceeding $1 billion.  Romney raised state fees and taxes more than $700 million per year, according to independent experts.  Romney raised fees by roughly $500 million in his first year alone, a figure that was highest in the nation.  Romney quadrupled gun licensing fees and raised fees on first responders, real estate transactions, the blind,golfers and many others.  Romney implemented three rounds of tax changes (which he referred to as “closing loopholes”) which increased business taxes by an estimated $400 million per year.  Massachusetts’ corporate tax climate now ranks 47th in the nation, according to the Tax Foundation. [The highlighted parts are my emphases] There is MUCH, MUCH more. But a clear picture emerges: Romney talks a good game but his words are deceptive, and his willingness to change positions for the sake of political expediency is ASTOUNDING. His hypocrisy knows no bounds, and he habitually lies about his so-called "achievements". Dive into this, and keep one thing in mid as you do: THIS ASSESSMENT COMES FROM REPUBLICANS! Posted by Joseph at 9:38 PM No comments: Email ThisBlogThis!Share to TwitterShare to Facebook Saturday, October 6, 2012ROMNEY THE LIAR'S CLEAN ENERGY LIES FROM THE DEBATE DAY-UM did Willard lie a LOT on Wednesday night. Among the multitude of blatant falsehoods flooding out of him were those on the clean energy question. FactCheck has the goods here: Romney falsely claimed “about half” of the clean-energy companies that received U.S.-backed loans “have gone out of business.” But 26 companies received loan guarantees under a loan program cited by Romney, and three of those have filed for bankruptcy. The three firms were approved for about 6 percent of the loan guarantees. Romney incorrectly claimed the “$90 billion in breaks to the green energy world” was provided “in one year.” It was two. He stated at one point that Obama put $90 billion “into solar and wind.” But only $21 billion went for renewable energy projects, “such as the installation of wind turbines and solar panels,” according to a White House document cited by the Romney campaign. The spending also included $18 billion for transit projects and $10 billion to upgrade the nation’s electrical grid. He falsely claimed the $90 billion was equal to “about 50 years’ worth of what oil and gas receives” in tax breaks, which he estimated at $2.8 billion. By his own figures, it would have been 32 years’ worth. But it’s even less than that. The administration estimates that eliminating oil and gas tax preferences would raise about $3.9 billion a year (23 years’ worth). The industry itself says the administration would increase its taxes by $8.5 billion a year (10.5 years’ worth). He falsely claimed Obama “put $90 billion into green jobs … that would have hired 2 million teachers.” But that $90 billion included loan guarantees, not just grant money, and the government can’t hire teachers with loan guarantees. There's much more, but you get the idea. I think a lot of people who were impressed by Willard's fraudulent salesman act on Wednesday night are taking a second look and realizing that this guy lied about EVERY issue, relentlessly and remorselessly. His election would be a catastrophe both for the nation and the world. I mean, when it comes to telling lies, Willard makes Richard Nixon look like a nun. HT: Faithful reader El Posted by Joseph at 9:05 PM 2 comments: Email ThisBlogThis!Share to TwitterShare to Facebook ROMNEY THE LIAR'S SICK JOKE The amazing Paul Krugman weighs in on one of Willard's more brazen and disgusting lies from Wednesday's debate. Excerpts: “No. 1,” declared Mitt Romney in Wednesday’s debate, “pre-existing conditions are covered under my [health care] plan.” No, they aren't — as Mr. Romney’s own advisers have conceded in the past, and did again after the debate. Was Mr. Romney lying? Well, either that or he was making what amounts to a sick joke. Either way, his attempt to deceive voters on this issue was the biggest of many misleading and/or dishonest claims he made over the course of that hour and a half. Yes, President Obama did a notably bad job of responding. But I’ll leave the theater criticism to others and talk instead about the issue that should be at the heart of this election. ******** [After pointing out that Romney's plan has nothing to do with anyone's definition of pre-existing.] What Mr. Romney did in the debate, in other words, was, at best, to play a word game with voters, pretending to offer something substantive for the uninsured while actually offering nothing. For all practical purposes, he simply lied about what his policy proposals would do. How many Americans would be left out in the cold under Mr. Romney’s plan? One answer is 89 million. According to the nonpartisan Commonwealth Foundation, that’s the number of Americans who lack the “continuous coverage” that would make them eligible for health insurance under Mr. Romney’s empty promises. By the way, that’s more than a third of the U.S. population under 65 years old. Another answer is 45 million, the estimated number of people who would have health insurance if Mr. Obama were re-elected, but would lose it if Mr. Romney were to win. Read the whole thing, and then spread the word: ROMNEY'S DEBATE PERFORMANCE WAS NOTHING BUT A PACK OF LIES DESIGNED TO DECEIVE PEOPLE. We cannot--we WILL NOT--allow our beloved country to fall into the hands of this greasy, lying, used car salesman Romney. Let's step it up! Posted by Joseph at 1:14 PM 2 comments: Email ThisBlogThis!Share to TwitterShare to Facebook IT'S OFFICIAL! ROMNEY THE LIAR TOLD ***27 LIES*** IN JUST 38 MINUTES IN THE FIRST DEBATE The verdict is in, and you can read all about it here. Willard was LYING HIS FACE OFF on Wednesday night. Here are some of my faves. (I'm sure you'll have your own!): “I don’t have a $5 trillion tax cut. I don’t have a tax cut of a scale that you’re talking about.” A Tax Policy Center analysis of Romney’s proposal for a 20 percent across-the-board tax cut in all federal income tax rates, eliminating the Alternative Minimum Tax, eliminating the estate tax and other tax reductions, would reduce federal revenue $480 billion in 2015. This amounts to $5 trillion over the decade. “My view is that we ought to provide tax relief to people in the middle class. But I’m not going to reduce the share of taxes paid by high-income people.” If Romney hopes to provide tax relief to the middle class, then his $5 trillion tax cut would add to the deficit. There are not enough deductions in the tax code that primarily benefit rich people to make his math work. “My — my number-one principal is, there will be no tax cut that adds to the deficit. I want to underline that: no tax cut that adds to the deficit.” As the Tax Policy Center concluded, Romney’s plan can’t both exempt middle class families from tax cuts and remain revenue neutral. “He’s promised all these things and he can’t do them all. In order for him to cover the cost of his tax cut without adding to the deficit, he’d have to find a way to raise taxes on middle income people or people making less than $200,000 a year,” the Center found. “The president’s put it in place as much public debt — almost as much debt held by the public as all prior presidents combined.” This is not even close to being true. When Obama took office, the national debt stood at $10.626 trillion. Now the national debt is over $16 trillion. That $5.374 trillion increase is nowhere near as much debt as all the other presidents combined. “I want to take that $716 billion you’ve cut and put it back into Medicare…. But the idea of cutting $716 billion from Medicare to be able to balance the additional cost of Obamacare is, in my opinion, a mistake." There’s that number again. Romney is claiming that Obamacare siphons off $716 billion from Medicare, to the detriment of beneficiaries. In actuality, that money is saved primarily through reducing over-payments to insurance companies under Medicare Advantage, not payments to beneficiaries. Paul Ryan’s budget plan keeps those same cuts, but directs them toward tax cuts for the rich and deficit reduction. Read 'em all--AND SPREAD THE WORD about this slick-talking sociopath Willard</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349718796603</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349719068042-36</Id><Title>Romney the moderate is losing his Tea Party base.</Title><Msg>Too bad for you Mittens, You leaned to the center and now your money is drying up.............boohooo</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349719068042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:57:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349719170723-37</Id><Title>Aufish</Title><Msg>lets forget about the bet and just meet to discuss politics. what do ya say?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349719170723</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:59:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349719334303-38</Id><Topic><Title>now Prof. Rosen who is Obama's economist is speaking out against Obama.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349717205607</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:26:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was Hope and Change for the 1%. The Republicans had lost all their goodwill in the 2008 meltdown and the bailout, and things were looking very bad for the 1%. But Obama came along with that perfect complexion and those pretty words and made everything peachy for the 1%.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1349719334303</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349719365121-39</Id><Title>Obama Followers in Full Panic Mode!</Title><Msg>As Obama Starts to Free Fall with the Independent Voters.... Romney will Crush Obama on November.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349719365121</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:02:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349719815361-40</Id><Topic><Title>borrow money from China to be paid for our kids and grandkids to pay for Big Bird today</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349715056937</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:50:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big Bird? Is that some new kind of drone or something? Billions of dollars are going to the drone program--I'm definitely in favor of cutting that.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1349719815361</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349719907607-41</Id><Topic><Title>I Urge All Americans To Vote For Barack Obama</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney55</Username><Timestamp>1349551010494</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:16:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You didn't answer my question. Why do we need a war criminal in the White House?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1349719907607</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:11:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349720154179-42</Id><Topic><Title>University of Colorado Study Continues to Point to a Romney Win!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349710456041</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:34:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have them crank the model with the economic data released friday Also - ask them to release their thumb from the scale when they run the model this time Thanks</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1349720154179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:15:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349720240201-43</Id><Title>Obama's Problem with Joe Biden... How Does One Debate Prep a Buffoon?</Title><Msg>By John Whitesides WASHINGTON | Sun Oct 7, 2012 6:01pm EDT (Reuters) - He has been stereotyped as the Obama administration's gaffe-prone sideshow. But Vice President Joe Biden also is a veteran debater who was in the U.S. Senate for a quarter century and is perhaps the Democratic White House's most passionate defender of the working class. Now, with his debate against Republican vice presidential nominee Paul Ryan coming up on Thursday, Biden is under pressure to help President Barack Obama's campaign recapture the momentum it enjoyed before Obama was outmaneuvered by Republican rival Mitt Romney last week in the first of their three debates. That debate trimmed Obama's lead in the polls and raised the stakes for the lone vice presidential debate, which also will be a national debut of sorts for Ryan, the Wisconsin congressman and budget specialist. With the Romney-Ryan campaign energized, Democrats are in the surprising position of relying on Biden, a perpetual political wild card, to fire up their campaign. Democrats did get a boost in Friday's jobs report, which showed the nation's unemployment rate dipped below 8 percent last month for the first time since January 2009, the month Obama took office....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349720240201</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:17:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349720354886-44</Id><Topic><Title>I Urge All Americans To Vote For Barack Obama</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney55</Username><Timestamp>1349551010494</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:16:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am voting for Obama</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349720354886</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:19:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349720537080-45</Id><Title>President Obama Looking Good!!</Title><Msg>stock market up, manufacturing up, consumer confidence way up - - jobless rate down, dependence on foreign oil down and opponents facts are down...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349720537080</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:22:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349720753596-46</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama Looking Good!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349720537080</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except in the polls Where Romney has Surpassed Obama... the One that Counts... You are Crowing Over a .003 Improvement in Un-Employment?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349720753596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349720853345-47</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Problem with Joe Biden... How Does One Debate Prep a Buffoon?</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349720240201</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:17:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden is a Buffoon! Obama Wanted to Replace Him with Hillary, but She Gave Obama the Middle Finger!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349720853345</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:27:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349721026736-48</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama Looking Good!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349720537080</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not if You are Un-Employed... Black Un-Employment Rate at 13 + %</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349721026736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349721047899-49</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans can't be Trusted</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349710381737</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what has Team Romney to offer America... besides myths and old wives' tale..!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349721047899</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:30:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349721553244-50</Id><Topic><Title>Romney the moderate is losing his Tea Party base.</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349719068042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:57:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tea Party never liked Mitt</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349721553244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:39:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349721665033-51</Id><Title>President Obama’s success in combating Al Qaeda</Title><Msg>given President Obama’s success in combating Al Qaeda, Romney has been largely at a loss as to how to draw a contrast on national security. For most of the campaign, he has avoided articulating a foreign policy approach, in favor of single-minded focus on the economy. When he has had to take positions on international issues, Romney has used every conceivable attack Obama, even ones that are mutually exclusive, without articulating a remotely coherent vision of his own.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349721665033</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349721740837-52</Id><Topic><Title>Romney the moderate is losing his Tea Party base.</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349719068042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:57:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You Must be Illiterate as Romney is Soaring in the Polls and His Base is Excited with Money Pouring in from the Base.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349721740837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349721880473-53</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama’s success in combating Al Qaeda</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349721665033</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How the Embassy Protection Going, eh? An Ambassador and Former SEALs Killed by Al Qaeda after begging for Protection... Protection DENIED by Obama! Obama has Blood on his Hands!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349721880473</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:44:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349722125365-54</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama’s success in combating Al Qaeda</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349721665033</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How the Embassy Protection Going, eh? i say a lot better than Bush's protection of the Twin Towers</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349722125365</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:48:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349722223174-55</Id><Title>Bombshell: US Security Teams Removed From Libya Prior to Attack, Over Stevens' Objections</Title><Msg>The former head of a Special Forces "Site Security Team" in Libya tells CBS News that in spite of multiple pleas from himself and other U.S. security officials on the ground for "more, not less" security personnel, the State Department removed as many as 34 people from the country in the six months before a terrorist attack in Benghazi that killed Ambassador Chris Stevens and three others. Lt. Col. Andy Wood will appear this week at a House Oversight Committee hearing that will examine security decisions leading up to the Sept. 11 terrorist attack on the U.S. compound in Benghazi. Speaking to CBS News correspondent Sharyl Attkisson, Wood said when he found out that his own 16-member team and a six-member State Department elite force were being pulled from Tripoli in August - about a month before the assault in Benghazi - he felt, "like we were being asked to play the piano with two fingers. There was concern amongst the entire embassy staff." "They asked if we were safe," he told Attkisson. "They asked... what was going to happen, and I could only answer that what we were being told is that they're working on it - they'll get us more (security personnel), but I never saw that." Wood insists that senior staff in Libya, including Ambassador Stevens, State Department Regional Security Officer Eric Nordstrom, and himself, all wanted and had requested enhanced security. "We felt we needed more, not less," he tells Attkisson. Asked what response their repeated pleas got from the State Department in Washington, Wood says they were simply told "to do with less. For what reasons, I don't know." ABC News has more: U.S. Ambassador to Libya Chris Stevens wanted a Security Support Team, made up of 16 special operations soldiers, to stay with him in Libya after their deployment was scheduled to end in August, the commander of that security team told ABC News. The embassy staff’s “first choice was for us to stay,” Lt. Col. Andrew Wood, 55, told ABC News in an interview. “That would have been the choice of the embassy people in Tripoli.” But a senior State Department official told ABC News that the embassy’s Regional Security Officer never specifically requested that the SST’s tour be extended past August, and the official maintained there was no net loss of security personnel... When confronted with this damning report, a State Department official blames the lack of security on insufficient paperwork (security preferences were never "specifically requested") and suggests that Washington believed there would be no "net" security loss on the ground. If you believe either of those excuses, re-watch the CBS News interview above -- or read this story from ABC News, which obtained a memo showing State rejecting specific security requests in Libya. Essentially, the administration told our diplomats to do more with less and trust Libyan forces to replace the elite American security personnel. Reporting from Newsweek's Eli Lake highlights the problems with this strategy, which Amb. Stevens recognized and addressed in a diplomatic cable sent the very day he was assassinated: Just two days before the 9/11 anniversary attack on the U.S. consulate in Benghazi, two leaders of the Libyan militias responsible for keeping order in the city threatened to withdraw their men. The brinksmanship is detailed in a cable approved by Ambassador Chris Stevens and sent on the day he died in the attack, the worst assault on a U.S. diplomatic mission since the 1979 hostage crisis in Iran. The dispatch, which was marked “sensitive” but not “classified,” contained a number of other updates on the chaotic situation on the ground in post-Gaddafi Libya. The cable, reviewed by The Daily Beast, recounts how the two militia leaders, Wissam bin Ahmed and Muhammad al-Gharabi, accused the United States of supporting Mahmoud Jibril, the head of the Libyan transitional government, to be the country’s first elected prime minister. Jibril’s centrist National Forces Alliance won the popular vote in Libyan elections in July, but he lost the prime minister vote in the country’s Parliament on Sept. 12 by 94 to 92. Had he won, bin Ahmed and al-Gharabi warned they “would not continue to guarantee security in Benghazi, a critical function they asserted they were currently providing,” the cable reads. The man who beat Jibril, Mustafa Abushagur, lost a vote of no-confidence Sunday, throwing Libyan politics back into further uncertainty. The threat from the militias underscores the dangers of relying on local Libyan forces for security in the run-up to the 9/11 military-style assault. Americans must ask themselves how these appalling failures were allowed to occur, and who is responsible. The administration peddled several false tales to the public for many days after the attack, even though intelligence reports indicate that they knew better from day one. Why? Not only were requests for reinforcements declined, existing defenses were scaled back, in spite of numerous threats and attacks leading up to the 9/11 massacre. Why? I've pondered whether the White House wanted to maintain a "light footprint" perception in Libya at all costs, rooted in political considerations. If so, those costs were quite high, indeed. I'll leave you with a devastating video of the cover-up timeline, produced by Heritage. This is slowly growing into a national scandal, but here's why it should already be A1, above the fold every day:</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349722223174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349722238108-56</Id><Topic><Title>Romney the moderate is losing his Tea Party base.</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349719068042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:57:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neither have I.</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1349722238108</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:50:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349722361570-57</Id><Title>Obama Purposely Lying Again about Romney's Tax Plan, eh?</Title><Msg>Princeton Economist: Obama Campaign Is Misrepresenting My Study on Romney's Tax Plan 8:45 AM, OCT 8, 2012 • BY JOHN MCCORMACK Last night, the Obama campaign blasted out another email claiming that Mitt Romney's tax plan would either require raising taxes on the middle class or blowing a hole in the deficit. "Even the studies that Romney has cited to claim his plan adds up still show he would need to raise middle-class taxes," said the Obama campaign press release. "In fact, Harvard economist Martin Feldstein and Princeton economist Harvey Rosen both concede that paying for Romney’s tax cuts would require large tax increases on families making between $100,000 and $200,000." But that's not true. Princeton professor Harvey Rosen tells THE WEEKLY STANDARD in an email that the Obama campaign is misrepresenting his paper on Romney's tax plan: I can’t tell exactly how the Obama campaign reached that characterization of my work. It might be that they assume that Governor Romney wants to keep the taxes from the Affordable Care Act in place, despite the fact that the Governor has called for its complete repeal. The main conclusion of my study is that under plausible assumptions, a proposal along the lines suggested by Governor Romney can both be revenue neutral and keep the net tax burden on taxpayers with incomes above $200,000 about the same. That is, an increase in the tax burden on lower and middle income individuals is not required in order to make the overall plan revenue neutral. You can check the math that shows Romney's plan is mathematically possible here.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349722361570</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:52:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349722403006-58</Id><Topic><Title>romneytheliar</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349715558974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:59:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, that worked... did it ever!</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1349722403006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349722405705-59</Id><Topic><Title>Show Me The Money! BA Style!</Title><Username>gilmoredominguez678</Username><Timestamp>1349702964272</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:29:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i have 2 accounts...have had them for years..and i am not going anywhere</Msg><Username>donnywest523</Username><Timestamp>1349722405705</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:53:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349723005459-60</Id><Topic><Title>Bombshell: US Security Teams Removed From Libya Prior to Attack, Over Stevens' Objections</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1349722223174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:50:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama and Rice Purposely Lied to the American People and to the World for Days after Knowing the Truth Within 24 Hours. Obama Wanted to hide his Foreign Policy Failures, but His Lies Blew Up in his Face! Can't wait to See How Obama Tries to Lie/Spin his Way Out of the Inconvenient Truth during the Foreign Policy Debate.!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349723005459</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:03:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349723298459-61</Id><Title>Shamefully Racist Obama Followers... Shame!</Title><Msg>TWITTER EXPLODES AFTER BLACK ACTRESS ENDORSES ROMNEY AS THE ‘ONLY CHOICE FOR YOUR FUTURE’ Posted on October 8, 2012 at 12:27am by Actress Stacey Dash, who has starred in everything from the 90#$%$ Clueless to CSI, prompted a firestorm on Twitter after publicly endorsing Republican nominee Mitt Romney, and then standing by her opinion. “Vote for Romney. The only choice for your future. @mittromney @teamromney #mittromney #VOTE #voteromney,” Dash wrote on her official Twitter page, accompanied by a photo of herself with an American flag. Not long after, presumed Obama supporters began insulting Dash for her opinion, saying she isn’t “black” enough, several even asking if the actress would just “kill herself.” One man wrote: “This hurts but you a Romney lover and you slutting yourself to the white man only proves why no black man married u @REALStaceyDash.” As news of Dash’s treatment spread, however, First Amendment-lovers nationwide began voicing their support for the actress using the hashtag #ISupportStaceyDash. Twitchy captured some of the worst responses to Dash’s Romney endorsement (content warning):</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349723298459</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349723446399-62</Id><Topic><Title>The Incredibly Expensive Big Bird</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349723237964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:07:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big Bird is Now on Other Channels other than PBS... Wake up Dik! Americans Have Choices... Obama is Not One of Them.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349723446399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349724066032-63</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans can't be Trusted</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349710381737</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What About the Convicted Felon George Soros and Hollywood's Billionaires Donating/Supporting Obama?</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349724066032</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349724182112-64</Id><Title>Gallup Poll</Title><Msg>According to Gallup's latest seven-day tracking poll, President Barack Obama has a slight 49%-46% edge over Romney among registered voters nationwide, which is within the survey's sampling error. But Gallup breaks down their poll into pre- and post- debate figures.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349724182112</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:23:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349724237192-65</Id><Topic><Title>The Incredibly Expensive Big Bird</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349723237964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:07:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, he is one of them</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349724237192</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:23:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349724320497-66</Id><Title>There is MUCH, MUCH more</Title><Msg>There is MUCH, MUCH more. But a clear picture emerges: Romney talks a good game but his words are deceptive, and his willingness to change positions for the sake of political expediency is ASTOUNDING. His hypocrisy knows no bounds, and he habitually lies about his so-called "achievements". Dive into this, and keep one thing in mid as you do: THIS ASSESSMENT COMES FROM REPUBLICANS!</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349724320497</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349724988071-67</Id><Topic><Title>Ah, Those Open-Minded Neocons From The South</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349723149770</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:05:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are all theories, which means they have yet to be proven. In the case of evolution, it is looking more and more like a theory everyday the billions of generations of fruit flies keep staying fruit flies. Note Darwin wrote about the evolution of species not species of 1 into another. Now in academia there are laws, like the Law of Supply and Demand which for some strange reason you libs refuse to believe in and keep trying to break with my tax money - meeting only failure.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1349724988071</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349725386913-68</Id><Title>Jack Welch gone Cuckoo!!</Title><Msg>Oct. 6 (Bloomberg) -- A good conspiracy theory is irrefutable. A bad one usually collapses when confronted by reality. The claim by some supporters of Republican challenger Mitt Romney that President Barack Obama’s Chicago-based campaign doctored September’s unemployment figures for political gain fall into the second category, according members of both parties who have served in the government’s economic data system. Jack Welch, the former chief executive officer of General Electric Co., touched off an Internet-based frenzy yesterday when he suggested on Twitter that Obama’s team lowered the country’s unemployment rate to 7.8 percent to give the president a boost. “Unbelievable jobs numbers. . . these Chicago guys will do anything. . . can’t debate so change numbers,” he wrote.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349725386913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:43:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349725805814-69</Id><Topic><Title>Jack Welch gone Cuckoo!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349725386913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:43:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We will Wait for the Revised Numbers and See Who was Correct. Jack is a very Smart and Successful Man! You Won't Make a Living Going Against Him.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349725805814</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349725952632-70</Id><Topic><Title>There is MUCH, MUCH more</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349724320497</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:25:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a Bunch of Crap from Terrified Liberals as they See Obama Sinking in the polls, eh? Can't wait to See Obama Try to Defend his Foreign Policy Failures...</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349725952632</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:52:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349726676015-71</Id><Topic><Title>Shamefully Racist Obama Followers... Shame!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349723298459</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:08:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you expect them to say?There still waitng for obummer to buy them a new flat screen.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1349726676015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:04:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349727085058-72</Id><Topic><Title>Five Great Reasons Not To Vote Republican</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349726967442</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:09:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get the freak out of my country, you socialist stooge</Msg><Username>dr_ooopha</Username><Timestamp>1349727085058</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349727116816-73</Id><Topic><Title>Five Great Reasons Not To Vote Republican</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349726967442</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:09:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Garbage... Obama Followers are Grasping at Straws as they See Obama Slip Sliding Away! The Mo is with Romney.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349727116816</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:11:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349727298671-74</Id><Topic><Title>Ah, Those Open-Minded Neocons From The South</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349723149770</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:05:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The creation by God ALSO is yet to be proven. Darwin postulated species change by adapting to a NEED to change. What has changed in the last 100 years that required fruit flies to adapt? Not DDT -- it didn't nothing every example of any species.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1349727298671</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:14:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349727443915-75</Id><Topic><Title>Ah, Those Open-Minded Neocons From The South</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349723149770</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:05:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"it didn't nothing..."... What? Government School!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349727443915</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:17:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349727721596-76</Id><Topic><Title>Jack Welch gone Cuckoo!!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1349725386913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:43:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neither are a whole lot of Americans who tried as hard to go along with him as was humanly possible. You see, very few Americans can even survive on $5-10/day. For that reason ALONE, Neutron Jack despises all us greedy American workers (including engineers).</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1349727721596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:22:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349727884347-77</Id><Topic><Title>Ah, Those Open-Minded Neocons From The South</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349723149770</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:05:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On the other hand, it has been demonstrated that certain soecies of microbes HAVE adapted -- to be resistant to antibiotics like penicillin.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1349727884347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:24:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349727954331-78</Id><Topic><Title>Ah, Those Open-Minded Neocons From The South</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349723149770</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:05:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>correction: ...several species of microbes...</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1349727954331</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:25:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349728074747-79</Id><Topic><Title>Ah, Those Open-Minded Neocons From The South</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349723149770</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:05:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I meant to type "nothingize," blister-brain.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1349728074747</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:27:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349728787187-80</Id><Title>Gallup: Romney pulls even with Obama after biggest debate win in recorded history</Title><Msg>Gallup poll numbers released Monday continue to demonstrate an apparent Mitt Romney surge, with the Republican nominee pulling even with President Obama on the heels of what Gallup deemed the biggest debate victory in recorded history. The new Gallup numbers show registered voters overwhelmingly considered Romney the winner of the debate in Denver. Seventy-two percent gave Romney the win, while 20 percent said Obama did the better job. Gallup reported the 52-point victory is the biggest the polling firm has ever measured -- the closest was Bill Clinton's 42-point win over George H.W. Bush in a 1992 debate. The sentiment appeared to have implications for Romney's national standing. Polling in the three days after the debate showed the candidates tied at 47 percent each. In the three days prior, Obama was leading by 5 points. The Gallup numbers follow a national Rasmussen survey which showed Romney leading 49-47 percent. Rasmussen also released several swing-state polls on Friday showing Romney pulling roughly even with Obama in the wake of the debate. Read more: http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/10/08/romney-pulls-even-with-obama-in-first-post-debate-gallup-poll/#ixzz28k4fSgAV</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349728787187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:39:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349728892698-81</Id><Topic><Title>Gallup Poll</Title><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1349724182112</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:23:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>my, my how skunk lies "Gallup poll numbers released Monday continue to demonstrate an apparent Mitt Romney surge, with the Republican nominee pulling even with President Obama on the heels of what Gallup deemed the biggest debate victory in recorded history. The new Gallup numbers show registered voters overwhelmingly considered Romney the winner of the debate in Denver. Seventy-two percent gave Romney the win, while 20 percent said Obama did the better job. Gallup reported the 52-point victory is the biggest the polling firm has ever measured -- the closest was Bill Clinton's 42-point win over George H.W. Bush in a 1992 debate. The sentiment appeared to have implications for Romney's national standing. Polling in the three days after the debate showed the candidates tied at 47 percent each. In the three days prior, Obama was leading by 5 points. The Gallup numbers follow a national Rasmussen survey which showed Romney leading 49-47 percent. Rasmussen also released several swing-state polls on Friday showing Romney pulling roughly even with Obama in the wake of the debate. Read more: http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/10/08/romney-pulls-even-with-obama-in-first-post-debate-gallup-poll/#ixzz28k4fSgAV</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349728892698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349729929699-82</Id><Topic><Title>Five Great Reasons Not To Vote Republican</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349726967442</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:09:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I only need one reason not to vote for them , his name is ROMENY</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1349729929699</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349730100371-83</Id><Title>Why Do Democrats Hate Freedom of Choice?</Title><Msg>They hate the idea of people choosing what schools their children can attend. They fight against the freedom to choose where charitable dollars go, they hate the idea of free trade.....about the only free choice they want is the freedom to kill innocent babies. .</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349730100371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:01:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349730229758-84</Id><Title>Sir Paul is so dumb he was taken to the cleaners and lost half his fortune to .......</Title><Msg>.....a one legged woman,,,,,,,LMAO...</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349730229758</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:03:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349730983549-85</Id><Title>My Belly Hertz.....</Title><Msg>.....every time a certain poster tries in vain to say something positive about Obumer. The desperation is hilarious. He has his head in the sand, his toe jam stinks, and I'm drinking his beer......life is good.......oh yea......Romney will win.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349730983549</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:16:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349731074357-86</Id><Topic><Title>Sir Paul is so dumb he was taken to the cleaners and lost half his fortune to .......</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349730229758</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:03:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots... he scores!!!</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1349731074357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:17:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349731267645-87</Id><Topic><Title>Sir Paul is so dumb he was taken to the cleaners and lost half his fortune to .......</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349730229758</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:03:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll always have a leg up on Sir Paul when it comes to money........heather says so.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349731267645</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:21:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349732021498-88</Id><Title>Hallucinations of Obama supporters</Title><Msg>Being friends with Sir dufus Paul Thinking Beyonce has half the class, intelligence, body and good looks as Stacey Dash. That his IQ is above single Digits That Obumer will get a second term.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349732021498</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349732583910-89</Id><Topic><Title>Ah, Those Open-Minded Neocons From The South</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349723149770</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:05:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Secretly they do believe in evolution. They believe monkeys evolved from Obama's Kenyan ancestors. :-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349732583910</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:43:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349733092814-90</Id><Topic><Title>Ah, Those Open-Minded Neocons From The South</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_123</Username><Timestamp>1349723149770</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:05:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finally........a truthful politician.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349733092814</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349733248920-91</Id><Title>Is Obama toast???????</Title><Msg>.......yes, I think so.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349733248920</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:54:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349733375102-92</Id><Topic><Title>help the name of the economist Obama has been misquoting? Since the attack dogs or Democraps have been calling Romney a liar</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349733115409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:51:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama gets most of his economic ideas from Charles Ponzi.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349733375102</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:56:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349733517015-93</Id><Title>Why they won't let Obama have a teleprompter at the debates.</Title><Msg>Because they can't find one with enough memory for all the ahhhs, uhhhhh, ahhhhh, ummmmm, ahhh, uhhhhh, ahhhhh, ummmmm, ahhh, uhhhhh, ahhhhh, ummmmm, ahhh, uhhhhh, ahhhhh, ummmmm, ahhh, uhhhhh, ahhhhh, ummmmm, for each question he's asked.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349733517015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:58:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349733958017-94</Id><Title>Did Obamer eat Bo yet?</Title><Msg>Just wondering because we never see Bo anymore.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1349733958017</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 18:05:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349735195084-95</Id><Title>Anyone know What happened to Obumer's 142% lead?</Title><Msg>.....or did it just disappear when he was exposed by someone who actually had a job, created jobs and knew what a job was?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349735195084</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 18:26:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349736184371-96</Id><Title>Why would any Defence Contractor employee vote for Obama??</Title><Msg>You will be getting your layoff slips soon because of the fiscal cliff!!! Nov. 2nd is the the last day Boeing has to inform you guys, good luck!!!</Msg><Username>cap_pig11</Username><Timestamp>1349736184371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 18:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349736319638-97</Id><Title>Obama Rolling Down Hill Like a Snowball Heading to Hell ! Obama is Cooked.</Title><Msg>All Polls Show Obama Losing Ground... The Mo is With Mitt....</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349736319638</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 18:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349736598254-98</Id><Title>Romney took Obumer to the woodshed....</Title><Msg>.....and gave him some good old fashioned school'n.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349736598254</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 18:49:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349736833766-99</Id><Title>There's No Way</Title><Msg>There can be 23 million Americans out of work with an unemployment rate at 7.8%. There's something fishy about those Government Numbers like that being issued less than 40 days from the Presidential race. Can't trust Obama or the Government coming up with factual numbers of any kind any longer. Unemployment is still at 14%. This is America's longest recession since the Great Depression. Obama spends all his time spinning and dodging his real record or in his case no record of improvement. But yet there are still ignorant fools out there who will blindly vote for Obama because he is personable and because he is admired for his coolness. Everything else be damned. Show me his record!!!!!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1349736833766</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 18:53:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349737343938-100</Id><Topic><Title>Why would any Defence Contractor employee vote for Obama??</Title><Username>cap_pig11</Username><Timestamp>1349736184371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 18:43:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.......................</Msg><Username>worth_repeating4</Username><Timestamp>1349737343938</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349737377450-101</Id><Title>MILITARY TIMES : R 66% O 26%...</Title><Msg>The professional core of the U.S. military overwhelmingly favors Mitt Romney over President Obama in the upcoming election — but not because of any particular military issues, according to a new poll of more than 3,100 active and reserve troops. Respondents rated the economy and the candidates’ character as their most important considerations and all but ignored the war in Afghanistan as an issue of concern. The Military Times Poll is a secure email survey of active-duty, National Guard and reserve members who are subscribers to the Military Times newspapers (see How We Did It, below). This population is older and more senior than the military population at large, but it is representative of the professional core of the all-volunteer force. The 3,100 respondents — roughly two-thirds active-duty and one-third reserve component members — are about 80 percent white and 91 percent male. Forty percent are in paygrades E-5 through E-8, while more than 35 percent are in paygrades O-3 through O-5. Almost 80 percent of respondents have a college degree — including 27 percent with a graduate degree and more than 11 percent with a post-graduate degree — while an additional 18.5 percent have some college under their belts. And they are battle-hardened; almost 29 percent have spent more than two cumulative years deployed since 9/11, while a similar percentage has spent one to two cumulative years deployed. The Military Times poll shows that Republicans continue to enjoy overwhelming support among the military’s professional ranks.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349737377450</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:02:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349737463418-102</Id><Topic><Title>Romney took Obumer to the woodshed....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349736598254</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 18:49:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, he got away with a lot of statements that contradicted earlier statements. Mittens is a business man and will say whatever it takes to close the deal. He has no moral compass. That said, he spanked Obama. I was shocked.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1349737463418</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349737544123-103</Id><Title>Emergency Rooms Overwhelmed by Obama supporters having heart attacks........</Title><Msg>......and emotional breakdowns.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349737544123</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:05:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349737920468-104</Id><Topic><Title>Shamefully Racist Obama Followers... Shame!</Title><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349723298459</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:08:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There still waitng " Uniposter please report back to 3rd grade. Return when you can differentiate: 1. They're 2. Their 3. There</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1349737920468</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:12:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349738356265-105</Id><Title>Who's the Liar - the Businessman or the Politician</Title><Msg>Businessmen who lie and don't keep their word soon go out of business. Honest men attract business. Politicians who never were in business and spent their whole life in government or as community agitators have had to live by lying.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349738356265</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349738869683-106</Id><Topic><Title>MILITARY TIMES : R 66% O 26%...</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349737377450</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:02:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No Wonder the Pathetic Obama Wants to Suppress the Military Vote! Shame on Hussein.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349738869683</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:27:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349738981069-107</Id><Topic><Title>Who's the Liar - the Businessman or the Politician</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349738356265</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:19:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell me, what color is the sky in your world?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1349738981069</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349739203377-108</Id><Title>NYTs Hates/Mistreats their Own Union While Espousing Pro-Union Rhetoric... Liberal Hypocrisy!</Title><Msg>NYT Union Chief: Times Is Hypocritical about Unions By Charles C. W. Cooke October 8, 2012 5:15 P.M. Comments4 I wandered down to the New York Times building in Manhattan this afternoon to watch the walkout, and I spoke to a union representative. I asked him whether he was concerned by the gap between the Times’s treatment of its unionized staff, and the pro-union rhetoric of the paper’s editorial board. He told me, “We have a problem with that. We’ve realized that what we’ve said in the New York Times editorial pages is not what is being followed…they fly in the face of their own editorial board…it’s just money”: On June 6th, the Times wrote an editorial that claimed, “Labor, so long in decline in the private sector, is also losing its clout in states and cities, unable to match or withstand the unfettered bank accounts of industry.” Indeed.</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349739203377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:33:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349739360544-109</Id><Topic><Title>Who's the Liar - the Businessman or the Politician</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349738356265</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:19:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a Proven Liar... Over and Over Again!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349739360544</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:36:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349739561769-110</Id><Topic><Title>Emergency Rooms Overwhelmed by Obama supporters having heart attacks........</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349737544123</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>put Dik, err Paul, Black... on and on at the Top of the List They are Desperate Now!</Msg><Username>imaccom</Username><Timestamp>1349739561769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:39:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349740002021-111</Id><Topic><Title>Why would any Defence Contractor employee vote for Obama??</Title><Username>cap_pig11</Username><Timestamp>1349736184371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 18:43:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, the white house has told contractors they dont have to adhere to the rule so they can wait till after the election to hand out notices. It has been talked about at length last week in the media.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1349740002021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:46:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349740145594-112</Id><Topic><Title>Why would any Defence Contractor employee vote for Obama??</Title><Username>cap_pig11</Username><Timestamp>1349736184371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 18:43:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope - search on M-12-19 from the executive office of the president ( POTUS) subject Memorandum for the Chief finacial Officers . . . Bottom line - Gubbermintm contractors are tweaked to NOT file required WARN notices on Nov 1 or 2, " to avoid confusion, yada yada" - and if they DO NOT file WARN NOTICES, Then the Government will pickm up all legal costs, and settlements etc in any case where they ( contractors ) get sued by the sheep- er slaves who get hosed/clipped/ and dumped. Its just a cost of buying votes - whats left in YOUR wallet ? send it in</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1349740145594</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:49:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349740953382-113</Id><Title>Ryan Vs Biden</Title><Msg>I heard Ryan got Gary Busey to play Biden in debate practice, but many in the GOP are worried that Gary isn't crazy enough.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1349740953382</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:02:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349742150200-114</Id><Topic><Title>Polls reveal after listening to Romney last week, they really do not want a job</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349741102140</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>posting this on every political board so people can see what Romney supporters think of them. Thanks and keep them coming.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1349742150200</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:22:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349742456131-115</Id><Title>Romney is a theif and a liar</Title><Msg>Stereotyping your neighbors doesn't help. God bless the President and the USA</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1349742456131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:27:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349742526526-116</Id><Title>God bless the President and the USA</Title><Msg>Our troops need a real President like President Obama. Not a joker like Romney</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1349742526526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349742587424-117</Id><Title>When will Romney discuss his tax plan and his taxes?</Title><Msg>I would like to know</Msg><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1349742587424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:29:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349743747598-118</Id><Topic><Title>God bless the President and the USA</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1349742526526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And just what have you been smoking ?</Msg><Username>kingslmon6</Username><Timestamp>1349743747598</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:49:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349743747702-119</Id><Topic><Title>God bless the President and the USA</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1349742526526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And just what have you been smoking ?</Msg><Username>kingslmon6</Username><Timestamp>1349743747702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:49:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349746380526-120</Id><Topic><Title>When will Romney discuss his tax plan and his taxes?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1349742587424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:29:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When will Mitt or any Repube discuss their treasonous actions against America and it's Veterans. Two wars - off budget Huge tax cuts during a time of war-off budget Supporting/initiationg war profiteering while leaving many Troops with inferior equipment/support Stop loss extentions for Active Military yet no Draft Filabuster the Veteran's Jobs Act Filabuster funds for payments of high tech prosthisis and PTSD care for Veteran</Msg><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1349746380526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 21:33:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349748184852-121</Id><Topic><Title>When will Romney discuss his tax plan and his taxes?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1349742587424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:29:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When will Obama admit that the U.S. embassy in Libya was hit by terrorists and that the video had nothing to do with it? When will Obama admit that he lied about all of it? When will Obama admit that his administration denied requested security support for the embassy before the attack? Obama: Romney is a murderer Obama: Romney is a liar Obama: Romney doesn't pay any taxes Obama: Romney doesn't "care" about the poor Obama: Romney is a felon Obama: It is not my fault, everyone else screwed up.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1349748184852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 22:03:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349749387185-122</Id><Topic><Title>Why would any Defence Contractor employee vote for Obama??</Title><Username>cap_pig11</Username><Timestamp>1349736184371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 18:43:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Falmouthharbor, If Obama wins, he is happy to go ahead with the defense industry reductions. Therefore, the delay (till after elections) is pure and blatant politics and the offer to pay for the "legal fees" to account for legal action due to WARN violations is tenuous. Obama can simply intone, "oh, well, I though that we could do that." No skin off his back. There is no legal basis for his offer for picking up the legal tabs. If Romney wins and the Democrats do not have controlling power of the congress, the defense reductions will be looked at again. However, the law stipulates that the WARN notices must be made either 60 or 90 days in advance of the actual layoffs. Boeing and all of the other affected contractors are risking large sums of money assuming that the current President is not lying (and gets re-elected) or that Romney can change it in time. Notice also that Obama offered to simply pay for the "legal fees", not the penalties and the punitive damages incured. Obama is a master of deception and double-speak. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1349749387185</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 22:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349751832620-123</Id><Title>Pew: Romney Leads By 4 In Post-Debate Survey</Title><Msg>In the first national poll to be conducted entirely after the opening presidential debate, former Massachusetts Governor Mitt Romney now leads President Barack Obama by 4 points. The poll, conducted by Pew Research Center from Thursday through Sunday and released on Monday, shows Romney leading Obama among likely voters nationwide, 49 percent to 45 percent. That's a stark contrast from Pew's mid-September poll after both parties' conventions, which showed Obama up 8 points among likely voters. The dramatic 12-point swing in Pew's poll from Obama to Romney is perhaps the strongest piece of evidence to date that the president has paid a political price for his listless performance in the Denver debate. Story on Yahoo News Bye, bye, Barack.</Msg><Username>dfwskier</Username><Timestamp>1349751832620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:03:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349751853284-124</Id><Topic><Title>When will Romney discuss his tax plan and his taxes?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1349742587424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:29:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A new record in the bald-faced false witness category for BB. May you gain some wisdom and humility some day.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1349751853284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:04:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349752080060-125</Id><Topic><Title>Romney took Obumer to the woodshed....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349736598254</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 18:49:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of contradictions, here's what Willard said Feb 22 this year: "We're going to cut taxes on everyone across the country by 20 percent, including the top 1 percent." Then last week: "I'm not going to reduce the share of taxes paid by high-income people. High income people are doing just fine in this economy."</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1349752080060</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:08:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349752400321-126</Id><Title>MNF</Title><Msg>Is there an update on tonight's game? When I found out it was the 666th MNF game, I had to destroy the tv so it wouldn't broadcast this satanic event into my living room.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1349752400321</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:13:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349753569354-127</Id><Topic><Title>Romney took Obumer to the woodshed....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1349736598254</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 18:49:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not that he's a bad debater, he's a bad president! I think many union members will vote against him!!</Msg><Username>cap_pig11</Username><Timestamp>1349753569354</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:32:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349753797076-128</Id><Topic><Title>When will Romney discuss his tax plan and his taxes?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1349742587424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:29:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BB Obama: Romney is a murderer; n/a#$%$ Obama: Romney is a liar; A serial liar IMHO... but I would guess you do your political and stock DD on a MB... Obama: Romney doesn't pay any taxes; certainly less tham most as a % of income and borderline illegal hiding money overseas to avoid US taxes. Obama: Romney doesn't "care" about the poor; What do you think? Obama: Romney is a felon; would be W/O his lawyers; ($77k deduction for a 'Dressage horse'?) Obama: It is not my fault, everyone else screwed up; Acctually, that was part of my point, also that people like Rawmoney and you support the decisions that have bankrupt America and refuse to help pay our debts for those decisions...GLTY sir...</Msg><Username>manferfish</Username><Timestamp>1349753797076</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:36:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>