<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-27"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361942690141-1</Id><Title>Good bop, voibrations</Title><Msg>no weather ice skating on natural lake nar 50 degrees F no grammy for the beach boys ? led zep ? grateful dead ? allop, i havwe idnetified the r\problem iun st moritz fluffy pillows and tea</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1361942690141</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 00:24:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361943108191-2</Id><Topic><Title>Good bop, voibrations</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1361942690141</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 00:24:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>soschi 2014 piont the tuna and the dolphin will follow ina ///can s</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1361943108191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 00:31:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361945021584-3</Id><Title>Can't this wait... the guitar gently weeps</Title><Msg>donate it all to the national trust the batteries o the moon</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1361945021584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 01:03:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361945276853-4</Id><Topic><Title>Can't this wait... the guitar gently weeps</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1361945021584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 01:03:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>unless your name is martha my der-the 12/gs14 point buck</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1361945276853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 01:07:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361945565709-5</Id><Title>seniors gitting ripped again</Title><Msg>These low interest rates, what are they good for? Not much as the current admin. is anti business. The economy is in shambles. Not so many businesses using the low interest rates. Home buying down, many of the underwater loans can't refinance to benefit. And seniors who relied on interest income to cover some of their retirement, not much help there. Now its coming to where there are banks in UK that are going negative interest rates. that's where the depositor instead of getting interest, will instead pay a fee to park their saving in the bank. It will be here soon enough.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1361945565709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 01:12:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361948049048-6</Id><Title>lol, no pension for the new hire, it sounds like BA is replacing old eng. workers with new hire fast</Title><Msg>to save more $$$ and more $$$ to top excutives..........lol</Msg><Username>styuiksv</Username><Timestamp>1361948049048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 01:54:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361950139182-7</Id><Title>40 mule tea,m</Title><Msg>Type message</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1361950139182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 02:28:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361950483266-8</Id><Topic><Title>40 mule tea,m</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1361950139182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 02:28:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yo[' borax from the mine and some gold.... type message here</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1361950483266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 02:34:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361961697217-9</Id><Topic><Title>Comparing Democrat's Marxism With the TEA Party's Freedom Agenda</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1361831595630</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 17:33:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Raven likes his Twinkies paid for by working tax payers. What a DFC.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361961697217</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 05:41:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361961784262-10</Id><Topic><Title>Vietnam admits they deploy Bloggers to support government views.</Title><Username>vendetta35000</Username><Timestamp>1361925584575</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 19:39:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you think that China is the model?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361961784262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 05:43:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361963492540-11</Id><Title>klasjdjawjifjiwa</Title><Msg>zllxclSKclsaP</Msg><Username>rndyjensen</Username><Timestamp>1361963492540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 06:11:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361965429134-12</Id><Title>Good News...kinda</Title><Msg>The first step in solving a problem is admitting that one exists...progress here..see WSJ" government investigators' limited experience with such devices is hobbling efforts to determine precisely why they burned"</Msg><Username>nidan7500</Username><Timestamp>1361965429134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 06:43:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361965840539-13</Id><Topic><Title>lol, no pension for the new hire, it sounds like BA is replacing old eng. workers with new hire fast</Title><Username>styuiksv</Username><Timestamp>1361948049048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 01:54:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yesssss....</Msg><Username>tallicat9300</Username><Timestamp>1361965840539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 06:50:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361971302120-14</Id><Title>Sequester fears take mainstream media hysteria to new heights</Title><Msg>R.E.M. sang, “It’s the end of the world as we know it.” If ever there were a theme song for the liberal media’s coverage of the sequester the band's iconic song would be it. The “broad and sweeping federal budget cuts” being debated on the Hill are being reported breathlessly in the news media. NBC’s Brian Williams called it “high anxiety” and a “Good Morning America” graphic sounded the alarm: “Seven Days to Fiscal Emergency.” ABC’s David Kerley said the sequester “sounds like a disaster movie.” He didn’t scream, but he still has time. In one of the best examples of political theater, famed Washington Post editor and reporter Bob Woodward reminded the world recently that the sequester was Obama’s idea. That set in motion a bizarre circumstance where Republicans were relying on Woodward and Democrats were trying to discredit him as a tool of the right. Yes, this was the same Bob Woodward who helped destroy Republican President Richard Nixon. Turn on almost any network newscast and there’s one theme. The federal budget might be cut! The horror! The New York Times warned the $85 billion in budget cuts – just 2.4 percent of the budget – were ushering in an era of “federal austerity.” The story began in a typically apocalyptic manner: “Fear of U.S. Cuts Grows In States Where Aid Flows – Recovery Seen At Risk – Wide Impact Looms on Jobs, Tax Revenue, and Schools.” Even the Times’ pretend conservative David Brooks blasted Republicans as “mindless anti-government fanatics.” The Huffington Post screamed with predictable hyperbole “AUSTERITY COUNTDOWN: 4 DAYS TIL PAIN” across its front page like Mr. T had taken over headline writing. It was followed by subtle subheads like: "'Prepare To Suffer’” and “‘The Road To A Lawless Society Is Being Paved.’” Who knows, tomorrow’s headline may lament “dogs and cats living together.” Every major old-school news outlet has shouted about the “worst-case scenario for government spending cuts,” as if they were deliberately doing the bidding of the liberal Democrats who couldn’t find a way to cut in a Ginsu factory. We’ve been told about cuts in research, cuts in jobs, defense-crippling cuts at the Pentagon that keep carriers in port and even vaccines that won’t ever get made. CBS’s Wyatt Andrews warned on February 25, about NIH research that “will one day find a drug to diminish the impact of old age.” As if prescription drug firms wouldn’t pay for that research … if they thought it potentially viable. Yet the sad truth is that in the eyes of the news media, every government program is perfect. It’s those evil Republicans who won’t raise taxes, after just raising them only two months ago. Turn on almost any network newscast and there’s one theme. The federal budget might be cut! The horror! By March 1, when the cuts start taking effect, the broadcast networks could well be using Hindenburg graphics with desperate government workers bailing out of jobs in mid-air to avoid the explosion. Not all journalists have been bad on this – just most.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361971302120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:21:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361972584059-15</Id><Topic><Title>Sequester fears take mainstream media hysteria to new heights</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361971302120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:21:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Headlines: "Austerity kills govt jobs!" Yiiikes! Really? Govt UNION jobs? HAHAHAHAHA Jobs where some duffus sits at a desk with a big staff of help, and waits for their early retirement, and big pension plan paid for by the real world workin stiff? Let Austerity begin!</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361972584059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:43:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361972676135-16</Id><Topic><Title>Leaked BA buy out report!</Title><Username>dennis.jacksonny</Username><Timestamp>1361970587265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:09:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rumor has it that Hasbro or Matel will buy Boeing.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361972676135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:44:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361972903364-17</Id><Topic><Title>Leaked BA buy out report!</Title><Username>dennis.jacksonny</Username><Timestamp>1361970587265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:09:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great news</Msg><Username>patrickthomas294</Username><Timestamp>1361972903364</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:48:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361972952404-18</Id><Title>Obama Tells America: “You Can’t Do Things by Yourself”...its true</Title><Msg>Just said it in a speech....Pretty Amazing we have a President this Anti Rugged Individualism and this Anti American and everything America stands for</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361972952404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:49:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361973808804-19</Id><Topic><Title>Gigantic Update for BA . **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>chacon.cross</Username><Timestamp>1361970258649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:04:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well done</Msg><Username>rodriguezjohn500</Username><Timestamp>1361973808804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:03:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361973905750-20</Id><Title>Durable Goods sending a message</Title><Msg>It's big drop this morning was affected by a drop is BA's sales. This can be translated into lower revenues and profits this quarter. Brace yourself.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361973905750</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:05:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361974010030-21</Id><Title>Obama and Democrats Working Hard to Take us to a High Level of Mediocrity</Title><Msg>Mediocrity and the mediocre class must be protected, coddled, and pandered to. Tell your kids to quit striving for good grades tell them Cs are good enough. Live in a mediocre home in a mediocre neighborhood, send your kids to a mediocre school, earn a mediocre income and Democrats will adore you. Why? Because they Know more American are willing to settle for mediocrity than the hard work it takes to strive for excellence and high achievement and where ever more Americans are, there are more votes to keep them in power earning high incomes, living in high class neighborhoods, private schools for kids and receiving excellent benefits. Gotta love em.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361974010030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:06:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361974266155-22</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Democrats Working Hard to Take us to a High Level of Mediocrity</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361974010030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:06:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Want answers where all of this massive debt Obama, and the left have created you only have to look to Greece, and the rest of Europe. The leftists have created a huge imbalance of govt workers vs. the private sector that pays for all of them. Govt workers that expect higher pay for less hrs. of work than their private sector counterparts. They expect early retirement. They expect a big fat pension plan, and when the money runs out as it is now in the USA as well as in European countries?....they take to the streets and turn over and burn cars, break out store windows, and steal. That is what you can look forward to in this country.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361974266155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:11:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361974350138-23</Id><Title>BA Should Make a Plane Out of Their BA Shares That Do Not Drop</Title><Msg>Trading at 5-year highs on news that BA cannot ship their fire-prone planes.</Msg><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1361974350138</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:12:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361974529685-24</Id><Title>BA Still Not Know What Caused Battery Fires But BA Has a Magic Fix for It</Title><Msg>BA knows what it does not know and does not know what it knows.</Msg><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1361974529685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:15:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361974745389-25</Id><Title>2 Planes Out of 50 Have Fires = Only a 4% Failuire Rate in 3 Months</Title><Msg>4% should be good enough for government work.</Msg><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1361974745389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:19:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361974800345-26</Id><Title>Joe Dope and the mediocre guy</Title><Msg>Just what the he l l do you think you guys are? If you cant understand the objective of the liberals then that sez a lot about you -- it says you are mediocre yourselves. All your bloviating about how great it is to be a success is just simply B__S. If you woke up and looked around you would see a lot of aged, sick and poor and homeless who are unable to help themselves on the meeger savings they have- which they were skrewwed out of by the big companies like Boeing who threw them away the minute they got into their 50's. These are the people who were dropped or otherwise denied health insurance or weren't able to get the education they needed for a good job for example. The assistance of social security for those that can get it, or medicare or even welfare is always so little that no one who receives it wants so little out of life. That person has no choice but to take what is offered to him. This kind of life can never be the goal of the average individual but only a safety net</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361974800345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:20:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361975039181-27</Id><Title>The White House Court Jesters of Sequester</Title><Msg>Traffic alert: There's a massive clown car pileup in the Beltway. And with the White House court jesters of sequester behind the wheel, no one is safe. Fiscal sanity, of course, is the ultimate victim. President Obama has been warning America that if Congress allows mandatory spending "cuts" of a piddly-widdly 2 percent to go into effect this week, the sky will fall. The manufactured crisis of "sequestration" was Obama's idea in the first place. But that hasn't stopped the Chicken Little in Chief from surrounding himself with every last teacher, senior citizen and emergency responder who will be catastrophically victimized by hardhearted Republicans. Curses on those meanie Republicans! How dare they acquiesce to the very plan for "cuts" -- or rather, negligible reductions in the explosive rate of federal spending growth -- that Obama himself hatched? How low will the kick-the-can Democrats go? Among the ridiculous claims the administration is making: The National Drug Intelligence Center will lose $2 million from its $20 million budget. That scary factoid appears in an ominous Office of Management and Budget report purporting to calculate the Sequester Disaster. So lock the doors and hide the children, right? Wrong. As Reason magazine's Mike Riggs points out, the NDIC shut down in June 2012, and some of its responsibilities were absorbed by the Drug Enforcement Administration. Ready for more reckless, feckless farce? Department of Homeland Security Secretary Janet Napolitano played Henny Penny during a panicked speech at the Brookings Institution Tuesday. She warned that her agency's "core critical mission areas" would be undermined by the sequester. To cynically underscore the point, "waves" of illegal aliens were released this week from at least three detention centers in Texas, Florida and Louisiana, according to the Fort Worth Star Telegram. MM</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361975039181</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:23:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361975404249-28</Id><Topic><Title>Leaked BA buy out report!</Title><Username>dennis.jacksonny</Username><Timestamp>1361970587265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:09:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>full detailed report. thanks</Msg><Username>cwilson_70</Username><Timestamp>1361975404249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:30:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361975413458-29</Id><Topic><Title>BA Insider Trading Reported !!!</Title><Username>doris.shealey</Username><Timestamp>1361811207875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 11:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good work!</Msg><Username>troyramsey146</Username><Timestamp>1361975413458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:30:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361975858058-30</Id><Topic><Title>BA Insider Trading Reported !!!</Title><Username>doris.shealey</Username><Timestamp>1361811207875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 11:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Useful information</Msg><Username>chapmankyle712</Username><Timestamp>1361975858058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:37:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361975868646-31</Id><Topic><Title>BA Insider Trading Reported !!!</Title><Username>doris.shealey</Username><Timestamp>1361811207875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 11:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for sharing!</Msg><Username>clarkpatricia386</Username><Timestamp>1361975868646</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:37:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361976159831-32</Id><Topic><Title>2 Planes Out of 50 Have Fires = Only a 4% Failuire Rate in 3 Months</Title><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1361974745389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:19:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are exactly right!!!! Boeing flew 5 test aircraft intensively for 2 years without a battery failure but the Japanese weren't able to get 3 mos out of the 787 before they had battery trouble. I SMELL a RAT</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361976159831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:42:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361976180138-33</Id><Topic><Title>FAA to Boeing , reports of Boeing 787 test flights "completely inaccurate"</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361932673504</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:37:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the planes boss, the planes I don't see them flying ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976180138</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:43:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361976260504-34</Id><Topic><Title>FAA 787-The safety of the flying public is our top priority and we won't allow the 787 to return to commercial service</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361906898594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 14:28:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just because it flying is the Boeing boardroom does not mean the FAA will let it fly in the sky !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976260504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:44:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361976270116-35</Id><Topic><Title>The White House Court Jesters of Sequester</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361975039181</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:23:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You obviously weren't smart enough to work for the FAA or are on Medicare etc- just what the F ... are you</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361976270116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:44:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361976335586-36</Id><Title>how many 787 have been delivered this year that are flying</Title><Msg>zero!</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976335586</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:45:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361976394596-37</Id><Title>Bernanke had to clean Sen Corkers clock at the Senate Fed meeting</Title><Msg>He manage to tell Corker his Tbag B__S was just that B_S</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361976394596</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:46:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361976463691-38</Id><Topic><Title>how many 787 have been delivered this year that are flying</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976335586</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:45:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey there Dell aren't you trysting with your boyfriend yet this morning</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361976463691</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:47:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361976639354-39</Id><Title>Boeing Bouyout!? A Joke</Title><Msg>I understand these message boards are open to anyone. But there should be some accountability to Yahoo or a regulator. How on earth can Hasbro buy Boeing? What strategic interest? Why buy a company with a big problem? Battery issue is serious (think about it, would you fly on a plave with a possible fire incident?). Propoganda and PR firms for Boeing working overtime to control "spin". Sales and confidence will be hurt in a major way. Airbus is capitalizing on it. Stay away from Boeing for the next 6 months or more.</Msg><Username>beingtheonenow</Username><Timestamp>1361976639354</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:50:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361976710178-40</Id><Topic><Title>BA Insider Trading Reported !!!</Title><Username>doris.shealey</Username><Timestamp>1361811207875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 11:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice!</Msg><Username>arthur.ptak</Username><Timestamp>1361976710178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:51:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361976788268-41</Id><Title>YTD , DOW up 6%, but BA lags at 2%,how many 787 are flying now ?</Title><Msg>S and P 500 is up over 5%, so any Boeing shareholder is a loser by 3 or 4 percent compared to the average stock gain for the dow and the s and p investors just do not drink the cool aid of the 6 boeing hacks that frequent this message board , how is the 787 delivery going now ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976788268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:53:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361976890575-42</Id><Topic><Title>Sequester fears take mainstream media hysteria to new heights</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361971302120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:21:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surprisingly, CNN’s presidential debate star seems to have grasped some basic economics or reporting. (Maybe even both!) Crowley called out one of the administration’s many liars, er, department heads, pretending the cuts will end the world as we know it – in this case air travel. Crowley had the audacity to tell Transportation Secretary Ray LaHood that “your post-sequester total at FAA ops and facilities and equipment is going to be about $500 million more than 2008 and the planes were running just fine.” When LaHood responded by talking about the dreaded “furlough of air traffic controllers,” Crowley came right back. “Is it true that domestic flights are down 27 percent from pre-9/11 levels and the budget at the FAA is up 41 percent?” That is the essence of the sequester. Federal budgets seldom really drop and any cut is seen as a crime against nature. Journalists, meanwhile, regurgitate talking points from their statist buddies who think the taxes should take every dollar out of your wallet, and then sell your wallet for good measure. Almost no one in the press is pointing out that all this budget cutting is just a drop in the bucket compared to what’s really needed to rein in trillion dollar deficits and our $16.5 trillion national debt. Any attempt to do that will require true cuts to our bloated government and its No. 1 fans in the media will again scream the sky is falling and the world is about to end.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361976890575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:54:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361976914229-43</Id><Topic><Title>FAA to Boeing , reports of Boeing 787 test flights "completely inaccurate"</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361932673504</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:37:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FAA points out Boeing claim of being allowed to fly the 787 soon is "completely inaccurate, don't drink the Boeing cool aid</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976914229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:55:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361977022784-44</Id><Topic><Title>BA Still Not Know What Caused Battery Fires But BA Has a Magic Fix for It</Title><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1361974529685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:15:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the shareholders know that Boeing is completely inaccurate about the 787 flying any time soon ! per FAA</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361977022784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:57:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361977333058-45</Id><Topic><Title>BA Still Not Know What Caused Battery Fires But BA Has a Magic Fix for It</Title><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1361974529685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:15:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More proof an idiot is borne each and every day. Get a life DDDD</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1361977333058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361977617694-46</Id><Topic><Title>Gigantic Update for BA . **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>chacon.cross</Username><Timestamp>1361970258649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:04:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bought fast</Msg><Username>digby.joseph</Username><Timestamp>1361977617694</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:06:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361977646111-47</Id><Topic><Title>Sequester fears take mainstream media hysteria to new heights</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361971302120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:21:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ALWAYS, and I mean ALWAYS, the liberal approach is to strike fear telling lies. That gets them the biggest audience given the mainstream media supports them. Then, afterwards the debate begins, and the truth comes out, but the left still wins political capital as most of the UNinformed don't get into the fine print stuff.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361977646111</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:07:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361977668943-48</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Bouyout!? A Joke</Title><Username>beingtheonenow</Username><Timestamp>1361976639354</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:50:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What planet do clowns like you originate from?</Msg><Username>yourgonnalosebigbucks</Username><Timestamp>1361977668943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:07:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361978016440-49</Id><Topic><Title>BA Insider Trading Reported !!!</Title><Username>doris.shealey</Username><Timestamp>1361811207875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 11:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks a lot! useful report</Msg><Username>darwinblake12</Username><Timestamp>1361978016440</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:13:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361978366437-50</Id><Topic><Title>Leaked BA buy out report!</Title><Username>dennis.jacksonny</Username><Timestamp>1361970587265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:09:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very useful,thanks</Msg><Username>oscarcarter844</Username><Timestamp>1361978366437</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:19:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361978618061-51</Id><Topic><Title>Gartman getting out of stocks!</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361453923595</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:38:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's good advice</Msg><Username>flightmomentum</Username><Timestamp>1361978618061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:23:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361978658232-52</Id><Title>Dreamliner Grounding Costs</Title><Msg>Seems the longer this plane is grounded the higher the stock price rises. Will Dreamliner customers at some time file suit to recover losses? Woukd Boeing be liable, does insurance cover such events? Can't imagine if Jeep "grounded" my car for months that I wouldn't seek some compensation.....What's the thoughts on Boeings exposure ??</Msg><Username>president_peace_prize</Username><Timestamp>1361978658232</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:24:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361979379725-53</Id><Topic><Title>Gigantic Update for BA . **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>chacon.cross</Username><Timestamp>1361970258649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:04:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>trusting</Msg><Username>eduardo.suggs</Username><Timestamp>1361979379725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:36:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361979630275-54</Id><Title>BA will break 80$.</Title><Msg>Monoply business is better than smart phones!!!!</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361979630275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:40:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361979933399-55</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner Grounding Costs</Title><Username>president_peace_prize</Username><Timestamp>1361978658232</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:24:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>boeing is using the billions it authorized for a stock buyback to artificially support the stock price while the institutions are selling out yes Boeing is not making any money on the grounded 787 planes and the only like that is making the big money is the 737 a union designed and built plane not a cheap outsource failure like the 787</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361979933399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:45:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361980025574-56</Id><Topic><Title>YTD , DOW up 6%, but BA lags at 2%,how many 787 are flying now ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976788268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and still a stock much less than the average dow or s and p average gainer for the year to date</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361980025574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:47:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361980086540-57</Id><Topic><Title>FAA to Boeing , reports of Boeing 787 test flights "completely inaccurate"</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361932673504</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:37:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and still a completely false report by Boeing that the 787 will be flying any time soon !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361980086540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:48:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361980365547-58</Id><Topic><Title>BA Insider Trading Reported !!!</Title><Username>doris.shealey</Username><Timestamp>1361811207875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 11:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great</Msg><Username>hopkinsdrew39</Username><Timestamp>1361980365547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:52:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361980373184-59</Id><Title>" Republican Plan for Sequestration "</Title><Msg>A red WARN NOTICE - 30-day notice of furloughs for most government agencies !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1361980373184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:52:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361980450181-60</Id><Title>99 percent of Democrats give the rest a bad name.</Title><Msg>the other 1% incarcerated felons.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361980450181</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:54:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361980774923-61</Id><Topic><Title>Leaked BA buy out report!</Title><Username>dennis.jacksonny</Username><Timestamp>1361970587265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:09:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very nice article</Msg><Username>brownsam56</Username><Timestamp>1361980774923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:59:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361980897606-62</Id><Topic><Title>99 percent of Democrats give the rest a bad name.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361980450181</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:54:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you sound like some kinda #$%$</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1361980897606</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:01:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361980982896-63</Id><Title>All The Police' Support My Gun Ban</Title><Msg>Type message</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361980982896</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:03:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361981034075-64</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Dope and the mediocre guy</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361974800345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:20:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" If you cant understand the objective of the liberals " they don't understand their own existence !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1361981034075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:03:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361981193379-65</Id><Title>All The Police' Support My Gun Ban, Everybody is for raising taxes and not cutting Spending........</Title><Msg>....and all Scientists believe the global warming hoax.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361981193379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:06:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361981625280-66</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Dope and the mediocre guy</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361974800345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:20:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think he's implying that a mediocre government should provide mediocre people with a mediocre existence so they can have a mediocre dependency. And put create huge obstacles in they way of anyone trying to be a high achiever.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361981625280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:13:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361981640886-67</Id><Title>All this time and still no battery answers from anyone!</Title><Msg>I do not understand why BA shares are up. They are submitting a battery solution to the FAA when they still have no clue what the problem is. So the solution is "yes, our batteries can catch on fire. So we will enclose them in more rugged boxes". Are you kididing? They don't allow the air canisters to be shipped on aircraft because they can cause fires. Te FAA is going to allow batteries that can catch fire on airplanes under any circumstances? Are you kidding me? And what happens when the battery catches generates massive heat in an enclosed box? The thing will eventually explode like a cannon ball. I just don't see how the FAA is going to go for this. And what happens at the next "fire" incident. What is the FAA going to do then? News said today that there were 2 fires in 50,000 flights, off the charts in terms of risk - especially when there are only 50 878's in service. Imagine the risk profile when there are 400 planes. If I were running the FAA, I would say identify and solve the problem. If you can't, then design a new system.</Msg><Username>thedeathrace</Username><Timestamp>1361981640886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:14:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361981721147-68</Id><Topic><Title>All The Police' Support My Gun Ban</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361980982896</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:03:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More content there than is normal for you.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1361981721147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:15:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361981758011-69</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Dope and the mediocre guy</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361974800345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:20:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he's saying - you're some kinda moron !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1361981758011</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:15:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361982313032-70</Id><Topic><Title>BA Insider Trading Reported !!!</Title><Username>doris.shealey</Username><Timestamp>1361811207875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 11:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you just make my day !!!</Msg><Username>tasha_cook</Username><Timestamp>1361982313032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:25:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361982695170-71</Id><Topic><Title>Leaked BA buy out report!</Title><Username>dennis.jacksonny</Username><Timestamp>1361970587265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:09:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with this report</Msg><Username>craigwall59</Username><Timestamp>1361982695170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:31:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361982887704-72</Id><Title>BA Shares now back to price where they were before all this battery stuff happened. How can that be?</Title><Msg>How can Boeing shares be back up to the old pre battery crisis levels when the company has no answers to the problem, all planes are grounded, there are no test flights going on (there was only one last week), and the FAA has not indicated anything about approving Boeings "duct tape solution". Looks like a trading short to me at above $77.</Msg><Username>thedeathrace</Username><Timestamp>1361982887704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:34:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361982943596-73</Id><Topic><Title>All this time and still no battery answers from anyone!</Title><Username>thedeathrace</Username><Timestamp>1361981640886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:14:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It appears the shares are up based on the information released by the FAA's investigative section. THey report that the battery they have examined shorted and went into thermal runaway. That cell runaway migrated to other cells.. Boeings solution proposed to the FAA is to further isolate the cells to prevent runaway and to eliminate the threat of fire if the battery does short. Some argue that Boeing is using stock buyback money to keep the stock price inflated. But the amount remaining in the stock buyback account was only $2B in mid-December. That is only 4 days worth of trading at the average shares traded rate. So that theory is simply rambling rhetoric from individuals who seem to be mentally deficient or seriously short.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1361982943596</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:35:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361982951192-74</Id><Topic><Title>BA Shares now back to price where they were before all this battery stuff happened. How can that be?</Title><Username>thedeathrace</Username><Timestamp>1361982887704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:34:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can one person be so naive as you are?</Msg><Username>yourgonnalosebigbucks</Username><Timestamp>1361982951192</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:35:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361983140069-75</Id><Topic><Title>BA Shares now back to price where they were before all this battery stuff happened. How can that be?</Title><Username>thedeathrace</Username><Timestamp>1361982887704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:34:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because they are very "short" (: )</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1361983140069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:39:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361983572409-76</Id><Title>phantom eye milestone</Title><Msg>ST. LOUIS, Feb. 26, 2013 -- Boeing's [NYSE: BA] liquid hydrogen-powered Phantom Eye unmanned airborne system completed its second flight Feb. 25, demonstrating capabilities that will allow it to perform intelligence, surveillance and reconnaissance (ISR) missions for up to four days without refueling. During the flight, at NASA's Dryden Flight Research Center at Edwards Air Force Base, Calif., Phantom Eye climbed above an altitude of 8,000 feet and remained aloft for 66 minutes at a cruising speed of 62 knots before landing. The aircraft exceeded what it achieved last year during its first flight when it flew at an altitude of 4,080 feet and remained aloft for 28 minutes. Landing was picture perfect on upgraded landing gear.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1361983572409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:46:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361983601624-77</Id><Title>William Pawelec interview finally made public on YouTube. NSA, CIA insider. Jaw dropping.</Title><Msg>One of the more revealing interviews. He made producer wait until he died before it could be made public. NSA and CIA insider speaks.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1361983601624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:46:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361983933361-78</Id><Title>Come on BOEING$$$</Title><Msg>Theys nothing stopping this Now$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1361983933361</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:52:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361984023144-79</Id><Topic><Title>YTD , DOW up 6%, but BA lags at 2%,how many 787 are flying now ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976788268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's wrong with my Kool-Aid.? By my calculations BA is up as of this moment 16.7% YTD and the DOW is up 16.3% YTD. By my calculations since the bottom was hit in March 2009 Boeing is up 160% and the Dow is up 110%.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1361984023144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:53:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361984206435-80</Id><Topic><Title>" Republican Plan for Sequestration "</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1361980373184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:52:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's wrong with that?</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361984206435</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:56:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361984374558-81</Id><Topic><Title>Gigantic Update for BA . **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>chacon.cross</Username><Timestamp>1361970258649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:04:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dont act be real</Msg><Username>corey_portillo</Username><Timestamp>1361984374558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:59:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361985022519-82</Id><Topic><Title>" Republican Plan for Sequestration "</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1361980373184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:52:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The responsible way is the GOP way...Put govt jobs in correct proportion to private sector jobs so that there isn't too much tax burdon on the private sector resuling in layoffs, and high unemployment continually. That has been the lbieral way, the European way of creating way too many gov jobs, and having an unemployment rate fo 10% or over the norm. Obama and the left want you to accept 8% unemployment as acceptable, and it isn't. And that doesn't even address the unfair compensation govt workers get vs. the provate sector comparable jobs.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361985022519</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:10:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361985889347-83</Id><Topic><Title>YTD , DOW up 6%, but BA lags at 2%,how many 787 are flying now ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976788268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne, check out the William Pawelec interview on YouTube. Highest level CIA-NSA insider to ever talk about US government and reveal lots of info. He required the tape not be broadcast until his death. He died under very mysterious circumstances shortly after the tape was made.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1361985889347</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:24:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361985894986-84</Id><Topic><Title>FAA to Boeing , reports of Boeing 787 test flights "completely inaccurate"</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361932673504</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:37:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dell looks like you and your boyfriend have this topic to themselves- hey enjoy</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361985894986</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:24:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361986306353-85</Id><Title>Senate Democrats Haven’t Passed a Budget in 1400 Days</Title><Msg>Why are they afraid of showing the country what they're spending our money on?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361986306353</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:31:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361986614790-86</Id><Title>SELL, and go SHORT NOW ?</Title><Msg>So since it seems that everytime this stock has been at this level time and time again, and I have just held, and took the ride down. I'm thinking this time of selling and going short... Mistake ? or what ?</Msg><Username>cnarntz</Username><Timestamp>1361986614790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:36:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361986702949-87</Id><Topic><Title>BA CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>tasha_cook</Username><Timestamp>1361981972208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:19:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bunp</Msg><Username>santac001</Username><Timestamp>1361986702949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:38:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361986962127-88</Id><Topic><Title>SELL, and go SHORT NOW ?</Title><Username>cnarntz</Username><Timestamp>1361986614790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:36:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go ahead dude nothing like the smell of BURING shorts in the Morning$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1361986962127</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:42:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361987002236-89</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing's really sucking up to the Obama Administration</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1361453917825</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:38:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this may be true but what big powerful corporation doesn't also do it ?</Msg><Username>santac001</Username><Timestamp>1361987002236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:43:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361987010283-90</Id><Title>Destructive Emotions</Title><Msg>Emotions are powerful mighty damaging when not under control. There is a good book by Ken Lindner. All Liberals should read it. Because Liberals most often substitute feelings for thinking they often get extremely confused about cause and effect. Take jealousy for example. Liberals spend an inordinate amount of time and energy being jealous of people more successful than they. This jealousy is so easily manipulated by unscrupulous politicians. That’s why punishing the high achievers plays so well. It may also be what will destroy our country as we know it. High achievers like my self have learned to never waste time or energy on jealousy. People who have achieved more than you should be an inspiration for you to work harder, smarter and achieve more. Champion football team don’t waste time being jealous, they are driven to be better. That’s why underdogs often win.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361987010283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:43:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361987040476-91</Id><Topic><Title>Gigantic Update for BA . **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>chacon.cross</Username><Timestamp>1361970258649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:04:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looking at it as we speak.</Msg><Username>sawyer.schubert</Username><Timestamp>1361987040476</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:44:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361987148050-92</Id><Topic><Title>BA CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>tasha_cook</Username><Timestamp>1361981972208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:19:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good work!</Msg><Username>hopkinsdrew39</Username><Timestamp>1361987148050</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:45:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361987193729-93</Id><Topic><Title>YTD , DOW up 6%, but BA lags at 2%,how many 787 are flying now ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976788268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>interesting video.</Msg><Username>santac001</Username><Timestamp>1361987193729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:46:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361987313082-94</Id><Title>Equality</Title><Msg>“ Equality of the general rules of law and conduct, however, is the only kind of equality conducive to liberty and the only equality which we can secure without destroying liberty. Not only has liberty nothing to do with any other sort of equality, but it is even bound to produce inequality in many respects. This is the necessary result and part of the justification of individual liberty: if the result of individual liberty did not demonstrate that some manners of living are more successful than others, much of the case for it would vanish.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361987313082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:48:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361987673525-95</Id><Title>Jealousy and Envy</Title><Msg>However human, envy is certainly not one of the sources of discontent that a free society can eliminate. It is probably one of the essential conditions for the preservation of such a society that we do not countenance envy, not sanction its demands by camouflaging it as social justice, but treat it as “the most anti-social and evil of all passions.”</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361987673525</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:54:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361988039847-96</Id><Topic><Title>FAA to Boeing , reports of Boeing 787 test flights "completely inaccurate"</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361932673504</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:37:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We can't let them get away with their anti-management tripe. Its only a battery fellows. The fix is there. The problem no longer rests with the battery. Whats holding up test flights of the 787 is the red tape at the FAA.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361988039847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:00:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361988197345-97</Id><Topic><Title>Leaked BA buy out report!</Title><Username>dennis.jacksonny</Username><Timestamp>1361970587265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:09:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we are looking good today!</Msg><Username>goldman_alan</Username><Timestamp>1361988197345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:03:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361988323779-98</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fact.. Libs are doing everything possible to squelch opposition to socialism. They want to get rid of Limbaugh, and Fox News....and it is a concerted effort to do so. Best just to be nice, and tell them to fukoff.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361988323779</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:05:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361988396272-99</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You stupid, old white #$%$ fool. Go back to the bar. Hannity and the rest of con artists playing old idiots like yourself.</Msg><Username>kgnicetoo</Username><Timestamp>1361988396272</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:06:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361988752499-100</Id><Topic><Title>Gigantic Update for BA . **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>chacon.cross</Username><Timestamp>1361970258649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:04:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what did you discover ?</Msg><Username>fredlesiuk</Username><Timestamp>1361988752499</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:12:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361988766006-101</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pssssst......Hannity is not a Republican......and he is not a Journalist either. He is a member of the Conservative Party and he is a talk show host. Makes a good straw man for the left though.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361988766006</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:12:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361989105887-102</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I told you the facts...you spewed BS, and you do just what liberals do, attack those opposed to socialism...so now I'll be nice, and tell you to fukoff.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361989105887</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:18:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361989559104-103</Id><Topic><Title>Gigantic Update for BA . **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>chacon.cross</Username><Timestamp>1361970258649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:04:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>report is number 1</Msg><Username>johnsonhector259</Username><Timestamp>1361989559104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:25:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361990202467-104</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are no longer any conservative Democrats the party has been co-opted by radical socialists/Marxists. It's some form of crazy narcissism that lets Democrats think that Republican are the only ones who hate their anti-American policies and Marxist ideology.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361990202467</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:36:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361990438502-105</Id><Topic><Title>Jealousy and Envy</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361987673525</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:54:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't that a quote from F A Hayek?</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1361990438502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:40:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361990723109-106</Id><Title>The more the state “plans” the more difficult planning becomes for the individual.</Title><Msg>Bureaucrats are now the obstacles to a vibrant growing economy. Rich guys like myself will continue to get richer because we will keep doing what made us rich. Same for the poor.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361990723109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:45:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361991080623-107</Id><Topic><Title>BA CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>tasha_cook</Username><Timestamp>1361981972208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:19:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing !</Msg><Username>sandra.sanders</Username><Timestamp>1361991080623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:51:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361991266389-108</Id><Topic><Title>Gigantic Update for BA . **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>chacon.cross</Username><Timestamp>1361970258649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:04:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SCAM BY UNEMPLOYED LOSERS REPORTED !</Msg><Username>alphonite</Username><Timestamp>1361991266389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:54:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361991277544-109</Id><Topic><Title>Gigantic Update for BA . **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>chacon.cross</Username><Timestamp>1361970258649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:04:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SCAM BY UNEMPLOYED LOSERS REPORTED !</Msg><Username>alphonite</Username><Timestamp>1361991277544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:54:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361991304718-110</Id><Topic><Title>BA Insider Trading Reported !!!</Title><Username>doris.shealey</Username><Timestamp>1361811207875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 11:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing !</Msg><Username>sandra.sanders</Username><Timestamp>1361991304718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:55:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361991572021-111</Id><Topic><Title>All The Police' Support My Gun Ban, Everybody is for raising taxes and not cutting Spending........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361981193379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:06:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thousand of Scientists oppose the mainstream scientific assessment of global warming. Among them are: 1 Scientists questioning the accuracy of IPCC climate projections 2 Scientists arguing that global warming is primarily caused by natural processes 3 Scientists arguing that the cause of global warming is unknown 4 Scientists arguing that global warming will have few negative consequences 5 Scientist that argue that global warming will have positive consequences When you take a fraction of an inch in a hundred miles of geologic time and try to extrapolate it into a trend you're not being very scientific......you're making irrelevant information fit an ideological agenda.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361991572021</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:59:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361991721322-112</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, The Tea Party Is In Great Shape...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987422266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:50:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Tea Party is dead. All attempts to revive it have failed.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1361991721322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:02:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361991894523-113</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They want to get rid of Limbaugh, and Fox News" Who doesn't?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1361991894523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:04:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361991979982-114</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of the world great discoveries have been found by a very small majority. Most of the world's tragic mistakes keep getting repeated over and over again by people who refuse to learn from history. Socialism and communism does not work well and it certainly does not foster individual liberty ........something the current Democrats have yet to learn.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361991979982</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:06:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361992264475-115</Id><Topic><Title>All The Police' Support My Gun Ban, Everybody is for raising taxes and not cutting Spending........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361981193379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:06:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I quit counting the scientists opposed to man created global warming at just over 600 world scientists. If you were a govt scientist that depended on a govt paycheck you went along with the scam. If you didn't work for the govt, and supported scientific data you opposed it.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361992264475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:11:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361992402936-116</Id><Title>Hmmmmmm.....WHITE HOUSE BLAMES BIG SIS FOR ALIEN RELEASE</Title><Msg>Does the White House ever have a clue of what's happening on its watch? The White House and the Department of Homeland Security were unaware of Immigration Customs and Enforcement's decision to release detainees until the agency announced it, administration officials said Wednesday. "This was a decision made by a career officials at ICE without any input from the White House, as a result of fiscal uncertainty over the continuing resolution, as well as possible sequestration," White House press secretary Jay Carney said Wednesday. Personnel at Department of Homeland Security headquarters in Washington were also unaware of the decision until the announcement was made, a department official told POLITICO. (Also on POLITICO: Blogs decry illegal immigrant release) ICE announced Tuesday that it has released several hundred undocumented immigrants in recent weeks as funding cuts loom. The detainees will instead be monitored in less expensive ways, the agency said. Carney described those released as "low-risk, non-criminal detainees," but several Republican members of Congress have spoken out against the releases. “It’s very hard for me to believe that they can’t find cuts elsewhere in their agency,” House Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio) told CBS News on Tuesday. “I frankly think this is outrageous…I can’t believe that they can’t find the kind of savings they need out of that department short of letting criminals go free.” Rep. Michael McCaul (R-Texas), the chairman of the House Homeland Security Committee, on Wednesday asked ICE for details of the agency's decision. "This decision reflects the lack of resource prioritization," he wrote to ICE Director John Morton, "and is indicative of the Department [of Homeland Security]’s weak stance on national security."</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361992402936</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:13:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361992478200-117</Id><Title>80 bucks yet?</Title><Msg>$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$4</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361992478200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:14:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361992569079-118</Id><Title>MONOPLY business with huge backlog..</Title><Msg>Do you get this?</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361992569079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:16:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361993144018-119</Id><Topic><Title>YTD , DOW up 6%, but BA lags at 2%,how many 787 are flying now ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976788268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does he wear an armband like yours?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1361993144018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:25:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361993669380-120</Id><Title>News out: Don't your breath for planes to fly soon! FAA</Title><Msg>FAA Chief: 'Great Deal of Testing' Needed Before 787 Flies Again Text Size Published: Wednesday, 27 Feb 2013 | 2:13 PM ET</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361993669380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:34:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361993991966-121</Id><Title>BREAKING-FAA SAYS 787 WILL FLY AFTER TESTIING</Title><Msg>Great news, says after testing, they will fly again. No time table but who cares? 1-2 months is great news if you ask me.</Msg><Username>jeffreysauctions</Username><Timestamp>1361993991966</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:39:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361994088846-122</Id><Title>Flashback: Remember When Obama Deplored Selling Access to Power?</Title><Msg>Obama's hypocrisy reel on the subjects of transparency and money in politics is long and sordid, but BuzzFeed's Andrew Kaczynski isolates an especially revealing illustration of The One's abject shamelessness (click through for video). Here's candidate Obama announcing his candidacy for President of the United States in 2007: As people have looked away in disillusionment and frustration, we know what's filled the void. The cynics, and the lobbyists, and the special interests who've turned our government into a game only they can afford to play. They write the checks and you get stuck with the bills, they get the access while you get to write a letter, they think they own this government, but we're here today to take it back. The time for that politics is over. It's time to turn the page. Now this man's former campaign organization is basically selling tickets to special presidential summits at the White House for five hundred grand a pop. Before you go on, read the transcript of the Springfield speech for a very special bonus passage about the perils of mounting debts (cough -- ahem -- cough). As Chuck Todd's segment revealed on Monday, Obama exploited the issue of high-dollar influencers and access-peddling as a major point of departure between himself and Hillary Clinton in the Democratic primary. Indeed, he once called it "the difference" between them. Another big one, by the way, was their divergence of opinion on the individual mandate to purchase healthcare, which Obama strongly opposed (cough). To their credit, some lefty good government groups are getting on Obama's case about his latest means-to-an-end betrayal:</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361994088846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:41:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361994220367-123</Id><Topic><Title>FAA to Boeing , reports of Boeing 787 test flights "completely inaccurate"</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361932673504</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:37:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don’t know how BA could be from proposed flight tests of a battery fix until they have fully bench tested the proposed solution. Proving the new containment system should be simple and quick, send a few batteries in a mockup of the surrounding battery area of the 787 into meltdown, and monitor the results. As for the second part, making the batteries less likely to go into catastrophic failure. That is going to take a lot more time. I will require testing the new battery in simulated discharging and recharging cycles like the battery will see in flight at an accelerated rate. If I was the FAA I would want the old batteries subjected to the same testing for comparison, and proof the new battery less prone to failure. I would if needed have the tests ramped up as needed to the point a lot of the old batteries would fail, and not see any of the new ones failing until they are operating well beyond expected operating parameters.</Msg><Username>stocksentinel</Username><Timestamp>1361994220367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:43:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361994337962-124</Id><Title>Any body remember When Obama said He would cut the Deficit in half........</Title><Msg>.....by the end of his first term? Now he's whining like a stuck pig after running up a $trillion deficit every year of his presidency and being forced to cut his rampant spending by 2 1/2 %.......even if it was his own idea.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361994337962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:45:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361994590245-125</Id><Topic><Title>Senate Democrats Haven’t Passed a Budget in 1400 Days</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361986306353</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:31:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good question.....but Democrat voters are content to plug their ears, cover their eyes and hum.....while they ignore the shenanigans of their party.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361994590245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:49:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361995501661-126</Id><Topic><Title>FAA to Boeing , reports of Boeing 787 test flights "completely inaccurate"</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361932673504</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 21:37:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I read an article on how BA tested the batteries in the lab, none of the tests duplicate how the battery failed which is why their numbers of estimated failure were way off. Another firm has been able to make the batteries fail with the shorting issue. As to why BA did not figure it out , maybe they did not want to have this statistic in the first place. In other words squew the results for the ok with the FAA for the use of the battery. Now the FAA is wise to the trick and that is why BA is not shorting the FAA review this time fool me once is done ! The FAA does not want a plane load of passengers to die on theri hands and Boeing is desperate to get the plane flying so tuff stuff for BA</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361995501661</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:05:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361995539212-127</Id><Topic><Title>Any body remember When Obama said He would cut the Deficit in half........</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361994337962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:45:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was for spending cuts before he was against it. THE PRESIDENT HAS MONUMENTAL SHIFTS IN ATTITUDE THAT DEFY RATIONALITY! Under closer scrutiny, I believe this President is using politics to his advantage as president to gain power over his politicial opponents at the expense of what is good for America and the American People. Obama is treacherous because of his extreme narcisisstic behavior! Use extreme caution when being under the influence of the President!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1361995539212</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:05:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361995633355-128</Id><Topic><Title>News out: Don't your breath for planes to fly soon! FAA</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361993669380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:34:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep and for the BA stock owners(for now) all the BA stock buy back is working , a great time to get rout of the stock and go for better stocks too</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361995633355</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:07:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361996212142-129</Id><Topic><Title>Any body remember When Obama said He would cut the Deficit in half........</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361994337962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:45:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When the President brought forth the issue of sequestration, democrats were praising him for it. Now that the President is against sequestration, the democrats are praising him for it. Someone here is being manipulated and it sure the hell isn't ME!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1361996212142</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:16:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361996246610-130</Id><Topic><Title>YTD , DOW up 6%, but BA lags at 2%,how many 787 are flying now ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976788268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>freeveritas use cnn money, BA YTD is up 2.8% Dow is up7.4%, it will do the math for you. just enter BA click on five year or ytd or what ever your comparison is . freeveritas for 5 years for example if that is your basis BA is up 4.2% for 5 years or less than 1% per year, then compare to the Dow up 14.76% if you want to pick and choose some kind of low low to date to dome kind of high high and play number games just go get a playboy to read with one hand oke !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361996246610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:17:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361996347072-131</Id><Title>BARCHART PUTS BUY ON - YTRV - OIL</Title><Msg>GONNA POP!</Msg><Username>wertgam</Username><Timestamp>1361996347072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:19:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361996466310-132</Id><Topic><Title>Flashback: Remember When Obama Deplored Selling Access to Power?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361994088846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:41:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our President: The most dangerous man in America</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1361996466310</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:21:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361996476942-133</Id><Topic><Title>YTD , DOW up 6%, but BA lags at 2%,how many 787 are flying now ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976788268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will take a look</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361996476942</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:21:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361996992255-134</Id><Topic><Title>Leaked BA buy out report!</Title><Username>dennis.jacksonny</Username><Timestamp>1361970587265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:09:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks, good report</Msg><Username>craig_woods68</Username><Timestamp>1361996992255</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:29:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361997377716-135</Id><Topic><Title>Flashback: Remember When Obama Deplored Selling Access to Power?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361994088846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:41:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think of how rich Obama could have become had he became a used car saleman instead of a crooked politician...then again</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361997377716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:36:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361998211794-136</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I watched the clip for myself and Ellison performed poorly and came away looking like an angry black man. Ellison was obviously upset that Hannity used clips of comments by Obama that show Obama contradicting himself, which as everyone knows is common practice for Obama. Hannity is calm polite and rational whereas Ellison is hysterical and unwilling to answer any questions. Ellison denies Bob Woodward's reporting that the sequester was Obama's request. Ellison doesn't want to debate he wants blind obedience to Obama. Look at Ellison's facial expressions and you can tell he is infuriated.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361998211794</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:50:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361998483902-137</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who doesn't? Ever notice the ratings, and the size of Fox News' audience compared to a leftist cable audience? Most liberal tv shows go bellyup. Al Gore had to peddle his failing tv station to a liberal friendly Al Jazeera! LOL!</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361998483902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:54:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361998709105-138</Id><Title>Obama Ed Chief's Claim Of Teachers Getting Sequester Pink Slips Proven False...</Title><Msg>...jut more lies from the Obama administration. The descriptions of the post-sequester landscape that have been coming out of the Obama Administration have been alarming, specific--and, in at least some cases, hyped. “There are literally teachers now who are getting pink slips, who are getting notices that they can’t come back this fall,” Education Secretary Arne Duncan said Sunday on CBS’s “Face the Nation.” When he was pressed in a White House briefing Wednesday to come up with an example, Duncan named a single county in West Virginia and acknowledged, “whether it’s all sequester-related, I don’t know.” And, as it turns out, it isn’t. Officials in Kanawha County, West Virginia say that the “transfer notices” sent to at least 104 educators had more to do with a separate matter that involves a change in the way West Virginia allocates federal dollars designated for poor children.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361998709105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:58:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361998837786-139</Id><Title>Admin. puts air safety on chopping block...</Title><Msg>(Reuters) - The head of the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration said on Wednesday the agency would have to begin furloughing air traffic controllers in early April because of a looming $627 million in automatic spending cuts, while Republican lawmakers argued there were other ways to handle the budget crunch. "We're looking at all options to reduce costs. We're looking at a hiring freeze, at cutting contracts and travel and other items not related to day-to-day operations," FAA administrator Michael Huerta told the U.S. House of Representatives Transportation Committee. "But to reach the large figure we need to cut, we have little choice but to make up the rest through furloughing employees," Huerta said, referring to the automatic federal spending cuts known as "sequestration" due to take effect on Friday.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361998837786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:00:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361999101610-140</Id><Topic><Title>Admin. puts air safety on chopping block...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361998837786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:00:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any necessary cutback that happens is a direct result of Obama's support for failed policies that have dried up the funding needed for needed programs. Just like a family unit. Have one member squander all the disposable family income, and you could be eating dirt for dinner. And that is what Obama has done.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361999101610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:05:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361999113599-141</Id><Title>Woodward: Obama's actions are Madness</Title><Msg>Bob Woodward blasted President Obama on Wednesday morning for deciding to recall an aircraft carrier from the Persian Gulf because of impending budget cuts, calling the decision "a kind of madness." Woodward: Can you imagine Ronald Reagan sitting there and saying ‘Oh, by the way, I can’t do this because of some budget document?’ Or George W. Bush saying, ‘You know, I’m not going to invade Iraq because I can’t get the aircraft carriers I need’ or even Bill Clinton saying, ‘You know, I’m not going to attack Saddam Hussein’s intelligence headquarters,’ as he did when Clinton was president because of some budget document? Under the Constitution, the president is commander-in-chief and employs the force. And so we now have the president going out because of this piece of paper and this agreement, I can’t do what I need to do to protect the country. That’s a kind of madness that I haven’t seen in a long time.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361999113599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:05:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361999208268-142</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Ed Chief's Claim Of Teachers Getting Sequester Pink Slips Proven False...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361998709105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:58:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone, but the uninformed knew that was a lie when Obama said it. State budgets fund teachers.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361999208268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:06:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361999373810-143</Id><Topic><Title>Well, The Asteriod Missed by 17,000 Some Miles</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360983644903</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 22:00:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raven thinks Marxism = a check in Ravens mail box, and a thumb in the eye of those who out-performed him . He likes that . Raven thinks Marxism = a check in Ravens mail box, and a thumb in the eye of those who out-performed him . He likes that .</Msg><Username>cluck_head_00</Username><Timestamp>1361999373810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:09:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362000232868-144</Id><Title>Sequester Fraud Continues</Title><Msg>this whole sequestration argument is merely 0bama playing out his class warfare game; 0bama in full campaign mode. Why even Common Cause is asking 0bama to stop campaigning and to start leading. Fat chance. What does 0bama want? Simple .. higher taxes on the rich. He already got a 4.6% increase in the tax rate on the rich in December. Then he added another 3.8% tax rate increase on many of the investments these evil rich people make. Then there’s a 0.9% Medicare tax increase on the rich, and more income tax surcharges coming up for rich people who don’t buy into his 0bamaCare health insurance plans. It seems rich people won’t be allowed to take care of their own health needs without paying a penalty. Now 0bama wants tax deductions removed so that the hideous rich will pay even more. 0bama truly despises the rich. He believes that the colonialization of his African homeland was driven by wealth, as was the colonialization of his birthplace, Hawaii. He believes that wealth is accumulated only by oppressing and victimizing others. And he KNOWS that political power can be gained and maintained by demonizing the rich and generating class envy and even hatred. This has been one of 0bama’s primary goals since he came into power. Demonize the wealth. Create and encourage envy, then hatred. Since the day he took office he has pounded the rich on the taxes they pay. First he said they “needed” to pay their fair share. They he said they “were not” paying their fair share. Never did he acknowledge that the top one-percent of income earners were earning 17% of the income but paying about 38% of the income taxes. He knew that he had the media on his side on this … that those numbers would never appear prominently in the Washington Post or New York Times, or on any of the broadcast networks. He had his cover, his protection, and his list of lies he could spread without consequence. 0bama then spreads the lie that rich people pay lower tax rates than their secretaries. Does he mention that he’s comparing capital gains taxes to income taxes? No. Why not? He doesn’t have to. It would destroy his argument, and he knows damn well the media isn’t going to call him on it. Now 0bama is using this sequester situation to once-again frighten the American people. He heads out to make campaign speeches telling people of the horrible consequences that will rain down on them if the horrible Republicans cause all of these disastrous spending cuts to take place because they’re protecting the rich from further tax increases. Disastrous spending cuts? If these spending cuts went through it would be like taking $4.60 out of a weekly food budget of $200. That’s less than a pound of coffee. This is going to cause your economic world to come to an end? Really? In December 0bama told the Republicans to give him his tax increases on the rich and he would talk spending cuts with them later. Now it’s later, and 0bama only wants to talk more taxes on the rich. 0bama and Harry Reid say we need some “revenue.” Remember --- the word “revenue,” to a Democrat, is code for “tax increase.” Democrats do not recognize that revenue increases can come from economic growth. To Democrats, revenue increases ONLY come from higher taxes. Oh .. and these dire consequences Obama is preaching in his tax-the-rich campaign swing across the nation? Remember … he has direct control over just how the spending cuts for the Executive Department will be implemented .. and that’s pretty much everything except the congressional budgets and our federal courts. He can make them as painful or as benign as he wants. He can cut the money available for the WIC program that purportedly helps to feed the babies that mothers who can’t afford babies have, or he can work to reduce the fraud that is rampant in this program. His choice, and his choice is to make the cuts as painful as possible, and then blame the Republicans. In the end, I full expect Boehner and McConnell to fold. That’s their history. The Republican party has NO leadership now. There is great potential in certain Senators from Florida and Kentucky … but the Democrats are, even as you read this, working on their plans to destroy these two people as quickly as possible. Make your escape plans, folks. NBN</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1362000232868</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:23:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362000558165-145</Id><Title>'The Sequestercist': So Terrifying, It'll Make Your Head Spin</Title><Msg>President Barack Obama has been out on the campaign trail….uh, I mean, traveling the country discussing how the sequester from Congress (even though he signed off on it) will bring doom and gloom to America...unless of course we follow his plan and raise more revenues through taxes. The president has warned of the dire consequences of sequestration; cuts to education and health care, dramatic federal worker furloughs, dangerous borders and a loss of national security. Enough fear to make your head spin. It’s sounds very scary, almost like a horror movie… “The Sequestercist.”</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1362000558165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:29:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362000991523-146</Id><Topic><Title>'The Sequestercist': So Terrifying, It'll Make Your Head Spin</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1362000558165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:29:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lies, lies, and more lies. What a shocker when folks find out nothin much changed. Obama, and congress are on track to spend more tax payer money this year even after the cutbacks. And the key here is, they will spend it given less tax revenue to support the spending then when GW Bush was growing the economy at a record level for a record duration. Liberalism is dying regardless of what Obama wants. The Market in the end, determines how much money is availabe to be spent, and Obama has depressed the Market.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1362000991523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:36:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362001053248-147</Id><Topic><Title>Any body remember When Obama said He would cut the Deficit in half........</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361994337962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:45:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The deficit has been reduced every year of Obama's presidency. I see the BA board is being converted to the right-fringers' bit chabout Obama board. You are reaching the vast majority of American voters! Harharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362001053248</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:37:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362001154301-148</Id><Topic><Title>Sequester Fraud Continues</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1362000232868</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:23:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has taken his campaign organization, and transformed it into a political agency where one can buy influence into the White House. For $500,000 big ones, you can sit down with our fascist leader, and buy some influence. And that's a fact. That's the price tag Obama has put on it.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1362001154301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:39:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362001213716-149</Id><Topic><Title>Woodward: Obama's actions are Madness</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361999113599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:05:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boxarox should not have invaded Iraq in any case.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362001213716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:40:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362001217964-150</Id><Title>Obama is Panicking - He needs that money to pay off Donors and Unions</Title><Msg>...he knows if they don't get their pay-off, they could turn on him.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1362001217964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:40:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362001335112-151</Id><Topic><Title>Woodward: Obama's actions are Madness</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361999113599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:05:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you say that?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1362001335112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:42:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362001360990-152</Id><Topic><Title>Woodward: Obama's actions are Madness</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361999113599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:05:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How did you imagine the right-fringe-created sequester defense cuts were going to play out? Mabe he'll start "layoffs" in the military. Wouldn't that cause screams from your idiots? Harharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362001360990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:42:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362001446562-153</Id><Title>It Has Been Confirmed</Title><Msg>Yes, Obama is DEFINATELY an (_o_) that Democrats can UNITE WITH when having BACKDOOR SEX!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1362001446562</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:44:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362001457714-154</Id><Topic><Title>'The Sequestercist': So Terrifying, It'll Make Your Head Spin</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1362000558165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:29:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But but ObUma did cut the deficit in half or better !!! Harry Reid came up with the ultimate solution !! Deficit is when you spend MORE than budgeted. Harry reid has refused to bring a budget for about 4 years. So by definition- NO budget - NO deficit ! I'm sure even those with 6th grade Math can understand that. Gotta give it to ole CanvasBack Harry - at least one too many blows to the head in his days as a pro boxer !</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1362001457714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:44:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362001774511-155</Id><Topic><Title>Woodward: Obama's actions are Madness</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361999113599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:05:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you concerned about your monthly Twinkie handout being cut from 6 cases to 5?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1362001774511</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:49:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362001910986-156</Id><Title>Obama panicking like a guy who's loan payment to the Mob is due</Title><Msg>.....an he ain't got no mo money ta pay em.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1362001910986</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:51:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362001921869-157</Id><Topic><Title>Any body remember When Obama said He would cut the Deficit in half........</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361994337962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:45:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only a DFC would believe such an outrageous statement.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1362001921869</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:52:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362002213300-158</Id><Topic><Title>'The Sequestercist': So Terrifying, It'll Make Your Head Spin</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1362000558165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:29:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, Don. Absolutely no. A deficit is when you spend more than you bring in, not more than budgeted. That's paper and D.C. has enough paper. And the way most people define deficit, Obama has been reducing it year over year.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362002213300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:56:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362002224735-159</Id><Topic><Title>'The Sequestercist': So Terrifying, It'll Make Your Head Spin</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1362000558165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:29:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now in bookstores everywhere!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1362002224735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:57:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362002270287-160</Id><Title>My My the Raven is Whining About the Cuts</Title><Msg>.....what's funny is there are no cuts ......just less of an increase. The president is lying and the Raven is defending his lying.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362002270287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:57:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362002339252-161</Id><Topic><Title>All The Police' Support My Gun Ban, Everybody is for raising taxes and not cutting Spending........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361981193379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:06:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You would be best advised to stick to your famed lectures on converting C to F. Less humiliation this way for Mir(de).</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1362002339252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:58:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362002391008-162</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's a "Romney?" Is that like a "Mir(de)" only with actual money?</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1362002391008</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:59:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362002413652-163</Id><Topic><Title>Any body remember When Obama said He would cut the Deficit in half........</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361994337962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:45:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Total lie. Obama has added to the debt over a Trillion big ones every year of his Presidency. You don't just blow off a Trillion dollars on a stimulus plan only the left supported, and then admit it did no good, and not increase the debt...at least without lying.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1362002413652</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:00:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362002593714-164</Id><Topic><Title>My My the Raven is Whining About the Cuts</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362002270287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Raven is too stupid to understand the issues. He can only parrot back what the extreme marxist radicals tell him.</Msg><Username>justshutupnfish</Username><Timestamp>1362002593714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:03:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362002728303-165</Id><Topic><Title>Any body remember When Obama said He would cut the Deficit in half........</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361994337962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:45:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Switching the topic to debt in no way contradicts what I was saying about the deficit. If an individual gets in over his head with debt, what is the acceptable solution: To start paying off that debt a little at a time, or to just stop paying his mortgage and his credit card bill? You illusionists seem to want it both ways.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362002728303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:05:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362002814425-166</Id><Topic><Title>Sequestration</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1362001604104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:46:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong as usual - the House has passed at least two budget proposals in the last two years. Hairy reid has not allowed any to come to vote. Obuma has yet to present a budget which even his loyal dimocrats will sign on to. Any movement is up to the senate to get off the pot ( including acupulco gold ) And the world as we know it will be pretty much the same saturday as it is today. less a bit of Obuma kool aid - which is still in good supply during his campaign stops.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1362002814425</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:06:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362002865564-167</Id><Topic><Title>My My the Raven is Whining About the Cuts</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362002270287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've switched the discussion, fringe-like, to debt instead of deficit. Yes the DEBT is growing, but less each year. Don't your righty-tighty talking points make a distinction between the two?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362002865564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:07:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362002976785-168</Id><Topic><Title>Sequestration</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1362001604104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:46:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What would he be campaigning for, Don? Repeal of the two-term limit for presidents?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362002976785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:09:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362002984064-169</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, The Tea Party Is In Great Shape...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987422266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:50:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Teabagger Party is more popular than: 1. Republicans 2. Cockroaches 3. Snakes 4. Various single-celled life forms Less popular than: 1. Boehner 2. Caribou Barbie 3. Millard Fillmore</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1362002984064</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:09:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362003081229-170</Id><Topic><Title>My My the Raven is Whining About the Cuts</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362002270287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be right.....he doesn't make any sense. Sound like someone who's been living on welfare too long.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362003081229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:11:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362003156242-171</Id><Topic><Title>BA Insider Trading Reported !!!</Title><Username>doris.shealey</Username><Timestamp>1361811207875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 11:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big thanks for this report !</Msg><Username>jeanwhite476</Username><Timestamp>1362003156242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:12:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362003263720-172</Id><Topic><Title>Sequestration</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1362001604104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:46:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's campaigning for more debt......want's to destroy capitalism.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362003263720</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:14:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362003321809-173</Id><Topic><Title>YTD , DOW up 6%, but BA lags at 2%,how many 787 are flying now ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976788268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mining_phd, I am watching the Pawelec video now. interesting. William is looking through his experience as you know. Hard to really comment on since it is mainly his personal opinion peppered with some of his work history. So what can anyone say now ? Sounds like he missed on the money on RFID and he is, like many other people the victim of a unethical theft of his invention. Pretty common, Edison is the man( mr failure DC power guy) who stole the genius invention Tesla , Gates and Jobs may have stole the think tank development , if you watch the Pirates of Silicon Valley. After the fact most history can be edited as you must know. I have seen supposedly secret blueprints ( top secret) left out at hanford with a Q and L clearance and been told not to worry about it. Boeing has open houses and so much is left out anyone walking around could steal it And yet a friend of mine got a cam for not locking a security box , so he turned in his key and refused to be the keeper , he should have never accepted the responsibility he did not have to do that in the first place. . Once more Boeing does not care or does not know about all their security fails. Just look at the Airbus book on the Boeing 787, much of it marked proprietary, but try to hop the fence to get to a time clock on time if your running late and are rank and file union worker and the Boeing security will see you get a cam and might shoot you for coming to work. . One time I had been working 12 hour days at Boeing Everett for two years and this guard watched me running to the gate and left his guard box and locked the turnstile on me. I am not the type of guy to take that #$%$ so I climbed the fence as he threatened me , I said," your going to look pretty foolish if you shoot me after locking the gate on me for reporting for duty". half way up the fence he wuzzed out and opened the gate and I sprinted the rest of the way into the plant and was not late. Sometime there is a wreck on the freeway and you just cant make it on time but if you tell your boss. he does not care and he wants you to miss so he can cam you and if you get 3 in a short period then he can force you to work and not be able to use your vacation , and on sick lea. If you have plenty of sick and vacation time they try to bully you into not using it for the team and be a hero #$%$. . many workers now get fired for refusing to work massive overtime. If you cant get the the md for a visit and work 12 hours per day and then you cant use your benefit neat plan . then Boeing does not tell you that you have a brief period of time to use all that overtime you accumulated after working several years of 12 hours day mandatory overtime, and you get your pay check one day with all the sick and vacation removed because after working for 365 days per year for 2 or 3 years straight with every 6th weekend off, and you have to work another 6 months to be able to take a day off which they refuse you. So yes what ever is your perspective there are people who want to control you for their advantage and it will always be so. As far as aliens yep, Area 51 stores the top secret planes under ground and fly at night, and in addition to the testing of security from the air at hanford where a twin engine plane buzzes security stations to see if the guard can read the number on the plane. there are luminous round object that approach hanford from the east ,the west and the south and merge over hanford at night and make no noise they hover for 30 seconds to about 1.5 minutes then take off toward Seattle and climb out of sight on clear nights with no clouds in three seconds and we have seen it , other workers . Yes there are center sections of US nuclear submarines buried at hanford and you can see them at Richland on barges when they are delivered to hanford. I used one of the barges to water ski off. I was twilight and a surreal experience for me that day . Those UFO discs are very bright and make no noise like a comet in brightness only they fly parellel to the ground and stop and hover and accelerate way too fast to be any conventional plane and I have seen them as early as the late 1959 era from my parents house while playing basketball with my school friends the first time I witnessed the silent glowing UFOs . When the USAF transports UFO they put guards on the shipment and one guard is supposed to verify the other guard does not take a peak , but two guard can agree neighter looked .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1362003321809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:15:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362003341697-174</Id><Topic><Title>Leaked BA buy out report!</Title><Username>dennis.jacksonny</Username><Timestamp>1361970587265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:09:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well prepared article</Msg><Username>b.matt52</Username><Timestamp>1362003341697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:15:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362003565169-175</Id><Title>Three Schools Obama attent have lots of Marxist Professors</Title><Msg>,,,and he admitted he hung out with the Marxist professors.... he appointed a Marxist./Maoist to his administration. His policies are built on the foundation of Marxism - class warfare and socialism. It's no wonder why the Raven thinks so highly of him.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362003565169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:19:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362004025077-176</Id><Topic><Title>Sequestration</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1362001604104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:46:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All of his photo ops with EMT and Navy props and . . . . are no different than any political campaign. Its harfd to tell when or IF he has ever stopped. Seems to me he should be meeting with both parties. By the time sequester starts, he will have spent a few 10's of millions in ' airfare" to various campaign stops to parade the poor downtrodden . for more details on his methods, I suggest reading Sol alinsky rules for radicals. Turning loose criminals is a favorite trick of despots almost to the beginning of history. OH wait ? He didnt know about that or approve it - sort of like Bengahzi And now we wont have enough moneyn to buy a wheelchair to use to push granny off then cliff ! Oh the humanity !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1362004025077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:27:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362004095612-177</Id><Title>George Zimmerman Still Being Persecuted for Defending Himself</Title><Msg>(Reuters) - George Zimmerman, the man whose fatal shooting of unarmed Florida teenager Trayvon Martin a year ago captured the nation's attention, wears a disguise or body armor in public as he feels threatened, his lawyer said on Wednesday. Zimmerman remains in hiding and "can't go out in public without wearing a disguise or body armor," defense attorney Mark O'Mara told CNN. Zimmerman claims to have mistaken Martin, who was 17, for a burglar and to have shot him in self defense after a confrontation on February 26, 2012. After police initially questioned and released Zimmerman, citing Florida's so-called Stand Your Ground gun law, celebrity protests and nationwide public demonstrations prompted a re-investigation that led to his arrest for murder. Martin's parents attended a one-year anniversary vigil in New York City late Tuesday, and continued their call for stricter gun laws nationwide. Passed in 2005, Florida's Stand Your Ground law allows people to use lethal force in self-defense. Numerous states have since passed similar laws. Critics of the law say it encourages vigilantes and fosters gun violence. The uproar after Martin's killing led the local police chief to step aside and the governor to appoint a special prosecutor, who charged Zimmerman with second-degree murder. The trial is scheduled for June. O'Mara will ask a judge to dismiss the charges on the grounds of self-defense, at a much-anticipated pre-trial hearing on April 29. O'Mara said Martin badly beat Zimmerman after a confrontation inside a gated community in Sanford, Florida. "George didn't have an opportunity to retreat, so calling this a 'Stand Your Ground' hearing in not accurate," O'Mara told CNN Wednesday. O'Mara said Zimmerman was "very stressed (and) very worried" about the trial and has remained in hiding for the past year.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362004095612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:28:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362004161613-178</Id><Topic><Title>USE (((EIPC))) tech for batteries in the dreamliner</Title><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1359083656473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 22:14:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they finally have someone checking thi issue out..</Msg><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1362004161613</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:29:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362004433594-179</Id><Topic><Title>'The Sequestercist': So Terrifying, It'll Make Your Head Spin</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1362000558165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:29:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A deficit is the amount by which a sum falls short of some reference amount. the reference amount I was referring to was the budget - planned expenditures based on planned income ( revenue) not transfer payments then other deficit re Reid is cognitive as in doing the same thing over and over and expecting different results -- oops that insanity - both fit !! Cognitive deficit, any characteristic that acts as a barrier to cognitive performance</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1362004433594</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:33:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362004776479-180</Id><Topic><Title>Sequestration</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1362001604104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:46:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama posed today with 3 year old Terrell Anderson Jr., one of Rosa Park's relatives, while unveiling a new statue of Rosa. Rosa rode on the bus but Terrell will likely be living in a bus as an adult trying to repay all the debt from Obamanomics. ROTF</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1362004776479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:39:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362005216501-181</Id><Title>Poor lil' innocent Trayvon Martin</Title><Msg>Martin was suspended from school 3 times, caught with a burglary tool -- a flathead screwdriver -- and 12 pieces of jewelry. ABC News (Naples, FL)-- When Trayvon Martin was found dead last week, carrying only a pack of Skittles and a can of tea, supporters took the candy items as a symbol of his innocence. But Florida police say it may be just another sign of the teen's troubled past. On Sunday, a covenience store near Sanford, FL -- just miles from where Trayvon was found shot by a neighborhood watch captain -- reported to police security footage that allegedly shows Martin stuffing the candy and drink into an oversized coat. He then leaves the store without buying anything.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362005216501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:46:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362005562692-182</Id><Topic><Title>Poor lil' innocent Trayvon Martin</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362005216501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:46:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Martin was a punk that did drugs. The left media makes him out to be a nice little kid when he was actually much older, and a much bigger bully than the picture he was shown as being. What's the name of the guy who is accused of killing Martin? Only a totally bad verdict would convict the guy.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1362005562692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:52:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362005749137-183</Id><Topic><Title>'The Sequestercist': So Terrifying, It'll Make Your Head Spin</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1362000558165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:29:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very handy, too, for your "Obuma" arguments. But I was talking about the REAL world. In your own family finances, if you EVEN HAVE a budget, you can overspend it in one category (say movies just before Oscar season) and make it up with a two fewer pizzas. A budget to YOU is nothing much but a general plan. I don't bother with one in my family finances (just check the categories to see where the money is going -- too much to entertainment, I try to cut back on movies over the long term.) The critical metric to balance against expenses is revenue, and you can run up the deficit between those two -- expenses and income -- by using credit so long as you can pay off the deficit at some point or over all the time your creditors will give you. You DO NOT have a deficit by overspending a budget, you have a deficit by overspending your income. You prefer to use the "budget" standard because it is easier for you to make it support your "Obuma" cracks. But the fact is that the DEBT (the accumulation of DEFICITS) is just as much the fault of the 2013 Congress -- and even the 1998 Congress and 1960 Congress, as it is "Obuma's."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362005749137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:55:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362005982025-184</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It doesn't look like he was kicked off at all, it just looks as if Hannity ended the segment. The segment lasted more than 6 minutes and all Ellison did was throw insults the entire time. I've never seen a Republican do that with any of the Democratic shills on CBS, NBC, ABC or PBS news programs have you? If a Black Republican acted as idiotic and childish as Ellison on a news talk show, you'd be screaming he was a crazy Uncle Tom.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1362005982025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:59:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362007005530-185</Id><Topic><Title>Poor lil' innocent Trayvon Martin</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362005216501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:46:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So shoplifting should be a capital crime? A vigilante should shoot to death a kid he ASSUMED was shoplifting?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362007005530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 18:16:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362007112138-186</Id><Topic><Title>'The Sequestercist': So Terrifying, It'll Make Your Head Spin</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1362000558165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:29:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FWIW - we ( family) have been using budget tracking for about 30 years, and I first wrote one for computer on an Apple ii . Has about 30 categories. The greatest increase percentage wise year over year has been in what we call the potty tax. water, stormwater, sewage, etc. We use about $ 20 dollars/month of water or less, but the rest of the $100 plus bill is for so called fees and taxes both local and county. We have zip control over that portion. Somehow though we managed to stay out of debt and rarely do we spend more than ' revenue" in any given year. The surplus allows me to spend a bit of time on the internet :PP No matter what you call it , or how you slice it, and granted both parties over the last two to four decades have increased spending, the facts still remain - we cannot spend our way out of debt by borrowing more money, or in the case of bernake and friends, printing more . Name one socialist system of each according to ability that has survived without having a lot of useable-sellable resources .</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1362007112138</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 18:18:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362007169730-187</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Still Being Persecuted for Defending Himself</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362004095612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:28:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't believe tracking a kid, calling 911 and being told NOT to confront the kid, was "defending himself"? Sorry I'm late in responding, but I had to wipe up the coffee I spluttered when I read your "tribute" to Zimmerman.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362007169730</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 18:19:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362007250785-188</Id><Topic><Title>Sequestration</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1362001604104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:46:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without capitalism, there's no such thing as debt.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362007250785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 18:20:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362007373663-189</Id><Topic><Title>My My the Raven is Whining About the Cuts</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362002270287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The first million $ is the toughest, x6. After you have a million $, it gets easier. Don't be jealous. You can do it too if you don't need a new car every two years, or have to pay dues at the Petroleum Club. Harharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362007373663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 18:22:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362007712339-190</Id><Topic><Title>My My the Raven is Whining About the Cuts</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362002270287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How come nobody believes a DFC?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1362007712339</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 18:28:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362007752060-191</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Still Being Persecuted for Defending Himself</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362004095612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:28:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor little criminal Levon.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1362007752060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 18:29:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362007904204-192</Id><Topic><Title>'The Sequestercist': So Terrifying, It'll Make Your Head Spin</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1362000558165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:29:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you need a special economic lesson that is dumbed down, using Twinkies instead of dollars, so that you can understand it?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1362007904204</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 18:31:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362007957024-193</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Still Being Persecuted for Defending Himself</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362004095612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:28:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If CG had a son, he would look like... But we all know CG doesn't have a son because if he did, he wouldn't have been #$%$ about having to put his Twinkie down and go 20 feet to his mailbox in the snow to get his WC!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1362007957024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 18:32:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362008169239-194</Id><Topic><Title>My My the Raven is Whining About the Cuts</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362002270287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't have to believe me, VaporLock. That's not how money works. You should know from reading Mir. Harharharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362008169239</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 18:36:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362008371876-195</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Still Being Persecuted for Defending Himself</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362004095612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:28:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't be suich a dolt, dolt. You are referring to a salute I once made to the U.S. Postal Service -- you know, that branch of the federal government specifically called for the in the U.S. Constitution (that "GD piece of paper" all you right-fringers love so much that you spank your monkey while misreading it. :-)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362008371876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 18:39:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362008784710-196</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Still Being Persecuted for Defending Himself</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362004095612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:28:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since you thinks it's OK to convict a man without due process let's just do the same with this thug Trayvon who was most certainly soon going to be headed to prison anyway and give a medal for saving the State of Florida 50 grand a year to house him.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362008784710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 18:46:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362009814674-197</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Still Being Persecuted for Defending Himself</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362004095612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:28:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who suggested dropping due process? Due process would have been to detain Zimmerman while an investigation was conducted. Zimmerman may yet get duly processed. He must have been clairvoyant -- and so are you -- to know how much the state of florida was saved.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362009814674</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:03:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362010221274-198</Id><Topic><Title>Any body remember When Obama said He would cut the Deficit in half........</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361994337962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:45:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes sir, you are correct. Deficit as a percentage of GDP: GDP Population Pct. of GDP 2009 13939 306.051 10.13 2010 14508.2 308.746 8.92 2011 14958.6 311.592 8.69 2012 15601.5 314.123 8.51</Msg><Username>eggs_acklee</Username><Timestamp>1362010221274</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:10:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362010976751-199</Id><Topic><Title>Any body remember When Obama said He would cut the Deficit in half........</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361994337962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:45:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And here is a table I found which does not introduce right-fringe-baffling concepts such as percwent of GDP :-)Recent US Federal Deficit Numbers Bush Deficits FY 2007: $161 billion FY 2008: $459 billion FY 2009: $1,413 billion (some say this should be attributed to Obama's term. Maybe so. But much of it is the $750 billion Bush-asked bail-out for the banks that were too big to fail.) Obama deficits: FY 2010: $1,293 billion FY 2011: $1,300 billion FY 2012: $1,089 billion FY 2013*: $901 billion the federal deficit is the amount each year by which federal outlays in the federal budget exceed federal receipts, the gross federal debt increases each year by substantially more than the amount of the deficit each year. That is because a substantial amount of federal borrowing is not counted in the budget.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362010976751</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:22:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362011483443-200</Id><Topic><Title>Any body remember When Obama said He would cut the Deficit in half........</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1361994337962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:45:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for reveling your ignorance.....but have you ever noticed how much bush had the deficit going down until the spend and tax Democrats took control of congress.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362011483443</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:31:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362011751538-201</Id><Topic><Title>My My the Raven is Whining About the Cuts</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362002270287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raven: "Yes the DEBT is growing, but less each year." YES....I guess in the Parallel Universe you and other huge spending communists inhabit/infest...I guess that really IS progress.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362011751538</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:35:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362011840547-202</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought the Kent commie was the worst excuse for a Journalist ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362011840547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:37:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362012057187-203</Id><Title>SPEEA STATUS</Title><Msg>Tech Negotiations SPEEA Technical Unit negotiations update Working through the mediator, The Boeing Company rejected our proposals for further improvements for Technical Unit members. Based on the more than 4,500 verified member responses from the recent Technical Member survey, the Technical negotiating team is resubmitting the existing contract offer to the membership for another vote. While disappointing that the current offer eliminates the pension for anyone hired after March 1, 2013, accepting the company’s last offer would lock-in the considerable improvements we achieved since Boeing’s initial, very regressive, offer we voted down by 97% in October. Those improvements include continuing annual 5% wage pools for the next four years, maintaining medical benefits without increases and continuing the benefits of the 2008-2012 contract for employees in the Technical Unit. Offer September 2012 Offer February 2013 Offer Wage Pools / Guaranteed 2013 - 3.5% / GWI - 1% 2014 – 3% / GWI - 1% 2015 – 3.5% / GWI - 1% 2016 – 3% / GWI - 1% 2013 - 5% / GWI – 2.5% 2014 – 5% / GWI – 2.5% 2015 – 5% / GWI – 2.5% 2016 – 5% / GWI – 2.5% Medical Increased employee contributions and copays No change to current plans Pension Replace BCERP with ‘enhanced 401(k)’ for new hires. Increase to basic benefit calculation for those remaining in pension. Replace BCERP with ‘enhanced 401(k)’ for new hires. Increase to basic benefit calculation for those remaining in pension. The next contract vote will be the third for the 7,500 members in the SPEEA Technical Unit. Members in the Professional Unit narrowly accepted the company’s second offer when votes were counted Feb. 19. Tech Negotiators tentatively scheduled a meeting of the Tech Bargaining Unit Council for Friday to plan for a vote of tech members. Ballots will go to the general membership shortly thereafter. SPEEA Technical Unit negotiations update Working through the mediator, The Boeing Company rejected our proposals for further improvements for Technical Unit members. Based on the more than 4,500 verified member responses from the recent Technical Member survey, the Technical negotiating team is resubmitting the existing contract offer to the membership for another vote. TRANSLATION SOLD OUT BY PRESIDENT AND STAFF</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1362012057187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:40:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362012192128-204</Id><Title>Its not about Gun Control...its about PEOPLE control.</Title><Msg>The plan is clear. Ban the weapons then confiscate them and when the time to turn them in has elapsed, anyone with a weapon is a dangerous criminal to be killed just like a dangerous animal. I feel like I am being herded just like an animal too. Nowhere to turn except the most basic instincts, fight or flight. Comply or die. It is coming, may God give us strength in the troubled waters ahead.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362012192128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:43:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362012493911-205</Id><Title>Marxism is another Term for Tyranny and Obama is a Marxist</Title><Msg>He follows the communist manifesto much more closely than he dose our constitution. His Playbook is Saul Alinsky's rules for Radicals.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362012493911</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:48:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362012970206-206</Id><Topic><Title>Its not about Gun Control...its about PEOPLE control.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362012192128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:43:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps you should become a football or wrestling fan. You'll live longer not having to worry about these phantom bugaboo things.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1362012970206</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:56:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362013414840-207</Id><Topic><Title>Poor lil' innocent Trayvon Martin</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362005216501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:46:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of what race is Oscar Grant? Who is Oscar Grant? You sound like a white liberals that hates white people.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362013414840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 20:03:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362014520188-208</Id><Title>FAA's Lead man HUERTA is short BA</Title><Msg>this might be the best trade I ever made. I can't believe the FAA head mn comes right out and openly admits he is short BA stock from the mid 70's. just notice how he says extensive testing will only be done after the plan is implemented and further explains plan implementation will only occur after plan approval. OMG, any dolt can read through the lines. The man has a three paragraph quote that says absolutely nothing, except basically he is going to drag this thing out prolly till summer and then cover his position. Yeeehaaa, I am going to use my proceeds to go on vacation. In all seriousness I shorted 50 more shares at 77.15, so now i have a total of 250 shares short and will continue to short, just waiting for that day. We all know hat day when BA gets kicked in the balls and he fog is lifted off everyone's face and sentiment changes instantly and we ride and bump down for like two months straight. We've all seen it before. The stock loses like 50% over that two months, along with. Couple of 11-12% down days mixed in to keep one amped up and staying short. You never see that happen to the upside, do ya? Maybe some biotech, but never a sluggish, behemoth like BA.</Msg><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1362014520188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 20:22:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362014884036-209</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots, he scores! lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1362014884036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 20:28:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362015023947-210</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Har Har Har Har HAr Har Har Har !!!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362015023947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 20:30:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362016649534-211</Id><Title>Obama administration has been employing “spambots to push Gun Legislation</Title><Msg>Probably some of the same Cointelpro spambots infesting this board and attempting to influence the weakminded. Republican Rep. Steve Stockman has vowed to further investigate allegations that the Obama administration has been employing “spambots” to send out fake twitter messages and emails to members of Congress to make it appear that there is a ground swell of support for gun control legislation. The messages have been linked to former Obama digital strategist Brad Schenck. The tweets were mostly sent from newly created accounts, and included the #WeDemandAVote hashtag — which Obama encouraged supporters to use. “Obama’s anti-gun campaign is a fraud,” Rep. Stockman said Monday</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362016649534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 20:57:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362016678964-212</Id><Topic><Title>Poor lil' innocent Trayvon Martin</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362005216501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:46:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Martin knew what his intentions were when he viciously assaulted Zimmerman. Under Zimmerman's life threatening position, I would have shot Martin too. No mercy for those who feel emboldened to inflict physical harm and suffering on others. Martin will be judged accordingly to his level of violence.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1362016678964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 20:57:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362016728251-213</Id><Topic><Title>Its not about Gun Control...its about PEOPLE control.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362012192128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:43:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Phantoms sure want our guns pretty bad</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362016728251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 20:58:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362017120559-214</Id><Topic><Title>Its not about Gun Control...its about PEOPLE control.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362012192128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:43:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's self evident that Sparacus knows what he's talking about. That's my conclusion anyway. Liberals try to reason their way out of every situation. What they don't fully understand is that life can be cruel</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1362017120559</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 21:05:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362017511768-215</Id><Topic><Title>Poor lil' innocent Trayvon Martin</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362005216501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:46:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Martin was another street criminal with criminal intentions. No one like Martin would ever be welcome in my home. Liberals, for their own safety, should stay in at nights.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1362017511768</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 21:11:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362017788521-216</Id><Title>In Obama's world</Title><Msg>everyone must be manipulated, one way or the other, to achieve his disired goals.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1362017788521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 21:16:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362017961414-217</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent Commie doesn't know what a journalist is.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1362017961414</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 21:19:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362018183696-218</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Still Being Persecuted for Defending Himself</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1362004095612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:28:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He complains about making the 20 foot trek to his mailbox to retrieve his handout.....what a putz.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1362018183696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 21:23:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362018296816-219</Id><Topic><Title>Its not about Gun Control...its about PEOPLE control.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362012192128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:43:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is the end game?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1362018296816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 21:24:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362019351544-220</Id><Topic><Title>Its not about Gun Control...its about PEOPLE control.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362012192128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:43:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Went by my local sporting goods store today, and there was a crowd outside, and they'd been there for hours waiting for the store to open. 10 AK-15s came in, and out they went, the other 90 folks got promises slips if more come in. Folks ae arming themselves by the droves. Many are buying assault weapons as an investment. They owe a debt of thanks to the Obamanator.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1362019351544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 21:42:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362019736549-221</Id><Topic><Title>YTD , DOW up 6%, but BA lags at 2%,how many 787 are flying now ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976788268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pick and choose? Right back at you. Too bad that my numbers don't support your "pick and choose" Boeing management bashing "numbers games" but as they say, "it is what it is". Boeing has outperformed the Dow by 50% over the last four years which just so happens to be the last lowest point for both the Dow and BA after the economy collapsed. It makes for a reasonable starting point by which to gauge performance long term performance. BA and the Dow are on par over the past 52 weeks. Granted BA is lagging behind since the start of the of 2013 but holding up well. Playboy? Who needs Playboy?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1362019736549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 21:48:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362022169468-222</Id><Topic><Title>”the worst excuse for a journalist I’ve ever seen”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361987979801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 12:59:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, Since it would be against your principles to actually watch Fox, I will tell you that the one that was out of control was Ellison. The congressman's performance was mind-boggling and an example of what trash has been placed into office. I know that some of the posters here have labeled other posters as "the Taliban xxx". Look again at Ellison's performance. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1362022169468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 22:29:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>