<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360131828688-1</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus displays garden variety paranoid schizophrenia psychosis- his complaints against the president always have a grain of truth which he points to to support his delusions but on the whole none of his delusionary ideas will stand up to the truth. Schizophrenia is now thought to be largely hereditary but drug treatment as well as psychotherapy is now used to treat this illness with some success (google this)</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360131828688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 01:23:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360131960473-2</Id><Topic><Title>FLASH! FAA Approves Dreamliner test flights for Boeing!</Title><Username>ohthestupidity344</Username><Timestamp>1360094436353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:00:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A few bad surges in batteries? There were only 50 planes in service and 4% of them caught on fire or came damn close to it. What caused the surges? A problem with the battery or the electrical system? The FAA may not allow these type batteries back in service and if so it is not simply a task to change out to another battery it means a major redesign to the electrical system and that may take a year to redesign and certify. A very risky investment and there are plenty of others to chose that can't catch fire or crash.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1360131960473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 01:26:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360132081077-3</Id><Title>Heavy forces pushing BA down whenever it tries to touch 77.</Title><Msg>Last time it touched 77, it went to 71.6. So far today it's gone back to 75.89. Watch tomorrow it may go below 75. Play the charts for now. It's a sell until roughly around 72. Just ride the seesaw back down and up again. This trading range will not be broken until this is all over.</Msg><Username>jenngreay</Username><Timestamp>1360132081077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 01:28:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360132437632-4</Id><Topic><Title>Was he shooting skeet or shooting</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1360102496022</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:14:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Floydian and Spartacus, I can't comment on the "smoke" - fake or not. However, the scenario of him skeet shooting is reasonable. Skeet shooting is potentially low elevation given the parameters: distance between clay bird and shooter of up to 63 feet, maximum height of target from 15 to 18 feet off the ground, and initial altitude of rifle of about 5 to 5.5 feet above ground; hence, delta altitude from 9.5 to 13 feet. I calculated an angle from the photo of 2.5 degrees, which would place the skeet only about 6.5 feet above the "low house" (3 ft) which throws the bird. The "tall house" is 10 ft; therefore not a likely source of the bird when Obama was shooting. (I simply got this off the internet.) We can criticize for many reasons but I don't think that this is one of them. Otherwise, there is too much noise in the commentary. Now, more important: a skeet shooter does not a gun enthusiast or supporter make. Just some recreation at Camp David. Not necessarily a "photo op" to deceive, but its value obfuscates the larger issue of valuing the 2nd Amendment. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1360132437632</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 01:33:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360135655534-5</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals and progressives not calling for Obama's impeachment are all liars and have no credibility</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360094235765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:57:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What? No counter argument? Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360135655534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 02:27:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360136882309-6</Id><Topic><Title>FLASH! FAA Approves Dreamliner test flights for Boeing!</Title><Username>ohthestupidity344</Username><Timestamp>1360094436353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:00:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The way I see it, the only certainty now is it will take a LONG TIME to figure out what exactly went wrong. Why did I say that? 1. Battery being a potential problem was recognized during the FAA approval process. Therefore, Boeing was aware of the potential problem early on. If it was an easy &amp; cheap fix, Boeing would have already done it. 2. The worst thing that could happen is, NOTHING. This will then drag on for months. No one from FAA will take the risk to approve flying of a plane that can catch fire. As far as the stock price is concerned, as others have said, it will be range trading for some time. Perhaps you can sell both calls and puts at a range comfortable to you to pick up the option premium. I have done that since the news and have been doing pretty good so far.</Msg><Username>oldtimer2013</Username><Timestamp>1360136882309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 02:48:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360139986985-7</Id><Topic><Title>Impeachment Obama for defending America from Terrorist</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1360099542315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:25:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>T O U C H È !!!</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1360139986985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 03:39:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360145367635-8</Id><Title>Imagine how high Share price would be if Dreamliner actually worked!</Title><Msg>Stock price is slowly climbing in spite of GROUNDED Fleet &amp; no idea how to fix BURNING Batteries. This is a worse case senerio yet shares are rebounding.... Go Figure!</Msg><Username>usenatgas</Username><Timestamp>1360145367635</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 05:09:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360146439608-9</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals and progressives not calling for Obama's impeachment are all liars and have no credibility</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360094235765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:57:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somehow I don't think you're really so stupid as to believe what you wrote there... Are you just another garden-variety TROLL?</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1360146439608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 05:27:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360146702647-10</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals and progressives not calling for Obama's impeachment are all liars and have no credibility</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360094235765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 14:57:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>x6xxx234 never has counter arguments; his activity here is limited to lifting his figurative leg on other posts, doggy-style. If he's not copying and pasting from 19th century sources like Bastiat, that is.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1360146702647</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 05:31:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360147890392-11</Id><Topic><Title>A FBI Boeing user has a question</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360096471007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:34:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ZNGA up another 6% in after market trade( 11% total) , in 2 week since you sold your BA , WNR is up 35% . Boeing has made 14% in 5 years. , S and P up 40% in 3 years , do not listen to the FBI team, they can nitpick but they can not treat Boeing stock like a business investment because it is the dow of the dow, any future opinon falls on the face of it the 787 is grounded , strikes cost money, the outsourcing per John Hart- Smith paper is spot on read it like you would a business you are thinking about investing with then read the stock chart and make your decison.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360147890392</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 05:51:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360150736789-12</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another Chris Genna ID</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360150736789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 06:38:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360150750831-13</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and another Chris Genna ID</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360150750831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 06:39:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360150763648-14</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and yet ANOTHER Chris Genna ID</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360150763648</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 06:39:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360151153109-15</Id><Title>Where is the "Liberal" outrage over Endless Wars ?</Title><Msg>Crocodile tears for children killed at Newton...10 x 10 that many children killed in endless wars and now drones...War in Afganistan going into 12th year .... Countless lives ruined. SPELL IT ....................... H Y P O C R I S Y !!!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360151153109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 06:45:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360151196446-16</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris Genna ID</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360151196446</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 06:46:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360151239069-17</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another one</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360151239069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 06:47:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360151637449-18</Id><Topic><Title>Was he shooting skeet or shooting</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1360102496022</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:14:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I dont have to calculate the hypotenuse of the square of PI' to determine the height of the clay bird Bob....Press Secretary said he was Golfing All Day....but you are right..we have far more to worry about then Photoshop'd pic of our beloved President holding a shotgun like a panzy.....</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360151637449</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 06:53:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360153030517-19</Id><Title>Newtown Father Blasts Gun Control</Title><Msg>The Control Freak Liberals are defintly getting routed in the gun control debate...but the Pathetic Mainstream Dinosaur media spun the following: Last week, MSNBC deceptively edited a clip of Neil Heslin, the father of Jesse Lewis, who was murdered at Sandy Hook Elementary, to portray second amendment activists as insensitive by claiming they were heckling Heslin when in reality they were answering a question he had asked them. “Criminals and tyrants – tyrants especially – beware – lockdown is not an option at the Stevens residence and 911 will be dialed after the security of my home has been established,” said Stevens, adding, “Why is that same security my daughter enjoys at home with her Dad not available at school in Newtown – that is what you should be considering, not making her Dad a criminal.” Stevens then quoted Charlton Heston, remarking, “I will tell you here today, you will take my ability to protect my Victoria from my cold dead hands,” before slamming his fist on the table as the audience cheered.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360153030517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 07:17:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360153381253-20</Id><Topic><Title>Ralph Nader: Obama A “War Criminal,” Worse Than Bush</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360120490647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:14:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MSNBC and CNN got hundreds of million in bailout money to catapult the propaganda...the Global Elite think you're an idiot and they think they can peddle any cr*p as reality and you will swallow it.....naturally...there are cult members (examples can be found on this board who ARE swallowing it)...listened to Steve Pizcienek, a former top CIA operative on the radio the other night and he swears the American people are being PSYOP'd as if there were a war going on.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360153381253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 07:23:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360153462184-21</Id><Topic><Title>AFTER SOLVING BATTERIES PROBLEM OTHER MAJOR PROBLEMS WILL ERUPT FOR THE 787</Title><Username>xawa</Username><Timestamp>1359992725444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:45:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sad story</Msg><Username>pierre_from_geneva</Username><Timestamp>1360153462184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 07:24:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360153768325-22</Id><Topic><Title>scafflow of the Boeing message board</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360094974292</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:09:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrrr45, you said waynedick is lost and dumb, he can bash a great American company but he can’t be bashed? what is he stupid? Domerrrrr45, at the end of your flag waving and SSBanner, when the BS flack you spew dies down, I have a question for you. What great American Company am I bashing? Boeing was once a American Company when TA Wilson was the CEO. Why, because all the Boeing engineering was done in America, most the parts were made in America and the result was great, the 1960 era 737 plane made in America, makes most of the profit of all the passenger planes produced by Boeing . The second best profit plane is the 777 another 100% American engineered plane.. I worked on both planes for over 15 years and retired with a full pension. All your BS is just that, Domerrrr45, you need to read the John Hart- Smith, A Boeing Engineer who authored a internal paper about Boeing outsourcing and how it would lead to failure. . This once great Boeing company is no longer located in Seattle, nor does Boeing have the American engineering horsepower to fix much of anything, thanks to past Boeing CEO Harry Stonecipher, a MD guy who called TA Wilson arrogant for using American engineers. Stonecipher a insult to American workers and the past CEO of Boeing outsourced the American worker, if Boeing is a great American company now, then as JOHN Hart-Smith said, the only thing Boeing or American for that matter is the Boeing logo on the plane! That may be outsourced too.domerrrrr45, you sir are an insult to every past, present and future American Boeing worker , including me !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360153768325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 07:29:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360154592070-23</Id><Title>#$%$ Morris dropped by Fox News</Title><Msg>WHY would Fox not renew, he was so good at lying and ignoring the obvious - I thought that's what they wanted! By Tim Kenneally TheWrap #$%$ Morris will no longer be serving as a contributor at Fox News, a spokesperson for the network told TheWrap. Morris' contract had recently expired, and Fox will not be renewing it, the spokesperson said. Bing: Diane Sawyer leaving ABC News? Morris, a former adviser to President Bill Clinton who later turned into a harsh critic for the Clintons, had been a longtime contributor to Fox, but has not appeared on the cable network in recent months. .......... Morris' exit at Fox News comes less than two weeks after news broke that former vice presidential candidate Sarah Palin, who had been a contributor for the cable news network since January 2010, had parted ways with th network. That departure came following reports that Fox News chairman and CEO Roger Ailes was so angry about Palin announcing her plans for the 2012 presidential election on a rival outlet that he wanted to bench her.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360154592070</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 07:43:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360154849823-24</Id><Topic><Title>Ralph Nader: Obama A “War Criminal,” Worse Than Bush</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360120490647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:14:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I talk to lots of Veerans every day..people are waking up</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360154849823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 07:47:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360154879330-25</Id><Topic><Title>A FBI Boeing user has a question</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360096471007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:34:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fbi team up early with a thumbs down hummm</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360154879330</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 07:47:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360154937069-26</Id><Topic><Title>Newtown Father Blasts Gun Control</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360153030517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 07:17:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was in thier face, speaking the truth to the political hypocrits as an honest man and a dedicated father...a true American spokesman.</Msg><Username>nidan7500</Username><Timestamp>1360154937069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 07:48:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360155194755-27</Id><Topic><Title>Newtown Father Blasts Gun Control</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360153030517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 07:17:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah I know Brother..I saw the video and was inspired...looked like Jimmy Stewart going to Washington or a Norman Rockwell painting......This is good vrs Evil now and our country is under attack.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360155194755</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 07:53:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360155353393-28</Id><Topic><Title>A FBI Boeing user has a question</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360096471007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:34:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"dow of dow" should be dog of the dow I guess some FBI does not like facts BA 1 % gain for one year 14% gain for 5 years , while s and and p gain for 3 years is 40%, sorry who is the thumbs down person you don' tlike making 40 cents on each dollar you invest, you would rather make 1 cent on each dollar in boeing or 15 cents in 5 years for each dollar you invested in Boeing , that would be less than inflation in 5 years. check food prices not counted in the Feds inflation figures most foods are 30 to 45% higher than they were 5 years ago, sorry you feel the need to opinion thumbs down to wanting 1 cent and not 40 cent refurn on your investment der !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360155353393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 07:55:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360156003532-29</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apply for a position with Fox News....Richard Morris was let go. You and him distort in similar ways. Maybe your on-camera charisma is better (whose wouldn't be) than his.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360156003532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 08:06:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360156054309-30</Id><Topic><Title>AFTER SOLVING BATTERIES PROBLEM OTHER MAJOR PROBLEMS WILL ERUPT FOR THE 787</Title><Username>xawa</Username><Timestamp>1359992725444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:45:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your right the outsourcing failure is system wide, 3.5 years late then gounded , there is no history that shows the system wide outsourcing failure to suddenly fly except that the idea flew in the Chicago board room, Wow a MBA bean counter runs into reality ! I guess the 787 is not buring up the stock price too much , so how is the outsourcing working for you now Boeing CEO I see why you were turned out of GE , we gae you more than 5 years to proove yourself at Boeing. The result the stock price for 5 years is up 14% while the CEO gae himself a 34% pay raise last year hummmmmmm me thinks the compensation consultant forgot to put actual real world flying planes in teh bonus plan !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360156054309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 08:07:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360156117831-31</Id><Topic><Title>Imagine how high Share price would be if Dreamliner actually worked!</Title><Username>usenatgas</Username><Timestamp>1360145367635</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 05:09:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Increase your shares on the dips - the 787 eventually (2017?) will be what they proposed it to be</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360156117831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 08:08:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360156335276-32</Id><Topic><Title>Imagine how high Share price would be if Dreamliner actually worked!</Title><Username>usenatgas</Username><Timestamp>1360145367635</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 05:09:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you could say the dreamliner is not making the Boeing stock fly up, but the 2 billion allocated in stockholder buy back is working so far .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360156335276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 08:12:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360156486591-33</Id><Topic><Title>Imagine how high Share price would be if Dreamliner actually worked!</Title><Username>usenatgas</Username><Timestamp>1360145367635</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 05:09:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so 100% gain in WNR in 1 year and 35% gain in the last two weeks and 11% gain in znga in one day, hope you do other trades until 2017/ Boeing up zero to 1% for one year and 14% for 5 years does not compare with 35% GAIN IN 2 WEEKS .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360156486591</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 08:14:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360156811681-34</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont believe in Left-Right paradigm..dont watch CNN OR FOX..get a better clue</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360156811681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 08:20:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360157107476-35</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$ Morris dropped by Fox News</Title><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360154592070</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 07:43:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And that's no spin. . . . . . . . . . . .</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360157107476</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 08:25:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360157692512-36</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you suppose they are losing viewers at an alarming rate?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1360157692512</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 08:34:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360158292652-37</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Should Get Off the Dime</Title><Username>beachbum92307</Username><Timestamp>1360095429920</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:17:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BEACHBUM92307, here is what a guy who knows batteries has to say about the 787 battery issue,"The lithium-ion batteries installed on the Boeing 787 are inherently unsafe, says Elon Musk, founder of SpaceX and owner of electric car maker Tesla. “Unfortunately, the pack architecture supplied to Boeing is inherently unsafe,” writes Musk in an email to Flightglobal. “Large cells without enough space between them to isolate against the cell-to-cell thermal domino effect means it is simply a matter of time before there are more incidents of this nature,” he adds."They [Boeing] believe they have this under control, although I think there is a fundamental safety issue with the architecture of a pack with large cells,” writes Musk in an email. “It is much harder to maintain an even temperature in a large cell, as the distance from the center of the cell to the edge is much greater, which increases the risk of thermal runaway.”</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360158292652</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 08:44:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360158995040-38</Id><Title>is the 787 the Washington Mutual of self regulation ?</Title><Msg>It sounds like a sick libertarian joke: We don't need independent government regulation of airliners, because if one crashes then customers will make the rational choice and not fly that plane. The free market works! But this is no joke. The blockbuster story from the Seattle Times' Kyung M. Song indicates that the Federal Aviation Administration pretty much let Boeing attest that Boeing's revolutionary 787 Dreamliner was safe. It's called "self-certification" and sounds like a recipe for disaster. We've been here before. After the "financial services industry" was deregulated, capped by the repeal of Glass-Steagall in 1999, the big banks and Wall Street went on a binge of cooking up exotic hustles in an ideological atmosphere of self-regulation. Not only did the banks themselves "train" regulators about such complex rackets as mortgages bundled in collateralized debt obligation derivatives, but the regulators were encouraged to let the banks regulate themselves. After all, the banks had every "rational" incentive to see that the system worked properly. Unfortunately, the banks' real incentives were to rake in huge short-term profits and compensation dependent on practices that were neither safe nor sound. This was on display at every big bank, but especially at Washington Mutual, a thrift operating with barely any regulatory oversight. Complexity equals fragility. And when government regulators are defanged, both dangers rise exponentially. In the case of the big banks, the world financial system was pushed to the edge of collapse. WaMu went down in the biggest banking failure in history. Trillions of dollars from taxpayers and the Federal Reserve were required to prevent a second Great Depression. Another spectacular failure: Self-regulation in food safety. Now comes Boeing, which told the FAA that the Dreamliner was safe. And the FAA allowed it to fly -- until undeniable trouble forced the grounding. And remember, when this airplane flies again it will go into service with many airlines that have outsourced maintenance to cheap locales around the globe, again mostly unregulated. Every twist of this story gets worse.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360158995040</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 08:56:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360159166905-39</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the "Liberal" outrage over Endless Wars ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360151153109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 06:45:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've provided examples of liberals like Ralph Nader and Dennis Kucinich who are assessing Obama as worse than W, so there are liberals who are outraged. These are the liberals with a mindset from the 1960s who would be in the streets demonstrating against Obama for all his lies and abuse of power. My conclusion is that people like Hooz, Genna and a few others here are not liberals and are something different. They are political fanatics, rather than true liberals like those mentioned earlier, who readily embrace Obama's lies and abuse of power and willingly sacrifice any liberal principles they might have had. They are displaying behavior that is eerily similar to the blind faith of religious fanatics.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360159166905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 08:59:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360160011166-40</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the "Liberal" outrage over Endless Wars ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360151153109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 06:45:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Communists...at least that is what the Hooz posted he espired to be. Liberals really don't have any principles. At least not any that stand the test of scrutiny. They hate rich folks, even though new rich folks are created every day, in a properly governed economy. Jobs created, new folks moving up the ladder, poor people that need a safety net benifiting from wealth creaion. Liberals destroy all of that. The health and welfare of the world, not just those in the USA benifit from a well functioning economic system that we had in the past, and it has deteriorated because of liberalism.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360160011166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 09:13:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360160277219-41</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Board of Directors, the club, bad stock to own</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360041458639</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 00:17:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for the 3 thumbs up, the other issue is how Boeing sets easy performance goals. I remember the executive bonus was tied to long term stock price growth. the definition was only 20 trade days with the stock price above a threshold, the threshold was a few cents , the next threshold was anothe few cents . This is what the IRS is trying to real in. Rank and file workers get a yearly income statment and then pay taxes on what they make less IRS allowed deductions. CEO's get to pick what is considered taxable income . Read up on it "Known as Section 162(m) of the Internal Revenue Code, that provision limits the tax deductibility of pay for the five highest-paid executives at public companies to $1 million, unless the pay is determined to be "performance-based." To qualify as performance-based pay, compensation committees must set "pre-established" and "objective" performance goals. Shareholders must approve the goals, and the compensation committee must certify they were met. The shareholders vote but Boeing is maily owned by institutions which go along with the compensation recomendations</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360160277219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 09:17:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360160560351-42</Id><Title>this battery thing is pathecic, it's got to be more</Title><Msg>this is a joke allready</Msg><Username>archarch_60477</Username><Timestamp>1360160560351</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 09:22:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360161765943-43</Id><Topic><Title>80 coming</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360080312582</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:05:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Seattle times: Employees at Boeing’s new manufacturing complex in South Carolina, which is non-union, will get a higher annual incentive bonus this month than those in the Puget Sound region. All South Carolina Boeing employees, salaried and hourly, will receive 17.95 days of extra pay on Feb. 28. That’s equivalent to a bonus of 4.9 percent of base pay. Boeing provides the South Carolina workforce a separate incentive plan from the rest of the company, with a payout based on a combination of 2012 financial results plus the North Charleston site’s performance on metrics assessing safety, quality, morale, delivery and cost. The company incentive plan for salaried workers elsewhere in Boeing’s commercial airplanes unit will pay out a bonus of 14.75 days’ extra pay on Feb. 28. And local hourly workers in the Machinists union have another, separate incentive plan that on Feb. 21 will pay a 3.1 percent bonus, though this is based on gross pay including overtime.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360161765943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 09:42:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360162198930-44</Id><Title>ICE Leader: Agents Prohibited From Enforcing Two Most Fundamental Sections of U.S. Immigration Law</Title><Msg>Yesterday during a House Judiciary Committee hearing on Capitol Hill, National Immigration and Customs Enforcement Council 118 of the American Federation of Government Employees President Chris Crane testified that immigration reform isn't about reform at all, but instead is about politics. "Death or serious injury to ICE officers and agents appears more acceptable to ICE, DHS, and Administration leadership, than the public complaints that would be lodged by special interest groups representing illegal aliens," Crane said. Crane detailed the massive problems within the agency with enforcement, how illegal aliens lie to work the system, how illegal aliens will lie in order to be granted amnesty and explained how moral within the agency is at an all time low. "The results from the most recent morale survey for Federal agents were released in December 2012. ICE Dropped in the rankings to 279 out of 291 Federal agencies surveyed leaving only 12 agencies that ranked lower in employee morale and job satisfaction than ICE," Crane said. "While ICE employees are frequently demonized by special interest groups and media outlets, it should be known that many ICE employees are themselves the sons and daughters of immigrants of grandsons and granddaughters of immigrants; or are married to immigrants, or are the proud parents of adopted babies born outside the U.S. For many of our officers, English was not their first language, or they grew up in a bilingual household.....ICE agents are not monsters as some would portray them." Crane also explained the erosion of the rule of law thanks to special interest groups representing and advocating on behalf of illegal immigrants while agents are often punished for simply enforcing the law. Crane even went so far as to suggest law enforcement has been turned into a joke. "For the last four years it has been a roller coaster for ICE officers with regard to who they can or cannot arrest, and which federal laws they will be permitted to enforce," Crane said. "Most Americans would be surprised to know that immigration agents are regularly prohibited from enforcing the two most fundamental sections of the Unites States immigration law. According to ICE policy, in most cases immigration agents can no longer arrest persons solely for entering the United States illegally. Additionally, in most cases immigration agents cannot arrest persons solely because they have entered the United State s with a visa and then overstayed that visa and failed to return to their country." KP</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360162198930</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 09:49:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360162988028-45</Id><Topic><Title>13 Indicator BA Research Report</Title><Username>michaelkovac</Username><Timestamp>1360160168445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 09:16:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great news!</Msg><Username>michelecook203</Username><Timestamp>1360162988028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:03:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360163476903-46</Id><Title>Another Obama Record - 8,830,026: Americans on Disability</Title><Msg>Vote Democrat - it's easier than working a job.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360163476903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:11:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360163638893-47</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the "Liberal" outrage over Endless Wars ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360151153109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 06:45:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look..thats why there is a phony left right paradigm..and why they are pushing a race war with balkanization race baiting...these are NOT true 60s style 'liberals" like you suggested.....Abuse of Power is out of control....the Zealots who will accept ANY outrage as a wonderful thing will be the first to call you a racist if you complain. Jedi Mind tricks only works on the weak minded</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360163638893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:13:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360163846088-48</Id><Title>Virginia moves closer to creating state’s own currency</Title><Msg>Lawmakers in Virginia say they want to keep their options open in case the value of the U.S. dollar ever collapses — so they’re considering minting state coinage. The Washington Post reported Tuesday that a proposal to study the effectiveness of such a plan “sailed through” the state’s lower house this week: The idea that Virginia should consider issuing its own money was dismissed as just another quixotic quest by one of the most conservative members of the state legislature when [Virginia Del. Robert G.] Marshall introduced it three years ago. But it has since gained traction not only in Virginia, but also in states across the country as Americans have grown increasingly suspicious of the institutions entrusted with safeguarding the economy.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360163846088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:17:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360163856212-49</Id><Topic><Title>80 coming</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360080312582</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:05:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe seattle should listen and throw the unions out.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360163856212</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:17:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360163926058-50</Id><Title>BTW BA UP AGAIN!!!!</Title><Msg>Just in case wayne didn't see it.....ROTFLMAO</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360163926058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:18:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360164226595-51</Id><Topic><Title>80 coming</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360080312582</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:05:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Either you need a new math class or be the SC math is way off. 17.95 days = 3.59 weeks. 3.59/52 weeks = 6.9% bonus. I hope when you or SC inspects part dimensions the math is closer.</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1360164226595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:23:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360164484612-52</Id><Topic><Title>BTW BA UP AGAIN!!!!</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360163926058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:18:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne is unaware ..sorry! He is busy learning 2d grade math!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360164484612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:28:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360164781033-53</Id><Topic><Title>BTW BA UP AGAIN!!!!</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360163926058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:18:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right you are! It is up about 70 cents from where it was on this date one year ago! Congrats to you!</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1360164781033</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:33:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360165066077-54</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good Post. What is shocking is non of these even brought the discussion of impeachment. Twer it have been GW BUSH the liberal media would have been all over it day, after day, after day until charges were brought.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360165066077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:37:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360165092486-55</Id><Topic><Title>BTW BA UP AGAIN!!!!</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360163926058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:18:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who said anything about holding it long term???? NOT ME</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360165092486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:38:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360165842510-56</Id><Topic><Title>80 coming</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360080312582</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:05:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seattle times Dominic Gates wrote the article. Seattle Times aerospace reporter Tell him.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360165842510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:50:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360165932705-57</Id><Title>When cnbc starts trying to drive a stock price down as they are now on BA.. ITS TIME TO BUY !!</Title><Msg>I have seen it so many times ...</Msg><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360165932705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:52:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360166856034-58</Id><Topic><Title>A FBI Boeing user has a question</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360096471007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:34:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr Fartz , did you get into ZNGA I am now up another 8.5% and that is 15.5% with 7% yesterday so I told you about WNR and I gave you a heads up yesterday on ZNGA so you could have booked a 8% profit a few minutes ago ! This is what I do while emailing about Boeing .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360166856034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:07:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360166874873-59</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alex Jones is SOOO much better !?!?!?!?!?!!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360166874873</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:07:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360167047292-60</Id><Topic><Title>scafflow of the Boeing message board</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360094974292</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:09:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>any more comment Mr domerrrrr45!</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360167047292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:10:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360167376096-61</Id><Title>Rethug efforts to wreck the Postal Service showing early results</Title><Msg>Today the Postal Service announced that they would stop Saturday deliveries in order to try to cut costs further. They would be making money if the Rethugligans hadn't succeeded in their attempt to load them up - as no other public function has been - with debt by demanding that they prepay their retirement benefits for the next 75 years. Anything to break a union!! Who else is going to deliver that letter to grandma's house from you at Christmas for 46 cents??? Nobody!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>windyhorn</Username><Timestamp>1360167376096</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:16:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360167492192-62</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Five times on one thread you have stated with certainty that other posters are me. None were. You would like people to think you are not a paranoid mental case but you prove you are every day.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360167492192</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:18:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360168142851-63</Id><Topic><Title>Sould We Dissolve the United States of America?.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360164410154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:26:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good question hope4......for those victims of socialized government education the Articles of Confederation may have been better for the country than the U.S. Constitution. It proved what was necessary for the states to interact with each other and provided international legitimacy for the Continental Congress to have a common defense and direct the American Revolutionary War. The close people are to their government the more ability they have to hold their government accountable. That may be why 49 out of 50 states have a balanced budget requirement, yet we don't have one for the federal government. $17 trillion of debt just might indicate how irresponsible the Federal Government has become and give us a hint why Democrats refuse to pass a budget.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360168142851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:29:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360168742992-64</Id><Topic><Title>When cnbc starts trying to drive a stock price down as they are now on BA.. ITS TIME TO BUY !!</Title><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360165932705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:52:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The NTSB comments on the definition of the 787 problem being weeks away seems to be a positive comment. They didn't say "weeks or months away" as some have said in the past However, it sounds like the upcoming NTSB briefing will be more of a propaganda presentation on the greatness of the NTSB than anything positive on the 787 problem. And the NTSB Chairperson Deborah Hersman is on the hot list for becoming the Transporation Secretary so she wants to paint a favorable picture of the NTSB. But if you couple the request from BA to do test flights with her "weeks away" statement, it does sound like there is light at the end of the tunnel and it isn't a train coming. Only time will tell.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360168742992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:39:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360169207954-65</Id><Title>CBO: Debt Spiral Deepening, Health Costs Soaring</Title><Msg>Behold, the projected consequences of four more years. Philip Klein surveys the wreckage described in the latest comprehensive budget report from the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office (most of these estimates assume an unrealistic "baseline" in which the "doc fix" doesn't happen and various unpopular cuts to Medicare actually go into effect): So between now and the end of the decade, the national debt will explode, at least seven million people will be denied keeping their current plan even if they like it (other estimates are considerably higher), federal healthcare spending is poised to swamp the rest of the federal budget, and unemployment is likely to remain dismally high. After 2023, the picture gets much worse. Former CBO director Douglas Holtz-Eakin runs through some of these numbers in chart form in this user-friendly report, which is worth a read. The actuaries also expect sluggish growth in the near and medium-term future, stunted by the growing debt burden. Tepid growth would still beat Q4 of 2012, in which the US economy actually contracted for the first time since 2009. Jim Pethokoukis adds a critical piece of information that contextualizes the anticipated debt boom: G.Bebson The flood of new debt comes despite tax revenue from 2015 through 2023 being higher than the historical average. Houston, we have a spending problem and a president who just doesn't get it.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360169207954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:46:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360169697734-66</Id><Topic><Title>Rethug efforts to wreck the Postal Service showing early results</Title><Username>windyhorn</Username><Timestamp>1360167376096</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:16:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Senate which is controlled by Dems are the ones that sponsored and passed the legislation requiring the repayment to the treasury according to this Bloomberg article. Where are you getting your information? Source please? ______________________________________________ Bloomberg News Projected Post Office Pension Surplus Shrinks as Rates Fall By Angela Greiling Keane on November 13, 2012 A pension-fund surplus the U.S. Postal Service has been counting on to help dig out of its financial hole is smaller than previously estimated because of lower interest rates. The projected excess in the Federal Employees Retirement System for benefits covering about 471,000 current postal employees shrank to $2.6 billion from $10.9 billion a year earlier, John Berry, director of the U.S. Office of Personnel Management, said in an Oct. 30 letter to Postmaster General Patrick Donahoe. The lower estimated pension surplus adds to the financial woes of the Postal Service, which is scheduled on Nov. 15 to report its loss for the fiscal year ended Sept. 30. The agency has said it may lose $15 billion in fiscal 2012, during which it exhausted its borrowing authority from the U.S. Treasury. The service skipped two payments due to the U.S. Treasury totaling $11.2 billion for health benefits of future retirees, saying it couldn’t afford them. Postal legislation the Senate passed in April would refund what was then an estimated $11 billion FERS account surplus and allow the post office to create its own health-benefits system. The Senate legislation would determine the repayment amount based on OPM’s analysis, meaning that sum would be less under the new estimate than it was when the bill passed. Senator Tom Carper, a Delaware Democrat who is a sponsor of the Senate bill, is reviewing the OPM’s latest calculation, Emily Spain, a spokeswoman, said.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360169697734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:54:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360170189515-67</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the "Liberal" outrage over Endless Wars ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360151153109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 06:45:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's so true, but it's not just limited to a few leftys on this board. Look at the liberal media types and the political left (democrats). They are having a religious cult experience with continuous war, illegal killings, gigantic all powerful government, leftist oriented fascism, and cultural self destruction. It's really very troubling and downright spooky. These people would normally never support these actions by the government, but it appears they are unable to even see this evil, much less take any action to oppose it. They actually fanatically support it! Go figure. It looks like a kind of religion, but to a very strange god.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1360170189515</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:03:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360170657940-68</Id><Title>Roughing it in George Town.</Title><Msg>Sometimes even rich guys like myself have to rough it. When I got down here, all 6 of my condos were rented so I have to stay in a friend's guest house on seven mile beach. The sun shinning off that white sand is hard on the eyes and you have to go inside to shower off after swimming in the salt water. No pool and not much to do here except watch an occasional group of topless European women trying to get their boobs sun burned. Not nearly as much thongs to watch as at the condos. It's not too rough though, we do have TV and internet even if there's no maid service or bartenders. It's tough but somebody has to do it.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360170657940</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:10:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360170682278-69</Id><Title>Boeing stock a chart look</Title><Msg>Boeing stock is in a narrow trade range slightly up mainly due to the 2 billion allocated shareholder stock buyback , it had a gap up open yesterday and as usual, in that situation for any stock, it filled in the gap today( went down firstto the 25 md average and held) it is up 38 cents .5% up. the resistance is at 75.91 the stock is above the 25-50 200 MDA %K is oer %D( good) the volume for 3 days has been average -not increasing (bad) the stock volume is less than 30% of the daily average in the first hour (bad) This stock neeeds to break out above 85 and hold to be a potential buy. ZNGA, as I already pointed out in another user comment was up 7% yesterday and then went up 6% in after market trading and I booked 15.5% gain in two days. Boeing in five years has made 14% so that is the comparison. 2 days 15.5% for me and 14 % gain in 5 years for all buy and hold Boeing investors. If you read up on John Hart-Smith,-outsourcing is a fail, then learn how to read a stock chart, and forget the FBI team. Only treat Boeing stock like a business investment, then you would realize it is a bad risk to reward and does not compare with the 3 major averages for return. the S and P is up 40.5% in 3 years .Think about it for the year Boeing has made zero gain while the CEO has given himself a 34% wage increase. There is no performance criteria for the CEO that reflects real flying airplanes. the Boeing executive is also the Chairman of the Board that is like the voter( shareholder) having his ballet reviewed and counted by the candidate without any oversight. Please review my other user subjects . thanks</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360170682278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:11:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360171292124-70</Id><Title>DHS Needs A Billion Rounds Of Ammunition To Stop Nine Tax Evaders</Title><Msg>DHS published this page yesterday, apparently explaining why they have purchased enough ammunition to shoot everyone in the US four times. Violent extremist groups ─ like al-Qa’ida and its affiliates and adherents, violent supremacist groups, and violent “sovereign citizens” ─ are leveraging online tools and resources to propagate messages of violence and division. If you follow their link to violent sovereign citizens, the only examples they have are nine people who refuse to pay taxes and who might own guns. They don’t list a single example of violence by a domestic group. They need 7,000 AR-15s and over a billion rounds of ammunition to stop non-existent violence from a few tax evaders. This is exactly what the founders of our country warned us against. That a well regulated militia, composed of the body of the people, trained to arms, is the proper, natural, and safe defence of a free state; that standing armies, in time of peace, should be avoided, as dangerous to liberty; and that, in all cases, the military should be under strict subordination to, and governed by, the civil power. Virginia Bill of Rights Which civil power does DHS report to? Contact your Congress people today, before it is too late. h/t Steve Goddard PS - The rounds being purchased by the DHS are all hollow point.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360171292124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:21:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360171373853-71</Id><Title>Rand Paul Introduces National Right to Work Act</Title><Msg>Kentucky Senator Rand Paul introduced the National-Right-to-Work act this week. The legislation strips current labor law of forced unionisim language which can prevent some Americans who seek employement from obtaining a job. "Every American worker deserves the right to freedom of association - and I am concerned that the 26 states that allow forced union membership and dues infringes on these workers' rights," Sen. Paul said on his website. "Right to work laws ensure that all Americans are given the choice to refrain from joining or paying dues to a union as a condition for employment. Nearly 80 percent of all Americans support the principles and so I have introduced a national Right to Work Act that will require all states to give their workers the freedom to choose." Paul describes six current provisions in the National Labor Relations Act (NLRA) and the Railway Labor Act (RLA) as "freedom crushing" and "infringing," pointing out there are 8 million workers who are currently forced by law to pay union dues. Paul is sure to see major push back on this, especially when it comes to Harry Reid in the Senate. Considering we just saw President Obama's appointments for the NLRB struck down by a court, he'll be in no mood to deal with this either. K Pavlich</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360171373853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:22:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360171925383-72</Id><Topic><Title>Virginia moves closer to creating state’s own currency</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360163846088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:17:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Real money might replace worthless paper? My what a novel Idea.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360171925383</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:32:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360172375740-73</Id><Topic><Title>Roughing it in George Town.</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360170657940</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:10:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why sit and watch that sounds boring you should go out and play with some boobs.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360172375740</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:39:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360172391085-74</Id><Title>Oh Did I mention it's 31degrees Celsius Here?</Title><Msg>.....that's 88 degrees Fahrenheit. hahahahaha.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360172391085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:39:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360172568003-75</Id><Topic><Title>Roughing it in George Town.</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360170657940</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:10:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like Paul Newman said, "why go out for a hamburger when you can have a steak at home."</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360172568003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:42:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360172797161-76</Id><Topic><Title>ICE Leader: Agents Prohibited From Enforcing Two Most Fundamental Sections of U.S. Immigration Law</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360162198930</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 09:49:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't it a violation of Obama's Oath of Office not to enforce laws? What are you guys paying him for anyway? Me, I decided not to pay him anything. Hahahahahahah.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360172797161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:46:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360173082024-77</Id><Title>Y'all Ain't Getting Worried about the Cost of Obama care are you?</Title><Msg>Most of the people stuck in the mediocre class ain't smart enough to worry about it till it hits them in the face like a baseball bat.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360173082024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:51:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360173742836-78</Id><Topic><Title>Will BA Bounce? SEE OUR IN DEPTH BA BOUNCE REPORT</Title><Username>kyledurham521</Username><Timestamp>1360012053563</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good report,thanks</Msg><Username>hermangill931</Username><Timestamp>1360173742836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:02:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360173885560-79</Id><Topic><Title>Y'all Ain't Getting Worried about the Cost of Obama care are you?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360173082024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:51:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"till it hits them in the face like a baseball bat." dude, I take it you are speaking from personal experience, because your posts make you sound like a fruitcake.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1360173885560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:04:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360174246342-80</Id><Title>Protecting Your Wealth With Gold</Title><Msg>Gold is REAL money and has been for more than 5,000 years. You people that are rich guys like myself, should have a minimum of a few hundred thousand dollars in a vault somewhere. Not a bank safety deposit box but a private commercial vault. And to be really safe split it up 2 or 3 hundred thousand in the U.S. and the same amount out of the country....like here on Grand Cayman. There is so much gold here that the Georgia Democrat Representative should be very concerned about the Island capsizing. You people in the mediocre class better stick to preserving beans and rice and finding some way to protect yourselves from people that will want to take it from you. Gold and silver is gonna dip soon.....will be a good time to accumulate. Democrats are ruining the country.....but only for those who ain't smart enough to know what to do to survive and thrive during their folly.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360174246342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:10:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360174280631-81</Id><Topic><Title>Rethug efforts to wreck the Postal Service showing early results</Title><Username>windyhorn</Username><Timestamp>1360167376096</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:16:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you posted doen't address what the Rethugs did in 2007 that started this mess. Try again!!</Msg><Username>windyhorn</Username><Timestamp>1360174280631</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:11:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360174364319-82</Id><Topic><Title>Y'all Ain't Getting Worried about the Cost of Obama care are you?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360173082024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:51:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Son....you been eat'n too much fruitcake.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360174364319</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:12:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360174898905-83</Id><Topic><Title>Rethug efforts to wreck the Postal Service showing early results</Title><Username>windyhorn</Username><Timestamp>1360167376096</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:16:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't have to as it was made clear that the Post Office had a pension surplus. You understand what a pension surplus means don't you? So what whatever happened in 2007 led to this pension surplus that Bloomberg refers to in this 2 month old article. Hos is that everyone else can figure this out from reading the Bloomberg article except you?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360174898905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:21:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360174955084-84</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not so sure about that Joe. Bush wnet over the line a few times during the "WMD's in Iraq" fiasco leading up to war.....naturally there was some arm twisting to get us into war. The level of corruption during the Obama tenure is beyond the beyond.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360174955084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:22:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360175406125-85</Id><Topic><Title>BTW BA UP AGAIN!!!!</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360163926058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:18:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrrr45, you said Wayne is unaware, sorry! He is busy learning 2d grade math! Domerrrrr45 please, you are a vulgarian with my name so please since you do not like me if that helps you continue your rant remember you changed my name to waynedick, . I called ZNGA and booked 15.5% in two days, it hit the resistance today at 3.09 broke but could not hold on lower volume. Boeing has made 14% in 5 years is that the second grade math? Ok the figures are right. WNR is up 100% in a year while Boeing is flat for a year. I am booked on WNR too. If getting together with your team is working for you , then good for you. If you need to identify with a group, I understand. I am aware. If that makes you of value to yourself good for you. Please go to the scofflaw subject and read and comment. First email or communicate with your team members get a group think going, if that is what you need first. What ever you need. Boeing is up 15 cents or .20% and went to the pivot point on lower volume and failed. I have detailed all this for you in my what 2d grade level for you to read. If that insult makes Boeing go up 15.5% in tow days get back to me on that method.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360175406125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:30:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360175512452-86</Id><Topic><Title>BTW BA UP AGAIN!!!!</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360163926058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:18:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who said anything about what or when, I did say what I said, and you, unposter76 are not standing up for anything , just waiting and trying to figure it all out.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360175512452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:31:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360175856972-87</Id><Topic><Title>BTW BA UP AGAIN!!!!</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360163926058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:18:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gambling no Boeing is up .15 cents or .18% and failed at the pivot point on less volume. ZNGA gained 15.5% in less than two days hit resistance at 3.09 and failed on lower volume I booked more in two day that Boeing has made in 5 years , that accordging to domerrrrr45 is 2d grade math and somehow that makes me unaware. Ok I am unaware with a gain of 15.5% booked and better than being a domerrrrr45 vulgarian with a zero yearly gain on Boeing and a 14 5 buy and hold for any Boeing shareholder for 5 years. I am very happy with reading a stock chart and making money and the feelings of the gourp think here , if it works for making money then I am in, if not I will use the stock chart .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360175856972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:37:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360176293023-88</Id><Topic><Title>BTW BA UP AGAIN!!!!</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360163926058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:18:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW Boeing up again, well yes it did exactly what i said it would do today it gapped open up yesterday and backfilled to the 25 mda at 75.46 and it is up 15 cents or .18 of a percent. unposter76 , is that like ZNGA up 15.5% in two days and booked I have booked my WNR at 100% for the year based on the stock chart and I have listed what is happening with Boeing stock . Who said what when is not responsive , I said what Boeing has done for one year and 5 years and compared Boeing to the 3 averages and two a long term stock I just sold WNR and a short term swing trade that I called and make 15.5% and the rersisteance for ZNGA is 3.09 and it went to 3.12 and failed I was out before that price . I can read a stock chart so I can do that .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360176293023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:44:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360176610182-89</Id><Topic><Title>Y'all Ain't Getting Worried about the Cost of Obama care are you?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360173082024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:51:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope- not worried a bit. Secretary Sebelius is doing a good job in spite of the nullification crowd and government exchanges are now being put in to place. These exchanges will force meaningful competition upon the Insurance Company pirates and make it possible to get insurance for a reasonable rate. The big lie about &amp;20,000 premiums is just that a lie and people are happily discovering this fact now.</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360176610182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:50:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360176821268-90</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not IMO. Bush wanted to go in right away IF Saddam had WMD's, and he demonstrated that he had them in killing hundreds of thousands of his people. All the free world intelligence sources said he had them Liberals on our intelligence committee said he had them. But liberals? They supported that corrupt United Nations, and liberal Hans Bliz, who would go in, and look for WMD's. He was only allowed in when Saddam would let him in, and only to locations acceptable to Saddam! 16 drawn out months going through the UN !! Bush didn't want to go to war. He grieved over having to go to war, but every liberal going gave speeches telling Bush we had to go to war. Congress overwhelmingly voted to go to war. It was after the war that liberals spun the lie that they didn't want to go to war. Don't you think that within 16 months Saddam could have had those WMD's transported to Syria maybe?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360176821268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:53:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360176827264-91</Id><Topic><Title>Virginia moves closer to creating state’s own currency</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360163846088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:17:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt if Virginia has to mint new money- they still have all that stuff they minted prior to 1865. I spose its a bit dry and wrinkled by now but its still just as worthless as any new money they might mint</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360176827264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:53:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360176872566-92</Id><Topic><Title>&amp; Obama administration can bring unemployment below 5% &amp;</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360173359728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:55:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Caymans are a good study in taxation. No income tax here, The GDP (PPP) per capita is about the same as the United states. It was higher before the U.S. threatened them over their tax secrecy laws. There are no natural resources here other than gorgeous beaches, good weather and great fishing. It is extremely isolated from most of the world. Yet there are more businesses here than there are people......literally. There is no unemployment. People are happy, speak English. With no income tax the U.S. with abundant natural resources and good proximity to huge markets should be able to double it's GDP. All it needs to do is quit Governing by jealousy, switch from punishing production and rewarding consumption and begin to free producers from the shackles of government intervention and start making the consumers pay their "FAIR SHARE" of the cost of running the government. Progressive Income tax is a communist idea.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360176872566</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:54:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360176997456-93</Id><Topic><Title>scafflow of the Boeing message board</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360094974292</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:09:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Waynedick...i thought u didnt work for boeing, now u claim u worked for 15 years w/ 777.....which one is it? By the way.....boeing is still a great american company! Notwithstanding your daily and moronic garbage... have a good look in the mirror!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360176997456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 13:56:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360177850750-94</Id><Topic><Title>scafflow of the Boeing message board</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360094974292</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:09:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrrr45 , you said i thought u didn't work for boeing,now u claim u worked for 15years w/777 which one is it? BTW...boeing is still a great american company. Not withstanding your moronic garbage. domerrrrr45 please post any statement from me that indicates I did not work for Boeing? If not why are you making up stuff ? what is your motivation to be a teller of untruth? Domerrrrr45, next respond to Boeing is a outsourced company not an american company. ,. It does have to employ way to many local workers to fix and repair the outsourced parts in shop. What constitutes a American Company to you then? Explain your reasoning. as a reminder here is what you are attempting to hide from "I said , I have a question for you domerrrrr45, . What great American Company am I bashing? Boeing was once a American Company when TA Wilson was the CEO. Why, because all the Boeing engineering was done in America, most the parts were made in America and the result was great, the 1960 era 737 plane made in America, makes most of the profit of all the passenger planes produced by Boeing . The second best profit plane is the 777 another 100% American engineered plane.. I worked on both planes for over 15 years and retired with a full pension. All your BS is just that, Domerrrr45, you need to read the John Hart- Smith, A Boeing Engineer who authored a internal paper about Boeing outsourcing and how it would lead to failure. . This once great Boeing company is no longer located in Seattle, nor does Boeing have the American engineering horsepower to fix much of anything, thanks to past Boeing CEO Harry Stonecipher, a MD guy who called TA Wilson arrogant for using American engineers. Stonecipher a insult to American workers and the past CEO of Boeing outsourced the American worker, if Boeing is a great American company now, then as JOHN Hart-Smith said, the only thing Boeing or American for that matter is the Boeing logo on the plane! That may be outsourced too.domerrrrr45, you sir are an insult to every past, present and future American Boeing worker , including me ! Domerrrrr45, When yoyu get the time after you consult with your group or on your own aaway from your FBI support group get back to me on your opinion and any facts to back up your claims. Domerrrr45 you seem to have thoughts that are not accurate. why ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360177850750</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:10:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360178049595-95</Id><Topic><Title>&amp; Obama administration can bring unemployment below 5% &amp;</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360173359728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:55:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please don't identify yourself as a conservative. Raising the minimun wage, first off, raises unemployment, not reducing it. I see you took basketweaving instead of Econ 101 in HS. And anytime you increase a businesses cost of doing business you raise the cost of goods that AVE Joe folks, and poor folks have to buy.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360178049595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:14:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360178202343-96</Id><Topic><Title>BTW BA UP AGAIN!!!!</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360163926058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:18:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrrr45, once more please post any statement that you have that indicates I said I did not work for Boeing, next your not responding to why you think boeing is a great american company. What makes you think that Boeing is a great American company, who does the engineering for Boeing now and who does the part building for Boeing now , is that done in America? Did you take the time to read up on John Hart- Smith or are you guessing and winging it as you go? I think you do not know what you are talking about and you cover for lack of skill, knowledge or ability with vulgarisms and out and out lies.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360178202343</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:16:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360178221840-97</Id><Topic><Title>Rethug efforts to wreck the Postal Service showing early results</Title><Username>windyhorn</Username><Timestamp>1360167376096</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 11:16:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is the meaning of surplus as in pension surplus referred to in the Bloomberg article I provided. I took it for granted that you would know but now I have second thoughts. Adjective More than what is needed or used; excess. Synonyms noun. excess - overplus - overage - superfluity - redundance adjective. redundant - superfluous - spare - excessive</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360178221840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:17:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360178239770-98</Id><Topic><Title>Virginia moves closer to creating state’s own currency</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360163846088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:17:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zosimama.....you sound as ignorant as the Kent Raven. Gold and Silver ain't worthless. It takes 23 of those paper dollars you like to buy what one of them would buy 100 years ago. In 1913 an ounce of gold cost 21 of those paper dollars today it would take 1677 of those paper dollars to buy that ounce of gold. Question: would you rather have 23 paper dollars or a one ounce gold coin?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360178239770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:17:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360178312833-99</Id><Topic><Title>scafflow of the Boeing message board</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360094974292</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:09:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which one is it...dellgeorge,waynedick or gaylord barry? Look in the mirror and let us know...</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360178312833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:18:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360178949592-100</Id><Topic><Title>13 Indicator BA Research Report</Title><Username>michaelkovac</Username><Timestamp>1360160168445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 09:16:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>props</Msg><Username>christopherhansen93</Username><Timestamp>1360178949592</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:29:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360179050493-101</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Introduces National Right to Work Act</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360171373853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:22:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell us about Rand Pauls verbage on repeal of the 13th amendment in his Right to Work act bill</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360179050493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:30:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360179147485-102</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock a chart look</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360170682278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:11:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for the thumbs up</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360179147485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:32:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360179198914-103</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock a chart look</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360170682278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:11:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW any user no matter how vulgar can express his opinion</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360179198914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:33:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360179468597-104</Id><Title>My guess is the FAA clears it for flying tests before the weekend..</Title><Msg>Any bets ?</Msg><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360179468597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:37:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360179469437-105</Id><Topic><Title>BTW BA UP AGAIN!!!!</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360163926058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:18:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>two thumbs down the FBI team is afraid to respond then ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360179469437</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:37:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360179665810-106</Id><Topic><Title>-+$+- The Boeing Company to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight! -+$+-</Title><Username>lucianoanderson120</Username><Timestamp>1359569677040</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 13:14:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>perfect report</Msg><Username>carrjoe180</Username><Timestamp>1360179665810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:41:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360179713861-107</Id><Topic><Title>BTW BA UP AGAIN!!!!</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360163926058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:18:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>interesting 2 thumbs down by the FBI Boeing team but no opinions , can not figure what to say I guess stumped by the facts and the truth it must be a sad day in the FBI camp</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360179713861</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:41:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360179850817-108</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Board of Directors, the club, bad stock to own</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360041458639</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 00:17:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for the 5 thumbs up any opinion from the Boeing FBI Boeing mismanagment camp or just use the vulgarian appraoch to substitute for facts if you like.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360179850817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:44:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360180375721-109</Id><Title>NTSB reported today the probe is probably weeks away from potential completion into the 787 fire</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The National Transportation Safety Board is "probably weeks away" from completing its probe into battery problems on the Boeing 787 Dreamliner, but will share its latest information on the jet on Thursday, agency head Deborah Hersman said. Hersman, who is considered a top candidate to be the next U.S. transportation secretary, said the agency was doing an exhaustive examination of a lithium-ion battery that caught fire in one of the planes and led to the grounding of the Dreamliner. "We're running through the macro level to the microscopic level on this battery," she told reporters at a Wednesday breakfast briefing. "We are going to have some information tomorrow, but I think we are probably weeks away from being able to tell people here's what exactly happened and what needs to change."</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360180375721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:52:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360180720583-110</Id><Topic><Title>My guess is the FAA clears it for flying tests before the weekend..</Title><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360179468597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flight tests won't be approved until they have a Test Readiness Review (TRR), which basically means that they have to have a whole lot of analysis done (i.e. FMEAs and safety analysis, etc.) and an actual Test Plan, Test Procedure, Test Equipment and expected Test Results. I'm sure that Boeing has most of this already, but it needs to be updated and reviewed by the FAA before the flight test is approved. Possibly that will happen next week, but not before this weekend. If you want specific information on the battery issue and what industry experts are saying, mosey on over to the aviationweek site. Lots of good technical information from competent engineers and reporters, with no biases. The longer this goes on with no news, the worse it becomes. Because they just don't know why the batteries caught fire, they cannot develop a solution. And since they cannot discover why the batteries caught on fire, either their assumptions or their models of their systems are either wrong or inaccurate at best. Once they find the root case, they need to find out why it wasn't exposed by the analysis and/or test, and then they will need to re-test or re-analyze everything else that might have been hidden by their incorrect model. Flight Tests may happen next week, but passenger flights won't be allowed till mid-March at this point. Why do you think the airlines have cancelled all their 787 flights through February already ? I've already placed my bets.</Msg><Username>madrusky</Username><Timestamp>1360180720583</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:58:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360181349290-111</Id><Title>CA Green Energy Firm Fined For Paying Mexican Workers --In Pesos!</Title><Msg>SUNNYVALE (CBS SF) - Bloom Energy Corp. has been ordered by a U.S. District Court Judge to pay $31,922 in back wages and an equal amount in liquidated damages to employees from Mexico after the company was found to have willfully violated the minimum wage, overtime and record-keeping provisions of the Fair Labor Standards Act. Bloom, a manufacturer of solid oxide fuel cells, has been paying 14 workers brought to the United States from Chihuahua, Mexico less than $3 per hour for refurbishing work performed at the company headquarters in Sunnyvale. The Department of Labor told KPIX 5 that the employees were skilled workers and they were in the United States on visitors’ visas, which does not allow them to work.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360181349290</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:09:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360181547100-112</Id><Topic><Title>My guess is the FAA clears it for flying tests before the weekend..</Title><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360179468597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The weekend is possible for experimental flights, but unlikely if they offload the design and manufacturing of the stencil to mark the planes prior to flying them.(before anyone takes this seriously, it is not meant to be that way)</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360181547100</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:12:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360181902197-113</Id><Title>As I said from the begining it has to do with the charging system.</Title><Msg>The problem originated on the ground. IMHO the voltage to the batteries was exceeded during ground operations. So what is different from in flight conditions, which was not the problem, and ground operations which is the problem. That is the key to the problem. I expect by this weekend Boeing will get permission to conduct test flights. Both the NTSB and the FAA has to allow this to confirm systems integrity. It's in the best interests for everyone involved. Boeing has put in many measuring devices for the test flights and should be approved. The answer to the problem is very close.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360181902197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:18:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360181986448-114</Id><Topic><Title>As I said from the begining it has to do with the charging system.</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360181902197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:18:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The second battery issue happened while the plane was flying</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360181986448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:19:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360182384186-115</Id><Topic><Title>My guess is the FAA clears it for flying tests before the weekend..</Title><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360179468597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your sentiment to sell is understandable. BUT I would not short Boeing. This is a test flight without passengers. Boeing has a lot to lose. It's their risk and no one elses. The test flight will be approved sooner than later. Remember BA is in Obamas home state.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360182384186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:26:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360182723990-116</Id><Title>They Shut The Gulf Down From Oil Drilling</Title><Msg>They Shut The Gulf Down From Oil Drilling for over 2 years! What do you think with lives at stake? Imho over 2 years till that bird flys again. I'm amazed at all the shareholder monies being spent to keep this puppy in the air.....</Msg><Username>locklimitup2000</Username><Timestamp>1360182723990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:32:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360182876246-117</Id><Topic><Title>As I said from the begining it has to do with the charging system.</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360181902197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:18:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. It started to experience a thermal runaway on the ground. Why do I feel this way? Because I've experienced thermal runaway's with Ni Cad batteries in the past. They are slow at first and then get into the temp runaway after a period of time. Sometimes an hour or two. This cockpit battery went overheat just soon after takeoff. IMHO it started on the ground like all the others.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360182876246</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:34:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360183104659-118</Id><Topic><Title>As I said from the begining it has to do with the charging system.</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360181902197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:18:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Starting on the ground is a reasonable speculation on what happened as you point out, I can't deny that nor confirm that. I've just never heard any press releases indictating that.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360183104659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:38:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360183430266-119</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Board of Directors, the club, bad stock to own</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360041458639</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 00:17:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you heard anything lately from "foulmouther"? Oops, I guess I shouldn't be using your nickname for falmouthharbor.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1360183430266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:43:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360183886748-120</Id><Topic><Title>As I said from the begining it has to do with the charging system.</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360181902197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:18:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When the Feds say its only weeks away that means any day now$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1360183886748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:51:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360184036093-121</Id><Topic><Title>My guess is the FAA clears it for flying tests before the weekend..</Title><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360179468597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll back you with some Cash if you need it!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1360184036093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:53:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360184363065-122</Id><Topic><Title>CA Green Energy Firm Fined For Paying Mexican Workers --In Pesos!</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360181349290</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:09:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FYI this is a group of ex-NASA boys from the Bush years that went out on their own, obtained VC money and used the free market to produce an innovative product. They offer economic value to customers without government subsidies unlike the wind energy companies who have failed for 25 years to be profitable or show real economic value in the free market and continue to survive only because of government crony capitalism off the backs of taxpayers. Bloom is the opposite of the Obama subsidized loser Solyndra.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360184363065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:59:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360184376072-123</Id><Topic><Title>As I said from the begining it has to do with the charging system.</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360181902197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:18:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We will know more tomorrow when they give the update on status of the investigation, but based on previous schedules released by Boeing, I've never seen thngs happen ahead of time. I'm not implying the FAA/NTSB is going to follow the same trend, it just doesn't seem to ever happen on the 787.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360184376072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:59:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360184394202-124</Id><Topic><Title>My guess is the FAA clears it for flying tests before the weekend..</Title><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360179468597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm confused by your "seemingly" contradictory statements. "BUT I would not short Boeing" and "Boeing has a lot to lose. It's their risk and no one elses" I agree that Boeing has a lot to lose, and in my opinion, a limited upside. That's why I'm short. It should not (it may, but it shouldn't) jump a few percent when they define the solvable problem. However, it should (but it may not) drop a few percent when they quantify the cost of the solvable problem. And I totally agree, the flight test HAS to be approved BEFORE they can get it re-certified, but the flight test isn't going to fix the problem, its just going to either show them what the problem is, or that they can't replicate the conditions to cause the problem. Obama doesn't care that Boeing is headquartered in Chicago. the money is already spread across each congressional district.</Msg><Username>madrusky</Username><Timestamp>1360184394202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:59:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360184536903-125</Id><Topic><Title>AFTER SOLVING BATTERIES PROBLEM OTHER MAJOR PROBLEMS WILL ERUPT FOR THE 787</Title><Username>xawa</Username><Timestamp>1359992725444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:45:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on</Msg><Username>copyright_member</Username><Timestamp>1360184536903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:02:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360184663777-126</Id><Topic><Title>Will BA Bounce? SEE OUR IN DEPTH BA BOUNCE REPORT</Title><Username>kyledurham521</Username><Timestamp>1360012053563</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great news,THX</Msg><Username>kennethburto</Username><Timestamp>1360184663777</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:04:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360184699117-127</Id><Title>Are we still gonna impeach President Obama</Title><Msg>... or did you miniature tyrants give up your quest for power !!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1360184699117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:04:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360184906923-128</Id><Title>CBO: Entitlements, ObamaCare To Make Up 53% of Federal Spending</Title><Msg>CNSNews) – According to projections from the Congressional Budget Office (CBO), entitlements and ObamaCare spending will comprise 53 percent of all federal spending over the coming decade, totaling $24.9 trillion. In its updated Budget and Economic Outlook report released on Tuesday, the CBO projects that Social Security will account for $11.149 trillion in spending from 2014 to 2023 while federal health care entitlements, including Medicare, Medicaid, and ObamaCare, will spend $13.85 trillion. (That total includes TRICARE, CHIP, and "other" spending listed by the CBO under healthcare.) ObamaCare’s insurance subsidies, exchange costs, and other spending are expected to cost the government $949 billion over the next 10 years. Medicare is expected cost $8.1 trillion while Medicaid is expected to cost $4.4 trillion.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360184906923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:08:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360185055274-129</Id><Topic><Title>CBO: Entitlements, ObamaCare To Make Up 53% of Federal Spending</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360184906923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:08:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When did Social Security become an Entitlement?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360185055274</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:10:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360186204505-130</Id><Topic><Title>As I said from the begining it has to do with the charging system.</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360181902197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:18:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The press seems to have alternative motives. What they are is up to the stock holders to understand those motives. Many reports are put on the internet by shorts. They feed information to the press that is not reliable. The only reliable reports are what is provided by BA, NTSB and the FAA. Everything else is conjecture. Unfortunately you never can believe what is in print or in the media these days. It's all your DD and speculation as to what is a good investment or isn't. As for me I know BA very well. They would never release an aircraft in flight if they didn't think it was safe. Yes, this is a set back for the 787 but it will be solved by BA sooner than later. Just keep in mind, from an investor standpoint, this is not the only aircraft BA makes. The backload of aircraft for BA is very, very strong.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360186204505</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:30:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360186500291-131</Id><Topic><Title>Are we still gonna impeach President Obama</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1360184699117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:04:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not possible, Obama exercised his Executive Privilege, and made it impossible to impeach him....fascism will remain. But give him another several years, and his minority base will be ready to lynch him.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360186500291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:35:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360187222835-132</Id><Topic><Title>Are we still gonna impeach President Obama</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1360184699117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:04:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another several years and the country will be a smoldering crater.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1360187222835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:47:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360187917041-133</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock a chart look</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360170682278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:11:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I can't polish yer #$%$, then giving you a thumbs up is the least I can do.</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1360187917041</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:58:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360188606835-134</Id><Title>battery fix?</Title><Msg>The WSJ reports that Boeing has a new battery design that it will be testing once the FAA lets them fly test flights. That is why BA requested that the FAA let them fly. It is still the lithium ion battery but with more space between cells to further isolate them from each other. It said sources say BA hopes to have the 787's back in service by March. Time will tell.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360188606835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:10:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360189067584-135</Id><Topic><Title>Are we still gonna impeach President Obama</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1360184699117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:04:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is not the problem-----we have always had communist in the country. The problem is people stupid enough to vote for one.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360189067584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:17:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360189121986-136</Id><Topic><Title>CBO: Entitlements, ObamaCare To Make Up 53% of Federal Spending</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360184906923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:08:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul Ryan and the conservaitves were deeply concerned about the need to reform SS, and Paul Ryan had the skill set to make some important reforms to SS before it went over the cliff. Obama and the left said hands off, and lied about sending Granny over the cliff dealing with the much needed reform.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360189121986</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:18:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360189226215-137</Id><Topic><Title>CBO: Entitlements, ObamaCare To Make Up 53% of Federal Spending</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360184906923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:08:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What cave do you live in? Or are you just a victim of socialized government education? Social Security has always been an entitlement.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360189226215</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:20:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360189444031-138</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Introduces National Right to Work Act</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360171373853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:22:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right to work states are cleaning the clocks of states that don't want people to have a choice.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360189444031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:24:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360190134142-139</Id><Topic><Title>Are we still gonna impeach President Obama</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1360184699117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 16:04:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>love that Executive Privilege !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1360190134142</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:35:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360191209950-140</Id><Title>Down over 60Cents!! What's happenning???</Title><Msg>What news just got released! Anyone have the TV on???</Msg><Username>mrlarry626</Username><Timestamp>1360191209950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:53:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360191526226-141</Id><Title>Rand Paul wants to repeal the 13th and 19th amendments</Title><Msg>Rand Paul as delightful a guy as any reptile is rumored to have leased the old slave market building in Savannah!</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360191526226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:58:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360192043835-142</Id><Topic><Title>Virginia moves closer to creating state’s own currency</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360163846088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 10:17:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Virginia hasn't had any gold or silver or platinum or titanium since G Washington threw the last dollar across the Potomac The paper money remains as worthless as the day Robert E Lee finally got to meet US Grant - against his will</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360192043835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 18:07:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360192068722-143</Id><Topic><Title>Down over 60Cents!! What's happenning???</Title><Username>mrlarry626</Username><Timestamp>1360191209950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:53:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure what channel you are watching. It closed up 40 cents and afterhours was 20 cents lower. Only news was WSJ release that BA has a new battery design they want to continue testing in the air when the FAA gives them the ok.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360192068722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 18:07:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360192222543-144</Id><Topic><Title>Down over 60Cents!! What's happenning???</Title><Username>mrlarry626</Username><Timestamp>1360191209950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:53:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's moving up and down from 75.75 and 76.. on the ameritrade afterhour ticker.. Right now it's at 76..down 29cents. What are you using?</Msg><Username>mrlarry626</Username><Timestamp>1360192222543</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 18:10:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360193125508-145</Id><Topic><Title>Oh Did I mention it's 31degrees Celsius Here?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360172391085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:39:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's nice weather too.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360193125508</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 18:25:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360193187590-146</Id><Topic><Title>Down over 60Cents!! What's happenning???</Title><Username>mrlarry626</Username><Timestamp>1360191209950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:53:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just yahoo finance. I read it worng. Down 29 cents in after hours. I wasn't wearing my glasses. (: )</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360193187590</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 18:26:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360193647899-147</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul wants to repeal the 13th and 19th amendments</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360191526226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:58:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's wrong with slavery?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360193647899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 18:34:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360194097692-148</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul wants to repeal the 13th and 19th amendments</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360191526226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:58:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rand Paul does have some very commonsense ideas on reducing the debt that no liberal even wants to address. They want to increase the debt not reduce it. It makes sense to a liberal to have the liberals in power increase taxes on hard working folks, and have a good portion of that money just going to servicing the massive debt they have created.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360194097692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 18:41:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360194507556-149</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you going to log back in and brag about your DFC under "general_meelee" and "nowarrantneeded" again like you did last year ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360194507556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 18:48:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360194569716-150</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lots of freebies for welfare recipients but FAR MORE for Banks....and we all know who Barry Soetoro works for....and is PROTECTED BY.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360194569716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 18:49:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360194635070-151</Id><Topic><Title>Newtown Father Blasts Gun Control</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360153030517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 07:17:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>google it</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360194635070</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 18:50:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360194896286-152</Id><Topic><Title>Newtown Father Blasts Gun Control</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360153030517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 07:17:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the terrible economy Obama and the liberals have created, their push for gun control sure has been an economic boom for the economy....guns flying off the shelves, and ammo shelves bare sales have been so robust. I stopped by my local sporting goods store today, and their were 50 people waiting for the doors to open....a concealed weapons permit class, and they run those weekly.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360194896286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 18:54:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360194961765-153</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Wallace slams NRA’s Wayne LaPierre</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360025900325</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 19:58:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didnt ask if the threat was higher ..I asked if the RIGHT to protect my children is any less Huge difference Moron....Maybe in your Cult member Universe you have little Self Respect and fiugure the President deserves MORE RIGHTS to defend his family then mine....you are WAYYYYYY out of line Junior</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360194961765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 18:56:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360195401370-154</Id><Topic><Title>battery fix?</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360188606835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:10:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In looking at events over the past month, it appears the NTSB still has no clue as to the cause of the battery events. They only know that there was thermal runaway. The NTSB chair went out of her way to say that the investigation was NOT thinking that the lithium battaries are unsafe for use in aircraft. So it is possible that the battery redesign is only adressing the thermall runaway and the new design will allow the 787 (assuming it works) to start flying again while the NTSB continues the investigation into the root cause of the initial incidents.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360195401370</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:03:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360195602236-155</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Wallace slams NRA’s Wayne LaPierre</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360025900325</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 19:58:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris Wallace is like the Hooz...on the side of wrong. Gun control ain't gonna happen. Talks cheap, and whiskey costs money. Libs aren't going to vote in gun control.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360195602236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:06:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360196663156-156</Id><Topic><Title>Headline of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360110250513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 19:24:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And todays Dimbicile ignored headlines: "Harry Reid twice wrong on '$2.6 trillion' cuts in 'This Week' interview" "Sexual Harassment Investigation May Delay Hagel Vote" "Exclusive—Zimmerman Brother: Obama 'Bullied' My Family" "Dem Congressman Warns Of "Mob Scenes" Without "Equity In Society" "Boy, 7, suspended from school for tossing IMAGINARY grenade during recess" "Panetta to propose military pay cut after Obama raised federal officials pay" "CIA 'operating drone base in Saudi Arabia'" "Gun-rights advocates swarm Annapolis to fight O’Malley’s gun control bill"</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1360196663156</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:24:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360197485347-157</Id><Title>FAA allows a one time flight</Title><Msg>(Reuters) - Boeing Co (BA) will be allowed to conduct a one-time ferry flight of a grounded 787 Dreamliner from Texas to Washington, the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration said on Wednesday. The FAA said the plane would have a minimal crew, which would have to continuously monitor the battery's status and land immediately if the flight computer displayed any battery-related messages.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360197485347</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:38:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360197509668-158</Id><Title>OK the FAA has cleared Boeing for flight testing, my only problem is that</Title><Msg>they are proposing a change of the cells position between each other in the batteries. This is to help in cooling between cells. IMHO I don't think that is the answer. The ability to see the charging rate of the battery, along with voltage and the heat of the battery during the process of ground operations is key to all their problems. Once that has been discovered then the problem can be solved. The electronics, coils, and cables during ground operation is the answer. Soon rather than later this will be determined.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360197509668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:38:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360198137659-159</Id><Topic><Title>FAA allows a one time flight</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360197485347</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:38:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If there is no problems on the ground then there will be no problems in flight, period. I would suggest holding for a period of time prior to takeoff. If there are no problems, then the flight will not experience any problems in flight. It's a ground charging problem IMHO. We'll see!!</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360198137659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:48:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360199135939-160</Id><Topic><Title>battery fix?</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360188606835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:10:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The root of the problem is still to be discovered. The battery redesign is not a solution. It is only a bandade to the problem. Knowing well before takeoff what the battery condition is will be the most important factor to aircraft systems integrity and to the pilots knowlege of what is happening. Once again I feel the charging systems and their fault warnings systems are at fault.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360199135939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:05:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360199577249-161</Id><Topic><Title>OK the FAA has cleared Boeing for flight testing, my only problem is that</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360197509668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:38:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There has been only one flight allowed. The FAA has not cleared them (yet) to do any more tast flights. The BA proposal for increased cell protection/distance is what the WSJ said is a possible interim step to get planes airborne while the NTSB continues to look for the root cause. I suspect the one flight is to gather data on the new design to give to the FAA/NTSB. Hopefully it leads to removing the flight ban and the root cause can be discovered.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360199577249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:12:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360199928870-162</Id><Title>incentive bonuses SC verses Puget sound</Title><Msg>SC to get 17.95 days of pay on average while PS gets 14.75, It probably works out about the same as SC pay would be some lower. Strange thing about this is that in deciding how much the bonus, morale is one of the key deciders. It would seem that morale would be higher after getting the bonus. And then there is the manager element. Having a manager in the area could be just about like a fog of no morale or bad morale. I hope it isn't going to effect my bonus, referring to Boeing management as dirtbags and the like. Maybe they didn't mean morale, but instead meant morals, higher would definitely be better, it would still be a challenge for Boeing management.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1360199928870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:18:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360200039551-163</Id><Topic><Title>FAA allows a one time flight</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360197485347</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:38:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ANA battery fire occurred in flight.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1360200039551</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:20:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360200092999-164</Id><Title>The CT DA is still investigating "potential suspects" and the case is still open</Title><Msg>Why is Obama trying to initiate a gun grab when the case is still open and suspects are still being investigated? ________________________________________ Connecticut State's Attorney Stephen Sedensky has argued that unsealing warrants in the Sandy Hook case might "seriously jeopardize" the investigation by disclosing information known only to other "potential suspects." Sedensky said that unsealing the warrants would also: "identify persons cooperating with the investigation, thus possibly jeopardizing their personal safety and well-being." The statement by the CT prosecutor's office is the first indication from state authorities that Adam Lanza may have not acted alone. The statement was made in support of a motion to continue the seal on the results of five search warrants for 90 more days. CT State Police Public Affairs Officer Lt. Paul Vance said in an official press release on December 16th that: The male subject identified as the shooter at Sandy Hook Elementary School has been identified as ADAM LANZA DOB: 04/22/92; he resided at 36 Yogananda Street. His cause of death was gunshot wound and his death is ruled a suicide. However, neither Vance nor the CT Attorney General's office have ever ruled out the possible presence of other suspects. The New Haven Register reports Vance as having said: "Whenever you conduct an investigation you don’t speculate as to where it’s going to take you, as I said, we’re going to look at every single thing, every piece of material and we’ll take it from there."</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360200092999</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:21:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360200609397-165</Id><Topic><Title>The CT DA is still investigating "potential suspects" and the case is still open</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360200092999</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not a "gun grab." Maybe you think that from too much grabbing of your own gun. And since the impetus for his desire for reasonable restrictions on guns and trafficking is based on Sandy Hook ONLY as one of dozens of examples, why does the case have to be closed before we proceed? Isn't that just standard Natl. Runt Assn. stall tactics?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360200609397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:30:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360200715822-166</Id><Title>scofflaw Have you no shame domerrrrr45</Title><Msg>domerrrrr45 on Feb 4 you state waynedick was a fired Boeing employee, on Feb 6, Domerrrrr45 , you state to waynedick "I thought you said ( to waynedick) u didnt work for boeing, now you claim u worked for 15 years. So first you make a false claim waynedickenson was a fired Boeing empoyee then two days later domerrrrr45 claims he thinks waynedickenson told domerrrrr45 that waynedickenson said he never worked for Boeing, you can't have it both ways . domerrrrr45, it is simple you are unaware that your lies catch up to you domerrrrr45 stop living in denial. BTW post your souce for your claim that waynedickenson claimed he did not work for Boeing, can not do that ! domerrrrr45 you claim to be aViet Nam veteran so that gies you the right to be a liar too and a vulgarian who is a scafflaw. You might be a Viet Nam Veteran but you sure act like a criminal . Dormerrrrr45 in two days you make two false statement in continuing Yahoo TOS violation. about waynedickenson domerrrrr45by domerrrrr45.Feb 2, 2013 9:29 PM.Permalink.Go to topic TOS TOS TOS..SCARY! • Re: WAYNEDICK....BOEING domerrrrr45by domerrrrr45.Feb 4, 2013 8:23 AM.Permalink.Go to topic • Waynedick...u r a fired employee of boeing...expected! Sentiment: Strong Buy o 2users liked this posts6users disliked this posts o • Re: Re: Re: Re: scafflow of the Boeing message board waynedickenson961by waynedickenson961.Feb 6, 2013 2:10 PM.Permalink.Go to topic domerrrrr45 , you said i thought u didn't work for boeing,now u claim u worked for 15y... domerrrrr45 , you said i thought u didn't work for boeing,now u claim u worked for 15years w/777 which one is it? BTW...boeing is still a great american company. Not withstanding your moronic garbage. domerrrrr45 please post any statement from me that indicates I did not work for Boeing? If not why are you making up stuff</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360200715822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:31:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360200800264-167</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Rock: Obama is ‘… Dad of the Country’</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360198000933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:46:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a point you have never been able to grasp, Spart: Just because one guy says it doesn't make it true.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360200800264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:33:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360200954303-168</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Rock: Obama is ‘… Dad of the Country’</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360198000933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:46:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many Obama voters don't know who their real dad is so they fantasize about the fabricated media version of Obama as being their dad. The rest of us knew our fathers as the guy that didn't want to kill American citizens overseas without due process.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360200954303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:35:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360201441115-169</Id><Topic><Title>OK the FAA has cleared Boeing for flight testing, my only problem is that</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360197509668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:38:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thousands of flights have taken place with the 787 without a problem prior to the fires and smoke on the two aircraft. The test flight will prove nothing. It will be a normal flight without any problems. UNLESS they see a battery problem prior to takeoff. Then we will see the problem. If so, it is a charging problem. We will be waiting to see the results. IMHO I think it is a charging problem.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360201441115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:44:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360201509415-170</Id><Title>Boeing is allowed to make a one time ferry flight, this is not approval for a test flight!</Title><Msg>While that request is pending, the FAA said on Wednesday it would allow a one-time "ferry" flight of a 787 to Washington. The plane will fly with a minimum crew and have to land immediately if the flight computer displays any battery-related messages,nder a best-case scenario, passenger flights could resume next month. It was not immediately clear when the flight would take place. please stop making misleading statments foulmouthharbor and laidlow, you can be honest try "Separately, U.S. aviation regulators said they would permit Boeing to make a special one-time 787 flight from Texas to Washington state, albeit with heavy conditions.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360201509415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:45:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360201640610-171</Id><Title>Amazing how everyone is rushing to get this plane back in service even when they don't know what</Title><Msg>caused the fires ! This shows you the power of Wall st as Boeing is on the Dow 30 index !</Msg><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1360201640610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:47:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360201706843-172</Id><Topic><Title>OK the FAA has cleared Boeing for flight testing, my only problem is that</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360197509668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:38:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The FAA said that they needed to be 1000% certain(yes, thousand) before they would allow the plane to fly commercially again. If this temporary fix gets them to 1000%, why wouldn't it be the permanent fix, too much weight?</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360201706843</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:48:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360201874041-173</Id><Topic><Title>The CT DA is still investigating "potential suspects" and the case is still open</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360200092999</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Maybe you think that from too much grabbing of your own gun." Now that's where we DO need gun control to stop all of the morons involved in out of wedlock births that responsible people end up having to pay for.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360201874041</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:51:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360202338225-174</Id><Topic><Title>OK the FAA has cleared Boeing for flight testing, my only problem is that</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360197509668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:38:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will not be a permanent fix at 1000% percent. Not until they know with absolute certanty what caused the batteries to overheat will we know the answer. Untill then it's just a wait and see. Don't believe what you read or hear from the media. Only from BA, NTSB and FAA</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360202338225</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:58:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360202529453-175</Id><Title>laylow 1991 is wrong the FAA has not approved test flights , one return ferry flight no testing stop spinning</Title><Msg>Boeing 787 Gets FAA Approval for Ferry Flight Today By Susanna Ray &amp; Mary Schlangenstein - Feb 6, 2013 5:36 PM PT. . .. Boeing Co.’s grounded 787 Dreamliner will fly today for the first time in three weeks after U.S. officials approved a one-time permit to ferry a plane to Washington state from Texas. The trip isn’t a commercial flight, and the only people aboard will be those needed for operation, the Federal Aviation Administration said in a statement. The plane must fly directly to Boeing’s widebody-jet plant in Everett, just north of Seattle, from Fort Worth, where it was being painted for China Southern Airlines. Investigators are still “weeks away” from determining what caused battery failures on the 787, the head of the U.S. National Transportation Safety Board said yesterday. The jets have been grounded since Jan. 16 after a fire on one and an emergency landing by another, and Transportation Secretary Ray LaHood declined to give a timetable yesterday for deciding on Boeing’s request to resume test flights. “There is an increasing concern that this could take longer than earlier anticipated,” said Michel Merluzeau, a consultant with G2 Solutions in Kirkland, Washington.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360202529453</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:02:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360202572485-176</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is allowed to make a one time ferry flight, this is not approval for a test flight!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360201509415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:45:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know there is a difference in a "ferry flight" and a "test" flight( I think the plane has to be certified to fly under these categories). Is an "experimental" flight in the same category as a "test" flight? I believe "test" flights means the plane is certified but is not the same as a "commercial" flight, An "experimental" flight has different restrictions than either of the previously mentioned categories if my research is correct. It reflects flying a non-certified plane or design People need to make sure they are using these different flight categories properly otherwise comments can be misleading. Don't take my information posted in this note as being accurate for the different catagories , I just want to point out the fact that there are many different categories defining what type of flight is being made</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360202572485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:02:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360202991136-177</Id><Topic><Title>The CT DA is still investigating "potential suspects" and the case is still open</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360200092999</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris when I thought about your comment further I realized the humor in your comment as Obama has been grabbing those other guns that you refer to for quite a long time and rumor has it he likes older white guns. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360202991136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:09:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360203106338-178</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is allowed to make a one time ferry flight, this is not approval for a test flight!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360201509415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:45:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cbx 6 cylinder , I was correcting Laylow 1991, not you. laylow 1991 claims to be a pilot and should know the difference between a ferry flight, no testing and a experimental FAA approved test. The article is very clear only people on board will be those needed to fly the plane back to home port, there will be no testing, this is to get a crippled, but flyable plane back to a home port that is all it is. The plane has heavy restrictions, a test flight put the plane through a series of tests , this is a potentially crippled plane flight home with fingers crossed . A test flight occurs after the ground tests have made it with pass, a ferry flight is to return a problem plane back to a home port. Itis like a red flag in a car race you can return to the pits very slowly and get off the track as safely as possible .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360203106338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:11:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360203219725-179</Id><Topic><Title>Amazing how everyone is rushing to get this plane back in service even when they don't know what</Title><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1360201640610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:47:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody I know would want to fly on that airplane. Even if the battery issue gets fixed, most people will take a wait and see attitude.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1360203219725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:13:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360203293411-180</Id><Topic><Title>incentive bonuses SC verses Puget sound</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1360199928870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:18:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>morals and management for Boeing are mutualy excludable statements</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360203293411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:14:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360203409263-181</Id><Topic><Title>Amazing how everyone is rushing to get this plane back in service even when they don't know what</Title><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1360201640610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:47:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is a pr scam there is one ferry flight allowed, no testing, laylow 1991 claims to be a pilot and if so would know the difference between a ferry flight and a test flight.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360203409263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:16:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360203602404-182</Id><Topic><Title>laylow 1991 is wrong the FAA has not approved test flights , one return ferry flight no testing stop spinning</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360202529453</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:02:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not spinning anything. It is a start to allowing test flights. Nothing more. I think Thursday or Friday could be an answer to allowing BA to conduct around the clock test flights.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360203602404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:20:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360203964868-183</Id><Topic><Title>OK the FAA has cleared Boeing for flight testing, my only problem is that</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360197509668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:38:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>with yur obvious expertise and knowledge - why hasn't BA simply offered you a few million to tell them where and how to fix the problem ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360203964868</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:26:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360204380311-184</Id><Topic><Title>My guess is the FAA clears it for flying tests before the weekend..</Title><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360179468597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I told you all this was coming..</Msg><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360204380311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:33:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360204595736-185</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is allowed to make a one time ferry flight, this is not approval for a test flight!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360201509415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:45:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne, my post was not directed to you, it was posted as general information to all the posters using all the different terms. Again, I do not want anyone to think I know the details for the differences of all the different categories(Test, Experimental, Ferry, Commercial, and I'm sure I missed some more that are out there). I just know there are different categories which seem to be getting thrown into discussions by people that may not be aware of this.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360204595736</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:36:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360206087229-186</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is allowed to make a one time ferry flight, this is not approval for a test flight!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360201509415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 20:45:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Almost forget about the "delivery" flight category, this can be a non-commercial flight on a certified plane and the plane is not complete for commerical flights( no interior/seats etc installed) Now I'm getting confused )</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360206087229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 22:01:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360206351418-187</Id><Title>Dronegate exposes Obama as a hypocrite</Title><Msg>Look for the focus of news to shift to Dronegate and gun control moved to page 16 in the paper.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360206351418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 22:05:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360208925214-188</Id><Topic><Title>Dronegate exposes Obama as a hypocrite</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360206351418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 22:05:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dronegate.......how about ali_ingesto-gate, just as silly, huh?</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360208925214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 22:48:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360209027739-189</Id><Topic><Title>Fewer People Than Ever Trust Fox News</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360205005931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:43:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It takes time but eventually the truth wins out</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360209027739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 22:50:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360209391421-190</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Rock: Obama is ‘… Dad of the Country’</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360198000933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:46:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The word terrorist 6 years ago meant torture, maim and execute if necessary. Now you want your American terrorist to be read his miranda rights. Now when the next Repub is president (maybe 12 yrs from now) - you'll be back to the "all things are fair in love and war".</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360209391421</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 22:56:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360210131223-191</Id><Topic><Title>Fewer People Than Ever Trust Fox News</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360205005931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:43:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must a Laid off postal worker, from last months jobs report... Rite around 4400 hunderd to be exact ... That lost the taxpayers, 16 billion last year .. Now thats polarizing...That came out from cnbc news and fox news.. LOL</Msg><Username>forland1966</Username><Timestamp>1360210131223</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 23:08:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360210646018-192</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Rock: Obama is ‘… Dad of the Country’</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360198000933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:46:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You were against water boarding with medical staff oversight but now you're OK with outright assassination. You're on twisted sister.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360210646018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 23:17:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360211130711-193</Id><Topic><Title>My guess is the FAA clears it for flying tests before the weekend..</Title><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360179468597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But, it hasn't come yet ! Or are you changing your statement?</Msg><Username>madrusky</Username><Timestamp>1360211130711</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 23:25:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360212738989-194</Id><Title>The Biggest Problem is with 787 Is....Drum roll Please</Title><Msg>The batteries are all over this bird... with four small generators to save weight... on the 787 no bleed system... the batteries are simply over worked...every moving part on the 787 is electric only... no hydraulic lines, what so ever on the 787....</Msg><Username>forland1966</Username><Timestamp>1360212738989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 23:52:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360212792466-195</Id><Title>Ridiculous BA is not down more</Title><Msg>With the uncertainty of the 787 Dreamliner battery debacle this stock should and will decline into the 60's</Msg><Username>feru012</Username><Timestamp>1360212792466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 23:53:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>