<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368333816736-1</Id><Topic><Title>Sir Beatle #9, this is Hertz #15 &amp; #22</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368323082718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 21:44:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Sparty was the actual writer of "Why Don't We Do It in the Road." He wrote it for Orly Taitz when he was trying to woo her.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1368333816736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 00:43:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368342108538-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is ashamed of himself, he hides behing</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368318470787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 20:27:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"My guess Stevens rejected Obama as a homosexual" what a tard remark</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1368342108538</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 03:01:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368342294584-3</Id><Topic><Title>even liberal nbc now mentions benghazi</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1367980756177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 22:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If one googles "floydianslips" they'll see a sad barber in prison for child molestation</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1368342294584</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 03:04:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368364233540-4</Id><Topic><Title>Man who opened fire on Ohio police possessed extremist literature</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368301406576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 15:43:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Instant_karma48 didn't know about Barry's killing of innocent people, so that is proof he certainly knows nothing about Chomsky and you chimed in after the fact pretending to be all knowing. It would have been better for a guy like you who pretends to be smart (in this post), to help karma out before he admits he doesn't read and doesn't know any actual facts on Barry's killing of innocent people and how he, in Chomsky's own words is 'worse than Bush'. You will be exposed as alying moron if you deny Chomsky said Barry was worse than Bush. I am accurate in that Barry has killed far more innocent people than the Ohio gunman and you can go pound sand but be careful where you pound as Hooz and the aliases heads are buried in that sand.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368364233540</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 09:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368367038922-5</Id><Title>Rand Paul suppots Constitution and opposes UN Small Arms Treaty</Title><Msg>Socialist Collaborator Media labels him a Kook</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368367038922</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 09:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368367415827-6</Id><Title>Michelle Obama Is A Percenter Acting Like A Welfare Queen</Title><Msg>Transparent Michelle did all she could to prevent access to her expenses under FOIA request, was sued and lost, so the records were made public. The less you listen to Michelle's lies and phony rhetoric and the more you let her actions do the talking, the more you begin to see that she is a corrupt person to her very core. She hates commoners in much the same way Marie Antoinette despised her subjects. ____________________________________________ What a show of arrogance! This information was obtained by Judicial Watch March, 2012. The administration had to be sued to get this through the FREEDOM OF INFORMATION ACT. Michelle Obama listed daughters as 'Senior Staffers' to justify her expensive African vacation and safari. October 5, 2011, Judicial Watch said the U.S. Air Force provided a C-32 ( a Boeing 757 ), modified by the military for the purpose of flying big-wigs around the world, to fly the First Lady and her entourage to and from Africa , at a cost of $424,142. Another $928.44 was listed as 'bulk food' costs per meal for the 192 on-board meals for the 21 people who made the trip. Lobster ain't cheap when you fly it around the world. The Obama daughters were listed on the manifest as senior staff. 'This trip was as much an opportunity for the Obama family to go on a safari as it was a trip to conduct government business,' said Judicial Watch President, Tom Fitton. This junket wasted tax dollars and the resources of our over extended military. No wonder we had to sue to pry loose this information. The nation is suffering with the economy sputtering, the national debt soaring and Obama's economic rescue policies not only failing, but actively making things worse. Meanwhile, the First Lady justifies an expensive trip to Africa to take a vacation and safari with her daughters by saying it's 'official business' and even going so far as to list her children as staffers. The level of arrogance and dishonesty on display here is nothing short of shocking.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368367415827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:03:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368368295136-7</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama Is A Percenter Acting Like A Welfare Queen</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368367415827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:03:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Judicial Watch" About as believable as FAUX news and Rush Limbaugh.</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1368368295136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:18:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368368618060-8</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul suppots Constitution and opposes UN Small Arms Treaty</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368367038922</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 09:57:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People with common sense who are not nuts label him a Kook. You are also a Kook, and a fool.</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1368368618060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:23:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368369013437-9</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul suppots Constitution and opposes UN Small Arms Treaty</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368367038922</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 09:57:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But a person who uses an ID called MarxMoron surely has nothing more to add !</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368369013437</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:30:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368369257639-10</Id><Topic><Title>Sir Beatle #9, this is Hertz #15 &amp; #22</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368323082718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 21:44:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>weak</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368369257639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368369462004-11</Id><Topic><Title>What stunt will Obama pull to divert attention from Bengazi-gate ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368307006787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:16:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only ones that have woken up in your parallel universe are you and your multiple ID personality disorder. Get help ...lose a ton of weight and ..then gain a job</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368369462004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368369891535-12</Id><Topic><Title>PASS THE POPCORN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368050289984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes Bob..and as you say when our leaders are not held to any standard of accountability, it is one more piece of evidence of the End Times. Yet it is far worse then lack of accountability...Whistleblowers were ordered to shut up and threatened if they talked....We have seen this repeatedly with this administration. Also - WHAT was the agenda.....WHY was Stevens killed and was he killed on purpose</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368369891535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:44:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368370431356-13</Id><Topic><Title>Sabre 06. this is Bongo 52 with a phone patch</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368322451380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 21:34:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you suggesting Petraeus was framed by the administration in order to keep him from testifying. ? seems irrelevant now.....</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368370431356</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368370542363-14</Id><Topic><Title>PASS THE POPCORN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368050289984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot a little incident that came to light. As the coffins were escorted at Dover in proper fashion for the four murdered- ObUma, Hillarious, and Bite me and Panetta each and everyone hugged the mother of one. And face to face- eyeball to eyeball- told her that ' they" would get the person who made the video that was the cause of it all. and that ' they" would get back to her when they had the details of how her son died. Of course re getting back - ZIP- but the ' perp" of the video IS still in jail on another unrelated charge. And as to the hearing- she was NOT invited since she was NOT a member of the immediate family The mother of one of the four Americans killed during the Benghazi attack last Sept. 11 said on Saturday that she found no closure in this week’s hearing on the assault. “Absolutely not,” Pat Smith declared to former Arkansas Gov. Mike Huckabee via satellite on his Fox News program. “I’m still waiting for answers to just about everything.” She is the mother of slain State Department Information Officer Sean Smith. He was a 10-year employee of the Foreign Service who also had served in Iraq, South Africa, Canada, and the Netherlands. He also was an Air Force veteran with a wife, a son, and a daughter. Besides Sean Smith, U.S. Ambassador Christopher Stevens and two other Americans also were killed at the U.S. post in Benghazi. The Obama administration has insisted that Pat Smith is not considered part of her son's immediate family.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368370542363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:55:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368370767558-15</Id><Topic><Title>What stunt will Obama pull to divert attention from Bengazi-gate ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368307006787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:16:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And how do you know this? You said it.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1368370767558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:59:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368371413310-16</Id><Topic><Title>What stunt will Obama pull to divert attention from Bengazi-gate ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368307006787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:16:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why a government-orchestrated distraction event is highly likely to occur in the next 7 days False Flag-O-Meter reaches the red zone Mike Adams NaturalNews May 12, 2013 This is a short but urgent warning: A false flag event, an act of war, a bombing or some other headlines-grabbing orchestrated event is very likely to occur in the next seven days precisely because the Obama administration is under intense fire right now and needs a quick distraction. In stage magic, it’s called the “art of misdirection.” In politics, it’s called the “Clinton method.” This is exactly what Bill Clinton did over and over again during his administration: Any time he was about to be raked over the coals for some political scandal, he would simply order the bombing of another “terrorist factory” somewhere around the globe. Magically, the Clinton News Network (CNN) would shift coverage to this heroic act of “national defense” and stop asking questions about his scandal back at home. That would give the Clinton administration enough time to intimidate, threaten or murder whoever might have been involved. (Vince Foster, remember?) Right now, Hilary Clinton and President Obama are facing the possible downfall of their political careers over the Benghazi cover-up. Thanks to recent testimony, we now know that the Obama administration actually ordered the stand-down of U.S. military forces, directly causing the death of a U.S. ambassador as well as those in the embassy who attempted to save his life. This is a scandal many times more explosive than Watergate. As the Benghazi investigation unfolds, it may very well end up in the forced resignation of Obama himself.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368371413310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 11:10:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368371871841-17</Id><Topic><Title>What stunt will Obama pull to divert attention from Bengazi-gate ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368307006787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:16:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You already missed the "false flag" event. Earlier this last week It was revealed that Hillary was responsible for Lincoln's death. So it's already out there for perusal by the great, steaming, massive pile of RWNJ discussion.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1368371871841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 11:17:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368372093687-18</Id><Topic><Title>PASS THE POPCORN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368050289984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The more I hear about the so-call leadership, the more I realize the evilness of it. Boy it takes some guts, standing in front of the American people lying through his teeth, and showing no remorse. Well, most of us already knew Barack Hussein Obama is as phony as his words...nothing real about him</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368372093687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 11:21:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368372712532-19</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama Is A Percenter Acting Like A Welfare Queen</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368367415827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:03:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are a non-partisan organization and the information is found in documents filed by Michelle. Drink all the Kool-Aid you want to be ignorant of documented evidence of corruption but without a logical response you're a laughing stock.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368372712532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 11:31:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368373444006-20</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama Is A Percenter Acting Like A Welfare Queen</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368367415827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:03:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is such hypocrisy for false flag OWS types to get their panties in a twist over Wall Street corruption while condoning corruption in the White House. It's no longer the people's house it's the 800 pound gorilla house of corruption charging $100,000.00 a pop for access.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368373444006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 11:44:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368373630033-21</Id><Title>Whats buried in the Immigration Bill? A Mandatory biometric Database.</Title><Msg>Oh just another eight hundred page “bipartisan” bill that nobody will read, mainstream media will refuse to cover, and that will merely further destroy any remnants of freedom left in these United States. Never forget the George Carlin quote on bipartisanship: “Bipartisan usually means that a larger-than-usual deception is being carried out.” From Wired: The immigration reform measure the Senate began debating yesterday would create a national biometric database of virtually every adult in the U.S., in what privacy groups fear could be the first step to a ubiquitous national identification system. Buried in the more than 800 pages of the bipartisan legislation (.pdf) is language mandating the creation of the innocuously-named “photo tool,” a massive federal database administered by the Department of Homeland Security and containing names, ages, Social Security numbers and photographs of everyone in the country with a driver’s license or other state-issued photo ID. This piece of the Border Security, Economic Opportunity, and Immigration Modernization Act is aimed at curbing employment of undocumented immigrants. But privacy advocates fear the inevitable mission creep, ending with the proof of self being required at polling places, to rent a house, buy a gun, open a bank account, acquire credit, board a plane or even attend a sporting event or log on the internet. Think of it as a government version of Foursquare, with Big Brother cataloging every check-in. “It starts to change the relationship between the citizen and state, you do have to get permission to do things,” said Chris Calabrese, a congressional lobbyist with the American Civil Liberties Union. “More fundamentally, it could be the start of keeping a record of all things.”</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368373630033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 11:47:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368373901415-22</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama Is A Percenter Acting Like A Welfare Queen</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368367415827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:03:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Larry Klayman founded Judicial Watch. Are you sure he is objective?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1368373901415</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 11:51:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368374780999-23</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama Is A Percenter Acting Like A Welfare Queen</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368367415827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:03:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They are a non-partisan organization ". They are not, they are very conservative based. Anyone can CALL themselves non-partisan, but few are. This one is not.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1368374780999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 12:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368375053258-24</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama Is A Percenter Acting Like A Welfare Queen</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368367415827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:03:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The founder, Larry Klayman, is a birther and writes for WND. He's so far to the right that you could legitimately call him on the fringe element right.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1368375053258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 12:10:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368375962290-25</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama Is A Percenter Acting Like A Welfare Queen</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368367415827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:03:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Her transparent hubbie added some pork to an Illinois bill that provided a Vice President's position to wonderful Michelle at a prominent Chicago hosipital that paid her around $175K a year that she did virtually nothing to earn. Great folks those corrupt, liberal elitists. And anyone that criticizes their corrupt activity is surely a racist.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1368375962290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 12:26:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368376285391-26</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama Is A Percenter Acting Like A Welfare Queen</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368367415827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:03:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Judicial Watch's hatred of Barack Obama is rivaled only by ali_infesto's.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1368376285391</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 12:31:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368376815409-27</Id><Topic><Title>Whats buried in the Immigration Bill? A Mandatory biometric Database.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368373630033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 11:47:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, great! A new conspiracy lunacy. Now we get a break from Benghazi.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1368376815409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 12:40:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368378350389-28</Id><Topic><Title>What stunt will Obama pull to divert attention from Bengazi-gate ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368307006787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:16:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More people live in my "parallel universe" than live in yours! Harharharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1368378350389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 13:05:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368378826864-29</Id><Topic><Title>Attention Boeing shareholders , please read this on the 787 and the Boeing management hacks included</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368235741181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:29:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump it for the hacks</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368378826864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 13:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368378828334-30</Id><Topic><Title>Atmospheric CO2 Concentrations Surpass 400 PPM Milestone on May 9th</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368286752824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 11:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are arguing like an imbecile, typical of the low-IQ right-wing dittoheaded politcal partisans and bigots, using words you do not know the meaning of and C&amp;P'ing a list of irrelevent questions to the facts. There is considerable evidence that over the very recent period of the last 100–1000 years, the sharp increases in human activity, especially the burning of fossil fuels, has caused the parallel sharp and accelerating increase in atmospheric greenhouse gases which trap the sun's heat. The consensus theory of the scientific community is that the resulting greenhouse effect is a principal cause of the increase in global warming which has occurred over the same period, and a chief contributor to the accelerated melting of the remaining glaciers and polar ice. Changes in the concentration of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere are a strong candidate to explain the overall pattern of climatic change. Carbon dioxide influences the mean global temperature through the greenhouse effect. The globally averaged surface temperature for the Earth is approximately 15 degrees Celsius, and this is due largely to the greenhouse effect. Solar radiation entering earth's atmosphere is predominantly short wave, while heat radiated from the Earth's surface is long wave. Water vapor, carbon dioxide, methane, and other trace gases in the Earth's atmosphere absorb this long wave radiation. Because the Earth does not allow this long wave radiation to leave, the solar energy is trapped and the net effect is to warm the Earth. Within a decade the world will never see days — even in the cleanest of places on days in the fall when greenhouse gases are at their lowest — when the carbon measurement falls below 400 ppm, said James Butler, director of global monitoring at the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration's Earth Science Research Lab in Boulder, Colo.</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368378828334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 13:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368378970815-31</Id><Topic><Title>Atmospheric CO2 Concentrations Surpass 400 PPM Milestone on May 9th</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368286752824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 11:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Environmental activists, such as former Vice President Al Gore, seized on the milestone. "This number is a reminder that for the last 150 years — and especially over the last several decades — we have been recklessly polluting the protective sheath of atmosphere that surrounds the Earth and protects the conditions that have fostered the flourishing of our civilization," Gore said in a statement. "We are altering the composition of our atmosphere at an unprecedented rate." Carbon dioxide traps heat just like in a greenhouse. It accounts for three-quarters of the planet's heat-trapping gases. There are others, such as methane, which has a shorter life span but traps heat more effectively. Both trigger temperatures to rise over time, scientists say, which is causing sea levels to rise and some weather patterns to change. When measurements of carbon dioxide were first taken in 1958, it measured 315 ppm. Some scientists and environmental groups promote 350 ppm as a safe level for CO2, but scientists acknowledge they don't really know what levels would stop the effects of global warming. The level of carbon dioxide in the air is rising faster than in the past decades, despite international efforts by developed nations to curb it. On average the amount is growing by about 2 ppm per year. That's 100 times faster than at the end of the Ice Age. Back then, it took 7,000 years for carbon dioxide to reach 80 ppm, Tans said. Because of the burning of fossil fuels, such as oil and coal, carbon dioxide levels have gone up by that amount in just 55 years. "What we see today is 100 percent due to human activity," said Tans, a NOAA senior scientist. The burning of fossil fuels, such as coal for electricity and oil for gasoline, has caused the overwhelming bulk of the man-made increase in carbon in the air, scientists say.</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368378970815</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 13:16:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368379011355-32</Id><Topic><Title>My weekly update from may 3 , 2013 last Friday on my stocks and Boeing for the week</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368229159221</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:39:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump it for the hacks, I called it , as usual hacks cant find a winner in the winners circle conclusion hacks should be ignored on Boeing or just look at the stock chart and figure it out airbus up over 185% in 3 years tsla more gain in 5 days 50% than Boeing in 5 years ,42%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368379011355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 13:16:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368379591114-33</Id><Topic><Title>Why did Obama and Hillary Lie?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1368134323559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 17:18:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well they believed they could speak as a politician under Washington state rules for political campaigns- which is that lies are allowed during election campaigns according to WA state supremes. anyone who was harmed by such lies supposedly have recourse under civil rules eg money will fix So by state rules- the only people who could complain or file suit to recover $$ are the 4 people lied about. But they are dead- and not available for deposition under oath If they were dims - they could still vote</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368379591114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 13:26:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368380283319-34</Id><Topic><Title>Atmospheric CO2 Concentrations Surpass 400 PPM Milestone on May 9th</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368286752824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 11:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Were humans around before they began monitoring? Pretty stupid post if you think they weren't. Quit farting all the time, and raise some plants if you want to do your part. Man's involvement in global warming has been proven to be a scam. But you want to continue perpetrating the scam? Ever hear of the carbon cycle? Most 5th graders understand the carbon cycle.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1368380283319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 13:38:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368380413482-35</Id><Topic><Title>Whats buried in the Immigration Bill? A Mandatory biometric Database.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368373630033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 11:47:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you have a reading comprehension problem?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1368380413482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 13:40:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368380493814-36</Id><Topic><Title>What stunt will Obama pull to divert attention from Bengazi-gate ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368307006787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:16:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like you're a certified crackpot then........in your very own "parallel universe" of course..........</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1368380493814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 13:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368380612090-37</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama Is A Percenter Acting Like A Welfare Queen</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368367415827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:03:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another Kent Raven alias trying to be witty.............</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1368380612090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 13:43:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368381467185-38</Id><Topic><Title>Atmospheric CO2 Concentrations Surpass 400 PPM Milestone on May 9th</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368286752824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 11:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>John Holdren was a supporter of forced abortions and forced sterilization of Africans and has the support of many Progressive Democrats for such a solution to curbing world population No Democrat supports forced sterilization. You are a liar and you deserve to be dragged into court and prosecuted for criminal libel. Also there should be a law forbidding rightwingers to be so stoooopid as you are</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368381467185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 13:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368384512835-39</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone with a whiz wheel can divide n.m. by knots or s.m. by m.p.h. and even convert between the two. But do you know how long it takes to mobilize the flight? Get the weather, brief the aircrew, fuel and arm the aircraft, program the GPS for the target and alternates and maybe air refueling rendezvous? Maybe the planes are kept fully fueled on the flight line. Are they armed? If not, a Spooky with three miniguns would need 18,000 rounds to fire all three for three minutes. That's at their SLOWEST rate of fire of 2,000 rounds per minute. Are the guns belt-fed or hopper fed? I don't know. But I know I don't know. Why do you think YOU do?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1368384512835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 14:48:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368385808219-40</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama Is A Percenter Acting Like A Welfare Queen</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368367415827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 10:03:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you say "witty", you mean above your level of intelligence. That's everything.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368385808219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 15:10:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368385923687-41</Id><Topic><Title>Sir Beatle #9, this is Hertz #15 &amp; #22</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368323082718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 21:44:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, I also used "Revolver", "Abbey Road", and "Magical Mystery Tour". Sir Paul is a genius on all of them.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368385923687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 15:12:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368386407438-42</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nuther lie from the dope</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368386407438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 15:20:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368386506634-43</Id><Topic><Title>PASS THE POPCORN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368050289984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spartacus, I have shared this before. "They perish because they refused to love the truth and so be saved. For this reason God sends them a powerful delusion so that they will believe the lie and so that all will be condemned who have not believed the truth but have delighted in wickedness." (2 Thess 2:10-12). Now, I understand that this is specifically in reference to the anti-Christ ("lawless one"), but it is the principle that people "refused to love the truth" - for whatever reason - and that they "delight in wickedness". That is this generation to a tee. So, now it does not surprise me that the groundwork for the end times is being laid. And Obama and his blatant lies and the people's acceptance and indifference to those lies will make Satan's work a piece of cake. Hence, God will send them a delusion and they will fall for it. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1368386506634</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 15:21:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368386535123-44</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Wright Bros. could have gotten there in time moron.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1368386535123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 15:22:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368386810743-45</Id><Topic><Title>Why did Obama and Hillary Lie?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1368134323559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 17:18:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dopey we liberals are going to see to it that you finally get locked up for being a nutcase when we overhaul the mental illness treatment in this country- hey its ok it will be for your own good</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368386810743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 15:26:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368386842390-46</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I already said a " SpookY" may not have been a good choice- but that dodges the real issue. Why was it not considered or the process started? NO one knew how long the attack would last - days, weeks, months or until everyone was dead ? And why not fly over with fighters to make a sonic boom , eetc. Would it have made a difference - nobody knows- but it was NOT even tried- because according to some pentagon types- there was NO tankers available. Since then several knowledgeable people in various positions have explained that even teams like delta force in croatia - were- by definition - assignment and long standing procedures able to get to benghazi in less than 7 hours. They were not called, nor were others in similar circumstances. The point is- NO help was put in motion during the attack- and as now disclosed by even the ARB report- security issues before the attack were ignored. Even the CIA initial report- talking points said so. As to the GPS on target- an unarmed drone with video was overhead within a few hours or less after the first attack. I think they are GPS equipped. :-P</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368386842390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 15:27:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368387238631-47</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about these comments from a retired Admiral ? onn oct 30,2012 Retired Admiral James A. Lyons likely pulled few punches as commander in chief of the US Pacific Fleet during his career … and he hasn’t started pulling punches now, either. In a blistering column at The Washington Times, the former commander blasts the lack of action from the US when the administration learned our consulate in Benghazi had come under attack, writing that “courage was lacking” that might have saved at least some of the four American lives lost on September 11. “Someone high up in the administration,” Lyons writes, “let our people get killed” — and he wants some answers immediately as to whom: The Obama national security team, including CIA, DNI, State Department and the Pentagon, watched and listened to the assault but did nothing to answer repeated calls for assistance. It has been reported that President Obama met with Vice President Joseph R. Biden and Secretary of Defense Leon Panetta in the Oval Office, presumably to see what support could be provided. After all, we had very credible military resources within striking distance. At our military base in Sigonella, Sicily, which is slightly over 400 miles from Benghazi, we had a fully equipped Special Forces unit with both transport and jet strike aircraft prepositioned. Certainly this was a force much more capable than the 22-man force from our embassy in Tripoli. I know those Special Forces personnel were ready to leap at the opportunity. There is no doubt in my mind they would have wiped out the terrorists attackers. Also I have no doubt that Admiral William McRaven, Commander of U.S. Special Operations Command, would have had his local commander at Sigonella ready to launch; however, apparently he was countermanded—by whom? We need to know.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368387238631</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 15:33:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368387278388-48</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know those Special Forces personnel were ready to leap at the opportunity. There is no doubt in my mind they would have wiped out the terrorists attackers. Also I have no doubt that Admiral William McRaven, Commander of U.S. Special Operations Command, would have had his local commander at Sigonella ready to launch; however, apparently he was countermanded—by whom? We need to know. I also understand we had a C-130 gunship available, which would have quickly disposed of the terrorist attackers. This attack went on for seven hours. Our fighter jets could have been at our Benghazi mission within an hour. Our Special Forces out of Sigonella could have been there within a few hours. There is not any doubt that action on our part could have saved the lives of our two former Navy SEALs and possibly the ambassador. Having been in a number of similar situations, I know you have to have the courage to do what’s right and take immediate action. Obviously, that courage was lacking for Benghazi. The safety of your personnel always remains paramount. With all the technology and military capability we had in theater, for our leadership to have deliberately ignored the pleas for assistance is not only incomprehensible, it is un-American. +++++</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368387278388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 15:34:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368387836209-49</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously you don't know much about the situation or SOP, so you might want to get the facts before you make yourself look like a complete idiot.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1368387836209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 15:43:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368387911912-50</Id><Topic><Title>Whats buried in the Immigration Bill? A Mandatory biometric Database.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368373630033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 11:47:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He comprehends everything he reads that's on a third grade level or below.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1368387911912</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 15:45:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368389177950-51</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just exactlry when were the Wright brothers alerted and they responded... Try sticking to the facts! About 4:15 p.m.: “The attackers gained access to the compound and began firing into the main building, setting it on fire. The Libyan guard force and our mission security personnel responded. At that time, there were three people inside the building: Ambassador Stevens, one of our regional security officers, and Information Management Officer Sean Smith.” About 4:45 p.m.: “U.S. security personnel assigned to the mission annex tried to regain the main building, but that group also took heavy fire and had to return to the mission annex.” About 5:20 p.m.: “U.S. and Libyan security personnel … regain the main building and they were able to secure it.” Around 6 p.m.: “The mission annex then came under fire itself at around 6 o’clock in the evening our time, and that continued for about two hours. It was during that time that two additional U.S. personnel were killed and two more were wounded during that ongoing attack.” 6:30 pm. (approximately): A six-man security team — four are part of a quick-reaction force and two are special-operations force members — leave Tripoli on a Learjet to Benghazi. 6:30 pm (approximately): In a different part of Tripoli, four of the Army’s Green Berets, who are in Libya on a training mission, are asked to awaken U.S. personnel and help with a preventive evacuation in Tripoli. About 8:00 p.m.: Deputy Chief of Mission in Libya Gregory Hicks briefs Secretary of State Hillary Clinton on developments in Benghazi from his post in Tripoli. He would later say that “most of the conversation was about the search for Ambassador Stevens.” He tells her that the remaining personnel in Benghazi should evacuate and she agrees. (Hicks gave his account of the phone call at a May 8, 2013, hearing of the House Committee on Oversight &amp; Government Reform.)</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1368389177950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:06:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368390221364-52</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>joe of course that was a documented speech to curtail any questions. Very similar to Obama's speeches pointed at 6th graders the average education here in America. These people won't ask questions, most take the statement like sheep to the slaughter. Like Biden addressing the blacks in Norfolk, a vote for the GOP will put you back in chains and slavery. Most believed it.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368390221364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:23:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368390571789-53</Id><Title>as the nations moves away from God and Christain beliefs who loses?</Title><Msg>women are still being burned in India, women have no rights in the Muslim world, children are sold for sex across the globe. Last year we heard the DNC boo the re-entry of God and Christain beliefs into their plateform. So is he really there after the boo's, I think not.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368390571789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368390780514-54</Id><Topic><Title>as the nations moves away from God and Christain beliefs who loses?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368390571789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:29:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must think you think like God thinks.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1368390780514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:33:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368390869831-55</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I moght. I certainly wouldn't want to rely on a little Flight Sim *hit like you, who wants us to think he knows all of it, but never shares any.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1368390869831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:34:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368390959874-56</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry Don. At some point, I have to just tell you what I really think. I think you're talking through your hat.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1368390959874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:35:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368391020292-57</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe because shooting up a place to protect a consulate is sort of the opposite of what diplomacy is all about. You think?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1368391020292</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:37:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368391080265-58</Id><Topic><Title>PASS THE POPCORN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368050289984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Am I going to hell, bob? Is that what you are saying? It's okay... you can give it to me straight.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368391080265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:38:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368391138039-59</Id><Topic><Title>as the nations moves away from God and Christain beliefs who loses?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368390571789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:29:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who loses? Nobody. America was never meant to be a Christian country.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368391138039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:38:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368393085872-60</Id><Topic><Title>as the nations moves away from God and Christain beliefs who loses?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368390571789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:29:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz is way t oo far left, and too much of a heathen to even make comment. Hooz's socialist, athiest ideology, and the corruption that goes with it makes it acceptable to athiests. They are completely void of a sense of decency, and a sense of moral values that are based in Christianity. Who loses? The nation loses. And it is much more hard felt by Christians, than by the hoozes.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1368393085872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368393230959-61</Id><Topic><Title>yes Obama gave 1%...cheapskate expects others to pay his way</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1367980758794</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 22:39:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so right chris_genna2 evades the truth, whatever charity Obama is the cheapskate expecting others to pay his way.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368393230959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:13:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368394331814-62</Id><Topic><Title>Obama likes to compare himself to Abe Lincoln, but Abe warned Americans of thugs like Obama.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368240984240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:56:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>9 posted dislike, even disliking an Abe Lincoln statement, Obvious Obama has corrupted America</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368394331814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368394533786-63</Id><Topic><Title>as the nations moves away from God and Christain beliefs who loses?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368390571789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:29:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I said there is not an official religion in America. And that's a fact!!!</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368394533786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368394769841-64</Id><Topic><Title>why do Dems believe and give Obama admin a walk on all his admin. lies</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368197537813</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:52:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a true tragedy of which the admin is tryting to sweep and it seems the #$%$ see no wrong in not protecting the Ambassador in a terrorist filled nation. They will give Obama and Hillary a walk. Now as we have learned with the Boston bombing these terrorist could very well have infultrated our society via Obama's immigration</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368394769841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:39:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368394784000-65</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like an emotional little girl who is too naive to know anything about military and foreign service operations.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1368394784000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:39:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368395014094-66</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Based on your complete lack of knowledge about the situation, I'm sure he could care less what you "really think".........putz.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1368395014094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:43:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368395244133-67</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad they didn't have you there so you could of asked them, diplomatically of course, to "please stop the attack".............hehehehehe......ya, you would have sure showed them!</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1368395244133</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368395318624-68</Id><Topic><Title>as the nations moves away from God and Christain beliefs who loses?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368390571789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 16:29:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spoken like a true card carrying communist insurgent........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1368395318624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:48:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368395365239-69</Id><Topic><Title>why are so many ignorant of the impact of the growing debt. A history lession</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368194110751</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:55:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>darm good post, I copies and posted it on my facebook. Hope you don't mind.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368395365239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368395707179-70</Id><Topic><Title>why are so many ignorant of the impact of the growing debt. A history lession</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368194110751</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:55:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't mind. By all means... it was pathetic, and good for my registration drive.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368395707179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:55:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368395852850-71</Id><Topic><Title>why are so many ignorant of the impact of the growing debt. A history lession</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368194110751</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:55:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please show it to your ESL class instead.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1368395852850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 17:57:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368396296800-72</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whereas you know all about it? I'm going to choke on my coffee, lameass.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1368396296800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 18:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368396360184-73</Id><Topic><Title>yes Obama gave 1%...cheapskate expects others to pay his way</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1367980758794</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 22:39:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell it to Moroni, Moron.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1368396360184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 18:06:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368396631422-74</Id><Topic><Title>PASS THE POPCORN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368050289984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, The Bible says, "Anyone whose name was not found written in the book of life was thrown into the lake of fire." (Revelation 20:15). (Lake of fire = hell). Is your name written in the Book of Life? Perhaps you do not know what that means. Have you accepted Jesus as your savior? I have no idea. But you do. Jesus spoke without confusion on this subject: "Whoever believes in him is not condemned, but whoever does not believe stands condemned already because they have not believed in the name of God's one and only Son." (John 3:18) Now, the question is put to you: do you believe in and have accepted Jesus as your Savior? That is a question for each individual, not just yourself. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1368396631422</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 18:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368396862544-75</Id><Title>Obama gave US $5.00 gas by Memorial Day when he walked into the White House it was $1.83 what happened?</Title><Msg>pumping more oil out of US then ever before, what happened?</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368396862544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 18:14:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368397565268-76</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As I said - while there are some valid questions- comments about using a gunship ( or even fighter guns/missiles ) in such close quarters, that does not excuse them from at least starting out and making loud noises from the get go. Instead the BS point was they would not have been there in time ( great future forecasting ) anyhow ??? Or perhaps the commo is so poor that once dispatched, no way to recall, or prevent a buzz job or even land troops at the local airport, etc. YEP- definitely would not consider sending troops into possible harms way - even if they wanted to go, and that was their defined mission- why ? looks bad politically and there is this election issue coming up- hell its not really an embassy- and the ambassador knew it was risky....</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368397565268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 18:26:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368397820951-77</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...I know those Special Forces personnel were ready to leap at the opportunity. There is no doubt in my mind they would have wiped out the terrorists attackers. Also .. he I in this case was a retired admirals comments .... Should have put that in quotes - as "I know those Special Forces personnel were ready to leap at the opportunity. There is no doubt in my mind they would have wiped out the terrorists attackers. Also ......" ++ from this a Former Pacific Fleet chief: We need full disclosure on Benghazi — now POSTED AT 9:31 AM ON OCTOBER 30, 2012 BY ED MORRISSEY Retired Admiral James A. Lyons likely pulled few punches as commander in chief of the US Pacific Fleet during his career … and he hasn’t started pulling punches now, either. In a blistering column at The Washington Times, the former commander blasts the lack of action from the US when the administration learned our consulate in Benghazi had come under attack, writing that “courage was lacking” that might have saved at least some of the four American lives lost on September 11. “Someone high up in the administration,” Lyons writes, “let our people get killed” — and he wants some answers immediately as to whom: The Obama national security team, including CIA, DNI, State Department and the Pentagon, watched and listened to the assault but did nothing to answer repeated calls for assistance. It has been reported that President Obama met with Vice President Joseph R. Biden and Secretary of Defense Leon Panetta in the Oval Office, presumably to see what support could be provided. After all, we had very credible military resources within striking distance. At our military base in Sigonella, Sicily, which is slightly over 400 miles from Benghazi, we had a fully equipped Special Forces unit with both transport and jet strike aircraft prepositioned. Certainly this was a force much more capable than the 22-man force from our embassy in Tripoli.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368397820951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 18:30:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368398599214-78</Id><Topic><Title>What stunt will Obama pull to divert attention from Bengazi-gate ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368307006787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:16:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you have been brought up the way Obama has been brought up, and the background and strategy of how liberals get ahead in politics, who knows what other corrupt activity Obama will chose to pursue?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1368398599214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 18:43:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368399670664-79</Id><Title>on cbs face the nation</Title><Msg>there was some intersting exchanges between Issa and Pickering "Issa also said he will on Monday request private testimonies from Pickering and Mullen and that his oversight panel has not been provided sufficient details on the State Department review. Pickering, who was sitting next to Issa during “Meet the Press,” said he wanted to appear at the Republican-led hearing Wednesday but was blocked. ****** Issa said Democrats could have invited their own witnesses, such as Pickering, but did not. " At one point as I watched- Issa complained that ( the committee ) still did not know who the ARB contacted, etc Pickering started to answer . . .we ( ARB) provided a list . . . and immediatley the subject was changed to the IRS issue. At that time he was apparently referring to the classified version which had been sent to ISSA committee. IMO- other comments by pickering such as " you lie !" when Issa said Pickering refused to appear .. . ' and later Issa said ' we were told that you . . ( refused? ) seem to indicate that somebody was speaking for Pickering and perhaps ** perhaps** some pages had been revised or pulled from the ARB report. Consider that Mr Hicks had been interviewed in a classified session - but had never had access to a transcript of either the classified or later public report which was to be released. And one other of the three - M Thomas- had offered to testify- but was never asked, and got no response Thats as bad as dealing with SPEEA !!!! And trash the whistleblower mode is in full effect- by the end of the week Mr hicks will be found guilty of pulling janes braids when they were in the then pre school sandbox- and will now be charged with assault and other henious crimes.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368399670664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 19:01:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368399671252-80</Id><Title>JFK birthday coming up, any body catch JFK on the History Channel, AirForce 1 taking JFK to Las Vegas to sex mob boss Gianconi's</Title><Msg>girlfirend. The press got tons of pictures but protected him and did not publish the trips, so nobody knew about them. Sound familiar? Michelle must feel like an uggly duck after all Obama womanizing. Ever see a president get away with such conduct before? at least JFK hid behind the press, Obama just spills his guts and lets the media figure out how to protect him.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368399671252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 19:01:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368400414417-81</Id><Topic><Title>Atmospheric CO2 Concentrations Surpass 400 PPM Milestone on May 9th</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368286752824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 11:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next ice age? 1500 to 3000 years. Warming will slow it, that's the good news for someone with a long time frame like yourself, but it won't stop it because we will eventually use up our fossil fuels and the oceans will absorb the excess carbon dioxide in a few hundred years. So start stocking up on coal right now.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1368400414417</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 19:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368400607665-82</Id><Topic><Title>Obama likes to compare himself to Abe Lincoln, but Abe warned Americans of thugs like Obama.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368240984240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:56:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe you're simply a megadoofus instead.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1368400607665</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 19:16:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368401642047-83</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps next time you should educate yourself on a topic before you post uneducated emotional rants?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1368401642047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 19:34:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368403083294-84</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How come you manage to #$%$ off every one here except for your aliases?" Cause his aliases are the onl ones who fawn over his posts ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368403083294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 19:58:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368404259856-85</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's a one man glee club who's on the wrong side of every issue.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1368404259856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 20:17:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368405739339-86</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you claim MY aliases are ?? source ? rotsa ruk dumbo</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368405739339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 20:42:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368406378955-87</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>directed at the Raven Lunatic..not you</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368406378955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 20:52:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368407425597-88</Id><Topic><Title>on cbs face the nation</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368399670664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 19:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OOOPs it was NBC meet the press ... here is part of the transcript REP. ISSA: You know, let’s not blow things out of proportion. This is a failure, it needs to be investigated. Our committee can investigate. Now, Ambassador Pickering, his people and he refused to come before our committee that… AMB. THOMAS PICKERING (Former Under Secretary of State for Political Affairs/Chair, Accountability Review Board on Benghazi): That is not true. GREGORY: All right. We’re-- we’re going to get to Ambassador Pickering. REP. ISSA: We have-- we have it in-- we have it in writing, we have White House correspondence. It may not have been the Ambassador’s decision but it was the White House decision. That has been reversed. We’re inviting him on Monday along with Admiral Mullen to come, to go through, with his papers, a private deposition so we can get the facts in a nonpartisan way. GREGORY: Right. REP. ISSA: We’ll have Republicans and Democratic… GREGORY: Well, all right. Ambassador Pickering, you-- you just jumped in here. You’re willing to appear? AMB. PICKERING: Of course. I’ve said the day before the hearings, I was willing to appear to come to the very hearings that he disclu-- he excluded me from. The White House told me back that he said… Advertise | AdChoices REP. ISSA: One second. Please-- please don’t tell me I excluded you. AMB. PICKERING: Well, the-- the majority was-- we were told the majority said I was not welcomed at that hearing. I could come at some other time. REP. ISSA: Well, as-- as the ambassador just said, the day before the hearing, if the White House said we’d like to have him, there’s a procedure. He could have been the Democratic witness. And we would have allowed him. The Democrats requested no witness. The fact is, we don’t want to have some sort of a stage show. We had fact witnesses. They testified. We have the Ambassador and-- and Admiral Mullen who conducted and oversaw the ARB. We’re inviting them on Monday. We’ll go through, not in fro</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368407425597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 21:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368407540727-89</Id><Topic><Title>on cbs face the nation</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368399670664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 19:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.... AMB. PICKERING: …there was contingency planning, David, and that contingency planning helped. The contingency planning involved the annex coming to help the people who were under attack at the mission. And it was fairly clear that that particular set of activities helped a great deal. We may have had more people killed if that hadn’t happened. We’ve been told that the only witnesses that are of any value are people in Tripoli. We interviewed everybody still alive on the ground who was at the U.S. mission that night. REP. ISSA: Well, and that-- ambassador… AMB. PICKERING: And I have... REP. ISSA: …that’s an important point. We’ve been denied even the names of those individuals. The fact is, our committee wanted to speak to the individuals from Benghazi. They were neither encouraged nor produced nor even their names made available to us. Look, two of the most respected career people I know, the Ambassador and Admiral Mullen, who I’ve-- I’ve worked with much more closely than the Ambassador, I respect them. We have an obligation to look for any of the inconsistencies, and yes, I understand that in seven hours, they look back and say we couldn’t have saved those men. The question-- one of the questions is, in hour one, what orders were given to begin the process? Who was put on alert? Who was asked? This could have gone on like Tehran. This could have gone on for weeks or months. So there’s a lot of those questions. All we’re really asking is, why is it that the Ambassador and the Admiral reached a conclusion? We have their output; their unclassified and classified output. GREGORY: Right. Let’s have the Ambassador-- let’s have the Ambassador respond to that. AMB. PICKERING: You also have access to the classified testimony. Advertise | AdChoices REP. ISSA: Well, actually… GREGORY: But let’s-- let’s-- I want-- but let’s… REP. ISSA: Ambassador, we’ve-- we’ve gotten the-- we’ve got the classified report but we don’t have any of the interviews you did. We don’t</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368407540727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 21:12:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368407575530-90</Id><Topic><Title>on cbs face the nation</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368399670664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 19:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMB. PICKERING: You also have access to the classified testimony. Advertise | AdChoices REP. ISSA: Well, actually… GREGORY: But let’s-- let’s-- I want-- but let’s… REP. ISSA: Ambassador, we’ve-- we’ve gotten the-- we’ve got the classified report but we don’t have any of the interviews you did. We don’t have even the-- we don’t even have the list of everyone you interviewed. So… AMB. PICKERING: The list of interview I believe is in the classified report… (Cross talk) GREGORY: All right. I-- I want to get to a larger picture though. Excuse me-- excuse me, Ambassador. I want to come back to this fundamental question. REP. ISSA: Yeah, please. GREGORY: Did you not pay sufficient attention to-- and time with the secretary of state? AMB. PICKERING: I believe we did. We had a session with the secretary. It took place very near the end of the report. It took place when we had preliminary judgments about who made the decisions, where they were made, and by whom they were reviewed. We felt that that was more than sufficient for the preponderance of evidence that we had collected to make our decisions and you know that our decisions was two of those people should be separated from their jobs. Two others failed in their performance. GREGORY: The press secretary to the president Jay Carney said back in November, he-- he talked about how changes were made, who made changes to these talking points prepared for Congress and for Ambassador Rice. This is what he said back on November 28th. ....</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368407575530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 21:12:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368409320061-91</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi - Air assets supposedly available</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368308799581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 17:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>makes no difference - you are still totally wrong wrong wrong wrong.. there was one other a long time ago. period</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368409320061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 21:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368409502659-92</Id><Topic><Title>PASS THE POPCORN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368050289984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Bob.....The Fear of the Lord is the most important virtue</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368409502659</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 21:45:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368409595636-93</Id><Topic><Title>Obama likes to compare himself to Abe Lincoln, but Abe warned Americans of thugs like Obama.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368240984240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:56:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love to see you #$%$ squeal like pigs. Twisting truths into a perversion of lies. Over the years only Obama has proved to be narcissistic hiding behind Executive Orders when he told Americans he wanted transparrancy. The hypocracy continues, historians will be publishing the biography.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368409595636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 21:46:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368409637439-94</Id><Topic><Title>Obama likes to compare himself to Abe Lincoln, but Abe warned Americans of thugs like Obama.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368240984240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:56:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you don't like Abe Lincoln?</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368409637439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 21:47:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368410211999-95</Id><Topic><Title>Atmospheric CO2 Concentrations Surpass 400 PPM Milestone on May 9th</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368286752824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 11:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When will your kind come to grips with the reality of man-made global warming? No doubt after it is too late! It is a mostly closed system. And semi-fragile, considering the 15 degree Celcius window that has persisted through even geologic eras. I am only allowed six mature plants and six immature plants at one time, and my doctor estimates my needs at 13 ounce per year. So what should I grow ?</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368410211999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 21:56:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368410384372-96</Id><Title>Benghazi Call Did Not Come From Hillary Clinton</Title><Msg>edited for content (slightly) Thomas pickering - The seasoned diplomat who penned a highly critical report on security at a U.S. outpost in Benghazi, Libya, defended his scathing assessment but absolved then-Secretary of State Hillary Rodham Clinton. "We knew where the responsibility rested," Thomas Pickering, whose career spans four decades, said Sunday. "They've tried to point a finger at people more senior than where we found the decisions were made," Pickering said of Clinton's critics. The Accountability and Review Board, which Pickering headed with retired Adm. Mike Mullen, the former chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff...concluded the decisions about the consulate were made well below the secretary's level. Pickering's defense of his panel's conclusions, however, was unlikely to quiet Republicans' calls for accountability for the attacks that left four Americans dead, including an ambassador. cont y/n</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368410384372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 21:59:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368410716945-97</Id><Topic><Title>PASS THE POPCORN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368050289984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The fear of the LORD is the beginning of wisdom" (Psalm 111:10).</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1368410716945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:05:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368411138319-98</Id><Title>When is the next False Flag to Save the Administration ?</Title><Msg>Prime time over the next two weeks ? Wag the dog anyone ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368411138319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368411189628-99</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Call Did Not Come From Hillary Clinton</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368410384372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 21:59:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans [have] shown little interest in relenting to explore what happened at the consulate, what might be done to prevent future such attacks and what political calculations went into rewriting talking points the U.S. Ambassador to the United Nations, Susan Rice, used on news shows the Sunday after the attack. Pickering said... he could have answered many of the question lawmakers raised, such as whether U.S. military forces could have saved Americans had they been dispatched to the consulate, some 1,600 miles away from the nearest likely launching point. A series of emails that circulated between the State Department and the CIA led to weakened – language that Rice used to describe the assault during a series of five television interviews the Sunday after the attacks. - BFD Try charges of weakend palgiarism...</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368411189628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368411193098-100</Id><Topic><Title>Obama likes to compare himself to Abe Lincoln, but Abe warned Americans of thugs like Obama.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368240984240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:56:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somebody is sadly very deluded or more likely, simply illiterate. "only Obama has proved to be narcissistic hiding behind Executive Orders " Herbert Hoover 968 Franklin D. Roosevelt 3,522 Harry S. Truman 907 Dwight D. Eisenhower 484 John F. Kennedy 214 Lyndon B. Johnson 325 Richard Nixon 346 Gerald R. Ford 169 Jimmy Carter 320 Ronald Reagan 381 George Bush 166 William J. Clinton 364 George W. Bush 291 Barack Obama 147 So more accurately, you mean "only" except for Bush, Clinton, Bush, Reagan, Carter, Ford, Nixon, Johnson, Kennedy, Ike, Truman, FDR, Hoover, et al. All but Harrison issued executive orders.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1368411193098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:13:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368411449395-101</Id><Topic><Title>PASS THE POPCORN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368050289984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bob...The older I get the more I agree with you ... Fear the Lord and obey his commands...the only way to have a chance to be a good man in this life....the wicked are in charge</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368411449395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:17:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368411512620-102</Id><Topic><Title>Obama likes to compare himself to Abe Lincoln, but Abe warned Americans of thugs like Obama.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368240984240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:56:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>put 'tea-potty' or 'patriot' in the name, call it an org apply for 501 status do direct mailing solicitations from RWNJ's count the dough</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1368411512620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368411963261-103</Id><Topic><Title>When is the next False Flag to Save the Administration ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368411138319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:12:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are not 100% a spartaloon... Go ahead, name it today..."over the next two weeks" oh, really... where is the list: Gold to over $2000 Obama out of the race by August 2016. etc. etc. etc. However, on your behalf...of course Ambassado Stevens had to die (oh really...why, exactly ?) so that he could live on with Elvis, JFK, and janis aboard the Residensea</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1368411963261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:26:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368412037623-104</Id><Topic><Title>Obama likes to compare himself to Abe Lincoln, but Abe warned Americans of thugs like Obama.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368240984240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:56:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The poster you responded to is lazy, marginally literate, ignorant, and satisfied with this lot in life.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1368412037623</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368412313743-105</Id><Topic><Title>B.O. Lied, Americans Died</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1368238634825</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what you're saying is, "What does it matter ?' . Apparently B.O. didn't think it mattered, he went to bed while Americans died . . What matters most is that B.O. let our sworn enemies, the terrorists, win . . George Bush never let the terrorists win, not when they could be defeated, HOORAH ! . . Y.T. Jumbojetski .</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1368412313743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:31:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368412831363-106</Id><Topic><Title>PASS THE POPCORN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368050289984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spartacus, You might find it interesting to read Ecclesiastes. Here is a person, Solomon, who was endowed with wisdom that exceed any by at least a factor of two at any time in man's history (at least back then if not actually through today; sorry, Einstein and Hawking). The world flocked to Jerusalem to hear him talk to hear what wisdom he had to impart. They lavished him with gifts and wealth. He also became greatly sinful having had 1000 wives and concubines and strayed from his worship of the Lord, allowing the worship of idols in Israel. In short, he experienced everything, and I mean EVERYTHING. He said that, in the end, all things were "vanity" (really meaningless) and that there was "nothing new under the sun". So, he summarized it all: "Now all has been heard; here is the conclusion of the matter: Fear God and keep his commandments, for this is the duty of all mankind." (Ecclesiastes 12:13) How can we but look at this man and learn how his experience does have an implication for ourselves? Indeed, we are not shortchanged in life because we are not a "great singer" or "great orator" or a "great thinker" or a "great athlete" because those things do not matter in terms of eternity with the Lord. Instead, they are the vanity that Solomon was talking about. But, Spartacus, my question to Hooz is also to yourself. It is the question that I had to answer for myself years ago: shall I believe on Jesus as my Savior? Or shall I spend eternity separated from the Lord? BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1368412831363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:40:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368412969564-107</Id><Topic><Title>PASS THE POPCORN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368050289984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even if you prayed and begged forgiveness...GOD would not 'command' you letalone buly-blob. "He" told me via inspiration to tell you that he is not a a he, she, or it...and to warn you about ypur use of langue et language skills, or lack thereof...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1368412969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:42:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368413355772-108</Id><Topic><Title>B.O. Lied, Americans Died</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1368238634825</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dumboyjetski,,,, shoont you be in atlantic city #$%$ out instead espousing your idiocy on this fine messageboard who got bin_laden, not your saudi-royal hand-holdin/butt-kissin' bushco oily #$%$ man-boy duhbya and your kind only got your kind in the works even if gov. christie thinks if he sheds 300 lbs... or randy paul thinks he looks erudite and spaeks for the people... they used to call me the midnight rambler now they only call me the bisbee_angler</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1368413355772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368413437446-109</Id><Topic><Title>PASS THE POPCORN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368050289984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bisbee, Sober up a little and try again. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1368413437446</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368413484101-110</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Call Did Not Come From Hillary Clinton</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368410384372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 21:59:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Taking fire"... "help"... 3....2...1... alert a RWNJ, timed event go...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1368413484101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:51:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368413931165-111</Id><Topic><Title>PASS THE POPCORN</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368050289984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 17:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bulky_bob110 posts | Last Activity: 6 minutes agoMember since: Jul 4, 2000 que sera, sera "He" ?</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1368413931165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 22:58:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368414362141-112</Id><Topic><Title>Just to get to high school</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1367997332018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 03:15:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just as the bubbles started to boil from a clear glass pot on a hot plate I was asked to sit down and not continue my fine "A" performance science oral report just because JFK had been shot thnaky god almighty, i was gonna wing -it...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1368414362141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:06:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368414433753-113</Id><Topic><Title>Atmospheric CO2 Concentrations Surpass 400 PPM Milestone on May 9th</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368286752824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 11:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gosh you're ignorant of facts. Page 837 Ecoscience 1977 "Indeed, it has been concluded that compulsory population-control laws, even including laws requiring compulsory abortion, could be sustained under the existing Constitution if the population crisis became sufficiently severe to endanger the society."</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368414433753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:07:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368414481146-114</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Call Did Not Come From Hillary Clinton</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368410384372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 21:59:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not even a "what's going on you said, old man" from a RWNJ time is a ticking...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1368414481146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:08:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368414751991-115</Id><Topic><Title>Atmospheric CO2 Concentrations Surpass 400 PPM Milestone on May 9th</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1368286752824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 11:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't ask any question that I didn't already know the answer to. I know the science/physics very well and I speak to climate scientists quite a bit. You are the one cutting and pasting ans Seth Borenstein is not a scientist, he's a whacko AP environmentalist writer. I only read peer reviewed science papers. That Is why I knew the Lewandowski paper contained in an article hooz C&amp;P was retracted. You're a joke and offer nothing on this subject you can't answer a single question I posed because you know nothing about the subject.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368414751991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368415637932-116</Id><Title>Global Warming and Cooling began at Creation. Ice formed along the Bering Sea Indians crossed over to America ice melted water returned</Title><Msg>ice formed again Eskimoes crossed over and water returned. Its part of Gods creation folks, nothing to be afraid of. Intellectuals are after tax dollars to study it, they use fear to get tax dollars. One of the most compelling crimes in America is Al Gore who was worth $2M when he left office who is now worth over $100 million due to Global Warming scare tactics</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368415637932</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368415886669-117</Id><Topic><Title>Obama likes to compare himself to Abe Lincoln, but Abe warned Americans of thugs like Obama.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368240984240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:56:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Abraham Licoln, the founder of the modern day Democratic Party, did not warn abour Obama being a thug, in h\igh contrast he warned about many of the same evils as did IKE...namely the corruption of the military-industrial...and congressional oilgarchies/complexes, etc. burp... the bisbee_angler</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1368415886669</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:31:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368416049929-118</Id><Title>Subjetc: Let me tell you how it will be.</Title><Msg>There's one for you, nineteen for me 'Cause I'm the taxman Yeah, I'm the taxman Should five percent appear too smallBe thankful I don't take it all'Cause I'm the taxmanYeah, I'm the taxman (If you drive a car, car)I'll tax the street(If you try to sit, sit)I'll tax your seat(If you get too cold, cold)I'll tax the heat(If you take a walk, walk)I'll tax your feet(Taxman) 'Cause I'm the taxmanYeah, I'm the taxman Don't ask me what I want it for(Ha ha, Mr. Wilson)If you don't want to pay some more(Ha ha, Mr. Heath)'Cause I'm the taxman Yeah, I'm the taxman Now my advice for those who die(Taxman)Declare the pennies on your eyes(Taxman)'Cause I'm the taxmanYeah, I'm the taxmanAnd you're working for no one but me(Taxman) Read more: and Paul thinks he was a walrus</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1368416049929</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:34:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368416429429-119</Id><Topic><Title>Just to get to high school</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1367997332018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 03:15:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>times a wasting...for a RWNJ response to "taking fire, help"... armchair warriors, RWNJ chickenhawks, parttisan political witch-hunters and hacks hey what about that CA attorney-general in 2016... Obama said she is "muy- calinete'</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1368416429429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:40:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368416764781-120</Id><Topic><Title>Just to get to high school</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1367997332018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 03:15:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>still sweating from the post afternnoon-recess bell world championship elementary school soccer championship higher grades field because next week we play football with the same teams... that's where I was when JFK was shot... and killed...murdered.</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1368416764781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368417046326-121</Id><Topic><Title>Obama likes to compare himself to Abe Lincoln, but Abe warned Americans of thugs like Obama.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368240984240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:56:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>greg do tom and max make jane squeal like a pig too- or do they just make you squeal</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368417046326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368417092392-122</Id><Topic><Title>Subjetc: Let me tell you how it will be.</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1368416049929</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:34:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stop right there... (If you drive a car, car)I'll tax the street(If you try to sit, sit)I'll tax your seat(If you get too cold, cold)I'll tax the heat(If you take a walk, walk)I'll tax your feet(Taxman) if you tax the seat of RWNJ's we will have more pennies from heaven than can fill a ten-gallon Bushco cow-boy wannbe#$%$ in under a parsecond... - the bisbee_angler, click on it...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1368417092392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368417120696-123</Id><Topic><Title>Obama likes to compare himself to Abe Lincoln, but Abe warned Americans of thugs like Obama.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368240984240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:56:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whats obvious is that the North has never forgiven Abe for not expelling the southern states from the union on a permanent basis--and with good reason</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368417120696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:52:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368417168567-124</Id><Topic><Title>Obama likes to compare himself to Abe Lincoln, but Abe warned Americans of thugs like Obama.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368240984240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:56:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that military industrial complex?? that would be the republican crooks of today</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368417168567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:52:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368417377507-125</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming and Cooling began at Creation. Ice formed along the Bering Sea Indians crossed over to America ice melted water returned</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368415637932</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:27:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>creation?? I suppose that was 5000 years agao eh #$%$</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368417377507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 23:56:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>