<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366431870977-1</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals are going to get this terrorist out of prison in 5 years with a PHd</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366417059193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:17:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EXCELLENT POST.....NOBAMA will probably request a FREE plane ticket back to Kirscheytan or whatever !</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366431870977</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:24:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366431941279-2</Id><Topic><Title>✈✈✈✈OPENS @ $80 on Monday...watch !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1366399277742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:21:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>heard that...this DOG will tank Monday !@!@...Massive layoffs and there's MORE to the battery issue than WE are being told ....</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366431941279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:25:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366431958243-3</Id><Title>Massive layoffs and there's MORE to the battery issue than WE are being told ....</Title><Msg>really.....</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366431958243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:25:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366432111461-4</Id><Topic><Title>SOLD my shares....we're heading back down due to Dreamliner flop</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1366396430394</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 14:33:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agreed</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366432111461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:28:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366436243886-5</Id><Title>Boeing becomes #21 MOST SHORTED STOCK !! replaces GE !!! **STRONG SELL</Title><Msg>and FAST</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1366436243886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 01:37:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366436465301-6</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P Report....APRIL 13, 2013....12 month price target $82...BOEING is a SELL boys !!</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1366415792963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 19:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO DOUBT</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1366436465301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 01:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366437157764-7</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing CEO made the list of the top 20 paid CEOs, but the shareholders have made less than 5% in 5 years ouch , bark</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366170938186</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 23:55:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey for all the Boeing hacks today, in addition to the FAA battery box approval and result of the weak stock price gain, it is 1.8% for BA and 3 % for Airbus. I said in the title pos, that t the 747 is two years late, cost 2 billion over projected development cost and not selling as promised and guess what!. I am right again, the newspapers just confirmed what I told you hacks.. Attention Boeing hacks, here it is. " slowdown is here " Apr 19, 2013 10:07am EDT April 19 (Reuters) - Boeing Co said it would cut the production rate for the latest version of the 747 jumbo jet from 2 aircraft per month to 1.75 aircraft citing lower demand for large passenger and cargo planes. Next, attention Foulmoutharbor , in one 5 day week Airbus has gained for their investors almost as much as Boeing took five years to make for Boeing investors. FMH, any questions now , eh ! cnn money, stock chart use it . BA for this week is down 1.39% and for 5 years up 5.9% while Airbus for this week is up 5.66% and for five years is up 125% enough said, maybe someone, its another Boeing hac, k should read my book, eh domerrrrr45 and the newspapers on BA and the CNN money stock chart on BA and on airbus eadsy !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366437157764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 01:52:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366437643319-8</Id><Topic><Title>SOLD my shares....we're heading back down due to Dreamliner flop</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1366396430394</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 14:33:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tucsonlighting747 , so your really actually ignoring the fact that while you bragged to me the FAA approved the battery in a box, and yet on that huge big deal news story today while Boeing jumped up 1.8% Airbus on no news just better performance is up 3% today. bark and ouch, and for the week BA is actually a loss of 1.3% while Airbus stock increased almost as much in 5 days as it took Boeing investors to gain in five years that is BA stock price down 1.3% this week, Airbus up 5.66% this week and BA up a pathetic 5.9% for five years of investment while Airbus investor's have gained in five years 125% on their investment, so tucsonlighting747 , speaking of ignorant trolls you seem to be leading in ignorance category ouch and bark for your comments tucsonlighting747 BTW as I stated BA is late by 2 years and 2 billion over budget on their extended 747 and now cutting production rate due to lack of orders learn how to trade a stock instead of being a Boeing hack eh !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366437643319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 02:00:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366437857337-9</Id><Topic><Title>6 months to change out a battery...Bwhahahahahahahahahaha!</Title><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366432047822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:27:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not as fast as CEO James Mcnerdy claimed in January, the 787 grounding was uncalled for and it was going to be grounded a very short time according to Mcnerdy CEO of BA, but wait it has been a quarter of a year, well Mcnerdy is always off anyway we expect a proven failure to miss.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366437857337</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 02:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366437951236-10</Id><Topic><Title>hey tucsonlighting747 today Boeing is up 1.8% today while Airbus is up 3% what is your point</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366401026890</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tucsonlighting747 stop trolling around get BACK HERE AND EXPLAIN YOURSELF</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366437951236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 02:05:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366439881771-11</Id><Title>Alex Jones is phoning it in === (Spartakook, this is for YOU.)</Title><Msg>Alex, your latest theory is terrible -- we expect more from you Alex Jones must be either getting lazy or think his readers are really dumb, because his grand theory about the Boston Marathon bombings is the sloppiest concocted narrative we’ve seen since that dog ate your homework. Of course, Jones and his comrades at InfoWars thinks the brothers suspected in the bombing are innocent, citing such reliable sources as Twitter user “Trippin No L’ 4/20.” But if the brothers Tsarnaev didn’t do it, who did? Jones laid out his unified theory of the event yesterday in a video promising “PROOF!” that the event was “staged” and an accompanying blog post. The basic outline is the same as all of his projects: A globalist cabal working through the U.S. government staged a “false flag” operation that will be blamed on terrorists as pretext to take away guns and civil liberties and eventually tyranny. Eventually, they will depopulate the entire planet through massive genocides. In the video, Jones calls the bombings “the biggest event” of his 18 years of broadcasting, so you would think he would bring his A game, but he really let us down with this one. There’s something you have to respect about a good conspiracy theory — Hollywood certainly does — and Jones is generally a master, but his latest work is so full of holes, internal inconsistencies and outrageous leaps in logic that only die-hard fans willing to suspend all disbelief will appreciate it. It’s really the Phantom Menace of the InfoWars franchise. Here are just a few of the things a good continuity supervisor would catch [...]</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1366439881771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 02:38:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366439944328-12</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones is phoning it in === (Spartakook, this is for YOU.)</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1366439881771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 02:38:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[...] The mask slips, Jones says, when the “whole script got screwed up” after CNN reported, and then retracted, that a suspect had been arrested (thanks, John King!). The reason for the change, Jones says, is that the conspirators didn’t anticipate that people would have access to public images of the bombing. Really? The omnipotent globalist regime didn’t think, gee, “I wonder if there will be any cameras at this very high-profile event. You know, the one where thousands of people come with iPhones and dozens of media outlets set up hundreds of camera along the route?” How are we supposed to take the globalist threat seriously when they can’t even get this right. In the space of few hundred words, InfoWars can’t decide if the media is merely useful idiots or direct coconspirators. First, the site says the bomb threat at the courthouse after the attack was a pretext to “distract the media,” but states that the “government … ordered the corporate media to ignore the Plan A.” But if you can simply order the media to do anything you want, why create a distraction? Why bother with any of this, really? Just order the media to make the whole thing up, catch the fall guy right away, then kick up your feet with a hot cup of global enslavement and wash it down with some mindcontrolling fluoridated water. It’s these kind of internal consistencies that really take the reader out the story. • Beyond this, let’s just step back for a moment and take a look at the overall concept. For a compelling narrative, you need a capable and scary villain, but these guys sound like the wet bandits of megalomaniacal cabals. They have the most powerful people in the world — including the media — in their camp, and they can’t even come up with a compelling coverup, let alone remember to take their baseball caps off? And when exactly does the cabal cash in on all these false flags? [...]</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1366439944328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 02:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366442196645-13</Id><Topic><Title>hey tucsonlighting747 today Boeing is up 1.8% today while Airbus is up 3% what is your point</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366401026890</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Dell didn't get insider info from Heidi? Maybe he got it from Paul Allen? BA up 141 percent in last 4 years (since 4/20/2009). Don't you like facts? So do you still think the market closed early on March 28th? And you call yourself a trader and you don't even know when they close.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1366442196645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 03:16:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366442487924-14</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing CEO made the list of the top 20 paid CEOs, but the shareholders have made less than 5% in 5 years ouch , bark</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366170938186</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 23:55:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still no reply to BA up 141 percent? Wayne ignoring facts that don't fit his bias.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1366442487924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 03:21:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366447004330-15</Id><Title>So what has McNurdy done for Boeing!</Title><Msg>Outsourcing 787 design all over the world to incompetent companies? The truth is that Boeing should have NEVER outsourced 1 piece of the 787 using new materials never used in an aircraft before until they developed the technology in house! Hard lesson learned. Maybe Boeing will get it right when they develop their next aircraft!</Msg><Username>wonder_dink</Username><Timestamp>1366447004330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 04:36:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366450237501-16</Id><Topic><Title>Every Lethal Attack</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1366411925323</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are both mus lams, you freakin dipstick!</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366450237501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 05:30:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366450340817-17</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals are going to get this terrorist out of prison in 5 years with a PHd</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366417059193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:17:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and Hitler are twins.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366450340817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 05:32:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366450557652-18</Id><Title>Un-American Liberals were quick to blame real Americans</Title><Msg>and are very disappointed that it was muz lam terrorists.................</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366450557652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 05:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366459904351-19</Id><Topic><Title>Protecting the ‘Second Amendment Rights’ of Thugs and Terrorists</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366418999202</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:49:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like The First Amendment protects kool aid drinkers, no matter what insane stuff you say.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1366459904351</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366463205933-20</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals are going to get this terrorist out of prison in 5 years with a PHd</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366417059193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:17:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you can't argue with the facts, deflect and criticize the grammar.</Msg><Username>db0865</Username><Timestamp>1366463205933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:06:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366463637747-21</Id><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Msg>Caught your discussion with Chris Genna and his disrespectful attack on Religion. ( Genna thinks God is a Conspiracy Theory).....Christian Mystics have always opined that a belief in God is an "act of Faith" of course ...so on that level the discussion is closed....But there are precedents in Science that argue that there are individuals who have gone to the great beyond and returned...and was wondering if you had read a book called "Proof of Heaven"....it is on the New York Times Best Seller List. The book itself is about a Neurosurgeon who has a Near death experience. Scientifically it is very hard to argue against since he is in a deep coma which precludes brain activity causing an Hallucination. All he has is brain stem activity for 7 days. He has an encounter in which he meets an Infinite Being with Unconditional Love....(God) ? and goes on to great lengths to describe his experience ... Just thought as a deeply spiritual man you might like to rad the book and strengthen your own faith.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366463803556-22</Id><Title>Japan's ANA to conduct up to 200 Boeing 787 test flights:</Title><Msg>before carrying passengers. First passenger flights not until June. This is an interesting development. Who pays for the extra month of no revenue?</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366463803556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:16:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366464051433-23</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones is phoning it in === (Spartakook, this is for YOU.)</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1366439881771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 02:38:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Real Journalists do the following ...they ask questions of our elected leaders and KEEP THEM HONEST....they do not repeat the talking points of the Government....ITs called Checks and Balances. So far we have not gotten any real answers to those real questions. Why were Navy Seals (caught on video with backpacks and navy seals hats) caught on video Why were they interacting with the suspect that was shot ? Why did they have backpacks...(in the same shape as the pressure cooker bombs) and earphones and looking away from the race..(.as the bomb went off) Why did the FBI say NOT to look at those videos Why did Putin offer help (two of the Patsies/suspects were from Russia) Why was another Saudi suspect ordered DEPORTED back to Saudi by Obama ? Why did InfoWars and Drudge break this event and then 5 minutes later CNN was forced to change their story ? Why ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366464051433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:20:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366465072993-24</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raven: " why would they release the fact that one suspect was caught?" McVeigh was caught and killed ...Lee Harvey Oswald was caught and killed t bin Ladin was supposedly caught. and killed... Didn't stop them from being the patsies in a False Flag event though did it ? In fact it is absolutely ESSENTIAL that a patsy be involved .. ...You make less and less sense each post....and the fact that "False Flag" is the number one search term IS a psychological turning point in the collective uncioussness of the Zeitgeist .</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366465072993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:37:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366467444420-25</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ahkmed, i mean sparty, are you trying to deflect from the root cause again, mobro made disasters?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366467444420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:17:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366467673853-26</Id><Topic><Title>Protecting the ‘Second Amendment Rights’ of Thugs and Terrorists</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366418999202</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:49:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Real Americans take a stand on the second amendment they are taking a stand for the Constitution and Civil Liberties and by definition Freedom.. “soft on crime” is often a necessity to maintain the Constitution if the OPPOSITE is Martial Law and the growing Police State.that represents everything America used to NOT represent...but has grown out of control under Bush/Obama Your posts show you STILL DON'T GET IT</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366467673853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:21:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366468645546-27</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do Communists hate religion?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366468645546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:37:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366468707381-28</Id><Topic><Title>Un-American Liberals were quick to blame real Americans</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366450557652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 05:35:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals are out of the mainstream and are nothing but radicals fanatics.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366468707381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366468941133-29</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beyond the steryotypical communist Manifesto "its the opiate of the people"...Most Liberal/communist/authoritarians feel that if God does not exist then ALL things are possible. Men have no natural rights to Freedom, homosexuality can be condoned and moral relativity becomes ascendant over the great fight between good and evil.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366468941133</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:42:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366469149783-30</Id><Topic><Title>Un-American Liberals were quick to blame real Americans</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366450557652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 05:35:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leftys go through life delusional and dumb as dirt. The Dem politicians like them that way. They are like little kids, easily impressed by anyone with a good story to tell.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1366469149783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:45:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366470084354-31</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones is phoning it in === (Spartakook, this is for YOU.)</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1366439881771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 02:38:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spazticus playing with spazticus, i mean corned_beef_dude</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366470084354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:01:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366471005075-32</Id><Topic><Title>Why was there a Bomb Treat EXERCISE BEFORE the Boston Marathon</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372765564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:59:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sometimes false flag operations can get pretty messy. Time for an Obama speach. That always calms down the libs. The problem is it's begining to really irritate everyone else.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1366471005075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:16:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366471750601-33</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another example of why sane people know your "reasoning" has been short-circuited, Sparty. I didn't "attack" religion. My SCORN (not attack) was directed at bulky, not at religion. But we understand why you go to extraordinary lengths to side with a few people on this board. When you're #$%$, you need friends; and the only likely candidates are those who are almost as nutty as you.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366471750601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366471792449-34</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They don't floyd. The hate people who ask vacuous questions. Hahahahahaha</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366471792449</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366471797385-35</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ahkmed I mean sparty I mean mobro I mean spaz I mean censored I mean bumper I mean fascist I mean spaz I mean censored worthless protoplasm</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1366471797385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:29:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366471862281-36</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMG! Sparty's trotted out his doctoral dissertation!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366471862281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:31:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366472044359-37</Id><Topic><Title>Why was there a Bomb Treat EXERCISE BEFORE the Boston Marathon</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372765564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:59:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like when Ronnie Raygun plagiarized John Gillespie Magee, Jr. to make a "speach" about the shuttle explosion.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366472044359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:34:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366472293861-38</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Didn't stop them from being the patsies in a False Flag event though did it ?" Not if you BELIEVE with all your fevered brain that those were false-flag operations. But that's begging the question. I would think you were just being stupid if I did not know you knew better. Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366472293861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:38:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366472775120-39</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Genna Maybe you can persuade Spartalunacy to deliver his famed Alamo dissertation again?</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1366472775120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:46:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366472935147-40</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did you become a Communist? Could you provide a few good reasons? (be specific)</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366472935147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:48:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366473120721-41</Id><Topic><Title>Un-American Liberals were quick to blame real Americans</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366450557652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 05:35:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are child like. Yes, and dumber than dirt.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366473120721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:52:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366473250160-42</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Raven alias making a request to the Raven..........in order to make it appear that the Raven has someone interested in his opinion.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366473250160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:54:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366475985120-43</Id><Topic><Title>hey tucsonlighting747 today Boeing is up 1.8% today while Airbus is up 3% what is your point</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366401026890</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991 as you can see you get 5 thumbs down for yoru crapola and here you are attempting to out trade me with a stock you picked, too bad it is not a stock, it is a toll symbol for working on the stock trader platform, yoru really a failure at being a critic too"Boeing company and the Boeing Hacks we all know who you are sprit and your various names remember this post today ACAD is up 65% in one day, 182% YTD, 700% for one year and 689% for 3 years and 52% for 5 years , not that I would buy and hold this stock. anyway sparti hows not following me working for you now ."2users liked this postsusers disliked this posts1Reply ACAD compared to IGZ by waynedickenson961 • Mar 21, 2013 3:57 PM Flag a well known Boeing hack attempted to keep up with me on my stock picks after I answered his debate style of the regular 25% gain with a demonstration not with words but in the few days it took me to make that gain on ACAD. I made 26% on ACAD this morning and am out. This certain Boeing hack claimed a stock IGS was up 144% so what was my point. har har har ?a certain Boeing hack without knowing how to trade stocks picked the wrong stock IGZ is not a stock , never was a stock, and never will be a stock it is a symbol used to test the trading platform, So a certain person who is a Boeing hack should probably use one of his other names now as he has just fooled himself sorry Less Less so sparti in just 19 days I made over 60% on ACAD while you pretended to show me up with a stock you thought was a real stock and it is a symbol used to check out the trade platform. Once more I remind you BA is not a buy or sell short, it is a poor stock investment compared to Airbus eadsy or... More • 1 Reply to waynedickenson961 • waynedickenson961 • 20 hours ago Flag o 4users liked this postsusers disliked this posts2 o Reply so sparti you asked me to stop poining out that your a very poor critic and I used your ignorant claim about a stock you offered to criticize my 19 day ago 26% acad gain. ? First of all sparti , you started the crapola yars ago with me and now you want to cry uncle? Why would I stop , you... More o 1 Reply to waynedickenson961 o spartacus99991 • 17 hours ago  0users liked this postsusers disliked this posts5  Reply I haven't owned BA for many years. Did you sell your $28M worth of AAPL when it was over $700, or did you ride it down a ways?  1 Reply to spartacus99991</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366475985120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:39:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366476182360-44</Id><Title>When Will We Know</Title><Msg>what firearms the bomber brothers were using aside from the ied's? And where they legally purchased them?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366476182360</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:43:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366476197329-45</Id><Topic><Title>hey tucsonlighting747 today Boeing is up 1.8% today while Airbus is up 3% what is your point</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366401026890</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacuss99991, I do nto have any Paul Allen boasts like you wstleffams, it's your crapola remember, its you that make these false claims as a troll your a failure , here it is remember ,"whsteffanms on his posts and MSFT, eh! 18-Jun-11 01:42 pm whsteffanms... I was wondering your IP address shows as Everett and you have 4528 update(6039)posts, with almost all of them containing slams and HAR HAR HAR and nothing of any value to anyone, how is it that you get along so well with Paul Allen? eh! Re: Microsoft Shows First Look at Windows 8 Interface VIDEO Whsteffanms said” dell george my address may be Everett, but my mansion is actually located over on Widbey Island( sure it is) and I get back and forth with my yacht( the full size scale model?)- I tie up next to Paul Allen a lot( a lot like never !) down in Elliott bay and confer( wow) with him quite a lot-- how do you like that eh ( just like all your other emails,, har, har , har ) Rating : (No ratings) Rate it: 1 star + unrated 5 stars whsteffanms... Male Everett WA ________________________________________ View Messages Ignore User Report Abuse</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366476197329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:43:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366477146371-46</Id><Topic><Title>hey tucsonlighting747 today Boeing is up 1.8% today while Airbus is up 3% what is your point</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366401026890</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991 a couple of years ago? wow, and bark ouch ! and your really grasping now, a couple of years ago ? have you no clue this is 2013, your really a sad case of how to fail at stock market money making . whatever your talking bout , if Heidi Wood is a analyst she told the world, not Dell, and that is her opinion what ever it was a couple of years ago then right !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366477146371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:59:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366477832664-47</Id><Topic><Title>Japan's ANA to conduct up to 200 Boeing 787 test flights:</Title><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366463803556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe they have stated they will be cargo carrying flights and will be charging for that cargo.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366477832664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:10:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366477898866-48</Id><Topic><Title>hey tucsonlighting747 today Boeing is up 1.8% today while Airbus is up 3% what is your point</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366401026890</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now you seem to be trying to be my critic on some date the stock market was closed now eh, so I do recall someone posting that Boeing stock would be up and I pointed out impossible as the stock market would be clsoed so once more here are the dates and if that is the point which you try to ignor New Year's Day January 1, 2013 Martin Luther King, Jr. Day January 21, 2013 Washington's Birthday (Presidents' Day) February 18, 2013 Good Friday March 29, 2013 Memorial Day May 27, 2013 Independence Day * July 4, 2013 * Labor Day September 2, 2013 Thanksgiving Day * November 28, 2013 * Christmas Day * December 25, 2013 So for your fellow Boeing Hacks if you state the BA stock will be up on one of these dates then that could nto happen and it is an example of mindless pump and dog and poney show crapola and if you really think that by picking a calendar lw and a high that makes any investor think about buying Boeign then your a less than smart person I give you a actual today stock market Ba compared to Airbus and use the cnn money stock charts I do not do the figures don't lie buy figure's like you do lie. dog and pony crapola here they are for today , cnn money stock chart for Friday--- BA up 1.8% airbus up 3%, for the week BA down 1.05%, Airbus up 5.66%, for the YTD BA up 16%, airbus up 32%, for 5 years BA up 6.27% airbus up 125% so in the past week Airbus has gained almost as much as BA has made for their shareholders in 5 years , do the math , try not to pick a low that has nothing to do with investing or trading yesterday get it now spartacus9991! in other words go back in time and buggy whips company stock were great not now , at one time horse company stocks were great not now get it nwo spartacus99991</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366477898866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:11:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366478607370-49</Id><Title>Japan ANA need 200 flights without passengers to trust BA and the FAA on the 787, is the 787 safe at any speed</Title><Msg>Some of the flights are for pilot training , but really what this is telling investors is obvious, ANA does not trust the fix, after all; the fix did not address the fire cause and the excuse is sometimes we don't know what we don't know. Wow, if you don't know then go with nicad and you will know, eh ! That is what Boeing told Cessna to do with their lithium fire problem and Cessna did exactly that. Instead Boeing builds a twice as heavy battery box than the nicad solution, so now we have a battery that will , no doubt catch on fire instead of a fix. The lithium battery solution has not been tested, this is a fix that includes the flying public taking a experimental battery fix and a seal containment vessel, on life threatening flights , the passengers should be paid for being test passengers , not revenue paying customers. So nothing can go wrong(this time),can go wrong , can go wrong warning , pull up, warning pull up , warning pull up splash silence dead silence . FAA to NTSB we are so sorry, we made the best decision we could based on the information we had in April of 2013 The insurance will pay each dead passenger family 100K thank you for flying and dieing on the 787</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366478607370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:23:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366478849928-50</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Boston deal was thunk up by the gubbermint NWO subcommittee on FFO (false flag ops) so nobody would notice they are shipping semi loads of FEMA coffins to FEMA camps. Plus, they concealed the gold price fluctuations of late. Worked, didn't it.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1366478849928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:27:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366481980980-51</Id><Title>ELEVATOR SHOES FOR ALL 787 MANAGERS!!!!!</Title><Msg>Even you Dudes in Philadelphia!!!</Msg><Username>caveman2501</Username><Timestamp>1366481980980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:19:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366483276582-52</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Neurosurgeon, who is entirely credible, had visions in which his interretation of God was one of "UNCONDITIONAL LOVE" ? Is that your interpretation of God ? Is God a God of Uncondtional Love ... or is God a God of Old Testiment retribution ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366483276582</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366483384886-53</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only person who would remember Chris Genna being wrong about the Louisiana Purchase ...and then LYING about it...2 years later..would be CHRIS GENNA</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366483384886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366483798086-54</Id><Topic><Title>6 months to change out a battery...Bwhahahahahahahahahaha!</Title><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366432047822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:27:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For to change to the same type of battery. A donkey does not stumble twice on the same stone.</Msg><Username>jackrip_eu</Username><Timestamp>1366483798086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:49:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366491672178-55</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, it's so obvious.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366491672178</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:01:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366493011416-56</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks, Hooz. He needs all the help he can ge distinguishing reality from fantasy.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366493011416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:23:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366493062930-57</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't Hamlet say that? Or was it William Shakespeare?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366493062930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:24:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366493129291-58</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes and in the context of describing his Life after Death experience with Papa Hamlet</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366493129291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:25:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366493221398-59</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The coffins weren't empty. They were filled with Bilderburgers.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366493221398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366493748930-60</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Slow down there and ease up before you have a myobrainial infartation.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1366493748930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:35:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366494410479-61</Id><Topic><Title>Un-American Liberals were quick to blame real Americans</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366450557652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 05:35:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zombiegrunt, now you lookie here lefty, we know you're buttering up both halves, so you know there ain't any further left than you hang. So come out of the closet, green side out, and become comfortable in public with your far leftist orientation for corruption and greed. You can re-write history, the golden rule, and your special type of bible, but you can't rewrite your final destination. That is where your reference to 'dirt' , as well #$%$ and 6 feet to hell come into playl</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1366494410479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:46:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366494474531-62</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>=....are you some kind of crazy fringe element ?= LOL... that YOU of all people should say something like that, HILARIOUS! _YOU_ are the veritable INCARNATION of "crazy fringe element ." And no, I am not Mr. Genna, as much as you wish it were so. Damn fool, that's what you are.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1366494474531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:47:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366494565157-63</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, you mean the one where David Crockett died fighting off illegal Mexican immigrants because it's so well known that the formerly FRENCH city of San Antonio, TX, was part of the Louisiana Purchase the U.S. bought from Naoleon in ? Even the folks in San Antonio -- who should know their own history -- don't say that. They even know (and can tell you) that the "1824" inscribed on the flag flown at the Alamo (otherwise known by it FRENCH name of Misión San Antonio de Valero) is the date of the signing of the MEXICAN constitution, which all Texians up to about 1832 had sworn ALLEGIANCE to, and claimed rights under. Or as Wikipedia puts it: Under President Antonio López de Santa Anna, the Mexican government began to shift away from a federalist model. The increasingly dictatorial policies, including the revocation of the Constitution of 1824 in early 1835, incited many federalists to revolt.[5] The Mexican border region of Texas was largely populated by immigrants from the United States. Is that the howler you're referring to? The best proof that Sparty knows almost NO facts, just the myths he would like us all to believe. What a putz the guy is!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366494565157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366494757962-64</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wikipedia says: Under President Antonio López de Santa Anna, the Mexican government began to shift away from a federalist model. The increasingly dictatorial policies, including the revocation of the Constitution of 1824 in early 1835, incited many federalists to revolt.[5] The Mexican border region of Texas was largely populated by immigrants from the United States. But of course your guru Alex Jones would say that Wikipedcia is all wrong. And he'd have no idea what the "1824" on the Alamo flag represented.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366494757962</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:52:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366494806739-65</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rule 1 when you're in a hole you can't get out of, Sparty: 1) Stop Digging. Loon.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366494806739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366495502025-66</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spartadupe: Here's a chance for you to do something: send a donation check to the guy in Watertown Mass whose boat got shot up when they found the 2nd #$%$ hiding inside it. A little step that you can take; then tomorrow, do another something good. Pretty soon you might make it to worthwhile status. Unless, of course, this is another bizarrely twisted conspiracy for the government to find out who donated to the guy and how it's part of the Literati and Orly Taitz and Who Let the Dogs Out and the Lindbergh baby.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1366495502025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:05:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366495644250-67</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Genna ...why do you suppose one of the suspects was deported to Saudi by Obama ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366495644250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:07:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366495846955-68</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weren't you conspiracy theorists braying a while back that Oswald, bin Laden, and McVeigh are all being held at Area 51 along with the Kenyan birth certificate, Donald Trump's spare hairpiece, and the formula for the New Coke.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1366495846955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366496062913-69</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Regular or with cheese?</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1366496062913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:14:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366496307540-70</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coffins 6-8 have the Bilderburgers with cheese. AMERICAN cheese. Coffin 16 has Bilderburgers with Havarti.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366496307540</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:18:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366496385056-71</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coffin 51 must therefore have alien, or imported cheese. HAR HAR HAR.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1366496385056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:19:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366496710267-72</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who says that happened, loon?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366496710267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:25:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366496728500-73</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Genna .. are you getting counseling for your multiple personality disorder ? Its becoming so obvious you are Hooz and Orly etc is laughable</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366496728500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:25:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366496846143-74</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spartacus, As I said, I cannot say whether or not these visions of heaven are true or not, but I am skeptical for the reasons stated. Yes, indeed, God is a God of unconditional love, but not unconditional forgiveness. That was born out by the provision of His Son, Jesus, to suffer on the cross for our sins. The single, the only one condition for "forgiveness" is believing in Jesus. Most people, tragically, do not "get" that. They insist that they must perform "good works" in order to be redeemed, to be "saved". But the Bible is very clear telling us otherwise (ref. Eph 2:8,9 and Romans 10:9,10). Relative to Him being a "God of retribution", I posted a while back on my conclusions upon reading the Old Testament. There is nothing but love and forgiveness in the Old T. If a person does not, is not able to, recognize that fact, there is fundamentally something amiss in that person's understanding of God. For example, the Israelites went in and out of outright disobedience to God over the 400 years that they played around with having a King - which God did not really want. Finally, He said, after forgiving their national behavior dozens of times, He said, "enough is enough" and they were carried away into captivity by Babylon, suffering heavy casualties. Yet there was still a "remnant" preserved in order to protect the lineage of Jesus. When the Jews wandered in the desert for 40 years, that gave all of the inhabitants of Canaan an opportunity to repent and turn from the evil which God said was the basis for their being destroyed by Israel. FORTY YEARS before they were to see judgment against them! Only one city sought to do right. When God destroyed the world with the flood, before doing so, it took Noah 100 years to build the ark. ONE HUNDRED YEARS. Now, you can see the pattern: God is longsuffering in His forgiveness and patient, but the so-called "retribution", as is often cited, is really the punishment which is clearly merited for the bad behavior. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1366496846143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:27:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366496901537-75</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong again, Spart. It was William Shakespeare. Hamlet AND his dad's ghost were FICTION -- like the moon landingas! Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366496901537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:28:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366497088183-76</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, Sparty; I have no problem with multiple voices on a message board -- just as you fave to problem with the multiple voices in your head.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366497088183</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:31:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366497137908-77</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you calling that poster floyd? I was absolutely sure they're different people! Hahahahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366497137908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:32:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366497393038-78</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: " ... you have no problem with the multiple voices in your head."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366497393038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366498812001-79</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your pushing of petty lies doesn't fool anyone who has noticed your history and habit of pushing GREAT BIG LIES. Spartapuss: A man (?) who prefers to believe the worst of everything about his nation, it's government, and it's people rather than believe anything good about any or those. All the while claiming to be a super-patriot and "oath-keeper."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366498812001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:00:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366498877751-80</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: "Spartapuss: A man (?) who prefers to believe the worst of everything about his nation, its government and i's people rather than believe anything good about any of those. All the while claiming to be a super-patriot and "oath-keeper."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366498877751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:01:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366499006836-81</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction again: Correction: "Spartapuss: A man (?) who prefers to believe the worst of everything about his nation, its government and its people rather than believe anything good about any of those. All the while claiming to be a super-patriot and "oath-keeper." I've been having too much fun; I'll go back to something more worthy than this comic interlude.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366499006836</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366499757229-82</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, Are you like the proverbial potshard that asks the potter, "what have you wrought"? Do you portend to judge God? It is pointless to even try. Did Jesus stone anyone to death? Did Jesus tell anyone to stone another to death? Are the rules different under Jesus, in this dispensation of "grace", than "under the law"? Yes, they are indeed. Is 40 years long enough to convince someone to repent? How about 100 years? How about 400 years? As soon as a person comes to grips with understanding that he or she is the "created" and not the "Creator" is the beginning of wisdom. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1366499757229</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366500335174-83</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes Bongo 52, I am Floyd, and as always, firm, but fair. I pulled alert, I know C Square and changeover, I know what an elephant walk is and stan eval, white scarfs, no notice check rides, ORI, the IP to the ARCP, cell nav leg, LNO, MITO, etc etc......The Raven does have issues. Ask him what a PIC is, just to confirm his level of knowledge...... Saber 6.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366500335174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:25:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366500432940-84</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you often repeat yourself when under stress?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366500432940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366500492263-85</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His aliases are his best friends, sad.....I hope he gets help......</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366500492263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:28:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366500833570-86</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366494885973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfortunately, "liking" Christ does not cut the mustard.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1366500833570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366500923193-87</Id><Topic><Title>"False Flag" number one Google search term</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366372389990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kind of a deranged, deluded, and downright weird post from somebody with 67517 attached. How many Yahoo I.D. versions has spartaloon owned? I say a few hundred.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1366500923193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:35:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366501609181-88</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BulkyBob: "God is longsuffering in His forgiveness and patient, but the so-called "retribution", as is often cited, is really the punishment which is clearly merited for the bad behavior." Yes but don't you see in that interpretation then God is not a God of Unconditional Love since he judges us and "Punishes us for bad behavior"..so how can that be unconditional Love ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366501609181</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:46:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366501959793-89</Id><Title>BOE5</Title><Msg>Boe5 flew to Alburquerque international from San Bernardino today.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366501959793</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:52:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366502131598-90</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366494885973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Perhaps... but I believe even Jesus Christ would think it was enough in the case of Mahatma Gandhi." #$%$, Dim projecting perceived thoughts of Christ once again in order to further their "Messiahs" agenda!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1366502131598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:55:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366502655900-91</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"spartacus mentioned the Old Testament God as a God of retribution. You responded that the punishment was merited. I don't think a public stoning was merited." Hooz, I can understand that with our view of the world and present day experiences that we find difficulty with comprehending how certain punishments "fit the crime" (or sin) back in the "Old T" days. You cited adultery, yet a child who cursed his parents was also to be stoned to death (Lev 20:9). Did it ever happen? I don't believe that there is a record of it in the Bible having actually happened. Yet it was the rule. Perhaps the rule was sufficient to put such behavior into abeyance. On the other hand, God killed two of Aaron's sons because they "offered incense" to God in an unauthorized and careless way (Lev. 10:1). The rules were different before Jesus. Folks followed examples and object lessons. Today, we are immersed with God's Word and sermons and analyses which allow us to intellectually rationalize belief. Indeed, faith is determined without eyewitness accounts, but simply by reading God's Word (Hebrews 4:12, Isaiah 55:11). It is interesting to note the envy that folks might feel towards Israel, in the sense that they are "the chosen people of God" (or at least were). But they were chosen for a very harsh and exacting path of worship of God - resulting in great reward and great chastisement on occasion. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1366502655900</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:04:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366502810350-92</Id><Topic><Title>Un-American Liberals were quick to blame real Americans</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366450557652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 05:35:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>..we know you're buttering up both halves, so you know there ain't any further left than you hang. So come out of the closet..." Poor pitiful Pauline projecting once again with her Bath House lingo. Don't fret Pauline, once you come to terms with your self loatings, others will begin to accept you as you are. In the mean time though, I suggest you keep a lid on your hormonal rants lest you are though as the loser you are at present!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1366502810350</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:06:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366502833411-93</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P Report....APRIL 13, 2013....12 month price target $82...BOEING is a SELL boys !!</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1366415792963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 19:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>selling monday am</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366502833411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:07:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366502863334-94</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing becomes #21 MOST SHORTED STOCK !! replaces GE !!! **STRONG SELL</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1366436243886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 01:37:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dump asap</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366502863334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:07:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366502907876-95</Id><Topic><Title>**MASSIVE LAYOFFS by Boeing...1700 Engineers,,,2300 Machinists **DREAMLINER flop !!!</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1366412348321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 18:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>come come now.......grasshopper</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366502907876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366502945252-96</Id><Topic><Title>✈✈✈✈OPENS @ $80 on Monday...watch !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1366399277742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:21:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sinking ship we think....</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366502945252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:09:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366503000531-97</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing TANKS Monday Dummies.........yes sir !!! A FIXED PLANE bwhahahahaha!</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1366404269338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 16:44:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>would YOU fly in one....????</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366503000531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366503051510-98</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366494885973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, I suspect that you will find this too hard, but while Mahama Gandhi may have accepted Jesus as his Savior, perhaps he did not. And if he rejected Jesus as Savior, he took the path of destruction which Jesus very clearly outlined in John 3:18: "Whoever believes in him is not condemned, but whoever does not believe stands condemned already because they have not believed in the name of God's one and only Son." And "liking" is not "believing on". What do you believe? BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1366503051510</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366503129782-99</Id><Title>INTRODUCING the "FLAMING...Smoking" DUMPLINER....ridiculous events</Title><Msg>are we being told everything ???? ASK yourself ??? 6 months to change a battery ??? Bwhahahahahahaha!</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366503129782</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:12:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366503592964-100</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is an inadequate example, but parents do punish their children for bad behavior. The Bible says, "Whom the Lord loves, he chastens." And it also tells us that "When justice is not carried out quickly, men think to do evil in their hearts." At some point and at some level, there has to be punishment or chastening (you call it retribution) for bad behavior. And that may mean death. Even the one thief on the cross with Jesus found that his punishment fit the crime and then he repented and was with Jesus in paradise that very day - because he believed in Him. We get too wrapped up in our little finite lives on this earth and often forget that there is an eternal life waiting around the corner. Now, the meaning of unconditional love is subjective. To me, it is that God gave His Son Jesus to die on the cross for our sins so that we can spend - if we believe - eternity with Him. Or we can reject that love and spend eternity apart from God.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1366503592964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:19:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366505975702-101</Id><Title>WHY YOU CAN’T AFFORD TO RETIRE</Title><Msg>FRONTLINE INVESTIGATES THE OTHER FINANCIAL CRISIS The Retirement Gamble Tuesday, April 23, 2013, at 10 p.m. on PBS For most Americans, traditional retirement is now a pipe dream: Six in 10 people believe they’ll have to delay retirement, just 14 percent are very confident they’ll be able to live comfortably once they stop working, and 17 percent believe they’ll never retire at all. Who is to blame? The Retirement Gamble, airing Tuesday, April 23, at 10 p.m. on PBS (check local listings), is an eye-opening investigation of a financial services industry that may be draining your retirement savings with every passing year. “This FRONTLINE film speaks directly to you, the consumer,” says FRONTLINE correspondent Martin Smith (The Untouchables; Money, Power and Wall Street). “It will help you understand both what is happening to your retirement money, and, most importantly, the questions you should be asking before investing it.” Using his own retirement fund as a case study, Smith undertakes an investigation that has implications for every working American. Through interviews with Wall Street executives at the helm of the mutual fund industry, professionals of all ages who are trying to navigate the retirement crisis, and current and former financial advisers who may or may not have their clients’ best interests at heart, he investigates the rise of the 401(k)—a product Americans buy without knowing its true cost.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366505975702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:59:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366506015636-102</Id><Topic><Title>WHY YOU CAN’T AFFORD TO RETIRE</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366505975702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FRONTLINE’s investigation reveals: •On any given street, one household may be paying 10 times as much to invest in a 401(k) as the household next door; •Over the course of a lifetime, a seemingly low annual fee of 2 percent can reduce what your balance would have been by more than 60 percent—potentially adding years to your working life; •Popular 401(k) providers often charge a plethora of hidden fees, burying them under opaque names like “Expense Ratio”; •Many financial advisers are not required to provide advice that is in their clients’ best interest; they are only obligated to give advice that is “suitable”; and •The best way to maximize your return might be to cut Wall Street out of the equation and invest in low-cost, unmanaged index funds. Whether you’re just starting your professional career, or nearing what you hope will be your golden years, The Retirement Gamble is essential viewing if you hope to one day retire.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366506015636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:00:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366508203916-103</Id><Topic><Title>WHY YOU CAN’T AFFORD TO RETIRE</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366505975702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hemroids, yet another Kent raven alias...........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366508203916</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:36:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366508640915-104</Id><Topic><Title>Un-American Liberals were quick to blame real Americans</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366450557652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 05:35:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366508640915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366509294502-105</Id><Topic><Title>Un-American Liberals were quick to blame real Americans</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366450557652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 05:35:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are Communists, plain and simple. Just ask the Kent raven.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366509294502</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366509810749-106</Id><Topic><Title>WHY YOU CAN’T AFFORD TO RETIRE</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366505975702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You like to fart in elevators and #$%$ in public pools, don't you Floyds.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366509810749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:03:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366510522020-107</Id><Topic><Title>WHY YOU CAN’T AFFORD TO RETIRE</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366505975702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Projecting again, Raven??? You DFC.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366510522020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:15:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366511799999-108</Id><Title>Russia asked the FBI to investigate Tamerlan Tsarnaev in 2011</Title><Msg>Russia asked the FBI to investigate Boston bombing suspect Tamerlan Tsarnaev in 2011, a source in US law enforcement told Reuters. The FBI had earlier reported on its website that an unnamed ‘foreign government’ had asked them for information. The slain Boston marathon bombing suspect Tamerlan Tsarnaev, who previously was designated as Suspect 1, was investigated in 2011 by the FBI upon a certain foreign state’s request. The state, which was not identified in the statement on the FBI website, filed a request concerning Tsarnaev saying that he was a follower of radical Islam and was preparing to leave the US for a particular region to join “unspecified underground groups.” The FBI says they checked all the information possible, looking for “derogatory telephone communications, possible use of online sites associated with the promotion of radical activity, associations with other persons of interest,” and checking the suspect’s travel history, plans, and education history. Tsarnaev and his family members were also interviewed by the FBI. Upon analyzing the data, the FBI had found nothing suspicious at the time. “The FBI did not find any terrorism activity, domestic or foreign, and those results were provided to the foreign government in the summer of 2011. The FBI requested but did not receive more specific or additional information from the foreign government,” the FBI statement says.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1366511799999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:36:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>